( HAUNTING MUSIC )
PRINCESS IRULAN: History
is written on the sands of Arrakis.
Muad'Dib is gone,
but his children remain...
...almost grown and about
to face the consequences
of their father's legacy.
A legacy fiercely guarded
by their aunt, Alia...
...even as she struggles
with the ominous destiny
of her own birthright.
( PENSIVE MUSIC )
( WIND BLOWS EERILY )
( ADVENTUROUS MUSIC )
MAN: Here I am. You remember me.
The Golden Path.
The path I couldn't take.
It's up to you now,
my son.
The Golden Path is dangerous,
son.
(Woman whispers) Leto.
I was hoping to see a worm.
You know they never come
close enough to see anymore.
The water has driven them away.
Everything's changing, Ghani.
Changing too fast.
You've had another vision,
haven't you?
My skin wasn't my own.
I was running across the desert
just so fast -
just running and running...
...to Jacurutu.
I saw him there again.
Our father.
Are you sure it was him?
Yes.
And he spoke of the Golden Path.
It frightens me.
I'm afraid of what
it could mean about us.
We're not like Alia, Ghani.
Are you sure?
Will you tell our grandmother
all this when we see her?
I don't know.
What do you think?
It might be wise
to understand her a bit better
before we allow her
to understand us.
( WINDS BLOW STRONGLY )
They've come for us.
Haven't they, Irulan?
( POWERFUL SURGE OF ENGINES )
I expect you both to be
courteous and respectful.
None of your sly comments.
She's a Bene Gesserit.
She'll know if
you're keeping things from her.
Why should we keep anything
from her?
Do we have anything
worth keeping?
That's what I mean, Leto.
Stilgar and I are almost
at our limits with your wit.
Worm sign.
I don't... see anything.
( VWOOM! )
( ADVENTUROUS MUSIC )
(Sighs)
Perhaps a slightly higher
altitude
would be advisable, Leto.
My father loved being this close
to the ground when he flew.
You, of course, know this
intuitively, don't you?
Just like how you knew to fly
without any training.
Don't forget your Bene Gesserit
training, Stepmother.
"Fear is the mind-killer."
I'm afraid she's about
to let it pass through her.
( ENGINES ROAR FASTER )
( TRANQUIL MUSIC )
It's beautiful.
Simply beautiful.
(Worm roars)
Have I gone too far?
Have we forgotten?
( DRAMATIC SURGE )
(Laughs)
Bless the Maker and his water.
Bless his coming and his going.
May his passing
cleanse the world.
May he keep the world
for his people.
Bi-la kaifa.
That wasn't funny.
(Laughs)
(Sniggers)
( REGAL MUSIC )
( WHISPERING VOICES )
(Voice whispers) Alia!
Alia!
Duncan!
(Whimpers) Love!
You've taken
too much spice again.
I've opened a bottomless pit.
A swarm of locusts
is flying out to arrest me.
Why can't I see, Duncan?
Why?!
See what?
The future.
My mission is incomplete.
The future. It's there, Duncan.
Just out of reach.
Why am I always
being pulled back?
Perhaps you should ask yourself
why is it necessary to see it?
You patronise me.
I don't patronise.
I care.
That's all.
Why is she coming, Duncan?
Why now?
So that's it.
After all these years
since she saw her grandchildren
on Caladan.
And in six months
they will be of age.
Reason for me, Duncan.
Be my Mentat for a moment,
not my husband.
No Bene Gesserit acts
without preordained plans,
without well-planned deceit.
And my mother, for all
her renowned independence,
is still a Bene Gesserit adept.
Clouds.
Moisture in the air.
MAN: It seems almost a sacrilege.
You sound like a Fremen.
I haven't forgotten the years
I spent among them.
I haven't forgotten the honesty
of their ways.
At times I wish
I'd never learned them.
I hate this planet, Gurney.
It took both the men I loved.
And it's still a place
of great danger, My Lady.
Rumours of assassination plots
are too numerous to ignore.
Stilgar has some word that even
Fremen may be involved.
Desert partisans who blame you
for Paul's interference
in the ecology of this planet.
I'm so weary of rumours.
They are the lifeblood
of this Empire, I'm afraid.
Reason enough this trip
should have been delayed.
( EERIE MUSIC )
( ROARING )
(Woman groans)
This way!
( BEAST ROARS )
(Gasps)
(Roars)
( BEEP! )
MAN: The tigers track the robes
flawlessly.
Our friend Palimbasha
has done his job well.
It appears your patience is
about to be rewarded, My Lady.
Yes.
I've waited many years, Tyek,
for just the right moment
to finish the Atreides.
Patience has been
my only nourishment.
Our allies on Arrakis continue
to instigate civil unrest.
Alia's hold on power
is beginning to slip.
And now we have the means
to deal with Muad'Dib's twins.
I hope My Lady's satisfied.
(Scoffs)
I won't be satisfied
until every bastard Atreides
is crushed beneath
the jackboots
of the Corrino Sardaukar.
( FOOTSTEPS )
Like the desperate pacing
of giant cats
in the zoos of ancient times.
I wouldn't know.
I'm not the scholar you are,
young prince.
Back and forth,
back and forth
until they made themselves sick
just like this worm.
Just like my mother
with her futile schemes
to regain power
for the House Corrino.
Your mother is
an ambitious woman, my prince.
Her ambitions tend to be
undisturbed by reality,
I'm afraid.
You don't share her desire
to regain your grandfather's
throne for yourself?
Only a fool covets power without
appreciating its delicate uses
or fearing its inherent perils.
The world of Shaddam IV
remains only in the texts
of crumbling history books.
We hate the Empire
that defeated it,
but we have no idea
what we'd like in its place.
The kind of society
we once had, I assume.
My mother may believe
that's possible, Tyek.
I'm not so sure.
I'm just not so sure.
I heard about your little stunt
in the desert.
I think of it as expert flying,
but carry on.
With your encouragement,
of course.
Our father's memories
are very instructive.
I should be grateful I don't
have to tell your grandmother
you were lost to a worm
before she saw you.
That would have been
an unpleasant task.
It's rumoured my mother
has resumed her allegiance
to the Bene Gesserit.
You know what
the sisterhood thinks
of those of us
who are pre-born.
You want us to pretend
to be something we're not.
I expect you
to protect yourselves.
No more talk of your father's
memories, spirit, or animas,
do you understand me?
Surely one can distinguish
between being pre-born...
And being possessed.
For some that's a distinction
without a difference.
And for us, that's dangerous.
What if she's simply coming
as mother, as grandmother,
and not as
Bene Gesserit inquisitor?
You share her memories, Alia.
Surely her motives
can't be that complex?
If my mother
wasn't that complex,
neither of you would be here.
She would never have
betrayed her training.
She never would have had a son.
I would have been her firstborn.
( VOICES ECHO )
Not your father.
And none of this
would have happened.
I warn you,
enemies often appear as angels.
I hope you two
can tell the difference.
We're going to lose her.
No, we already have.
( WONDROUS MUSIC )
You're nervous, aren't you?
Why should I be?
You haven't seen her
for many years.
Your grandmother and I
had an unsettled relationship.
But you wanted her affection,
didn't you?
Affection wasn't possible
under the circumstances.
But I am due some respect
after all this time.
( GRAND MUSIC )
Stil, please.
When you first came here
many years ago,
Muad'Dib told me
his father said...
..."Beauty has finally arrived
to hold back the wilderness."
In his honour, may I borrow
your Duke's words today?
Good friend.
The Imperial Regent, My Lady.
It's been so long!
Of course, you recognise
your grandchildren.
Even after all this time.
I hope we can find time
to shed formality
and get to know each other
again.
The mother of Muad'Dib
has returned to us!
(All cheer)
You must offer them
your blessing, Grandmother.
I see the hypocrisy of ritual
still thrives.
Sometimes it is necessary
to accommodate ritual.
In order to survive it.
(All continue cheering)
(All respond
in native language)
(Man yells) Mother!
Reverend Mother!
I bring you a warning.
The blessings of Muad'Dib
have been corrupted.
The religion of Muad'Dib
is not Muad'Dib.
He renounces it...
...as he renounces you.
All of you!
(Crowd chants)
Muad'Dib! Muad'Dib!
Muad'Dib is dead!
And sand will cover this place.
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
Sand will cover you.
( BANG! )
( WEAPONS FIRE )
( CROWD PANICS )
Take them alive!
(Yells) Alive!
(Groans)
Get out!
( WEAPON BLEEPS )
(Shouts urgently)
( EXPLOSION )
It's impossible to guard
against every madman
willing to suicide themself.
We've tried to limit
Alia's public appearances.
Are we sure she was the target?
These times,
anyone in the royal family
could be vulnerable.
I seem to recall times not long
ago that were not so different.
And we survived them.
As we will survive them again.
I heard the voices in the crowd
calling out, "Muad'Dib!"
We don't know where he's from
or what his motives are.
The say he calls himself
'The Preacher'.
People think he's Paul -
don't they, Stil? - this Preacher?
Some do. Some need to.
What do you think?
His kind have blown in
from the desert every day -
Messianic vagabonds.
And Alia's priest
tolerates such heresy?
Her priest would like
to flay him alive
for the heresy he spews
but she won't allow it.
"Oh, " she says,
"he's harmless."
It's because she thinks
it might be true, isn't it?
Well, we hope
you'll be comfortable.
Please do let us know
if you need anything.
Paul's gone, My Lady.
He walked into the desert.
Blind. Alone.
Shai-Hulud came for him.
He is gone.
I want to supervise
the interrogation
of those we found
on the street.
I'd like Gurney to go with you
if that's agreeable.
It would be my honour, Stilgar.
And my pleasure.
( REFLECTIVE MUSIC )
LETO: This was their room.
Alia kept it
exactly as they did.
We used to play here
when we were little.
It made us feel...
close to them.
For a moment, you almost
imagined that's who we were.
Didn't you?
You almost let yourself
believe that we were...
...Father and Mother.
It was not an...
unpleasant moment.
I've missed so much.
You've never been far from us,
Grandmother.
Your presence is always strong
within us both.
( DOOR OPENS )
I thought we agreed
to let her rest first.
Seeing my grandchildren
is all the rest I need.
And there will be time enough
for our reunion, Grandmother.
Now is the time
for you and your daughter.
They're complicated.
Yes.
What did you expect?
They're Paul's children.
He would be proud.
You've done well.
You look... wonderful.
I try my best.
My people expect it.
The greening of the desert's
proceeding
faster than I ever imagined.
Paul used to say
the only permanence is change.
I wasn't prepared for how much
the desert's retreating.
Only the great
mother wilderness of the south
remains untouched.
We still meet
with some resistance.
As I've noticed.
Some of the older Naibs
have withdrawn from our council
and taken their tribes
to the far regions.
We're better off without them.
Though some remain
to attack you directly.
We know how to deal
with our enemies.
It must be so hard -
the responsibility.
The loneliness.
(Testily) What can you know
of loneliness?
I've had my share.
Is that why you're here, then?
'Cause you're lonely?
I came to see my grandchildren.
To see you.
Don't try to conceal
anything from me, Mother.
I can read truth
in the slightest tic
of human behaviour.
This was your gift to me,
remember?
It's in my blood -
in my blood before I was even born,
thanks to you.
Alia, I...
Don't interrupt me!
I am the Regent of this Empire.
I rule in Paul's name
for his children.
I am the supreme authority here.
You abandoned me...
to fend for myself after Paul died.
I was only 15, Mother.
You had Stilgar,
you had Duncan, you had...
...the Council of Naibs.
No-one could challenge you.
You knew how I felt
about this place.
And yet, here you are,
after all these years, to judge me,
just like that wicked
Bene Gesserit bitch who taught you.
We were right to kill her.
MAN: Abomination.
Abomination.
That's what you called me.
Alia, I can't undo the past.
But I can influence the future.
Paul taught me that well enough.
That's what you're afraid of, isn't it?
You're afraid I have Paul's vision.
His power.
No, my darling.
I'm afraid that you will get lost
trying to achieve it.
I hate you.
I love you.
I will never forgive you.
( STREET HUBBUB,
BOISTEROUS MUSIC )
Blasphemers!
( HUBBUB STOPS )
Idolaters!
You fool yourselves
with images of things
you cannot possibly understand.
You cripple yourselves
with these... toads
of ritual and ceremony.
They give you only fear.
And in return...
you give them obedience.
But I give you a warning.
Those who accept self-deception
shall perish
by that self-deception.
And those who pray for dew
at the desert's edge...
...shall bring forth the deluge.
(All chant) Muad'Dib.
Muad'Dib. Mua...
(Man continues preaching
in the distance)
MAN: My Lady?
(Sobs gently)
Don't torture yourself.
He's mad.
He's a mere thunderclap
in the night -
startling for a moment,
then gone.
Then if I asked you
to kill him... would you?
I wouldn't hesitate.
But I would advise against it.
MAN: Alia?
It's not time to move against
The Preacher yet.
Listen to him, darling.
Let him gain some currency.
He's so handsome, isn't he?
Let our enemies rally.
The man has flaws.
When the time is right,
they can be used to discredit him.
Just what the doctor ordered!
Better he is disgraced
than martyred.
You're always good medicine
for my distress, Javid.
Whatever the cause
of that distress, My Lady.
( URGENT LOVE SIGHS )
( DRAMATIC MUSIC
INTENSIFIES )
(Both pant and gasp)
(Alia moans ecstatically)
( GENTLE MUSIC )
Reverend Mother?
They told me
I might find you here.
I was afraid it might be gone.
Paul... Muad'Dib would never
have permitted that.
He said your promise
to the old housekeeper Mapes
would never be broken.
It seems a little silly now,
though, doesn't it,
considering the changes
that are everywhere.
People don't come to visit
like they used to,
but still, it remains a symbol.
Symbolism is everywhere
these days,
just like these weeds.
I'm truly happy to see you, Irulan.
Your devotion to my grandchildren
has been a comfort to me.
They are the source
of my happiness.
And your occasional exasperation, I hear.
(Giggles) They are... strong-willed.
As I would've expected, considering.
And what else did you expect,
Reverend Mother?
Considering.
I am... was a Bene Gesserit,
trained just as you were.
I know the sisterhood
has never lost interest
in the children's bloodlines,
although they would never
confide as much
to a defector like me.
Isn't it ironic, Irulan?
We're both Bene Gesserits.
We've deserted our sisterhood
for the same reason.
Love.
Love of men who are now dead.
I did love your son, Jessica.
And I would have made him
a good wife.
Instead, I have satisfied myself
being a good teacher
to his children, and friend.
Nothing...
nothing will harm them
as long as I can prevent it.
Do you understand?
I don't know.
Perhaps it would be better
if I never became emperor.
(Laughs) I'm being selfish,
I know.
But I think it's necessary
for me and Ghanima
to have the freedom
to learn to live with what we are.
And what are you, Leto,
that you need this time
to find out about yourself?
Why don't you tell me?
That's why you're here, isn't it?
You remind me of your father.
And my grandfather?
My namesake? Your beloved Duke?
Such an admission would be
complicated, wouldn't it?
We may have to enter
a realm of intimacies
that would make us
both uncomfortable.
In a way, I find it reassuring...
...that he lives on in you.
How little you understand
how he lives on in me!
(Voice reverberates) Is that
what you're struggling with?
(Laughs)
Yes.
To know the future
is to be trapped by it, Grandmother.
My father knew it
but he couldn't escape it.
I want more freedom than that.
A universe of surprises -
that is what I pray for.
Is such a universe possible
for someone like you?
Possible? Oh, yes.
But is it desirable?
I have a difficult decision
to make, Grandmother.
Do I... accept
the Atreides mystique...
...dress myself in our myths...
...live for my subjects
and die for them...
...or do I choose another path,
a golden path...
...one that may change me,
change human destiny, forever?
I don't understand.
No, I know you don't.
Because you do not
understand time.
I can help you, Leto.
(Voice reverberates) Oh,
on the contrary, Grandmother.
It is I who will help you.
(Giggles)
( DOOR OPENS )
We must work together.
We?
Otherwise we're vulnerable.
To what?
Oh, stop being coy.
Want to know how coy he is?
Try playing this game with him.
(Both laugh)
This is not a game!
Powerful forces
are conspiring against us.
Fremen rebels hate the way
I'm ch...
...WE are changing their planet.
The damned Spacing Guild
can't tolerate our monopoly on spice.
They have no choice
but to accept it, Alia.
And now she is here.
I want to know what she wants.
No, Alia, what you want
is for us to engage
in the spice trance.
Don't turn your backs
on your heritage.
Your father was the greatest man
in history.
He gave you
such wonderful talents.
They could be put to such great
use. Why won't you use them?
You want us to see things
you cannot.
I need you to help me see.
To see the future.
Other lives hover in the enigma
of our consciousness, Alia.
(Voice reverberates)
Consciousness, Alia.
Shared lives.
It's the curse of all pre-born.
(Voice reverberates)
They are the real danger.
Not the rebels, not the guild,
not our grandmother.
You should understand that
better than most.
One day...
...each of you will come
face to face with the horror
of your own existence.
One day,
you will cry out for help.
One day, each of you
will find yourself...
...alone.
(Alia opens door)
What if she's right?
Check.
( STREET HUBBUB )
(Voices reverberate) Alia!
Alia, come back!
Alia!
Stop it.
Alia, listen to me!
No, listen to me, Alia.
Alia!
(Screams)
( UNSETTLING DRONE )
( MUFFLED SHOUTING )
MAN: Go on, out! Do as I say!
Leave her alone!
Get out! Leave her to me!
So, Grand-daughter,
you finally meet
a spiritual gom jabbar.
(Laughs)
STILGAR: We've learned much
these past few days.
It was meant to look like
rebel Fremen.
Tribes harbouring resentment
towards the Atreides
and changes to Arrakis.
But I don't believe it.
Why?
During interrogation,
the ones we captured
cried out the name Jacurutu,
and then died.
You tortured them?
Posthypnotic
suicide compulsion, My Lady.
The sound of the word alone
simply stopped their hearts.
Leto and I heard rumours
of Jacurutu Sietch
when we first came here.
We could never find out whether
the place actually existed.
The name Jacurutu is a synonym
for evil, Jessica.
The Iduali tribe
came from there.
They were water stealers...
...the most heinous criminals
under Fremen law -
the first and greatest sin.
( VOICES YELL )
Other Fremen tribes
banded together
to declare war on the Jacurutu.
The Iduali were slaughtered...
...their water spread
upon the sands.
Jacurutu Sietch
was declared taboo.
No Fremen was allowed
to look for it.
But legend persists
that not all the Iduali were wiped out,
that some escaped
to become known as the Cast Out.
And you believe
that these Cast Out
might be responsible
for what happened the other day?
The possibility
makes my blood run cold.
If the Cast Out exist,
they would camouflage
themselves as something else.
We would not permit them
to live if we knew.
Gurney, contact
your old smuggler allies -
the ones in the deep desert.
See what they know
about Jacurutu...
...and the Cast Out.
If such a people still exist,
they could be
our greatest threat.
I had full consciousness
long before birth.
Knowledge of all the lives
that came before.
The genetic rivers...
...flowing in my veins.
Reverend Mothers.
The Atreides.
My entire heritage...
...alive... in me.
Ever present.
I had no defence against
their invasion of my mind.
HARKONNEN: And so
you are stalked by fear.
Fear.
Always fear of judgment.
The pre-born are possessed.
The Abomination.
Bene Gesserit rubbish.
If you succumb to the fear,
it will defeat you.
The trial of Abomination...
...it's death.
But we won't let that happen,
will we?
We? You're dead!
(Spasmodically) I killed you.
Yes, you.
Clever little minx.
You killed me, and yet, here I am.
Go away. Just go away!
Oh, but you need help, Grand-daughter.
The others in here,
they want your entire consciousness.
They want to drive you out,
but I only want a tiny
little corner for myself,
an occasional moment
with your senses.
An occasional taste,
an occasional touch.
No-one need ever know.
No.
You murdered my father.
You tried to destroy my family.
You would have killed Paul.
Oh, yes, yes, all that.
Yes, of course
I would've killed you.
I mean, you and your brother
stood in my way,
but that's old business.
You won - I am dead.
Thanks to you, my darling,
I have only a fragile existence,
a mere memory-self within you.
You are alive,
and I am yours to command.
And how little I ask in return.
Mine?
To command?
Oh, yes, yours.
Yours, my precious girl.
Think of what we can accomplish
together.
Your power and my experience.
There will be nothing
standing in our way.
The voices in my head...
Will be silenced.
My enemies...
Will be destroyed.
BOTH: No-one will stand
in the way of our powers.
From this moment on
the future is ours.
(Both laugh)
It comes
just like you summoned it.
No, it summoned me, Stil.
And may I ask why...
...you risked a sand crossing
at night without bodyguards?
Come, come, Stil.
How often
do you ride the sands anymore
when you want, where you want?
Calling a worm
instead of running
with a flock of 'thopters?
How often... how often do you
arm the thumper and just go,
like the Fremen you used to be?
"Used to be"?
Mmm?
You know, in many corners
of the universe,
this delicate thing...
...is considered
a wondrous beauty.
But here, here it's a symbol...
...a symbol of the corruption
infecting Arrakis.
It wouldn't exist but for
the changes we're enforcing
on this place.
Changes
inspired by your father.
No, that's the official
Stilgar speaking,
the Government Stilgar.
The Fremen Stilgar
is still repulsed
at this alien life, isn't he?
Huh.
I have a serious problem, Stil.
So I've gathered.
The problem with me
is the problem with this place.
My father,
he left so many things undone.
I don't understand.
A good ruler doesn't need
to be a prophet, Stil.
Not even godlike.
A good ruler has to be sensitive
to the ones he rules.
Mm-hm.
The ancient meaning
of the Fremen word 'Naib'
is 'servant of the sietch'.
When the owner dies,
the crysknife dissolves, yes?
It is our legend.
Muad'Dib has dissolved
but his crysknife has not.
Stil, a new path must be taken.
One that may require me
to demystify my own father...
...to destroy his legacy.
These are not sentiments
I'd share with your aunt
or her priests, young lord.
Beware Alia, Stil.
She's no longer your friend.
And, Stil, you must promise
to protect Ghanima.
If anything should happen
to me - anything -
my sister will be your only hope.
You were in the desert?
Yes, I, uh... I couldn't sleep.
I could have kept you company.
You were sleeping.
I didn't want to disturb you.
You used to...
...all the time.
We'd sneak out
of the sietch together.
No-one ever knew.
Sometimes we wouldn't be back
till dawn.
I had to talk to Stilgar.
Oh, I see.
Ghanima, we may have to face
some of what's coming apart.
That doesn't mean
you have to face it alone.
The Atreides man
named Gurney Halleck
is being sent to the desert
to ask questions.
Sooner or later,
he will encounter someone
who can be bought.
Then we must make sure
he buys the right answers.
What shall I do
with the blind fool, Father?
He can still be useful.
Take him into the desert
until we need his sermons again.
Out of chaos comes civil war -
Fremen and Atreides
destroying each other.
The water of our enemies
will feed our revenge.
Our suffering will be repaid
a thousandfold.
Jacurutu.
ALL: Jacurutu.
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
I should never have left here.
It was a cowardly thing to do.
You lost so much here.
I know it, Leto knows it.
Even Alia must know it
in a way.
It helps, doesn't it -
the 'Litany Against Fear'?
You were thinking it,
weren't you?
"Fear is the mind-killer."
Ghani, I've decided
I want you to know my fear -
fear I've kept hidden too long -
a fear for those
who are pre-born.
Just before we came to Arrakis
the first time,
I brought a Reverend Mother
to meet your father.
He was just a boy.
I remember.
I've been told.
The Reverend Mother
brought a nerve induction box.
Tested Paul with it.
I was forbidden to interfere.
He might have died.
But he survived.
Of course, you remember this
in a way that I cannot.
And that's what your fear is...
...the memories I've inherited,
the possibility of possession,
the possibility of abomination.
Not you.
I'm sure of that now.
But you're not sure about Leto?
Is he strong enough, Ghani -
Leto?
Can he survive what's coming?
What is it that's coming?
(Speaks Chakobsa)
The Golden Path.
Leto used those words
when he and I were together.
He has visions...
...of a pilgrimage
deep into the desert.
A journey to a faraway place...
...where he sees our father...
...and speaks to him
of how things must change.
Change?
How?
He can't tell me.
I think he's holding things
back from me.
But I know this -
it's not possession
and it is not abomination.
And when it is
my brother's turn to be tested,
he too will survive...
...just as our father did.
MAN: The man has arrived
to take you deeper into the desert.
He says he will help you find
what you're looking for.
So now it is decided.
We're all going to the desert.
So you're the Atreides man?
Gurney Halleck.
I don't like it.
Why would the Corrino family
send gifts
to Muad'Dib's children?
An attempt to curry favour
with the future emperor
and his sister.
You don't believe that
any more than I do, Duncan.
Nothing is ever as it seems
with my sister.
Even an innocent gift
of clothing can be dangerous.
But how?
I want these examined
thoroughly.
And report back to me before
they're given to the children.
Is that understood?
I can feel your suspicion,
Duncan.
You're wondering if
there's something
more complex in my motives,
aren't you?
The history of what brought
a Corrino princess
into House Atreides
is not easily forgotten.
Plans within plans -
is that it, Mentat?
Do you doubt my allegiance
to this family?
Allegiances once changed
can change again.
Our sources in the palace
assure me
the robes were delivered.
The catalyst is well-hidden.
Little precious Irulan
will never find them.
Well done.
Alia's paranoia
is growing stronger day by day.
She sees enemies everywhere.
And her only solution -
more and more repression.
Exactly as we want.
The more terror we sow,
the more fear and confusion
we harvest.
The more severely Alia responds,
the more Fremen
she drives into the south,
and the sooner
they will openly rebel.
And then with the twins
out of the way,
well, Alia will be
more vulnerable than ever.
But, uh, you mustn't let Farad'N
know about our plans
until they're done.
He doesn't have
the stomach for it.
How dare you?
These robes are gifts
from Prince Farad'N -
a gesture of goodwill.
An opportunity to ease tension
between the houses.
Javid arranged for this
himself.
With the Regent's approval,
of course.
I had to satisfy myself.
Satisfy yourself?
That there was no subterfuge,
no danger.
You insinuated yourself
into a diplomatic matter
that's none of your business!
The safety of the twins
is every bit my business.
You bloodless bitch.
Alia.
How is it that I'm blessed
with such an extraordinary
counselor as you, Irulan?
What devious finger of fate
turned you from a Corrino toad
into a simpering Atreides sycophant?
That's enough!
No, it's not nearly enough.
From now on,
my niece and nephew
are no longer under your care.
You can't do that.
I'm the Regent of the Empire.
I'm their guardian.
I rule in their name.
HARKONNEN: That's right.
And don't let them forget it.
(Harkonnen laughs fiendishly)
Perhaps you should rest.
How can I rest, Mother,
when I am surrounded
by such incompetent fools?
Do you see what's become
of my world, Mother?
Do you see the chaos
I must endure?
Yes, I see it.
I'm afraid I see it all too clearly.
HARKONNEN: Get rid of them.
Get out.
All of you, out.
Come.
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
HARKONNEN: Still the same
arrogant Bene Gesserit cow
( DOOR OPENS )
You must forgive my daughter,
Irulan.
She let temper get in the way
of judgment this afternoon.
I'm sure she let her words
run away with her.
Do not concern yourself
with me, Reverend Mother.
I remember what it's like
to be in her position.
I remember how lonely
it can be sometimes.
I understand.
At the same time,
you're never alone.
There are always
people around -
people who need you.
Yes, life in a court
can sometimes be suffocating.
Easy to lose your perspective.
I'm glad that we can be honest
with each other.
I feel that I can trust you.
Completely.
My only concern
is for the health and safety
of your grandchildren.
You must take care
of your own wellbeing too.
Thank you for your concern
for me, Reverend Mother.
You're very important to me.
I will let Alia know
that I bear no ill feelings
because of her harsh words.
You're very understanding.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
( HUBBUB OF NOISE )
(Creature growls)
There they are - those two.
Did you see them?
We have a shuttle waiting.
Leto, come.
Hurry.
Anybody who helped
the twins get out of the city
must be arrested
and brought to me.
I will make an example
of ALL who defy me!
Get out!
(Breathes heavily)
This is my mother's doing.
I want her dead.
Now.
HARKONNEN: No, my dear.
Not just yet.
Patience, my dear.
Patience and calm.
That is the palliative
for fury and despair.
Everyone is turning against me.
Ohh, don't worry, child.
There are many clever ways
to rid oneself
of a troublesome witch.
(Snorts) Your efforts
to the contrary, I suppose.
No, unfortunately,
my efforts were, shall we say,
interrupted by a wonderfully
devious and cruel little girl.
(Laughs humourlessly)
You took great pleasure in it,
as I recall.
I had to admire
your ruthlessness.
Had you only been
a few years older!
Why am I even listening to you,
you perverted old fool?!
Because I'm here to help you.
Because I am the only one
you can trust.
What you must do is take care
of your mother in public.
Why don't you call in
that lovely boy?
The priest.
Javid, eh?
Ohh!
Mix business with pleasure,
perhaps, huh?
(Laughs)
( GENERAL CHATTER )
(Bird squawks)
(Knocks at door)
( DOOR OPENS )
You were right, Muriz.
Her paranoia deepens
with each passing hour.
He's ordered
immediate retaliation.
Good.
The more the repression,
the greater the rebellion.
The greater the rebellion,
the sooner our enemies
slaughter each other.
Get word to that Corrino witch.
Tell her we continue
to work our mischief.
(Harkonnen laughs)
Even though
she's not of Council any longer,
I have asked Lady Jessica,
adored mother of Muad'Dib,
to join us
for the ritual of supplication.
We bring before the holy family
a Kadeshian troubadour.
A miserable wanderer
who has lost everything
but the clothes on his back
and now must beg the court
for...
Mercy, Holy Mother!
I am Ghadhean al-Fali,
Naib of Sietch Gare Kulaan.
My ladies,
do not listen to this man.
His appeal is not approved.
I am here concerning
a matter of the desert.
A matter of the desert
is a concern
of great magnitude, Fedaykin.
But, Reverend Mother...
Yes, My Lady.
I am Fedaykin.
Once offering his life
at the side of Muad'Dib.
This is not the proper forum
for...
We will hear
this matter of the desert.
We have abandoned our friend
the desert, Holy Mother.
Shai-Hulud
no longer roams the sands.
He cannot be found
except in the empty quarters
far from our people.
The superstitious
of the inner desert
have always feared
the transformation of our land.
A land where nothing grew.
Now there are plants.
They spread
like maggots upon the wound.
There are clouds in the sky.
And rain.
Precious mother of Muad'Dib,
rain from the sky of Dune!
It is a death to us all.
We only do what Liet
and Muad'Dib intended us to do.
Would you challenge
their holy words?
And what of the worms, then?
There'll always be some desert.
Some worms.
As go the worms,
so goes the spice.
And if the spice does not flow,
what coin do we have?
Silence!
These are matters of state.
And you will not challenge
the wisdom of this Government
to do what it decides is best.
The rabble of the desert
must be made to comply
with our judgment.
It is WE who rule here!
Not the mob of the sands.
No!
(Speaks Chakobsa)
There are those of you who fear
that I have returned to Arrakis
as a Bene Gesserit.
That I have abandoned
my loyalty
to the Atreides partnership
with the desert.
But since the day
the Fremen gave life to me
and to my son...
...I have always been Fremen.
And I will always be Fremen.
Be quiet!
We cannot abandon the desert.
My daughter is lying!
The worms will not survive
if the desert shrinks.
She knows this.
Spice production will slow
until it is only a fraction
of what it has been.
And when that happens...
We'll have a corner
on the scarcest commodity
in the universe.
You will have a corner in hell!
( BANG! )
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
Fedaykin,
we who have been scorched
know how to stand back to back.
I have men here, My Lady.
( HAUNTING MUSIC )
WOMAN: When religion and
politics ride in the same cart,
the whirlwind follows.
PAUL: The Golden Path.
It's up to you now.
(Roars)
The desert storm
that can't be stopped.
The whirlwind.
GHANIMA: Leto!
Don't.
The Golden Path is dangerous.
The path I couldn't take.
Leto, don't.
(Screams)
Leto!
You were having another vision,
weren't you?
Events are moving faster
than we anticipated, Ghani.
We have to go now.
To Jacurutu?
The answer's there.
I know it.
We can't turn back.
We have to finish this.
Muad'Dib the god
must be destroyed.
We must find the Golden Path.
It's a dangerous path.
It's the only way
out of the trap.
He saw us at the end.
Father's last vision.
He knew it was possible.
Don't you see?
That's... that's why he left.
He left it to us.
You're not telling me
everything, are you?
There are things you've seen
that you keep from me.
I can tell.
Only things that...
I don't even understand.
Yet.
But I have faith, Ghani.
Faith that no matter
what happens
when the time comes,
we will both know what to do.
Are you sure we can make it?
I'm sure that if we don't try,
we'll have failed.
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
I'm afraid.
If fear is the mind-killer...
"I will face my fear."
"I will let it pass through me."
(Laughs)
We are ready for tonight.
Have you seen that one?
The one
who's gone over to our enemies?
Without doubt.
Palimbasha.
I saw him in the bazaar
at Arrakeen with the tigers.
No doubt
he has his part to play.
You ready?
It's ironic, using gifts from our enemies
as means of escape.
(Chuckles)
You're enjoying the charade
anyway, aren't you?
You know me too well.
Yeah, too well.
Promise me we'll only be
as reckless as necessary.
Only as necessary.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
It won't be long
before the alarm goes out.
There. The way to Jacurutu.
They'll never think
we've gone in that direction.
( TENSE MUSIC )
AL-FALI: We can rest here
until arrangements are made
to get you out of the city.
Unless something is done,
civil war is inevitable.
We must get a message
to Stilgar.
He must call
for a Council of Naibs.
We must bring a trial
of possession against Alia.
You know what that will mean,
Reverend Mother.
She is your daughter.
I know what it means.
An official warrant for
the arrest of Fedaykin al-Fali
and his confederates
from Sietch Gare Kulaan.
Post it in every city.
Send word to every sietch.
Their conspiracy to murder
the Imperial Regent
and kidnap
the mother of Muad'Dib
must be crushed without mercy.
Are you looking at me
or analysing me, Duncan?
I'm gathering data.
You must find her, Duncan.
You must find her
and return her to me.
Surely your data
must point to the danger I'm in!
WE are in.
Perhaps your lover will be
a better comfort to you than I.
I've made so many mistakes,
Duncan!
So many mistakes.
Because I've been afraid.
I'm ashamed of my weakness.
Please try and forgive me.
I lost my temper in there,
Duncan.
I know it was a mistake
but I can fix it.
It was an accident of fatigue,
nothing else.
I can make everyone understand.
Everyone except HER.
You HAVE to deal with her.
She is your mother!
She's Bene Gesserit, no matter
what she said in there!
Those damnable hags
would like nothing more
than put me to the test.
Please, Duncan!
Please.
You're the only one I can trust.
The only one
who loves me enough.
You must eliminate her.
No harm must come
to House Atreides.
No matter what the cost.
(Sobs)
You handled that well.
Shut up!
As you wish, My Lady.
(Sobs)
(Laughs)
We found their clothing
near the bakery, Stilgar.
We're certain they're no longer
in the sietch.
They must be wearing those robes
they brought from Arrakeen.
Our search parties can't find
a trace of them in the desert.
They won't. Not unless
the children want them to.
( LOUD DRONING )
LADY JESSICA: They do not
appreciate my presence here.
These are puritans,
Reverend Mother.
What they do not like
is what's become
of their revolution.
Then I must convince them
that neither do I.
A messenger has arrived
under immunity of Stilgar.
It is urgent.
You have a message
from Sietch Tabr?
Fali, hold.
Your grandchildren are missing.
I'm to bring you to Sietch Tabr
as soon as possible.
You can't go with him,
Holy Mother.
He is a ghola.
He was my Duke's
most trusted warrior.
He died once
saving Muad'Dib's life.
And mine.
But he is...
...Alia's husband.
He is still Atreides.
It is my daughter who is not.
We don't have much time.
What about these Fedaykin
who have helped me?
Alia has issued a warrant
against them.
Crimes against the Imperium.
Of course she has.
Stilgar has offered sanctuary,
if they can make it to Tabr.
Then that is what you will do.
When the Imperial agents
find this place,
there must be nothing left
but the wind
humming through the rocks.
As the Holy Mother commands.
(Speaks Chakobsa)
May Shai-Hulud
clear the path before you.
( ENGINES ROAR )
Is it true
about my grandchildren, Duncan?
You wouldn't have come if
you didn't believe it, My Lady.
Alia?
No.
Stilgar suspects they may
have seen this crisis coming.
He fears they've gone
into the desert.
I made many mistakes
with my daughter, Duncan.
There have been many mistakes,
My Lady.
And I repeated most of them.
She will not survive
a trial of Abomination.
No.
This is not the course
of the Sietch Tabr, is it?
No, My Lady, it is not.
Are you going to tell me
where you're taking me?
Somewhere even Alia
won't think to look for us.
I don't think they saw us.
I don't think
they were looking for us.
We don't have much time.
( HAUNTING MUSIC )
We'll have to make those rocks
before sunset.
Search parties will certainly
come out this far.
( GUTTURAL ROAR )
That's not a worm.
But an animal.
More than one.
( ELECTRONIC BUZZING )
( SOFT GROWLING )
It's closer now.
Much closer.
(Roars)
(Creature growls)
LETO: Ha!
(Both growl menacingly)
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
( MUFFLED GROWLING )
(Snuffles and slathers)
(Roars)
(Creature continues growling)
There's a cave up there.
Run!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Roars)
(Both growl)
Get in!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Leto screams)
( SQUELCH! )
(Growls)
PRINCESS IRULAN: The saga
of Dune is far from over.