History is written
on the sands of Arrakis...
where rebellion and civil war
continue to breed...
fed by Alia's brutal tyranny
and repression...
as she sinks deeper into
the abomination of her own ghosts...
unable to recognize the forces
conspiring against her...
unaware of the whirlwind...
sweeping towards her
across the desert.
Well...
who's gonna explain this to me?
Who's gonna tell me why
I have rioting in my streets...
why my name is being used as a curse?
You simple fools.
The royal twins are missing
from Sietch Tabr.
Lady Jessica
has been abducted off-world.
Rebel alliances are being formed
by tribes to the south.
And now we have anarchy
in the streets of Arakeen!
You are to blame.
Go.
Perhaps you should rest, milady.
It's difficult to think clearly
when one is exhausted by stress.
Leave me. I'm fine.
Such a pity, eh?
Why did you send
that lovely boy away?
I'm not in the mood to indulge
your lurid perversions tonight.
Are they mine
or simply yours in disguise?
After all, I'm only enjoying...
what you started.
Is that so?
Don't forget, child.
I'm not really here.
I'm simply the manifestation...
of what you already are.
Go away! Go away!
Who else knows they are
requesting sanctuary here?
The Spacing Guild, of course.
They would provide transport
with Idaho's bribes.
The Bene Gesserit will surely be
informed, if they don't know already.
Then Alia will be forced
to implicate us in this adventure.
She'll have to make it appear
as if we arranged the whole thing.
We should refuse them safe harbor...
return them to Arrakis and wash
our hands of the entire matter.
On the contrary, Tyek.
Perhaps we should think
of Lady Jessica's visit...
as an endowment, not a threat.
The woman has many talents, I've read.
Perhaps they could be of some use to us.
You mean to you.
I see no reason why I shouldn't continue
my education by all means necessary.
Any woman who can seduce
Duke Leto Atreides...
and a planet of desert Fremen
is not to be trifled with.
Are you suggesting
she might try to seduce me?
Don't play the fool, Farad'n.
She would be a dangerous guest.
But... a grateful one.
He may have a point.
May the wind strip the flesh
from your bones.
May Shai-Hulud
clear the path before you.
Sachar-Nabai.
When we meet again.
My skin is not my own.
The Golden Path is dangerous, Son.
It's the choice I couldn't take...
the desert storm
that cannot be stopped.
You will become that storm...
my son--
the whirlwind.
And nothing will be able
to stop you...
not even yourself.
This is for Leto.
We've confirmed that it was
Ghanima's knife that killed Palimbasha.
And the communicator he was wearing?
Off-world manufacture for sure.
We found a transceiver implanted
in a tiger's neck.
And we also found this in the desert.
Should I arrange transport
to the palace?
No!
Whoever will benefit
from the death of these children...
will not rest until
they're sure they've succeeded.
Until the time is right...
she'll be safer here than anywhere.
Sand trout.
So you know your desert farming,
young Atreides.
That's right, Atreides.
Don't be foolish.
We have your water in our cup.
Alive? She's alive?
That clever bitch Ghanima
survived our tigers.
We must improvise quickly.
Tell our man in the Atreides palace,
the priest Javid...
he must stir Alia's pot some more.
Yes, Princess.
They left our priest's body
where we would be sure to find it.
He was assassinated by Fremen rebels
from a sietch near Hirbana Erg.
He was traveling with diplomatic
immunity when they attacked.
They carved blasphemy
into his skin, milady.
Horrible, profane curses
about you and your family.
"Cursed be the name Atreides.
Burning be on you for the abomination
you have visited on our desert.
You shall have no soul, no spirit.
You shall not be permitted
to come up from the depths."
The obscenities
of desert rebels, Holiness.
An example must be made...
to warn other tribes what happens...
if they persist
in this insurrection.
No mercy.
I want all traces of
the rebel sietch wiped out.
You will be Leto...
son of Muad'Dib.
I am Sabiha.
I am meant to watch over you.
Yes, and no doubt kill me
if I try to escape.
That won't happen.
Drink.
I warn you, any attempt at witchery
shall result in immediate execution.
We are seeking safe harbor,
not an opportunity for treachery.
So you say.
But why should we risk...
sheltering fugitives
from the Imperium?
Who says that we are fugitives?
Your confrontation with Alia
has already taken on...
mythic proportions, Lady Jessica.
Several Fremen tribes are known to be
in open revolt against the Quizrate.
Civil war seems imminent.
My grandchildren will prevent that.
Not if they're dead.
I'm sorry, Jessica Atreides...
to be the bearer of bad news, but...
it seems your grandchildren
have been the victims...
of a well-planned
assassination plot.
- Assassination?
- Our reports indicate...
the Atreides twins went missing
from Sietch Tabr.
They were attacked in the desert.
Leto was killed.
They're not sure
what became of the girl.
We have reason to believe Alia herself
may have planned the killings.
- That is impossible.
- Jessica.
It's well known your daughter's
on the verge of abomination.
Since Muad'Dib's heirs
were of age...
they were soon to be invested
with all the powers of his government.
Alia's role as regent
was coming to an end unless--
unless your grandchildren
could be eliminated...
and the blame laid on her enemies.
On us.
Events on Arrakis are spinning
wildly out of control...
Jessica Atreides.
Now, we can retreat and watch
the empire collapse on top of us...
or we can give each other sanctuary.
I can protect you
from Alia's reach...
and you can protect me
from her madness.
And how do I do that?
By announcing publicly that we did not
kidnap you, as Alia now alleges--
that you came of your own free will,
an emissary of the Bene Gesserit...
sent to...
take over the education of my son.
You want me to teach him
as the Bene Gesserit are taught?
An offer I could not resist.
Your mentat is conspicuous
by his silence.
One must be careful to evaluate...
who has the advantage
in such situations.
Perhaps there is
mutual advantage all around.
Stilgar refuses
to allow Ghanima to travel...
saying she's not strong enough...
saying her safety
cannot be guaranteed.
- He has offered sanctuary.
- He is naib of the sietch.
- We cannot overrule his wishes.
- We'll see about that.
The activities at Tabr
are curious and provocative.
No one is allowed to visit or depart
without Stilgar's permission.
They're planning to go over
to the rebels.
That's unlikely.
We know Stilgar
has initiated dialogue...
with the insurgent naibs to the south,
but only as emissary.
Continue your surveillance
of Sietch Tabr.
I want to know who's coming
and who's going...
and where all the communications
are directed.
Time to pay Stilgar a visit.
If you hadn't taken them from
the city in the first place...
- this never would have happened.
- I am their guardian, Alia.
Are you suggesting she wouldn't
be safe at the palace with me?
I am demanding that she not be used
as a pawn in a civil war.
You know as well as I that Ghanima
must be returned to the court.
She's right, Irulan.
As long as I designate
Sietch Tabr neutral territory...
no violence may be committed
by any party to this conflict.
However, holding Ghanima against
the imperial regent's will...
could be considered abduction.
As naib of this sietch...
I surrender Ghanima to
the imperial regent on one condition--
that the Princess Irulan
accompany her.
If any harm comes
to either the princess...
or the royal heir...
the neutrality of this tribe
will be forfeit...
and allegiance
to the imperial throne...
disavowed.
Agreed.
I want the girl ready.
We leave for Arakeen immediately.
Forgive me, Irulan.
I may have placed you
in grave danger.
Keep feeding him more and more.
The more we feed him,
the deeper his trance.
The deeper the trance,
the more dangerous the trance.
- He's stronger than we thought.
- Then we must increase what we give him.
By the time we're through,
he'll be as mad as Alia.
What are you doing to me?
That's spice essence!
Do you hear them--
the voices in your head?
Are you crazy yet, like your aunt?
Does that frighten you?
Not as much as
it will frighten you, Atreides.
Listen to me, Leto.
Put the weapon away, Cast Out.
That is what you are, isn't it?
Adopting the chameleon colors
of a smuggler tribe...
in order to keep
your true identity secret.
Allowing us to survive.
Trading spice.
That's not all, is it?
You're breeding sand trout.
I've seen the holding pens.
Selling worms off-planet, you hope to
break the Atreides monopoly on spice.
It is dangerous for you
to know these things.
More dangerous for you.
None of your worms survive long
away from Dune.
- Not yet.
- Not ever.
You're already saturated with spice.
And it can no longer harm me.
I have survived the crucible, Sabiha.
I have silenced the voices
within who would have possessed me.
Only I remain now
to do what I must do.
And what is that?
Save the desert.
My skin is not my own.
I can't-- I can't do it.
You can. You will.
I'm here. I try to see myself there,
but I can't.
- I can't.
- Patience.
Concentrate on visualizing
the flow of time.
It must move, not you.
It would have been easier
to begin this when you were younger.
I'm surprised you never asked
for a Bene Gesserit teacher before.
They'd have leapt at the opportunity
to put you in their debt.
My mother had other training
in mind for me when I was younger.
- You can still learn.
- If I'm patient?
You must learn
each and every muscle...
as if it were a single string
on a baliset.
When you learn how
to play them individually...
you'll know how
to play them together.
The union of opposites,
isn't it, Jessica?
Recognizing the essential
instability of our universe...
one must learn to make it
one's own creation.
It is the Bene Gesserit way.
So you haven't forgotten
everything you were taught.
You need a bath.
We'll continue tomorrow.
He is a slow learner.
On the contrary, he's making more
progress than I would have expected...
in so short a time.
And you?
I know what I intend to get
out of this relationship, Wencisia.
What is it you expect?
Our houses are at
their crossroads, Jessica--
families weakened from within.
You and I both confront the greatest
danger from those closest to us.
You have a daughter
from whom you are estranged.
I have a son
in whom I have little confidence.
What do you expect me
to do about that?
Simply...
consider the union of opposites.
We hear rumors
of your granddaughter.
- Ghanima?
- It seems she has survived.
Alia has taken her from Stilgar,
but Irulan is with her.
Get to the point, Wencisia.
An alliance.
Corrino and Atreides.
An alliance through marriage.
Under your tutelage.
Farad'n could be fashioned
into an acceptable mate...
for someone as special
as your granddaughter.
He has his talents,
and he's a fast learner, as you say.
Worse things could happen...
than an alliance
between old enemies.
Your son was clever enough
to see its potential once.
Surely you can see
the need for it now.
The idea repulses me.
Surely your mentat reasoning
can see the value in it.
That an Atreides would willingly
marry into the house...
that has vowed its destruction--
it's madness!
That's exactly what my son did
when he married Irulan.
Politics ruled that decision,
and it averted a war.
Do you not see the similarity
to our present situation?
Do you really think Alia
will agree to a marriage...
between Ghanima and Farad'n?
She is the reason you must be the one
to deliver this proposal.
She loved you once, Duncan, and
there's a part of her that still does.
You're the only one who might
reach that part of her...
that still knows who she is.
She's lost to me now.
You saw the evidence of that yourself.
You could be saving the life
of Paul's daughter, Duncan.
As long as Ghani lives,
she's a threat to Alia.
If we can make my daughter
believe that her niece...
is the means to eliminating
an even greater threat...
we can save her life...
and buy precious time.
I assume you see merit
to this marriage proposal...
since you gambled your own safety
to deliver it personally.
Merit and risk.
You must decide which bears
the greater weight.
My priests object to the idea.
Because they are
myopic and parochial...
interested only in preserving
their own power.
Be careful, Duncan.
You're already standing
on the precipice.
It is no secret desert rebels probe
your defenses with increased success.
Riots here in Arakeen are the subject
of much discussion off-world.
Whispers of weakness and disarray
are spreading amongst the great houses.
Rumors encouraged by my enemies
to spread doubt and fear.
The jackals are gathering, Alia.
An alliance between
Corrino and Atreides...
would serve as reassurance
and a warning.
Prepare a formal response
to House Corrino.
We will allow negotiations
for a union...
between Ghanima
and Prince Farad'n to begin.
But make it clear,
Atreides interests will dominate.
Leave me.
Only my husband may remain.
I should have you executed
for what you did.
My diplomatic immunity
as Corrino envoy...
would make that an unwise decision.
Why did you come back here?
My allegiance to House Atreides
would permit nothing less.
I played no part in your decision?
I struggled not to allow it.
You can't remain at the keep.
I must banish you
for your treachery.
Otherwise, people would question
my judgement, my ruthlessness.
A quality you must demonstrate
often these days, no doubt.
They're difficult days, Duncan.
Lonely days.
I've missed you.
Where would you have me go?
Sietch Tabr.
Neutral territory.
Stilgar is trying to broker a peace
between the Quizrate and the rebels.
Perhaps your mentat qualities
can be useful.
At least you'll be safe there.
There is no one to restrain Alia.
Her forces are probing deeper and deeper
into the southern regions...
attacking rebel sietches
wherever she thinks they are.
And still, there are riots
in the streets of Arakeen itself.
And what of the boy Leto?
What do they say about him?
If he survived the assassin,
he did not survive the desert.
Worms, storms--
There won't be a body.
Where are you going?
- To look for the boy.
- That cannot be permitted.
We never had any intention of helping
someone like you, enemy of ours.
Cursed be your name, Atreides.
Burning be on you for the abomination
you have visited on our desert.
You shall have no soul, no spirit.
You shall not be permitted
to come up from the depths.
The only thing that doesn't fear
an Arrakis storm...
is the worm.
I will not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
I will face my fear.
I will let it pass through me.
I will not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
I will face my fear.
I will let it pass through me.
I will not fear!
Fear is the mind killer!
I will face my fear!
I will let it pass through me!
I will not fear!
I could have killed you.
It wouldn't have been that easy.
I wanted to believe you.
I wanted to believe that
I could do it, but I didn't.
I couldn't.
I didn't truly think it was possible.
And then my mind melted away.
I gave up fighting you,
and it happened.
It wasn't me you were fighting.
It was myself.
All that I've learned-- all the
nonsense I've imprisoned myself with--
I feel--
I feel like I'm being reborn...
like I'm standing on the threshold
of something extraordinary.
Para-Bindu balance, Farad'n.
But only on the threshold.
- Patience?
- Yes, patience.
Remember...
it's one thing to gain control
of your perceptions...
quite another to gain control
of your desires.
And if I succeed?
You'll find reality to be quite
a bit different than you thought.
My skin is not my own.
Must you insist on
sneaking away like this?
I still feel him, Irulan.
His presence. Sometimes I even think
I can hear his laughter in the wind.
Mocking your decision
to marry Farad'n, I hope.
Why should he mock it?
I cannot stand by and let you be used
as a pawn in Alia's schemes.
Is that what you think,
that I'm being used?
That I've agreed to this marriage
as part of some conspiracy with Alia?
No. But I know you, Ghani.
There is more to your decision
than anyone else believes.
Alia wants my grandmother back.
Farad'n is simply the means.
But what do you want?
Farad'n's blood on
the wedding sheets, not mine.
You cannot remain neutral
any longer, Stilgar.
You must ally your tribe
with the rebel forces.
Never! Rebellion against
the sister of Muad'Dib...
would bring the greatest dishonor
I could imagine.
There is no more sister of Muad'Dib.
She's gone--
lost to the evil that possesses her.
And as long as you refuse
to believe it, you wear its collar.
Enough!
You are the guest of my tribe.
I have given you my countenance.
But I swear, if you provoke me further
with talk of insurrection...
I will have your water!
What is it, Tariq?
- Why have we stopped?
- Desert demon.
In human form.
There are no such things.
Your guide has released the worm.
We have a little time
before he returns.
You made it stop.
The worm obeyed your command.
Yes.
They say Leto Atreides is dead...
killed by Corrino treachery.
A myth I have allowed to persist
until I am ready.
For what?
To undo what's been done
in your name... Father.
You have no idea who I am.
This is your ring, Father.
Passed from Duke Leto to you,
and then unto me.
How far has it gone...
this thing you've done to yourself?
I am a desert creature.
Was there no other way?
There was only one way
to bring about The Golden Path.
You cannot control the future.
A man named Muad'Dib
should have heeded that advice.
Do you think Muad'Dib couldn't see
the thing that you want to do?
Do you think he didn't
confront the possibility?
Muad'Dib was afraid.
He was trapped
by his own prophecy...
a victim of what he knew
he could not choose.
So I have chosen...
to make a world where humankind
can create its own future...
from moment to moment...
free of one man's vision...
free from the perversion
of the prophet's words...
and free of future
pre-determined.
This does not belong to me.
How many nights I have sat
on a dune just like this...
imagining a night just like this...
with my father.
Just the two of us...
talking and-- and laughing.
And how many nights I have gone to sleep
on the cold floor of the sietch...
dreaming of his arms around me...
sheltering me from everything
I was afraid of...
everything I could not understand.
Are you still a good Fremen?
Yes.
Then will you permit...
a blind man...
to go out into the desert...
and find peace on his own terms?
Not yet.
Cursed be the name Atreides.
Body shield. Armed.
Eight of nine new settlements
have been abandoned.
Many of the old sietch communities
are becoming overrun with refugees.
The holy regent demands that you abandon
your pledge of neutrality.
Ally your forces with hers and
put an end to this damnable rebellion.
Alia is Fremen.
She knows she cannot make
such a demand on me...
or on any other naib!
You can no longer remain
above the fight, Stilgar.
Your feeble attempts to mediate
have accomplished nothing.
It is time for you to choose.
Are you with the empire
or against it?
It is not a choice
I will make because...
some fop of a priest demands it.
Well, perhaps the royal consort...
can talk some sense
into this obstinate fool.
I can do better than that.
The "royal cuckold" thanks you
for this opportunity.
Stilgar will now make his choice.
You have violated sanctuary.
You have defiled...
the honor of my people.
No, Stil.
I have just cut the collar
from around your neck.
That was the right choice, Stil.
Two deaths for the Atreides...
the second one for no better reason
than the first.
It was a sign.
He forced our hand.
Now Alia will be forced
to move against us.
He has taken the tribe
into the desert.
No one knows where...
but his only refuge
will be with the rebels.
Idaho acted impulsively, milady.
He was--
Was my husband!
Kanly...
vendetta...
on Stilgar and all of his tribe
that joined him.
Let them be hunted down
like desert rabbits.
Yes, yes. Kill them.
I want their skins
when they're caught.
Nice touch, yes.
Very creative.
This is the one
we took on the south face.
He came across the bled
from the south wall.
So, they say you rode a worm here.
A 20-thumper ride.
- And yet, you are not Fremen.
- They taught me well.
Rumors across the desert
say you're dead, Gurney Halleck.
There are many
who wished it were true.
The sons of Esmar Tuek
are not among them, old friend.
We've been waiting on you,
Gurney Halleck.
- How did you know I'd come here?
- My father told me.
Your father?
Well, in the desert,
sheltered once is sheltered always.
After the Harkonnen invasion,
these were the men who protected you...
before you were finally
reunited with Muad'Dib.
A reunion which allowed me
to join his rebellion...
against Shaddam
and the imperial forces.
Another rebellion awaits you,
Gurney Halleck.
My loyalty is to House Atreides.
I am House Atreides.
And what of your aunt?
My aunt is lost--
lost to forces
she could not control...
to forces who want
to destroy House Atreides.
What have you done to yourself?
I have made a choice...
accepted a destiny, nothing more.
My eyes can see it...
but my mind refuses to believe it.
Believe it, Gurney.
Remember the words of my father
and my grandfather, your duke.
They spoke to you of desert power.
I am desert power...
and nothing can stop
what is going to happen.
We are here to honor
the throne of Muad'Dib...
and his sister, the holy regent.
We are here to honor his esteemed
daughter with the presentation...
of our son, Prince Farad'n...
heir to the throne
of House Corrino.
We offer our deepest condolences
on the loss of your brother.
Perhaps the union of our houses...
can put an end to the treachery
that took his life...
treachery that was bred
on Salusa Secundus.
What did you say?
I am ashamed to say that the animals
that killed Leto, son of Muad'Dib...
were created and trained
on my planet.
And the regent of House Corrino
knew of this?
- She planned it.
- How dare you!
I'll dare quite a few things
from now on, Mother.
You've been quite adept
at making decisions in my name...
decisions which I've found
extremely distasteful.
You insolent bastard.
Let's not discuss
your weaknesses now, Mother.
I forbid you to say another word.
You forbid nothing.
As heir to the throne of House Corrino,
I am now the author of my own decisions.
My mother is stripped of all accounts
and privileges of the House Corrino.
She is no longer
sovereign regent of this family.
She is, from this moment forward,
banished.
You're more of a man
than I'd ever thought possible.
And you can spend the rest of your days
pondering that in utter darkness.
Patience is a virtue I have
in abundance, if you haven't noticed.
Hold.
Did you have anything to do
with the death of my brother?
I knew nothing of the plot against him
until it was too late.
Forgive me.
I am at your mercy.
This is my wedding present to you.
I have nothing else.
No dowry.
Only the truth.
I believe him.
Take her. Leave him.
Maybe he'll amuse us
with more intrigue...
and double-cross in the days to come.
Don't you find it interesting,
Jessica...
how the sins of the mother
bloom in the children they bear?
She's weakened by madness.
She still commands
the imperial armies.
They are retreating to the city...
trapped by the shield wall
from which they are vulnerable.
They say the price on your head
keeps going up.
Then I say unto you...
send men...
to summon worms!
Then let us go...
to Arakeen...
to collect it.
Manut.
A storm.
Not a storm.
- I must get word to the palace.
- Yeah.
Don't be afraid, Gurney-Man.
There is no way...
to hasten
what is meant to be.
When the time is right...
he will find us.
Who are you?
Who I am
doesn't matter anymore.
It matters to me.
Do you think I would have
left this place if I had known?
Do you think I would have abandoned you
if I knew you were still alive?
You did what you
were meant to do.
Tell me.
Let me hear you say it.
Tell me it isn't true.
I couldn't live...
if I knew I had forsaken you.
Paul Atreides is no more,
Gurney-Man.
The desert winds have erased
all trace of his passage here.
And soon...
Muad'Dib must follow.
Please, Gurney, I'm tired...
hungry.
Get me some food.
Ah, Stil. So predictable.
It's as if they're daring you
to confront them...
challenging you
to commit troops, thopters.
They think I've retreated to the
sanctuary of the city where I'm trapped.
It's a tactic learned from my brother
when he defeated Shaddam...
and took back Arrakis.
Poor Stil.
If you only knew
it is you who are trapped...
not I.
They are still over a day's ride
from Arakeen.
Fine.
I'm going back to the palace.
I have a wedding to attend.
Leave me.
Do as I say!
There's no need for that
with me, Ghanima.
Our plan worked.
You're alive!
I knew it.
Oh, I have missed you.
I'm sorry, Ghanima.
I'm so sorry.
I had to let you think that I was dead.
It was the only way--
the only way that I could start
what must now be finished.
Idolaters! Blasphemers!
You'll spoil this place!
The desert will swallow you!
His words are sacrilege.
His presence must not be tolerated.
You must give the order, Holy One.
You must send us to take him.
Caution, darling.
Do not act impulsively.
Not yet.
He is an outrage
to the religion of Muad'Dib.
But that's the point, my darling.
We must know for sure whether
he really is your brother...
mustn't we?
It would not do to make
a martyr of him just yet.
Who is it
that calls for Muad'Dib?
Help us, Muad'Dib.
Muad'Dib's words are the wind.
They vanish...
like water on the sand.
I'll give you Muad'Dib's words.
I'll rub your faces in them!
I am the voice
from the wilderness...
and I bring you a warning.
The water we spread upon the desert
has become blood.
Blood... upon the land
which was once clean and pure.
We have provoked the desert...
forsaken its ways.
We have succumbed
to mindless ritual...
and seductive ceremony...
placed faith in those
who crush dissent...
enrich themselves with power...
commit atrocity.
All in the name
of righteousness!
All in the name...
of Muad'Dib.
We have fouled the nest...
and it is killing us.
But I have seen another path...
a golden path--
the path Muad'Dib could not take.
I have stood upon the sand...
and I have seen a beast rise up.
And upon the head of that beast...
is the name of salvation...
come to spill water
upon the sand...
come to lead us back...
to a dry and thirsty land.
Only one blasphemy remains...
and that blasphemy...
is Alia!
Forgive me...
Sister.
It's in your hands now...
Son.
Where is she?
Behold me, family!
I am Leto!
Lion of Atreides...
returned from the desert
to announce Sachar Nabai--
The Golden Path--
to rid humanity of the perversions
done in Muad'Dib's name...
and to save it from the abomination
known as Alia.
Seize him!
The time has come, Aunt.
You must face the future.
I'll drink your blood!
Alia, stop it!
Stop yourself!
You sorry bitch!
You Bene Gesserit whore!
Did you think
you could escape my vengeance?
I was defeated forever?
I have her, daughter--
your precious Alia.
She's mine! I won!
Demon! Let her make
her own choice!
Mommy... please help me.
Help yourself.
Yes! Yes, do it.
Sink it in.
Bathe our hands
in his hot blood.
No! Darling! Stop! Stop!
Stop! We're so close!
I love you. I can save you.
Don't stop now. We're so close.
I want my brother.
You'll not change your mind
and return with me to Caladan?
I must remain here, my lady...
at Sietch Tabr with Stilgar.
He will need my help
to bring peace back to this land.
- And you?
- I have no home but here.
Besides, there will be children again,
and they will need me.
Dear friend.
Alia's water.
Take it into the desert and spread it
upon the open sand in the midday sun.
It is our way.
Are you going back
to Sietch Tabr?
I wish to return
to our old ways.
The desert's dying, Stil.
And the Fremen, too, I'm afraid.
We're about to go through
the crucible...
but we'll come out
the other side.
We always arise
from our own ashes.
Everything returns later in its...
changed form.
Your grandfather's ring...
and your father's.
And now the Fremen's...
to remind you of Muad'Dib...
to remind you
that all humans make mistakes...
and that all leaders
are but human.
He runs and runs and runs.
And when he's exhausted himself...
he returns to me...
puts his head in my lap...
and asks me to help him
find a way to die.
But why does he want to die?
To save himself...
from the sacrifices
he must make--
sacrifices for the future of us all.
Then there is a place for me
in this future?
Your blood was spared
the day Leto came back to me.
What of our marriage then?
As my mother was not wife...
you shall never be husband.
Politics.
But in time, there may be love...
which is more
than my brother will have.
One of us
had to accept the agony.
He was always the stronger.
History is written
on the sands of Arrakis.
A chapter has ended...
swept away by the whirlwind.
One door has closed...
but another has opened.
And on the other side...
our future.