( DISTANT EXPLOSIONS RUMBLE )
WOMAN: 12 years of war.
12 years since
Emperor Shaddam IV was defeated
and Paul Muad'Dib's wild Fremen
spread out across the universe,
exterminating all that remained
of the old Imperial armies.
Colonising the planets
of the known universe
one by one, under his rule.
Sweeping away anything and anyone
who resisted.
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
Millions have been defeated,
millions more have been slaughtered.
There are no innocents anywhere
and the name of Muad'Dib
is no longer a prayer.
For many, it is now a curse.
MAN: The mercy of Muad'Dib
is comfort to all enemies.
The compassion of Muad'Dib...
MAN: Commander Farok!
The conversions have begun!
Anyone refusing the peace of Muad'Dib
will be executed!
So it is written!
MAN: You who deny the glory
of Muad'Dib
are condemned to death.
Sir, your son.
He's been wounded.
Your soul...
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
My eyes. My eyes!
I'm blind, Father. I'm blind.
Don't give me to the desert, Father.
Please!
Don't send me to die.
(Screams) Muad'Dib!
WOMAN: If history teaches us anything,
it is simply this -
every revolution carries within it
the seeds of its own destruction,
and empires that rise will one day fall.
Arrakis.
Dune.
Once the wasteland of the universe,
now an Imperial capital,
for it is here and only here
the giant worms still roam,
creating spice -
still the greatest treasure in the universe,
still the cause of conspiracy,
betrayal and murder.
( EXOTIC MUSIC )
( BELLS TOLL )
( EPIC MUSIC )
MAN: Alia!
WOMAN: Alia!
MAN: It's her!
WOMAN: The holy sister!
WOMAN: Alia!
( CROWD CHEERS )
(Crowd chants)
Alia! Alia! Alia! Alia!
In the beginning, we were all empty.
ALL: Ignorant of all things.
We did not know the power
that resides in every place.
ALL: And in all time.
He is the power that awakens the soul.
ALL: And brings us joy.
Muad'Dib. Muad'Dib.
(Crowd cheers)
MAN: Muad'Dib!
I don't suppose you feel
it's necessary to inform me
when you go on these walkabouts?
You'd only try and stop me.
Again.
The streets are full of danger, Muad'Dib.
The truth is in the streets, Stil,
not in this parade of sycophants
who flutter around this palace
with their meaningless statistics
and empty ritual.
Ritual is the whip by which
men are enlightened, Muad'Dib.
Tell me, Korba,
when was it you reinvented yourself from
Fremen Fedaykin to religious fanatic?
The day you defeated Shaddam
and his armies, Muad'Dib.
The day I saw the future.
The city's filled with adventurers,
Muad'Dib,
not to mention agents
of the Spacing Guild,
the Bene Gesserit
and the former Imperial family.
Surely they conspire to
something a little more elegant
than assassination
on the streets of Arrakeen?
You are vulnerable, Muad'Dib.
No matter how powerful
you have become,
you cannot escape this simple fact.
You're right about one thing, Stil.
There is no escape.
(Whispers) Chani.
( ETHEREAL MUSIC )
I'm not asleep.
I thought the doctor said
you were supposed to rest.
As long as you insist on wandering
the city like some off-world pilgrim,
I will never be able to rest.
Are you going to lecture me too?
Hmm!
While I was walking,
I stepped in a puddle...
...an open pool of water in the street.
Muad'Dib has brought
many wonders to Arrakis...
(Sighs)
..the people say.
"Muad'Dib spends water like a madman."
That's what they say, Chani.
The old Fremen, I hear them...
...on the streets when I walk.
"We've become water-fat."
They resent the 'wonders'
I've brought to their desert.
They resent me.
You know what I'd pay
to end these wars?
Separate myself from this...
...damnable myth I've become?
What's to stop you?
Command it, Muad'Dib.
After all, you are the Emperor.
Even if I vanished tomorrow,
the revolution would follow my ghost.
This is not a clean place.
It's time to return to the desert.
We were happy there.
( MAN YELLS, EERIE MUSIC )
BOY: Father.
I'm waiting and I'm ready.
To know the future is to be trapped by it.
But knowing there's a trap
is the first step in evading it.
It's the first step along the Golden Path.
I'm the answer.
I'm ready, Father.
And I am ready, Father.
The answer's
standing right in front of you,
on the Golden Path.
(Gasps)
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
Is there no other way?
(Sighs)
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
Everywhere we turn,
his power confronts us.
He's a curse.
He's a messiah.
You can't launch a frontal attack
on a messiah.
Even if you succeed,
their martyrdom remains.
But he is human,
and because he is human,
he has his weaknesses.
So, what do you suggest, Princess?
Something subtle,
something... unexpected.
A ghost, perhaps?
Mmm.
May I introduce our friend,
Reverend Mother, Scytale of the Tleilaxu.
Get to the point, Wensicia.
I haven't travelled all the way
to the edge of the universe
to discuss nonsense
with a... face dancer.
No, you Bene Gesserit
are desperate to regain control
of Muad'Dib's bloodline
and because you want
to break his monopoly on spice.
He who controls the spice
controls the universe.
As long as Muad'Dib controls Arrakis,
we are all at his mercy.
And that's why I intend
to destroy that domination
and return the Imperial Throne
to the planet Kaitain,
and the Corrino family,
where it rightfully belongs.
Face dancers, sex toys,
musicians, technicians.
Whatever the need...
...we have the breed.
(Gasps)
Good God!
Good chemistry is more like it.
Duncan Idaho.
WENSICIA: Yes, the Atreides hero.
Paul Muad'Dib's
most beloved friend and teacher.
But Idaho is dead.
Killed by your father's Sardaukar.
Even in defeat,
my father's men did not abandon
wisdom, Reverend Mother.
A few precious pieces
of Idaho's ruined flesh,
hidden away, saved.
Awaiting just the right time,
the right place.
A perfect duplicate.
A perfect ghola.
Perfect gift for a lonely emperor.
A time bomb, waiting
for the trigger to explode.
You intend to KILL Muad'Dib?
Exactly.
But that will mean chaos.
Spice production will be disrupted.
Learn the lesson my father ignored -
it's not who controls the spice,
but who has the ability to disrupt the spice
who controls the universe.
But what makes you think
Muad'Dib will ever accept this... ghost?
I'm leaving it up to the Spacing Guild.
And what of the trigger?
The device to set the time bomb off?
Leave that to me.
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
Test after test, and still nothing.
I'm healthy, strong.
No matter what they do,
the doctors can't find the reason
why I am unable to conceive.
What does Muad'Dib say?
Muad'Dib is... afraid.
He fears for me if I have another child.
I can feel it.
He may be right to fear.
Someone has been feeding you
a poison.
It's the only possibility left.
But the doctors
have never found evidence.
They wouldn't.
Its traces are subtle, confusing.
Of the most sophisticated chemistry,
beyond our knowledge.
Surely from off-world.
But... there are remedies.
The ancient Fremen diet,
which might overcome
the contraceptive's effects.
But it's dangerous.
You would be required
to eat greater and greater
quantities of spice.
And if you conceive,
it will accelerate your pregnancy.
But the question remains,
"Who has been able
"to feed you the contraceptives
for so long?"
MAN: Be that as it may,
this is a question
that cannot be delayed any longer.
The Great Houses are still demanding
that a constitution be on the agenda
at the next convention
of the Landsraad.
It's nothing but a ruse,
contrived by enemies of House Atreides
to conceal far more sinister motives.
Perhaps we could offer
the appearance of a constitution.
Something ceremonial.
It doesn't need to be real.
Deceit, after all,
is a legitimate tool of statecraft.
Bravo, sister-in-law.
I couldn't have said it better.
Yes, perhaps something
at the local level?
Something impotent.
Virtually meaningless.
No!
Atreides power
must never be marginalised
by the chaos of democracy.
I'm sure my brother agrees.
(Voice echoes) Father, Father.
I'm waiting.
You must decide.
It's the first step. It can't wait.
Love is all you have.
The answer's
standing right in front of you
but you must decide.
( BLADE RINGS, BABY CRIES )
(Voice whispers) Muad'Dib.
Alia knows my mind.
I forbid a constitution.
"Order in Council this day, " etc, etc.
Irulan. Are you taking this down?
Yes, My Lord.
We will deliver the formal declaration
when the Guild ambassador arrives
to present his credentials.
Then there's nothing more.
A Guild embassy, Muad'Dib, on Arrakis?
The Council of Naibs
won't like this, Muad'Dib.
We remember well how the Guild
brought those who oppressed us,
how they blackmailed us for spice
to keep our secrets from our enemies.
Think I've forgotten, Stil?
This... decision troubles me, Muad'Dib.
There's something... reckless about it.
Not reckless, necessary.
You will know my reasons soon enough.
Now, I trust you'll convince the Naibs
of the wisdom in this.
IRULAN: A Guild ambassador,
here on Arrakis.
Muad'Dib's decision strikes some
as mysterious, even dangerous.
But Muad'Dib never does anything
without reason.
( DRAMATIC FLOURISH )
I should spill your water on the sand
for what you've done.
I know it was you, Irulan.
You're the only one
who could have hidden the poison.
(Hoarsely) Don't lie!
You will insult me if you lie!
It is my right to bear the royal heir.
It is your duty to play a role,
nothing more.
I am his wife!
You have his name.
I am the one he calls 'wife'.
Do you think you are the only woman
who truly loves him?
No.
But I am the only woman HE loves.
I could cuckold him.
Dare him to expose me.
Cuckold him all you like.
As long as you're discreet,
he won't deny you.
But no child, Irulan.
Ever.
( METAL CLASHES )
So, what do you think, Tyekanik?
Does my little prince have what it takes
to lead a Sardaukar army one day?
There are many ways
to lead an army, Princess.
Being a warrior is only one of them.
And not necessarily the best.
MAN: Prince Farad'N, your turn.
Muad'Dib's decision
to accept the Guild ambassador
is causing much unrest on Arrakis.
Hmm. Good.
Once the face dancer is insinuated
into Muad'Dib's palace...
...we shall light the fuse.
( THUD! )
PRINCE: Arggh!
And the Idaho ghola will do its work.
Mom! Mommy.
What is this?
I am sorry, Princess.
A future emperor crying?
I don't want to be an emperor.
Let someone else do it.
Oh, nonsense! Wipe your tears. Here.
Getting all over me now.
Alright, now, go back to your men.
Go back. Go.
Do you want the men to see you crying?
Do you want them thinking you're weak?
I don't care.
Well, I do.
So now you will go back.
And this time...
...you will do it properly.
Won't you?
(Caws)
( MAJESTIC MUSIC )
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
Commander Farok,
hero of the Naraj campaign.
I bring you greetings
from your new friends
on Salusa Secundus.
Hurry. The eyes of Muad'Dib
are everywhere.
These are seats once occupied
in sietch by Muad'Dib...
...during the days when
he taught us the weirding way.
It is some time since you've seen him.
I think he's forgotten I ever existed.
He's blind.
Your son.
At the battle of Naraj.
I wonder if Muad'Dib knows how many
have been maimed in his name.
I couldn't leave him to the desert.
Even I violated the old laws.
Laws of men have gone.
The laws of a god have replaced them.
We were a noble people once.
We had a proper sietch.
I owned a crysknife.
My own share of spice.
I was a rider of worms.
And then Muad'Dib came.
With his witch mother.
And he promised to fulfil Liet's prophecy.
And we fought.
You joined his jihad.
Do you know why?
I heard there was a thing called a 'sea'.
Men came back from Muad'Dib's wars
and they said they had seen it.
And... did you find your sea?
It healed me of jihad.
Now I'm ready to help rid the universe
of the cancer that is Muad'Dib.
And that is Otheym's daughter?
Lichna.
If you bring her to Muad'Dib,
he will never refuse to see her.
I was hoping that's what you'd say.
( WHIRRING )
(Gasps and chokes)
Lichna.
I will enjoy being called Lichna.
What is the meaning of this?
Helen Gaius Mohiam
of the Bene Gesserit,
you have violated Muad'Dib's eternal
order never to set foot on Arrakis again.
I am not on Arrakis. I am in free space.
There is no such thing as free space
where Muad'Dib rules.
( TENSE MUSIC )
( MAJESTIC MUSIC )
I abase myself before the Emperor.
We welcome you to our court,
Edric of the Spacing Guild,
and to a new understanding between us.
Please allow me the honour
of presenting His Majesty
with a small token of our esteem.
( AUDIENCE GASPS )
According to our investigators,
this one was killed here on Arrakis.
The body recovered
after the unfortunate conflict
between Houses Atreides
and Harkonnen.
Terrible wounds required
many months of regrowth
by Tleilaxu technicians.
We acquired him
as a gift befitting an emperor.
What is your name, ghola?
They say it was Duncan Idaho.
Idaho is dead!
This... thing is a horror!
Send him away!
And do you enjoy the name?
It stirs up curious feelings.
You don't know who you are?
I know nothing of my past, Sire.
How was this one trained?
It amused the Tleilaxu
to train him as a Mentat.
I beg you, My Lord!
Let me take its water.
Find quarters in the keep
for the ghola, Stil.
We accept this gift
in the spirit with which it was given.
Majesty, there is the matter
of Reverend Mother Mohiam.
She was removed from our heighliner
by your agents
in violation of our neutrality.
Be careful, Ambassador.
To be neutral is to be indifferent.
You would do well
to disassociate yourself
from those who have proven they are not.
As you will learn, Edric,
my sister has the pulse of the court.
Be advised.
Reverend Mother.
I shudder to see you
in such circumstances.
I've been in worse.
Do the cards answer all your questions?
Answers only breed more questions.
What is important is how
one navigates between the two.
So you haven't forgotten
everything we taught you.
Has the Emperor explained
why I am to be detained?
He has not confided in me,
Reverend Mother.
But I hope it will not be too long.
We understand.
The sisterhood is aware of my delay?
They have changed your schedule
in light of the situation.
I'll be patient, then.
You seem to be
adapting to life here quite well.
I have made my peace with it.
I hope your training has been a help.
A comfort.
One day, even Muad'Dib
will know the good you have done.
For us all.
( STIRRING MUSIC )
( METALLIC WHIRRING )
( BLADES WHIRR )
(Laughs)
You know how dangerous that was?
11 blades, Paul! 11!
(Laughs)
Some of the finest swordsmen
in the Imperium
have never gone up against
more than nine.
Experienced swordsmen
would never be so reckless.
This is why you invaded my privacy?
To disapprove of my recklessness?
Spice gatherers
found a body in the desert.
A young woman - a Fremen.
Fremen?
Decapitated.
And her hands removed.
So someone's afraid she'd be found
before the desert does its work.
I want you to examine the scene
the way our mother taught us.
You will take the ghola Mentat with you.
I assume you can handle him.
I should arrange a 'thopter.
( HAUNTING MUSIC )
( WIND BLOWS )
Poison!
How can you tell?
The moulting of the skin.
Clearly the effect
of rapid neurological atrophy -
a Tleilaxu speciality.
Tleilaxu?
Face dancers.
This is a dead Fremen girl, My Lady.
What if there are no women
reported missing amongst the Fremen?
Otheym's daughter, My Lord.
Lichna.
It's been many years since I've seen you.
And my father.
I must beg Muad'Dib's forgiveness
for this intrusion, but...
...I am the smoke
who banishes sleep in the night.
Sit.
Deliver your warning, then.
You must visit my father
as soon as possible, My Lord.
There is a plot against you.
There are many plots against me.
This is a Fremen plot, Majesty.
My father has information for you.
But he is weak.
He is sick.
He needs you to visit so he can tell you.
Why didn't he tell you
so you could tell me?
He feared I might be captured
before seeing you.
If I know nothing, I can divulge nothing.
I leave for Otheym's tonight.
(Sighs)
Otheym has missed... his old friend.
A face dancer.
Good one too.
Let me take its water.
No, Stil.
This must play out the way I've seen it.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
MAN: Cursed be thy name, Atreides.
Your time has finally come.
BOY: Korba!
The stone burner is set and ready.
Let the others know, Javid.
Muad'Dib is in the streets.
Go.
So you've come, then.
We meet again, Muad'Dib.
Answering the call of the Fedaykin.
I carry your water burden, Otheym.
Command me.
(Coughs and chokes)
(Hawks and spits)
(Groans)
(Sighs) I caught the spitting disease
in Tarahell.
Ohh.
The tribe will take my water soon.
Let me summon my doctors.
WOMAN: We've had doctors...
...as good as any Muad'Dib could provide.
There's treachery, Muad'Dib.
I'm ashamed to say it.
Fremen plot against you.
They want time to stop.
They want things
the way they used to be.
Bijaz has told me their names.
He was a gift to me,
after our victories in Tarahell.
I am a person, not a gift.
Cheap to feed, but costly to fill.
Empty me as you will, Sire.
He always prattles on like that.
He's a good spy, though.
You should take him tonight.
Our enemies will think
I'm selling him for the money.
To be gone is to be bygone.
Let bygones be bygones
and Bijaz and Muad'Dib
must be gone by now.
He's right, Muad'Dib.
It's not safe for you to be here.
These are troubled times, old friend.
It was better when
we were alone in the desert...
...with only the Harkonnen
as our enemies.
BIJAZ: There's a thin line
between enemy and friend.
Where that line stops,
there's no beginning.
And no end.
Bygones be bygones,
let them fall where they may.
This has been a dirty day.
( WIND BLOWS )
( METAL CHINKS SOFTLY )
The wind speaks of demons.
That is not the wind.
( HOWLING )
( METAL CLANGS )
( LOUD RATTLING )
Stone burner!
( EXPLOSION )
Don't look at it, My Lord!
You can't look at it!
(Screams)
(Man yells in pain)
It was in the old quarter.
Stone burner, for sure.
What about Muad'Dib?
We are just entering the area now.
( BROODING MUSIC )
(People whimper in pain)
My Lord, is that you?!
Here. I'm over here!
Take this one
and get him to the keep immediately.
Your eyes.
Do it, Fedaykin. DO IT NOW!
This way.
My Lord... your eyes.
My eyes are gone, Stil.
Muad'Dib... my gods!
Muad'Dib...
Calm, Stil.
They've blinded my body...
but not my vision.
There are men who need your help,
Fedaykin, here and here!
The Law, Muad'Dib.
We live by Atreides law now, Stil.
None of these men
are to be taken out into the desert.
Anyone who wants
is to be fitted with Tleilaxu eyes.
MAN: Without eyes, yet he sees.
He has sight without eyes.
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
You knew this would happen.
It had to be.
Why?
For our son.
How long have you known?
I've always known.
It was just a matter of when.
Forgive me, Chani.
There was no way I could spare us this.
I waited as long as I could.
We will return to our desert, my love...
...to the sietch where our son will be born.
I'm afraid, Muad'Dib.
I suddenly feel like
we have so little time.
We have eternity.
YOU have eternity.
I have only now.
So you are Bijaz?
Would I were Bijou and not Bijaz,
a jewel is prettier than a horse's ass.
You're a mockery, then.
A trick of nature
meant to confuse and annoy.
Annoy, yes.
Confuse, no.
Is wind a trick?
Then you're the wind?
No, I am words in the wind,
words that are names,
names that are death.
He knows.
What does he mean?
What I mean is what I say,
and what I say is what I mean.
Time for account,
unless you come just to mock at me.
My brother says you know
the names of the traitors.
Poor Muad'Dib... poor Bijaz.
(Sings) ♫ Betrayed and betrayer
together at last. ♫
You will give me the names
of those who would betray us.
Very well, then.
Let's start with your priests.
He has another agenda.
How do you know?
I sense it.
Senses are dangerous.
They can be fooled.
Only a machine functions without senses.
Are you a machine, ghola?
I am a Mentat.
I trust only logic and statistics.
Not mysticism and prophecy?
My brother had a Mentat teacher
who talked like that.
Hawat.
You remember?
You did that on purpose.
You remember.
No.
I feel.
There is a difference.
(Laughs) Is there?
It frightens you, doesn't it?
The memory?
You're afraid
you'll remember who you were.
No ghola has ever been restored
to his former being, child.
I'm no child.
I awakened to consciousness
in my mother's womb.
I have memories of many women
alive inside of me.
I know what they knew,
I feel what they felt,
but I can handle it.
Can you?
(Bird squawks)
Palace Fedaykin are everywhere.
By the time Alia's through,
a common pickpocket won't be safe.
The fools even had a stone burner
and they couldn't succeed.
Our spies have no idea
who was responsible.
It could have been Fremen rebels
from the deep desert.
It could have been an element within
the Gesserit itself. We may never know.
What about Scytale?
He maintains his masquerade.
And the dwarf?
Confined to the keep.
No-one knows where.
Then our plan is still in place.
Mmm.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
He's alive?
Gurney, tell me he's alive.
He is alive.
But he's blind.
It was a stone burner.
Stilgar suspects Fremen.
Alia? Chani?
All safe.
Blind?
There are rumours that Paul can still see
despite his blindness - vision sight.
They say it's a miracle.
Another brick for the myth of Muad'Dib.
My Lady?
Make arrangements
for the Guild ambassador
for immediate transport to Arrakis.
I don't think that would be wise.
It was only a matter of time
before this happened.
Might not be long
before it happens again.
And you would not want to encourage it.
Oh, forgive me, My Lady,
but those who would
rid themselves of Muad'Dib
would only be more provoked
by the arrival of his mother.
If Paul needs you,
he would surely send for you.
( BROODING MUSIC )
( EERIE MUSIC )
We go forward. We come back.
Don't be afraid, Father.
The answer's right in front of you.
The Golden Path. But you must decide.
It's the only way.
( MUSIC BUILDS TO CRESCENDO )
What troubles you, My Lord?
The future.
You're drunk on too much time.
I'm drunk on too much me.
You know how many people have died
since I became Emperor?
Even your empire must live its time...
and then die.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
Is that what you've seen...
in your visions?
It's obvious to anyone who can see.
It's what the Tleilaxu
have written upon you - to kill me.
( DOOR OPENS )
What is it, Stil?
I have just received word
from Salusa Secundus.
Shaddam is dead.
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
How very generous of Muad'Dib
to permit his wife to attend
the funeral of his mortal enemy.
And how grateful you must be
for the safety
my sacrifice assured our father...
...and you.
(Squawks)
Not one major house representative.
Not one!
Muad'Dib would not allow
any formal delegations, My Lady.
As far as he was concerned,
your father died
the day he was defeated on Arrakis.
My father was the 81st
Padishah Emperor, a colossus!
I mean, who is this bastard Atreides
but some Bedouin charlatan?
Do not underestimate the power
of Muad'Dib's prescience, My Lady.
Your father did... to his great misfortune.
My father was betrayed by you
and your simpering Spacing Guild
and those witches of the Bene Gesserit.
And for what? For spice.
You abandoned your emperor for spice.
We cannot guide our ships
without it, My Lady.
And that is why you will help me
kidnap a worm and bring it here.
I mean no disrespect, Princess,
but take a worm from Arrakis?
Even if the Idaho ghola succeeds,
there is still the sister to contend with.
We must be prepared with other means
to diminish the Atreides power.
You want to bring a worm here?
Salusa Secundus might prove hospitable
to the great worms of Arrakis.
If they thrived,
a new spice cycle could begin.
And...?
Atreides monopoly would be broken.
Plans within plans.
If Muad'Dib ever suspected
such a gambit,
he would smash this planet
and the Corrino name into oblivion.
We're already in oblivion.
( BROODING MUSIC )
Kidnap a worm from Arrakis.
The spice must flow.
( SLOW DRAMATIC DRUMMING )
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Roars loudly)
(Roars)
Get out of the way!
(Men scream)
The doctors say
her metabolism has accelerated.
Pregnancy is proceeding
faster than normal.
It, er... will be a dangerous birth.
Beloved.
I'm sorry. I've distracted you.
Shh, shh, shh.
(Laughs)
If only you could distract me forever.
My body is confusing me, Muad'Dib.
My life burns faster.
I'm so hungry.
Always hungry.
Make arrangements, Stil.
We leave for the sietch
as soon as possible.
The baby will be born there.
Inform my sister.
(Alia speaks other language)
(Cries)
( VOICES ECHO )
How long have you been there?
Long enough.
Are you sick, My Lady?
You don't know what it's like
to hunt the future.
( VOICES ECHO )
You've taken spice.
Too much.
My brother needs me, Duncan,
and my vision is incomplete.
I need to remember. I need...
I need to remember the future.
I'm going to summon doctors.
No, no.
(Desperately) Don't leave me.
I just need to... just...
(Sighs deeply)
( DISEMBODIED HUMMING )
(Desperately) I can't move.
What are you doing to me?
I am playing. (Voice echoes)
You were made to be played...
...like Otheym, poor fellow.
We had a terrific struggle with you.
The flesh did not want to come back.
(Hums tunefully)
You are Tleilaxu?
Born and bred...
in the same tank... just we two.
First me, then you.
Then you.
You are trying to bring out
the violence in me.
Oh, no... not yet.
The script is written...
but the stage is not set.
But one day soon,
the Emperor will come to you,
a mask of grief obscuring his face.
A mask of grief. (Hums tunefully)
And he'll say, "She's gone."
"She is gone."
And then you will finally remember
what you're expected to do.
What you're expected to do.
"She is gone." (Hums tunefully)
PAUL: She is gone, Duncan.
Now it's time to forget
what you remember
when day becomes night.
(Sings)
♫ Forgetting is not having
♫ Till the words are right. ♫
What do you see with those eyes?
What everyone sees.
( ETHEREAL MUSIC )
We're leaving for the sietch this morning.
And I'm being left behind?
Appropriate, I'd say,
considering what you've done.
I never meant to hurt Chani... or you.
I just...
I've given orders
no harm is to come to you.
No matter what happens.
Is she...
She's well.
For the moment.
I've been cruel to you, Irulan.
I don't want your pity.
I'm offering none.
Simply telling you the truth.
You were destined.
A condition I understand only too well.
Destined to be used.
By you?
By your father.
By the Bene Gesserit,
by the Spacing Guild.
Protect them from me.
And they'll get their wish.
I'm not exactly as they'd like.
I don't understand.
The time of plots and revenge
is coming to an end.
You must have a chance to find peace.
I'm going to give you that chance.
It's ironic...
...but your selfish, clumsy attempts
to mother an Imperial heir
actually prolonged Chani's life.
And for that, I am grateful.
Forever.
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
Muad'Dib, is it truly necessary
to bring the face dancer AND the dwarf?
They have their parts to play, Stil,
just like you and me.
( WIND HOWLS )
Chani and I will take this one.
Muad'Dib!
I know the way
better than anyone else, Stil.
Except, perhaps, you.
You must remain here, as we agreed.
Time to settle accounts.
( SHIP ENGINE POWERS UP )
(Both moan and gasp)
MAN: Stay where you are!
What's the meaning of this?
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
You plotted against Muad'Dib, Korba.
You conspired against your emperor.
You are under arrest for treason.
(Men grunt)
I am a Fremen.
I demand to be judged by Fremen law.
You will be, Korba.
You will be.
I used to hunt these here,
when I was little.
It's amazing,
the simple pleasures one has as a child.
But the desert is leaving now...
...taking simple pleasure with it.
I wonder if my father would approve
of the future he inspired.
A storm comes, My Lady.
(Whispers) I am a desert creature, ghola.
I know when to hide.
Ooh!
Paul said he would join you
as soon as the night council is concluded.
You called him Paul...
...his Atreides name.
I did.
A memory intruded
where none should have been.
Then there are more...
and it frightens you.
Duncan's memories, they scare you.
Are they Duncan's memories...
...or the inventions
of those who made me?
When the moment comes to decide...
...you will know.
(Moans)
My Lady...
Ohh!
Oh!
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
( WOMAN SINGS HAUNTING SONG )
(Weakly) Muad'Dib.
It was the birth, My Lord.
They said her body was drained
by the speed of it.
( BABY CRIES )
These are your children, Muad'Dib.
Both are alive and strong.
Children?
Twins, My Lord. A boy and a girl.
( BABIES CRY AND GURGLE )
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
I never saw children.
CHANI: Muad'Dib.
(Weakly) Muad'Dib.
Beloved...
...forgive me.
There are some things no-one can bear.
Problems in this universe...
...for which there are no answers...
(Tearfully) ..for which
nothing can be done - nothing!
I am sorry.
Nothing in this universe...
...is as great...
...as my love for you.
(Inhales sharply)
(Moans)
( SORROWFUL MUSIC )
(Panicked) Oh, I can't see!
My Lord? My Lord!
She's gone.
(Hums)
She is gone, Duncan.
(Softly) She is gone.
(Chokes)
VOICE: Then you'll finally remember
what you're expected to do.
(Continues humming)
...you're expected to do... (Echoes)
This was the moment
you came back to me, Duncan.
( FOOTSTEPS SCURRY )
(Extracts knife)
( BABIES CRY )
Stay where you are, both of you.
I warn you, a face dancer can move
faster than you can possibly imagine.
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC )
So, it is truly you.
Duncan Idaho of the Atreides.
A ghola CAN regain his past.
Tell me, what do you remember?
Tell him.
Everything.
My childhood, my youth...
...my death.
We did it! We did it.
Majesty, don't you see what this means?
You can have her back again,
your beloved Chani.
The proof is standing right in front of you.
We can restore the flesh and the spirit.
We can re-create her.
This was your plan all along.
Plots within plots, My Lord -
you should know better than anyone.
We've been trying for decades
to achieve this.
Make an alliance with us, Muad'Dib,
the Tleilaxu.
Let us restore your beloved Chani.
(Sobs)
Live content and safe
for the rest of your life...
...with her, with your children.
(Echoing) With her, with your children.
My Lord, please, don't listen
to this blasphemy.
Don't move, Duncan Idaho.
You kill me, and you're killing
Muad'Dib's children.
(Babies cry)
You can feel it, can't you, Muad'Dib?
(Sobs)
Can't you?
You can hear her...
CHANI: I am afraid, Muad'Dib.
...calling your name.
(In Chani's voice) Muad'Dib.
Muad'Dib.
Father... don't be afraid, Father.
I'm here, Father,
as you knew I would be.
We go forward, we go back -
don't be afraid.
We are pre-born, my sister and I,
thanks to our mother and the spice.
Thanks to you.
Father, yes, it IS me!
We go forward, we go back...
Father, we are pre-born, my sister and I.
Thanks to you.
(Echoing) My eyes...
...let me see for you.
I can do it. I can bring her back to you.
Use my eyes, Father. Use them!
My eyes, let me see for you.
My eyes, Father. Use them!
I can do it. I can bring her back.
Let us give you back your love.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS )
(Groans)
( DRAMATIC PERCUSSIVE MUSIC )
( EXPLOSIVE SOUNDSCAPE )
The children. The children!
They're safe, Muad'Dib.
(Babies gurgle)
( UPLIFTING MUSIC )
I meddled in the future,
in all possible futures...
...trying to create them.
Instead, they created me
and I became trapped by them.
Yes, but knowing there's a trap
is the first step in evading it.
The first step along the Golden Path.
Don't be afraid, Father.
The answer is right in front of you.
(Baby cries)
Finally I am free.
IRULAN: History is written
on the sands of Arrakis.
Those who wished an end
to House Atreides have failed.
No longer an emperor, no longer a god,
a simple blind Fremen
wanders alone into the desert
to die.
They say he has gone on a journey...
...into the land
where men walk without footprints.
He will not be found.
Yet all men will find him.
I wonder if that's what he wanted.
I need you, Duncan.
More than ever.
Stay with me.
( MAJESTIC MUSIC )
(Worm roars)
IRULAN: Muad'Dib is gone
but his children remain
and conspiracies continue to breed.
The saga of Dune is far from over.
( DRAMATIC THEME MUSIC )