( THEME MUSIC )
IRULAN: History is written
on the sands of Arrakis
where rebellion and civil war
continue to breed,
fed by Alia's brutal tyranny
and repression
as she sinks deeper into
the abomination of her own ghost.
( SHOUTING )
Unable to recognise the forces
conspiring against her,
unaware of the whirlwind
sweeping towards her
across the desert.
Well?
Who's going to
explain this to me?
Who's going to tell me why
I have rioting in my streets?
Why my name is being used
as a curse?
You simple fools.
The royal twins are missing
from Sietch Tabr,
Lady Jessica has been abducted
off-world.
Rebel alliances have been formed
by tribes to the south
and now we have anarchy
in the streets of Arrakeen!
You are to blame.
Go.
Perhaps you should rest,
My Lady.
(Voices echo harshly) Alia!
( CACOPHONY OF VOICES )
It's difficult to think clearly
when one is exhausted
by stress.
Leave me.
(Whispers) I'm fine.
Such a pity, eh?
Why did you send
that lovely boy away?
I am not in the mood to indulge
your lurid perversions tonight.
Are they mine,
or simply yours in disguise?
After all, I am only enjoying
what you started.
Is that so?
Don't forget, child -
I'm not really here.
I'm simply the manifestation
of what you already are.
(Voices echo harshly) Alia!
ALIA: Go away!
Go away!
WENSICIA: Who else knows they
are requesting sanctuary here?
The Spacing Guild, of course.
They would provide transport
with Idaho's bribes.
The Bene Gesserit
will surely be informed...
...if they don't know already.
Then Alia will be forced to
implicate us in this adventure.
She'll have to make it appear
as if we arranged
the whole thing.
We should refuse them
safe harbour.
Return them to Arrakis and wash
our hands of the entire matter.
On the contrary, Tyek.
Perhaps we should think
of Lady Jessica's visit
as an endowment, not a threat.
The woman has many talents.
Perhaps they could be
of use to us.
You mean to you.
I see no reason why I shouldn't
continue my education
by all means necessary.
Any woman who can seduce
Duke Leto Atreides
and a planet of desert Fremen
is not to be trifled with.
Are you suggesting she might...
try to seduce me?
(Squawks)
Don't play the fool, Farad'N.
She would be a dangerous guest.
But... a grateful one.
He may have a point.
( TENSE MUSIC )
(Gasps)
Leto!
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
( DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS )
May the wind strip the flesh
from your bones.
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
May Shai-Hulud clear the path
before you.
Secher Nbiw.
When we meet again.
My skin is not my own.
PAUL: The Golden Path
is dangerous, son.
It's the choice
I couldn't take.
The desert storm
that cannot be stopped.
You will become that storm,
my son.
The whirlwind.
And nothing will be able
to stop you.
Not even yourself.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
(Groans)
Jacurutu.
(Woman sighs softly)
(Woman laughs)
(Sighs)
( THUD! )
(Gasps)
(Cries out)
WOMAN: This is for Leto.
(Calls out)
(Sighs)
( ETHEREAL MUSIC )
Leto?
We've confirmed
that it was Ghanima's knife
that killed Palimbasha.
And the communicator
he was wearing?
Off-world manufacture,
for sure.
Hmm.
We found a transceiver implanted
in a tiger's neck.
And we also found this
in the desert.
( ETHEREAL MUSIC CONTINUES )
Should I arrange transport
to the palace?
No!
Whoever will benefit from
the death of these children
will not rest until
they're sure they've succeeded.
Until the time is right,
she'll be safer here
than anywhere.
( EERIE SOUNDSCAPE )
( SLITHERING )
( SLITHERING INTENSIFIES )
Sandtrout.
MAN: So, you know your desert
farming, young Atreides.
That's right, Atreides.
Don't be foolish.
We have your water in our cup.
( SINISTER MUSIC )
WENSICIA: Alive?
She's alive.
(Screeches)
That clever bitch Ghanima
survived our tigers.
We must improvise quickly.
Tell our man in the Atreides
palace, the priest Javid,
he must stir Alia's pot
some more.
Yes, Princess.
MAN: They left our priest's body
where we would be sure
to find it.
He was assassinated
by Fremen rebels
from a sietch near Habbanya Erg.
He was travelling
with diplomatic immunity
when they attacked.
They carved blasphemy
into his skin, My Lady.
Horrible, profane curses
about you and your family.
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
"Cursed be the name Atreides.
"Burning beyond you
for the abomination
"you have visited
on our desert.
"You should have no soul
nor spirit.
"You shall not be permitted
to come up from the depths."
The obscenities
of desert rebels, Holiness.
An example must be made
to warn other tribes
what happens
if they persist
in this insurrection.
No mercy.
I want all traces
of the rebel sietch wiped out.
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
( SCREAMING )
(Woman whispers) Leto!
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
(Inhales sharply)
You would be Leto.
Son of Muad'Dib.
I am Sabiha.
I am meant to watch over you.
Yes, and no doubt kill me
if I try to escape.
That won't happen.
Drink.
I warn you,
any attempt at witchery
shall result
in immediate execution.
MAN: We are seeking
safe harbour,
not an opportunity
for treachery.
So you say.
But why should we risk
sheltering fugitives
from the Imperium?
Who says that we are fugitives?
Your confrontation with Alia
is already taking on mythic
proportions, Lady Jessica.
Several Fremen tribes
are known to be in open revolt
against the Qizarate.
Civil war seems imminent.
My grandchildren
will prevent that.
Not if they're dead.
I'm sorry, Jessica Atreides,
to be the bearer of bad news,
but it seems your grandchildren
have been the victims
of a well-planned
assassination plot.
Assassination?
Our reports indicate
the Atreides twins went missing
from Sietch Tabr.
They were attacked
in the desert.
Leto was killed.
We're not sure
what became of the girl.
We have reason to believe
Alia herself may have planned
the killings.
That is impossible.
Jessica, it's well-known
that your daughter's
on the verge of abomination.
Since Muad'Dib's heirs
were of age,
they were assumed to be
invested with all the powers
of his government.
Alia's role as Regent
was coming to an end, unless...
...unless your grandchildren
could be eliminated,
and the blame laid
on her enemies.
On us!
Events on Arrakis
are spinning wildly
out of control, Jessica Atreides.
Now, we can retreat
and watch the Empire collapse
on top of us,
or we can give each other
sanctuary.
(Whispers) I can protect you
from Alia's reach.
And you can protect me
from her madness.
And how do I do that?
By announcing publicly
that we did not kidnap you,
as Alia now alleges -
that you came
of your own free will,
an emissary of the Bene Gesserit
sent to...
...take over the education
of my son.
You want me to teach him
as the Bene Gesserit are taught?
An offer I could not resist.
Your Mentat is conspicuous
by his silence.
One must be careful
to evaluate who has the advantage
in such situations.
Perhaps there is
mutual advantage all around.
( GENERAL HUBBUB )
Stilgar refuses
to allow Ghanima to travel,
saying she is
not strong enough,
saying her safety
cannot be guaranteed.
He has offered sanctuary.
He is Naib of the sietch.
We cannot overrule his wishes.
We'll see about that.
The activities at Tabr
are curious and provocative.
No-one is allowed
to visit or depart
without Stilgar's permission.
They are planning
to go over to the rebels.
That's unlikely, My Lady.
We know Stilgar's
initiated dialogue
with the insurgent Naibs
to the south,
but only as emissary.
Continue your surveillance
of Sietch Tabr.
I want to know
who's coming, who's going
and where all the communications
are directed.
Time to pay Stilgar a visit.
If you hadn't taken them from
the city in the first place
this never would have happened.
I am their guardian, Alia.
She wouldn't be safe
at the palace with me?
I'm demanding she not be used
as a pawn in a civil war.
You know as I do, Stilgar,
Ghanima must be returned
to the court.
She's right, Irulan.
As long as I designate
Sietch Tabr neutral territory,
no violence may be committed
by any party to this conflict.
However, holding Ghanima
against the Imperial Regent's will
could be considered abduction.
As Naib of this sietch,
I surrender Ghanima
to the Imperial Regent.
On one condition -
that the Princess Irulan accompany her.
If any harm come to either
the Princess or the royal heir,
the neutrality of this tribe
will be forfeit
and allegiance to
the Imperial Throne disavowed.
Agreed.
I want the girl ready. We leave
for Arrakeen immediately.
Forgive me, Irulan. I may have
placed you in grave danger.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
(Woman whispers) Leto.
Leto!
(Voices whisper) Leto!
( ROARING )
MAN: Keep feeding him
more and more.
SABIHA: The more we feed him,
the deeper his trance.
MAN: The deeper the trance,
the more dangerous the trance.
WOMAN: Leto!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Coughs)
He is stronger than we thought.
Then increase what we give him!
( SCREAMING )
( EERIE WHISPERING )
( TIGER GROWLS )
(Exhales painfully)
By the time we're through,
he'll be as mad as Alia.
(Groans)
( ROARING )
(Gasps)
What are you doing to me?
That's Spice essence!
Do you hear them?
The voices in your head?
Are you crazy yet?
Think you aren't?
Does that frighten you?
Not as much as it
will frighten you, Atreides.
(Coughs)
( OMINOUS MUSIC )
( HARSH ECHOES )
(Whispers) Leto!
Listen to me, Leto.
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
( URGENT PERCUSSIVE MUSIC )
(Grunts)
(Screams)
( SILENCE )
Put the weapon away, Cast Out.
That is what you are, isn't it?
Adopting the chameleon colours
of a smuggler tribe
in order to keep
your true identity secret.
Allowing us to survive.
Trading spice.
That's not all, is it?
You're breeding sandtrout.
I've seen the holding pens.
Selling worms off-planet,
you hope to break
the Atreides monopoly on spice.
It is dangerous for you to know
these things.
More dangerous for you.
None of your worms survive long
away from Dune.
Not yet.
Not ever.
You're already saturated
with spice.
And it can no longer harm me.
I have survived the crucible,
Sabiha.
I have silenced
the voices within
who would have possessed me.
Only I remain now
to do what I must do.
And what is that?
Save the desert.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC )
(Laughs)
My skin is not my own.
I can't...
...I can't do it.
You can. You will.
I'm here. I try to see myself
there but I can't.
I can't.
Patience.
Concentrate on visualising
the flow of time.
It must move, not you.
It would've been easier to begin this
when you were younger.
I'm surprised you never asked
for a Bene Gesserit teacher
before.
They'd have lapped
at the opportunity
to put you in their debt.
My mother had other training
in mind for me when I was younger.
You can still learn.
If I'm patient?
You must learn
each and every muscle
as if it were a single string
on a baliset.
When you learn how to play them
individually,
you'll know how
to play them together.
The union of opposites,
isn't it, Jessica?
Recognising the essential
instability of our universe,
one must learn
to make it one's own creation.
It is the Bene Gesserit way.
So you haven't forgotten
everything you were taught?
You need a bath.
We'll continue tomorrow.
He is a slow learner.
On the contrary.
He's making more progress
than I would have expected
in so short a time.
And you?
I know what I intend to get out
of this relationship, Wensicia.
What is it you expect?
Our houses are at
their crossroads, Jessica.
Families weaken from within.
You and I both confront
the greatest danger
from those closest to us.
You have a daughter
from whom you are estranged.
I have a son in whom I have
little confidence.
What do you expect me to do
about that?
Simply... consider
the union of opposites.
We hear rumours
of your grand-daughter.
Ghanima?
It seems she has survived.
Alia has taken her from Stilgar,
but Irulan is with her.
Get to the point, Wensicia.
An alliance -
Corrino and Atreides.
An alliance through marriage?
Under your tutelage.
Farad'N could be fashioned
into an acceptable mate
for someone as special
as your grand-daughter.
He has his talents and he's
a fast learner, as you say.
Worse things could happen
than an alliance
between old enemies.
Your son was clever enough
to see its potential once.
Surely you can see
the need for it now.
DUNCAN: The idea repulses me.
Surely your Mentat reasoning
can see the value in it.
That an Atreides
would willingly marry
into the house that has vowed
its destruction - it's madness!
That's exactly what my son did
when he married Irulan.
Politics ruled that decision.
And it averted a war.
Do you not see the similarity
to our present situation?
You really think
Alia will agree
to a marriage
between Ghanima and Farad'N?
She is the reason
you must be the one
to deliver this proposal.
She loved you once, Duncan,
and there's a part of her
that still does.
You're the only one who might
reach that part of her
that still knows who she is.
No.
She's lost to me now.
You saw the evidence
of that yourself.
You could be saving the life
of Paul's daughter, Duncan.
As long as Ghani lives,
she's a threat to Alia.
If we can make
my daughter believe
that her niece is the means
to eliminate
an even greater threat,
we can save her life...
...and buy precious time.
ALIA: I assume you see merit
to this marriage proposal
because you gambled
your own safety
to deliver it personally.
DUNCAN: Merit and risk.
You must decide
which bears the greater weight.
My priests object to the idea.
Because they are myopic
and parochial,
interested only in preserving
their own power.
Be careful, Duncan!
You're already standing
on the precipice.
It is no secret desert rebels
probe your defences
with increased success.
Riots here in Arrakeen
are the subject
of much discussion off-world.
Whispers of weakness
and disarray
are spreading
amongst the great houses.
Rumours encouraged
by my enemies
to spread doubt and fear.
The jackals are gathering, Alia.
An alliance between
Corrino and Atreides
would serve as reassurance
AND a warning.
Prepare a formal response
to House Corrino.
We will allow negotiations
for a union between Ghanima
and Prince Farad'N to begin.
But make it clear,
Atreides interests will dominate.
Leave me.
Only my husband may remain.
I should have you executed
for what you did.
My diplomatic immunity
as Corrino envoy
would make that
an unwise decision.
Why did you come back here?
My allegiance to House Atreides
would permit nothing less.
I played... no part in your decision?
I struggled not to allow it.
You can't remain at the keep.
I must banish you
for your treachery,
otherwise people would question
my judgment, my ruthlessness.
A quality you must demonstrate
often these days, no doubt.
They're difficult days, Duncan.
Lonely days.
(Giggles)
I've missed you.
( MUFFLED,
SINISTER LAUGHTER )
Oh!
Where would you have me go?
Sietch Tabr. Neutral territory.
Stilgar's trying
to broker a peace
between the Qizarate
and the rebels.
Perhaps your Mentat qualities
can be useful.
At least you'll be safe there.
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
There is no-one to restrain Alia.
Her forces are probing
deeper and deeper
into the southern regions,
attacking rebel sietches
wherever she thinks they are.
And still there are riots
in the streets of Arrakeen itself.
And what of the boy Leto?
What do they say about him?
If he survived the assassin,
he did not survive the desert.
Worms, storms -
there won't be a body.
Where are you going?
To look for the boy.
That cannot be permitted.
We never had any intention
of helping someone like you -
enemy of ours.
Cursed be your name, Atreides,
burning beyond you
for the abomination
you have visited on our desert.
You shall have no soul, no spirit.
You shall not be permitted
to come up from the depths.
(Groans repeatedly)
( WIND BLOWS FIERCELY )
The only thing that doesn't fear
an Arrakis storm is the worm.
I will not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
I will face my fear.
I will let it pass through me.
I will not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
I will face my fear.
I will let it pass through me.
I will not fear!
Fear is the mind killer!
I will face my fear!
I will let it pass through me!
I will not fear!
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC )
(Pants)
I could've killed you.
It wouldn't have been that easy.
(Gasps excitedly)
I wanted to believe you.
I wanted to believe
that I could do it, but I didn't.
I couldn't. I didn't
truly think it was possible.
And then my mind melted away.
I gave up fighting you
and it happened.
It wasn't me you were fighting.
It was myself.
All that I've learned,
all the nonsense
I've imprisoned myself with,
I feel...
...I feel like I'm being reborn.
Like I'm standing
on the threshold
of something extraordinary.
Prana-Bindu balance, Farad'N.
But only on the threshold.
(Laughs) Patience?
Yeah. Patience.
Remember...
...one thing to gain control
of your perceptions,
quite another to gain control
of your desires.
And if I succeed?
You'll find reality to be
quite a bit different than you thought.
( THUNDER RUMBLES )
(Gasps)
(Groans)
( INSISTENT,
PERCUSSIVE MUSIC )
This skin is not my own.
( MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
( PEACEFUL MUSIC )
Must you insist
on sneaking away like this?
I still feel him, Irulan.
His presence.
Sometimes I even think I can
hear his laughter in the wind.
Mocking your decision
to marry Farad'N, I hope.
Why should he mock it?
I cannot stand by
and let you be used
as a pawn in Alia's schemes.
Is that what you think?
That I'm being used?
That I've agreed to this marriage
as part of some conspiracy with Alia?
No. But I know you, Ghani.
There is more to your decision
than anyone else believes.
Alia wants my grandmother back.
Farad'N is simply the means.
But what do YOU want?
Farad'N's blood
on the wedding sheets, not mine.
DUNCAN: You cannot remain
neutral any longer, Stilgar.
You must ally your tribe
with the rebel forces.
Never.
Rebellion against
the sister of Muad'Dib
would bring the greatest
dishonour I could imagine.
There is no more sister of Muad'Dib.
She's gone. Lost to the evil
that possesses her.
While you refuse to believe it,
you wear its collar.
Enough! You are the guest
of my tribe.
I have given you my countenance.
But I swear,
if you provoke me further
with talk of insurrection,
I will have your water!
(Worm groans repeatedly)
What is it, Tariq?
Why have we stopped?
There's a demon.
(Whispers) In human form.
There are no such things.
( EERIE MUSIC )
Your guide
has released the worm.
We have a little time
before he returns.
You made it stop.
The worm obeyed
your command.
Yes.
They say Leto Atreides
is dead.
Killed by Corrino treachery.
A myth I have allowed
to persist until I am ready.
For what?
To undo what's been done
in your name... Father.
You have no idea who I am.
This is your ring, Father.
Passed from Duke Leto to you
and then unto me.
( EMOTIVE MUSIC )
( MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
(Gasps with emotion)
How far is it gone -
this thing
you've done to yourself?
I am a desert creature.
Was there no other way?
There was only one way
to bring about the Golden Path.
You cannot control the future.
A man named Muad'Dib
should have heeded that advice.
Do you think
Muad'Dib couldn't see
the thing
that you want to do?
Do you think he didn't confront
the possibility?
Muad'Dib was afraid.
(Hisses)
He was trapped
by his own prophecy.
A victim of what he knew
he could not choose.
So I have chosen...
...to make a world
where humankind
can create its own future
from moment to moment.
Free of one man's vision.
Free from the perversion
of the prophets' words.
And free of future predetermined.
This does not belong to me.
How many nights I have sat
on a dune, just like this...
(Voice wavers) ..imagining a
night just like this, with...
...with my father.
Just the two of us,
talking and laughing.
(Half-laughs, sniffs)
And how many nights
I have gone to sleep
on the cold floor of the sietch,
dreaming of his arms around me,
sheltering me from everything
I was afraid of,
everything
I could not understand.
Are you still a good Fremen?
Yes.
Then will you permit... a blind man
to go out into the desert...
...and find peace on his own terms?
(Sniffs)
Not yet.
(Sighs)
Cursed be the name Atreides.
( BODY SHIELD BEEPS )
Body shield. Armed.
(Prays)
MAN: Eight of nine new settlements
have been abandoned.
Many of the old sietch communities
are becoming overrun with refugees.
The Holy Regent demands
that you abandon
your pledge of neutrality.
Ally your forces with hers,
put an end
to this damnable rebellion!
Alia is Fremen.
She knows
she cannot make such a demand
on me or on any other Naib!
You can no longer remain
above the fight, Stilgar.
Your feeble attempts to mediate
have accomplished nothing!
It's time for you to choose.
Are you with the Empire...
...or against it?
It is not a choice I will make
because some fop of a priest
demands it.
Well, perhaps the royal consort
can talk some sense
into this obstinate fool.
( LOW MURMURS )
I can do better than that.
Idaho!
The royal cuckold thanks you
for this opportunity!
Stilgar will now make his choice.
You have violated sanctuary.
You have defiled
the honour of my people.
No, Stil.
I have just cut the collar
from around your neck.
(Unsheaths crysknife)
Oh!
Ah!
( WOUND SQUELCHES )
That was the right choice, Stil.
Two deaths for the Atreides.
The second one for no better reason
than the first.
(Withdraws crysknife)
( LOW MURMURS )
It was a sign.
He forced our hand.
Now Alia will be forced
to move against us.
MAN: He has taken the tribe
into the desert.
No-one knows where,
but his only refuge
will be with the rebels.
Idaho acted impulsively,
My Lady.
He was...
Was my husband!
Kanly... vendetta...
...on Stilgar and all of his tribe
that joined him.
Let them be hunted down
like desert rabbits.
(Harkonnen hisses)
Yes. Yes. Kill them.
I want their skins
when they're caught.
Nice touch, yes.
Very creative.
( UNEASY MUSIC )
( DRAMATIC FLOURISH )
This is the one
we took on the south face.
He came across the plain
from the south wall.
So, they say
you rode a worm here?
A 20-thumper ride.
And yet, you are not Fremen.
They taught me well.
Rumours across the desert
say you're dead,
Gurney Halleck.
There are many
who wish that were true.
The sons of Esmar Tuek
are not among them, old friend.
LETO: We've been waiting on you,
Gurney Halleck.
How did you know I'd come here?
My father told me.
Your father?
When in the desert,
sheltered once, sheltered always.
After the Harkonnen invasion,
these were the men
who protected you,
before you were finally reunited
with Muad'Dib.
A reunion which allowed me
to join his rebellion
against Shaddam
and the Imperial forces.
Another rebellion awaits you,
Gurney Halleck.
My loyalty
is to House Atreides.
Well, I AM House Atreides.
And what of your aunt?
My aunt is lost.
Lost to forces
she could not control.
To forces who want to destroy
House Atreides.
What have you done to yourself?
I have made a choice.
Accepted a destiny,
nothing more.
My eyes can see it
but my mind
refuses to believe it.
Believe it, Gurney.
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
Remember the words of my father
and my grandfather, your duke.
They spoke to you
of desert power.
I AM desert power...
...and nothing can stop
what is going to happen.
( HEAVY THUMPS )
( LOW, TENSE MUSIC )
( MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
( Worm screeches and groans )
(Worm roars)
( HEROIC MUSIC )
( EXPECTANT MUSIC )
We are here to honour
the throne of Muad'Dib
and his sister,
the Holy Regent.
We're here to honour
his esteemed daughter
with the presentation
of our son, Prince Farad'N,
heir to the throne
of House Corrino.
We offer our deepest
condolences
on the loss of your brother.
Perhaps the union of our houses
can put an end to the treachery
that took his life.
Treachery that was bred
on Selusa Secundus.
What did you say?
I am ashamed to say
that the animals that
killed Leto, son of Muad'Dib,
were created and trained
on my planet.
And the Regent of House Corrino
knew of this?
She planned it.
(Hisses) How dare you?!
I'll dare quite a few things
from now on, Mother.
You've been quite adept
at making decisions in my name,
decisions which I found
extremely distasteful.
You insolent bastard.
Let's not discuss
your weaknesses now, Mother.
I forbid you
to say another word.
You forbid nothing.
As heir to the throne
of House Corrino
I am now the author
of my own decisions.
My mother is to be stripped
of all accounts and privileges
of the House Corrino.
She is no longer
sovereign regent of this family.
She is, from this moment
forward, banished.
You're more of a man
than I'd ever thought possible.
And you can spend the rest
of your days pondering that
in utter darkness.
Patience is a virtue.
I have an abundance,
if you haven't noticed.
GHANIMA: Hold.
Did you have anything to do
with the death of my brother?
I knew nothing
of the plot against him
until it was too late.
Forgive me. I am at your mercy.
This is my wedding present
to you.
I have nothing else.
No dowry...
...only the truth.
I believe him.
Take her.
Leave him.
Maybe he'll amuse us
with more intrigue and double-cross
in the days to come.
Don't you find it interesting,
Jessica,
how the sins of the mother
bloom in the children they bear?
( EDGY MUSIC )
STILGAR: She's weakened
by madness!
She still commands
the Imperial armies.
They're retreating to the city,
trapped by the Shield Wall
from which they are vulnerable.
They say the price on your head
keeps going up.
Oh! Then I say unto you,
send men to summon worms!
Then, let us go... to Arrakeen
to collect it.
( MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
Manud!
A storm.
Not this time.
We must get word to the palace.
Yeah.
Yaaah!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Worms screech and groan)
( MARKET HUBBUB )
( FOREBODING MUSIC )
Don't be afraid, Gurney-man.
There is no way to hasten
what is meant to be.
When the time is right...
...he will find us.
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
Who are you?
Who I am doesn't matter anymore.
It matters to me.
Do you think I would have left
this place if I had known?
Do you think
I would've abandoned you
if I knew you were still alive?
You did
what you were meant to do.
Tell me.
Let me hear you say it.
Tell me it isn't you.
I couldn't live
if I knew I had forsaken you.
Paul Atreides is no more,
Gurney-man.
The desert winds have erased
all trace of his passage in.
And soon, Muad'Dib must follow.
Please, Gurney. I'm tired. Hungry.
Get me some food.
( REFLECTIVE MUSIC )
Oh, Stil. So predictable.
It's as if they're daring you
to confront them.
Challenging you
to commit troops, 'thopters.
They think I've retreated
to the sanctuary of the city
where I'm trapped.
It's a tactic learned
from my brother
when he defeated Shaddam
and took back Arrakis.
Poor Stil. If you only knew
it is you who are trapped, not I.
They are still over a day's ride
from Arrakeen.
Fine.
I'm going back to the palace.
I have a wedding to attend.
( ETHEREAL MUSIC )
( WIND BLOWS )
(Man whispers) Ghanima?
Leave me.
Ghani?
Do as I say.
( MYSTERIOUS MUSIC,
WIND BLOWS )
There is no need for that
with me, Ghanima.
Leto?
(Laughs quietly)
( POIGNANT MUSIC )
Our plan worked.
You're alive!
I knew it.
(Giggles quietly)
(Both laugh)
How I have missed you.
I'm sorry, Ghanima.
I'm so sorry.
I had to let you think
that I was dead.
It was the only way,
the only way that I could start
what must now be finished.
(Man yells) Muad'Dib!
(Yells hysterically)
(People chant) Muad'Dib,
Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib.
MAN: His words are sacrilege.
His presence
must not be tolerated.
You must give the order,
Holy One.
You must send us to take him.
HARKONNEN: Caution, darling
Do not act impulsively
Not yet.
He is an outrage
to the religion of Muad'Dib.
Ah, but that's the point,
my darling.
We must know for sure
whether he really is
your brother, mustn't we?
It would not do to make
a martyr of him just yet.
(People chant) Muad'Dib,
Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib,
Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib.
(Laughs)
WOMAN: Muad'Dib?!
Who is it
that calls for Muad'Dib?!
MAN: Help us, Muad'Dib!
Deliver us, Muad'Dib!
Muad'Dib's words are the wind!
They vanish...
like water on the sand!
I'll give you Muad'Dib's words!
I'll rub your faces in them!
I am the voice from the wilderness
and I bring you a warning.
The water we spread upon
the desert has become blood.
Blood... upon the land
which was once clean and pure!
We have provoked the desert...
forsaken its ways.
We have succumbed to mindless ritual
and seductive ceremony,
placed faith in those
who crush dissent,
enriched themselves with power,
commit atrocity...
...all in the name of righteousness!
All in the name...
...of Muad'Dib!
We have fouled the nest...
...and it is killing us!
PREACHER: The Golden Path!
The path
Muad'Dib could not take.
I have stood upon the sand...
...and I have seen
a beast rise up...
...and upon the head
of that beast...
...is the name of salvation...
...come to spill water
upon the sand...
...come to lead us back...
...to a dry and thirsty land!
Only one blasphemy remains...
...and that blasphemy...
...is ALIA!
(Grunts)
(Crowd gasps)
(Crowd murmurs)
Forgive me...
...sister.
JACURUTU!
OH!
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
(Sighs heavily)
(Removes knife)
( WIND HOWLS )
It's in your hands now...
...son.
( SOLEMN MUSIC CONTINUES )
(Screams and roars)
( WIND HOWLS )
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
Where is she?
( WIND ROARS )
LETO: Behold me, family!
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Roars)
I am Leto...
...Lion of Atreides...
...returned from the desert
to announce Secher Nbwi...
...the Golden Path...
...to rid humanity
of the perversions done
in Muad'Dib's name...
...and to save it from
the abomination known as Alia.
Seize him!
( TENSE MUSIC )
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
(Grunts with exertion)
(Grunts repeatedly)
(Gasps for breath)
The time has come, Aunt.
You must face the future.
I'll drink your blood!
HARKONNEN: Yes! Yes!
(Screams and babbles
incoherently)
Alia, stop it! Stop yourself!
You sorry bitch!
(In Harkonnen's voice)
You Bene Gesserit whore!
Did you think
you could escape my vengeance?
I was defeated forever?
I have her daughter!
Your precious Alia, she's mine!
(Laughs) I've won!
No!
Demon, let her make her own choice!
( VOICES ECHO AND SCREAM )
Mommy... help me.
(Groans)
( DRAMATIC MUSIC )
Help yourself.
(Grunts with exertion)
HARKONNEN:
Yes, yes, do it. Sink it in.
(Echoes) Bathe our hands
in his heart blood.
(Alia whimpers)
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC )
( ETHEREAL MUSIC )
HARKONNEN: No, darling!
No, stop, stop!
No, stop, stop! We're so close.
Alia, for heaven's sake,
you don't stop now. We're so close!
So close. We're so close.
(Stabs herself)
(Drops knife)
( SOMBRE MUSIC )
I want my brother.
( SOMBRE MUSIC INTENSIFIES )
JESSICA:
You'll not change your mind
and return with me to Caladan?
I must remain here, My Lady,
at Sietch Tabr with Stilgar.
He will need my help
to bring peace back to this land.
And you?
I have no home but here.
Besides, there will be children again
and they will need me.
Dear friend.
( ENGINES WHINE )
( WIND BLOWS )
( SOLEMN MUSIC )
Alia's water.
Take it into the desert
and spread it upon the open sand
in the midday sun.
It is our way.
Are you going back to Sietch Tabr?
I wish to return to our old ways.
The desert's dying, Stil.
And the Fremen too, I'm afraid.
Well, we're about to go
through the crucible...
...but we'll come out the other side.
We always arise from our own ashes.
Everything returns later
in its... changed form.
Your grandfather's ring.
And... your father's.
And now the Fremen's.
To remind you of Muad'Dib...
...to remind you
that all humans make mistakes...
...and that all leaders
are but human.
( MUSIC SWELLS )
He runs and runs and runs.
And when he's exhausted himself...
...he returns to me...
...puts his head in my lap...
...and asks me to help him
find a way to die.
But why does he want to die?
To save himself...
...from the sacrifices he must make...
...sacrifices for the future
of us all.
Then there is a place for me
in this future?
Your blood was spared
the day Leto came back to me.
What of our marriage then?
As my mother was not wife,
you shall never be husband.
Politics.
But in time, there may be love...
...which is more than
my brother will have.
( REFLECTIVE MUSIC )
GHANIMA: One of us
had to accept the agony
He was always the stronger.
History is written
on the sands of Arrakis.
A chapter has ended...
...swept away by the whirlwind.
One door has closed...
...but another has opened...
...and on the other side...
...our future.
( SOMBRE ORCHESTRAL MUSIC )