A beginning is a very delicate time.
Know then, that it is the year 10191.
The Known Universe is ruled by the
Padisha Emperor Shaddam IV, my father.
In this time, the most precious substance
in the Universe is the spice melange.
The spice extends life.
The spice expands consciousness.
The spice is vital to space travel.
The Spacing Guild and its navigators, -
who the spice has
mutated over 4,000 years,
use the orange spice gas, which
gives them the ability to fold space.
That is, travel to any part of
the Universe without moving.
Oh, yes.
I forgot to tell you.
The spice exists on only one planet
in the entire Universe.
A desolate, dry planet
with vast deserts.
Hidden away within the rocks of these deserts
are a people known as the Fremen,
who have long held a prophecy,
that a man would come, a messiah.
who would lead them to true freedom.
The planet is Arrakis.
Also known as Dune.
A secret report within the Guild.
Four planets have come to our attention
regarding a plot which could jeopardize spice production.
Planet Arrakis,
source of the Spice.
Planet Caladan,
home of House Atreides.
Planet Giedi Prime,
home of House Harkonnen.
Planet Kaitain, home of the Emperor
of the Known Universe.
Send a third-stage Guild Navigator to Kaitain
to demand details from the Emperor.
The spice must flow.
-Father?
-Irulan, you must leave.
A third-stage Guild Navigator
will be here within minutes.
-We felt his presence.
-I shall want telepathy during his visit and a report when we're finished.
I am your Truthsayer, my lord.
He's here, my lord.
The Bene Gesserit witch must leave.
-Leave us.
-Yes, my lord.
We are alone.
-We have just folded space from lx.
-Yes?
-How was your journey?
-Many machines on lx.
-New machines.
-Oh? Yes.
Better than those on Richese.
You are transparent.
I see many things.
I see plans within plans.
I see two great houses,
House Atreides,
House Harkonnen feuding.
-I see you behind it.
-Yes
You must share with us.
The Atreides House is building a secret army using a
technique unknown to us. A technique involving sound.
The Duke is becoming more popular in the Landsraad.
He could threaten me.
I have ordered House Atreides to occupy Arrakis to mine
the spice, thus replacing their enemies, the Harkonnens.
House Atreides will not refuse because of the
tremendous power they think they will gain.
Then, at an appointed time, Baron Harkonnen will return
to Arrakis and launch a sneak attack on House Atreides.
I have promised the baron five legions of
my Sardaukar terror troops.
-So the Harkonnens will rid you of House Atreides.
-Yes.
-One small point.
-Here it comes.
We, ourselves, foresee a slight problem within House Atreides.
Paul.
Paul Atreides.
-You mean, of course, Duke Leto Atreides, his father?
-I mean Paul Atreides.
We want him killed.
I did not say this.
I am not here.
I understand.
Why would they want the Duke's son killed?
We must have a look at Paul Atreides.
On Caladan.
Planet Caladan
The powerful Bene Gesserit sisterhood for
90 generations, has been manipulating bloodlines
to produce the Kwisatz Haderach.
A super being.
On Caladan, Jessica, a member of the sisterhood
and the bound concubine of Duke Leto Atreides
had been ordered to bear only daughters.
Because of her love for the Duke,
she disobeyed and gave birth to a son. Paul.
Paul Atreides.
Here we are now. Caladan.
And 19 light-years beyond.
Beyond Bene Tleilax.
The training planet of the Mentats, the human computers.
Know a Mentat by his red-stained lips.
There, Arrakis.
Spice Mining.
Carry-alls lower the harvester to the sand,
and lift it off to safety when a worm attacks.
Worms attack all rhythmic vibrations.
Weather. See storms.
No Precipitation.
Never one drop of rain on Arrakis.
And the Harkonnens are near. There.
Giedi Prime and the Baron Harkonnen. The enemy.
The Baron Harkonnen has sworn to destroy House Atreides,
and steal the ducal signet ring for himself.
I know, Thufir, I'm sitting
with my back to the door.
I heard you, Doctor Yueh,
and Gurney coming down the hall.
Those sounds could be imitated!
-I'd know the difference.
-Yes. Perhaps he would at that.
My father sent you to test me.
Music, then?
-No music. I'm packing this for the crossing. Shield practice.
-Shield practice?
-Gurney, we had practice this morning. I'm not in the mood.
-Not in the mood?
Mood's a thing for cattle and love play.
Not fighting!
-I'm sorry, Gurney.
-Not sorry enough.
What's wrong with Gurney?
He's not faking this.
Now, guard yourself for true!
-Is this what you seek?
-Good.
The slow blade penetrates the shield. But, ah
look down.
We'd have joined each other in death.
You did seem finally to get in the mood.
-Would you really have drawn my blood?
-If you'd have fought one whit below your abilities,
I'd have given you
a good scar to remind you.
-Things have been so serious here lately.
-Soon we'll leave for Arrakis.
Arrakis is real.
The Harkonnens are real.
Doctor Yueh, do you have any information
on the worms of Arrakis?
I've obtained a filmbook of a small specimen.
Only 125 meters long.
-Only?
-There have been documented sightings of worms
as large as 450 meters in the deep desert.
That's far from where we'll be in Arrakeen.
The desert belt and the south polar region
are marked forbidden.
-How do the Fremen survive there?
-We don't know much about the Fremen.
They live in the deep desert, some of them in the cities.
They have blue-within-blue eyes.
The eyes. Yes... Saturation of the blood
by the spice melange.
-Could the spice affect us in other ways?
-Many dangers exist on Arrakis.
For one, the Harkonnens would not have
given up their CHOAM Company contract so easily.
The Harkonnens are our enemies, yes.
But behind them, I suspect, is the Emperor.
You'll make a formidable duke.
Now, remember, the first step in avoiding a trap
is knowing of its existence.
-I know, but if it is a trap then why are we going?
-We have our new army.
Doctor Yueh, put the weirding module on him.
Clear and lock the room!
Activate a fighter.
Make the range two meters.
Precise control.
Duncan!
Paul, I was just on my way
to say goodbye to you.
-I have to go on ahead, alone, I won't be seeing you for a while.
-I wish you were coming with us. Why?
It's something for your father.
He wants to talk to you.
I'll see you on Arrakis.
-May the hand of God be with you.
-May the hand of God be with us all, Duncan.
-Father.
-Thank you for joining me, Paul.
Thufir Hawat has served House
Atreides three generations.
He swears you are the finest
student he has ever taught.
Yueh, Gurney, and Duncan
say the same.
-Makes me feel very proud.
-I want you to be proud of me.
I'll miss the sea.
But a person needs new experiences.
They jar something deep inside
allowing him to grow.
Without change,
something sleeps inside us,
and seldom awakens.
The sleeper must awaken.
Arrakis...
Dune. Desert Planet.
I will kill you.
The second moon.
Tell me of your
home world, Usul.
I know she has come to test him.
No man has ever been tested with the box.
Tonight, I may lose my son.
Jessica, you were told to bear
only daughters to the Atreides.
-Jessica!
-It meant so much to him.
You thought only of a Duke's desire for a son?
Desires don't come into this.
An Atreides daughter could have been wed
to a Harkonnen heir and sealed the breach.
We may lose both bloodlines now.
I vowed never to regret my decision.
-I'll pay for all my own mistakes.
-And your son will pay with you.
Arrakis... Dune...
Desert Planet.
Moving.
We'll salvage what we can.
But I can tell you, dear God,
for the father, nothing.
For the father, nothing?
Did you really think you could bear the Kwisatz Haderach?
The Universe's super being?
How dare you!
My greatest student.
And my greatest disappointment.
He's awake. He's listening to us.
Good!
Ready yourself, young Paul Atreides. I want to see you
in your mother's chambers in one-quarter of an hour.
Paul... this is very important.
Kwisatz Haderach? The super being?
For the father, nothing?
This is the Reverend Mother
Gaius Helen Mohiam.
She's going to observe you.
-Please. Jessica, you know it must be done.
Your Reverence. What does she fear?
-What about my father?
-Paul...
listen to the Reverend Mother
and do what she tells you.
Now, you, come here.
She's using the Voice.
-No.
-Some strength there. Surprising.
Come here.
Do you see this?
-Put your right hand in the box.
-What's in the box?
Pain. Stop!
Put your hand in the box.
I hold at your neck the gom jabbar.
This one kills only animals.
-Are you suggesting the Duke's son is an animal?
-Let us say, I suggest you may be human.
Your awareness may be powerful
enough to control your instincts.
Your instinct will be to remove your hand
from the box. If you do so,
you die.
You will feel
an itching
there.
Now, the itching becomes burning.
-Heat upon heat upon heat. Upon heat.
-It burns.
Silence! Silence!
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer. Fear is the little death
that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear.
I will permit it to pass over me and through me.
I must not fear.
-You feel the flesh crisping.
-Fear is the little death that brings total obliteration.
-Flesh dropping off.
Fear is the little death.  I must not fear.
Fear is the little death.  I'm...
-The pain!
-No! Enough!
Kull wahad! No woman child
ever withstood that much.
Take your hand out of the box
and look at it, young human.
Do it!
Pain by nerve induction.
A human can resist any pain.
-Our test is crisis and observation.
-I see the truth of it.
Could he be the one? Maybe.
But will he be ours to control?
Tell me of your home world, Usul.
Do you know of the Water of Life?
The bile from the newborn worms of Arrakis?
-I have heard of it.
-It is very dangerous.
The Bene Gesserit sisterhood
use it to see within.
There is a place
terrifying to us, to women.
It is said a man will come.
The Kwisatz Haderach.
He will go
where we cannot.
-Many men have tried.
-They tried and failed?
They tried and died.
Jessica.
My son lives!
I sense your teachings in him.
Ignore the regular order of training.
-His safety requires the Voice.
-I've heard enough of my safety.
What about my father?
I heard your talking.
-You speak as if he were dead. Well, he's not!
-Paul.
-Well, he's not. And he won't die. Tell me he won't die.
-What can be done has been done.
Mother, tell me!
Planet Giedi Prime
Mentat Piter De Vries. Message for Mentat Piter De Vries.
The Baron is impatient for Leto's reply.
It is by will alone I set my mind in motion. It is by the juice of Sapho that thoughts acquire speed, that lips acquire stains, that stains become a warning.
It is by will alone I set my mind in motion.
It is by will alone I set my mind in motion.  It is by the juice of Sapho that thoughts acquire speed, that lips acquire stains, that stains become a warning.
-My lord.
-Piter.
The Atreides will be leaving Caladan soon, Baron,
and I have here your answer from Duke Leto.
-What does Leto say, Piter?
-He wishes to inform you that vendetta,
as he puts it, using the ancient tongue,
the art of Kanly, is still alive.
He does not wish to meet or speak with you.
I've made my peace gesture.
The forms of Kanly have been obeyed.
Bring in Feyd and Rabban.
As you instructed me, I have enlightened
your nephews concerning my plan...
My plan.
The plan to crush the Atreides.
Feyd... Rabban...
go quietly.
No other great house of the Landsraad must ever
know of the Emperor's aid to the Baron.
The entire Landsraad would turn against the Baron
and the Emperor.
Put the pick in there, Pete,
and turn it round real neat.
You are so beautiful, my Baron.
Your skin, love to me.
Your diseases
lovingly cared for, for all eternity.
I will have Arrakis back for myself!
He who controls the spice,
controls the Universe! And what Piter did not tell you is we have control of someone who is very close,
very close to Duke Leto.
This person,
this traitor, will be worth more to us
than 10 legions of Sardaukar.
-And who is this traitor?
-I won't tell you who the traitor is,
or when we'll attack. However,
the Duke will die before these eyes and he'll know...
He'll know that it is I,
Baron Vladimir Harkonnen,
who encompasses his doom!
This is what I'll do to the Duke and his family.
Oh, I'll miss
Caladan so much.
Caladan...
Soon they will
begin to fold space.
Far off in the control rooms
of spice gas. Traveling...
...without moving.
And now... the prophecy.
One will come.
The voice from the outer world.
Bringing the Holy War, the Jihad,
which will cleanse the Universe,
and bring us out of darkness.
House Atreides took control of Arrakis
63 standard days into the year 10191.
It was known that the Harkonnens, the former rulers
of Arrakis, would leave many suicide troops behind.
Atreides' patrols
were doubled.
Duncan.
What have you discovered about the Fremen, Duncan?
Tell me.
-Why haven't we heard from you?
-My lord, I suspect so much.
I think they are the allies we seek. They are strong, fierce.
They do not give their loyalty easily or quickly.
As you know, the Imperium has never
been able to take a census of the Fremen.
Everyone thinks that there are but few wandering here and there in the desert. My lord,
I suspect an incredible secret has been kept on this planet.
That the Fremen exist
in vast numbers.  Vast.
And it is they who control Arrakis.
Each trooper will be charged with responsibility
for preserving water.
Our existence as an operating army
depends on these following water-saving procedures.
Remember, water is life.
Why is the shield not yet up?
Sir, we found and removed another sabotage device.
I think it'll go up now, sir.
They're finding these sabotage devices too easily.
House shields activated.
Duke Leto is now here.
Spice mining inspection to start immediately.
So you are Doctor Kynes.
The Judge of the Change.
-And the Imperial Ecologist, Sire.
-Our intelligence informs us that there's still a strong Harkonnen presence.
-The process of removal continues.
-This is my son, Paul.
-Are you a Fremen?
-I've been on Arrakis in the service of the Emperor, long enough for my eyes to change.
-In the service of the Emperor.
-We are in your hands, Doctor.
Your gift of the stillsuits is much appreciated.
Will you give us an explanation of their workings?
Well, this is a still suit of Fremen manufacture,
the most efficient type on Arrakis. Basically...
-It's all right, Gurney.
-Yes, Sire.
Basically, it's a high-efficiency
filter, and heat exchange system.
Perspiration passes through the first layer
and is gathered in the second.
The salt is separated.
Breathing and walking provide the pumping action.
The reclaimed water circulates to catch pockets
from which you can drink
through this tube
around your neck.
Urine and feces are processed
in the thigh pads.
Should you be in the open desert,
remember to breathe in through your mouth
and out through this nose tube.
With a Fremen suit in good working condition,
life can be sustained for weeks, even in the deep desert,
Sire.
My thanks.
With your permission. You've worn a stillsuit before.
-No.
Your suit is fitted desert fashion.
Who told you how to do that?
No one. It seemed the proper way.
That it is.
He shall know your ways as if born to them.
We're wasting time, Sire.
That language?
Translate it.
Very faint.
Harkonnen.
Air speed, zero-five.
Ambient temperature,
300 degrees Kelvin.
That's where I told your sandmaster
to concentrate the harvesting today.
Southeast, over the Shield Wall.
Ambient temperature, 350 degrees Kelvin.
Air speed, one-three-zero.
Caution. You've now cleared
protective Shield Wall and entered open desert.
-Will we see a worm?
-Where there is spice and spice mining,
-there are always worms.
-Always? -Always.
Why do they come?
To protect their territory.
Vibrations attract them.
He must be a Fremen or in with them.
He's studying us.
He's hiding something about the spice.
Is there a relationship between
the worms and the spice?
As I said, they defend
the spice sands.
As to their relationship
with the spice, who knows?
My message, it's here.
There are more enemy bodies coming in for your
inspection, Doctor Yueh.
-Are you all right?
-Yes, I'm fine. Thank you, Thufir.
-Dust cloud ahead, Sire.
-That's it. Spice mining.
No other cloud quite like it.
Wormsign? Is it wormsign?
Yes. Worm. Big one.
You've got sharp eyes.
May I?
Calling Harvester Pad Nine.
Wormsign.
-Who calls Pad Nine?
-Don't mention the Duke. This is an un-coded channel.
Unlisted flight northeast of you.
Wormsign on intercept course.
-Estimated contact, 15 minutes.
-Have sighting confirmed. Stand by for a fix.
Contact in 16 minutes minus.  Very precise estimate.
Who's on that unlisted flight?
-What happens now?
-The carry-all will come and lift off the spice harvester.
Try to get in close over the harvester.
You'll find this interesting, Sire.  They work until the very last minute.
Spotter control, there's no sign of the carryall.
It isn't answering.
The worm is eight minutes away, Sire.
Spotter control, give me a report by the numbers.
Report One. No contact.
Report Two. Negative.
Report Three. Negative, Sire.
Report Four. No contact.
Repeat, no contact.
-I think they've got our carryall.
-Damn it! Harkonnens.
We're coming down to take you off the harvester.
All spotters are ordered to comply.
-Ordered by whom?
-Duke Leto Atreides.
-Yes. Yes Sire.
-How many men do you have?
-Full crew, 26 men.
-But, Sire, we can't leave all this spice.
-Damn the spice! Get out of there!
Two men in each of the spotters!
You, over here! Run! Run!
I can't see him yet, but he is very close now.
Damn sloppy.
Really damn sloppy. Come on, boys.
Come on.
-We're going to be heavy, Sire.
Spice.
Pure unrefined spice.
Here he is!
We've got to go!
Bless the Maker and his water. Bless the coming and going of Him.
May His passing cleanse the world.
-What's that you're saying?
-Nothing.
Gods, what a monster.
Someone is going to pay for this, I promise.
He's more concerned over
his men than the spice. I must admit...
against all better judgment,
I like this Duke.
My lady, the local people, the maids and servants,
await your inspection.
Hawat has cleared them.
Excuse me, my lady.
The Harkonnens may have tampered with them medically.
When you said Harkonnens,
I didn't know you had
so much reason to hate them.
Well, my wife... But, of course, you...
You didn't know my wife.
-The Har...
-Forgive me.
- They must have killed her.
-Please excuse me if I can't talk about it.
He's holding something back.
Yet....
There's the imperial conditioning....
Assurance of trust.
The Bene Gesserit mother, the legend.
Where is your son?
I must warn you.
You are in great danger.
Safe.
Spice.
What is it doing to me?
Second moon.
The sleeper must awaken.
Am I the one?
A hunter-seeker!
It can't get me
if I don't move.
It's too dark in here
for it to see clearly.
I've got to try to grab it. The suspensor field will make
it slippery on the bottom.
I must grip it tightly.
Who is operating that thing?
It has to be someone in the palace.
I could shout for help,
but it would kill whoever opened the door.
Hold still.
-It would have killed me.
-I was its target.
It went to the motion.
-Who are you?
-I am the Shadout Mapes, the housekeeper.
I must cleanse the way between us.
You saved my life, and
we Fremen pay our debts.
A Fremen.
It is known to us that you've a traitor
in your midst.
Who it is, we cannot say.
but we are certain of it.
A traitor.
Set up a sonar probe immediately.
Harkonnen.
They've tried to take the life of my son.
-Sector 6 through 80 progress reports, Sire.
-Take it, Thufir.
Sector 680, copy the 6th, the summit, the 8th, quadrant over,
the 9th plus 84 circles, weave the 80 and call the 4th. Copy.
8. Thufir Tawat, Mentat,
Master of assassins.
Uh, the palace is now secure.
The city of Arrakeen is under martial law.
We have troops here
headquartered underground
on sub-floors 6 through 10.
The rest of the troops are stationed in Arrakeen,
and we have some on the airfield.
Our new army is still in training, but everything,
everything is shielded.
And with this shielding
we are impenetrable.
Sleep well, my son.
Um, Father, drugged.
Jessica, what is wrong?
Forgive me, my beloved concubine.
I should have married you.
Why hold a dream to ascend to the throne
through a political marriage?
I should have married you.
What happened?
Yueh! He sabotaged the house generators.
We are wide open!
-House shield deactivating.
-I've destroyed the new army's weirding modules.
I've brought House Atreides down.  -Why?
I wish to kill a man.
Not you, my dear Duke.
You were already dead.
But you'll get close to the Baron before you die.
You'll be tied and drugged, but you can still attack.
You can still attack!
When you see the Baron,
you'll have a new poison gas tooth.
He'll want you close,
so he can gloat over you.
One bite on this tooth
and a strong exhale...
-Refuse....
-No! You mustn't!
Because, in return, I'll save the lives
of your Paul and Jessica.
For Paul.
When you see the Baron,
remember the tooth.
The tooth! The tooth!
The shield is down!
Open the doors!
Signals!
Get that shield up!
The shield! The shield!
The weirding modules!
Destroyed!
Long live Duke Leto!
The drug was timed.
Dr. Yueh has been
very valuable to us.
What a pity you must remain gagged.
We can't let ourselves be swayed by your witch's voice,
now, can we?
Leto, where are you?
How simple to subdue us.
Goodbye, Jessica.
And goodbye to your sweet son.
I want to spit once on your head.
Just some spittle in your face.
What a luxury.
We were ordered to kill them.
So kill them!
I wish this was Paul.
I knew Yueh's wife.
I was the one who broke
his Imperial conditioning.
I've thought of
many pleasures with you.
It is perhaps better that you die
in the innards of a worm.
-What are your orders, Piter?
-Take them to the desert, as the traitor suggested.
The worms will destroy the evidence.
Their bodies must never be found.
They're down on this floor
somewhere.  Down there.
Duncan!
You wish now to join your wife?
Is that it, traitor?
-She lives?
-You wish to join her?
Join her, then.
You think you've defeated me?
You think I don't know
what I've gained, for my wife!
Take him away.
Yueh's sign.
He's left us stillsuits.
Don't touch my mother!
He's trying the Voice.
The Reverend Mother said it could save him.
-Did you hear a noise from the little one, huh?
-No, I didn't hear anything.
The little one.
-Remove her gag.
-Excellent!
There's no need to fight over me.
A poisoned blade.
First cut my son's bonds.
That's it.
It's under control.
Duke Leto Atreides.
Where is the ducal signet ring?
I must have his ring.
The ring!
He was brought to us
as is, my lord Baron.
You killed the doctor
too soon, you fool!
The doctor, Yueh, what did he say?
Paul and Jessica safe.
-Yes. The tooth!
-He's coming around, Baron.
Where's your ring? Huh?
You do not answer?
-Wait! Wait!
-You must come closer.
The water of my life... for Paul.
He's crying.
He's crying!
What does that mean,
Piter?
Come closer Baron.
No! Jessica... Leto...
Leto, he's dead!
-No, he's dead!
-I know.
Am I alive?
-Am I alive?
-Yes, you're alive, my Baron.
I'm alive, eh?
I'm alive!
Lever!
I can't maintain any altitude.
We'll never reach the safety of rock!
-Maybe that small rock.
-Where are we, do you think?
The south polar regions.
The forbidden area.
Hold on!
Hurry!
Take the stillsuits!
This crash might bring a worm.
-The signet.
-A million deaths are not enough for Yueh!
Where are my feelings?
I feel for no one.
The second moon.
I mean Paul Atreides.
We want him killed.
Why? Why do they want me killed?
It has to be something
to do with the spice. But what?
He who controls the spice,
controls the Universe!
This moon holds my future.
Never one drop of rain on Arrakis.
The sleeper must awaken.
They will call me... Muad'Dib.
Listen to me. Listen!
You wanted to know about my dreams.
Well, I've just had a waking dream.
Do you know why?
The spice!
-It's in everything here.
-Calm yourself.
Like the Truthsayer drug.
It's a poison. You knew the spice
would change me.
But thanks to your teachings,
it's changing my consciousness.
-I see it! I can see it!
-Is he the one?
-You carry my unborn sister in your womb.
-He knows.
Father!
Father, I promise,
one day the sleeper will awaken.
And I will avenge your death.
I will not stop...
until I destroy the Emperor and the Baron.
Father.
Go now.
Take him to his desert to die.
Go.
Yueh's left the plan
for the weirding modules.
We have to get to
that mountain of rock.
We have entered the time when all will turn against us
and seek our lives.
It's further than I thought.
A worm is sure to come.
I'll plant this thumper.
That should divert it.
Remember, walk without rhythm, and we won't attract a worm.
It will go to the thumper.
I'm ready.
Faster!
It's deafening!
The spice!
-Do you smell it?
-Yes!
A thumper.
The worm. Spice!
Is there a relationship?
What's happened?
Why did it leave?
Someone started
another thumper.
We're not alone.
-Man-carved steps.
-Yes.
Such stealth.
I didn't hear them.
Perhaps these are the ones the Shadout Mapes told us of?
I will take the boy-man.
He shall have sanctuary
in my tribe.
Get back!
She has the weirding way.
Great Gods!
If you can do this to the strongest of us,
you're worth 10 times your weight of water.
As the leader of my people, I give you my bond.
Teach us this weirding way,
and you both shall have sanctuary.
Your water shall mingle with our water.
Then I will teach you our way of battle.
-I give you the word bond of a Bene Gesserit.
-It is the legend.
I am Chani, daughter of Liet.
I would not have permitted you
to harm my tribe.
From my dreams.
So beautiful....
Come with me.  I'll show you
an easier way down.
You have strength.
You shall be known as Usul,
which is the strength of the base of the pillar.
This is your secret name in our troop.
But you must choose the name of manhood,
which we will call you openly.
What do you call the mouse
shadow in the second moon?
-We call that one Muad'Dib.
-Could I be known as Paul Muad'Dib?
You are Paul Muad'Dib.
And your mother shall be a Sayyadina among us.
We welcome you.
The dream unfolds.
-Moisture.
-Wind traps. Huge ones.
Water. Millions of dekaliters.
-A treasure.
-Greater than treasure, Usul.
We have thousands of such caches,
and only a few of us know them all.
And when we have enough, we shall change
the face of Arrakis.
Tell me of your home world, Usul.
"Tell me of your home world, Usul."
Rabban! Rabban!
We're knee-deep in Atreides blood!
We've gutted them! We've gutted them!
Rabban! Rabban!
I place you in charge of Arrakis.
It's yours to squeeze, as I promised.
I want you to squeeze
and squeeze and squeeze!
Give me spice! Drive them! Drive them into utter submission!
Do not show the slightest pity or mercy!
-Never stop! Go! Go! Show no mercy!
-Yes, Baron!
Feyd...
And when we've crushed
these people enough,
I'll send you. Feyd.
Lovely Feyd.
Where's my doctor?
Jessica...
our Reverend Mother is too old.
She has been calling through space and time, for you to come
and let her rest.
She asks that you pass within, and become
our Reverend Mother.
If you be a Reverend Mother,
let Shai-Hulud judge now!
The Water of Life.
But what of my unborn child?
One day, I will have to do this.
Following the Bene Gesserit tradition, the old Reverend Mother
surrendered her life as she surrendered her knowledge.
Jessica had successfully transmuted
the poisonous Water of Life.
Every man who has tried has died.
Am I the one?
The sleeper must awaken.
The tremendous power of the Water of Life
caused the premature birth of Jessica's daughter, Alia.
Alia was born with all the knowledge
and powers of a Reverend Mother.
Feyd, even though he's aging,
Thufir is one of the finest Mentats in the Universe.
And he's mine, Feyd,
all mine.
Try it now.  -I will.
Come.
Oh, Thufir! I see they've installed
your heart plug already.
Don't be angry. Everyone gets one here.
But this is not why we're here.
We've brought you a little cat, Thufir.
You must care for it if you wish to live.
A poison has been introduced into your body, Thufir Hawat.
By milking this,
this smooth, little cat body, you receive your antidote.
It must be done each day.
All I can see is an Atreides that I want to kill.
Feyd, no, no. Thufir's a Harkonnen now.
Aren't you, Thufir?
My Duke, how I've failed you.
Chani, I love you.
I've always loved you.
The Holy Warriors.
No one ever dreamed there were so many.
I am Usul. Paul Muad'Dib.
Our shared enemy, the Harkonnens,
are once again in control of Arrakis,
Stilgar, your leader, has asked me and my mother
to teach you the weirding way
to crush the Harkonnens.
We must do more than this.
We must totally destroy all spice production on Arrakis.
The Guild and the entire
Universe depends on spice.
He who can destroy a thing,
controls a thing.
I will take 100 of your warriors and train them.
This 100 will train the thousands that remain.
When the spice flow stops,
all eyes will turn to Arrakis.
The Baron and the Emperor himself
will be forced to deal with us.
Arrakis will become
the center of the Universe.
Orato.
This obelisk is of your hardest stone.
Kick it.
Hit it.
Yell at it.
Break!
Korba, cut it.
Move back.
This is part of the weirding way
that we will teach you.
Some thoughts have a certain sound,
that being the equivalent to a form.
Through sound and motion,
you will be able to paralyze nerves,
shatter bones, set fires, suffocate an
enemy, or burst his organs.
We will kill until no Harkonnen
breathes Arrakeen air.
Stilgar.
Muad'Dib.
My name is a killing word.
They are ready to fight.
Yet in order to lead them, I must conquer the worm,
conquer Shai-Hulud.
Take the kiswa maker hook of our sietch,
and ride as a leader of men.
I must not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
Only the very strong ones
travel this deep.
Usul has called a big one!
Again, it is the legend.
Usul, these are 15 of our finest warriors
to serve you as your guard.
The Fedaykin.
Now.
When the spice flow stops,
all eyes will turn to Arrakis.
The Baron and the Emperor himself
will be forced to deal with us.
Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib, Muad'Dib...
What happened to you and your men?
-Muad'Dib!
-What are you saying?
-He's been repeating that name ever since we found him.
-Who is this Muad'Dib?
In the two standard years that followed, Muad'Dib and the Fremen
brought spice production to a standstill.
Fearing for his life, Rabban did his best
to hide this fact from his uncle, the Baron.
Paul's sister Alia matured at a frightening rate.
Her small body harbored
tremendous powers.
Paul and Chant's love grew.
-We surprised a band of smugglers.
-Too bad. I thought they were Harkonnen.
Gurney!
You've no need of your weapons
with me, Gurney Halleck.
-Don't you trust your own eyes?
-They said you were dead.
They said...
-Gurney!
-You young pup!
Emperor Shaddam lV, you have one last chance
to take matters into your own hands,
- and bring the situation
under control on Arrakis.
-What do you mean, one last...
-Silence. Do not speak. Listen!
You do not have more than this one chance.
I represent the entire Guild in this matter.
Our navigators warn you that spice production is in great danger.
A new Fremen leader, Muad'Dib,
has stopped spice mining on Arrakis.
Our navigators suggest he is not of Arrakis.
No one on the outside world has been able to see him.
We do not know who he is.
The Harkonnens cannot stop him.
Remedy this situation, restore spice production,
or you'll live out your life in a pain amplifier.
The Emperor will stop him.
He won't take the Water of Life.
That's why they want me killed.
They're afraid I'll take the Water of Life.
I want 50 legions of Sardaukar on Arrakis at once!
-50 legions?  That's our entire reserves as well.
-This is genocide, the deliberate and systematic destruction of all life on Arrakis!
-The Emperor is coming!
-Chani! Chani!
You were calling my name.
It frightened me.
Oh, Chani.
All the images of my future are gone.
-I have to drink the Water of Life.
-No, Paul, please.
I've seen the men who have tried.
I've seen how they died.
I'm dead to everyone unless
I try to become what I may be.
Only the Water of Life
will free what can save us.
Paul...
I must drink the sacred water.
I must go now.
-Hurry. All I see is darkness.
-Paul...
I will love you forever.
You are my life.
-Many men have tried.
-They tried and failed?
They tried and died.
The worm is the spice.
The spice is the worm.
The worms.
They're not attacking.
Why?
Alia...
Mother.
It's Paul.
He's taken the Water of Life.
There is a place, terrifying to us,
to women.
This is the place
they cannot look.
Traveling without moving.
Now I truly control the worm...
and the spice..
And I have the power
to destroy the spice forever!
Paul...
Father!
Father, the sleeper has awakened!
Arrakis... Dune... Desert Planet.
Your time has come.
A storm is coming. Our storm.
And when it arrives,
it will shake the Universe.
Emperor, we come for you!
We come for you!
-Long live the fighters!
Suspicion confirmed. The Emperor's
had Rabban seized.
Gurney, when the storm hits,
set off the atomics.
I want an opening through
the entire shield wall.
Stilgar, do we have wormsign?
Usul, we have wormsign,
the likes of which even God has never seen.
Bring in that floating fat man, the Baron.
-Why have you brought me here?
-Your Highness, there must be some mistake.
-I never requested your presence.
-Ah, but your lack of action demanded it.
Your dreadful mismanagement, your bad judgment
in assigning to Rabban the governorship.
You've forced me to come here
and set things straight, personally.
I am a messenger from Muad'Dib.
Poor Emperor.
-I'm afraid my brother won't be very pleased with you.
-Silence!
Kill this child.  She's an abomination.
Kill her.
-Get out of my mind!
-Not until you tell them both
who I really am.
Alia...
daughter of Duke Leto the Just,
and the royal Lady Jessica.
Sister of Paul Muad'Dib.
Paul's sister?
Paul is Muad'Dib?
Alia keeps pace with the storm.
With the storm, their air power will be useless.
On Arrakish it's desert power.
Gurney...
-Now!
-Atomics!
My brother is coming
with many Fremen warriors.
Impossible!
Not impossible.  I told you.
He is here now.
Father, today I will avenge your death.
Emperor, an impassable storm has descended.
The Shield Wall has been penetrated by atomics.
Release the Sardaukar.
Baron, give this little abomination to the storm.
Wait for my brother, Baron.
Wait for my brother.
-Alia, now.
-Come to me Baron.
Feyd Rautha.
Emperor Shaddam IV, there are Guild Heighliners
above us, containing many Great Houses of the Landsraad.
-Send them back.
-How dare you speak to me in...
Stop your speaking.
You have some idea
of what I could do.
Don't try your powers on me.
Try looking into that place where you dare not look.
You'll find me there staring back at you.
-You mustn't speak...
-Silence!
I remember your gom jabbar.
Now you'll remember mine.
I can kill with a word.
And his word shall carry death eternal
to those who stand against the righteous.
-The righteous?
-There is a Harkonnen among you.
Give the Harkonnen a blade,
and let him stand forth.
If Feyd wishes,
he can meet you with my blade in his hand.
-I wish it.
-This is a Harkonnen animal.
-Let me. Please, my lord.
-The Emperor's blade.
Why prolong the inevitable?
I will kill you.
I will kill him!
Paul!
Who is the little one?
A pet, perhaps?
Will she deserve my special attentions?
Poisoned.
You see your death.
My blade will finish you.
I will bend like
a reed in the wind.
-Muad'Dib?
-Usul no longer needs the weirding module.
Muad'Dib had become the hand of God,
fulfilling the Fremen prophecy.
Where there was war, Muad'Dib would now bring peace.
Where there was hatred, Muad'Dib would bring love,
to lead the people to true freedom,
and to change the face of Arrakis.
We Fremen have a saying.
God created Arrakis
to train the faithful.
One cannot go against the word of God.
And how can this be?
For he is the Kwisatz Haderach.