Arrakis.
Dune.
A land so starved for water
a single tear is cherished.
It is here and only here
where it can be found: the Spice.
Greatest treasure
in the universe.
And the neverending cause
for conflict, betrayal, ...
and murder.
No.
Another bad dream, uncle?
No, it's a digestion, that's all.
Miserable food here.
I can't wait to be off
this foul planet.
What are you doing here, boy?
They're dead, uncle.
The Bene Gesserit witch
and her son. Both dead.
We discovered a Fremen siege not far from
where our thopter was supposed to crash.
They've been rescue by this
Atreides snake Duncan Idaho.
The ecologist, Kynes, was with them.
The emperor's man.
We killed Idaho, captured Kynes.
The witch and her son were last seen
driving a thopter into a sand storm.
- You've seen the bodies?
- They are most certainly dead.
You've seen the bodies?
Nothing survives one
of those storms, uncle.
The wind was over 800 kilometres an hour.
Nothing survives.
How long have I been asleep?
Not long.
The storm passed a little while ago.
It was Yueh.
He's the one who betrayed us.
They had his wife.
You should put it on, Paul.
You're the duke now.
We have to get out of here.
I found some supplies
stowed in the compartment by the hatch,
Paracompass, vision goggles, stillsuits.
- But where will we go?
- To find the Fremen.
Fremen?
We're going to need them...
...to take back Arrakis.
How do we know which way to go?
South.
That's into the deep desert.
There were rumors
of sietch communities there.
That's where we'll find the Fremen...
...or die trying.
I'm all right.
It's just the stress. I'm fine.
Please, Your Majesty, please.
You must control your anger.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
Or did you think I would just be
too simple-minded to see the truth?
Leave us alone.
What happened on Arrakis
was beyond my control, Daughter.
An ancient feud between royal houses.
Don't patronize me, Father.
Isn't it enough that you used me?
Used you?
Sending me to the duke
as a token of your support...
...making me a courier
of your esteemed respect...
- ...while you were plotting behind his back.
- Quiet, child.
Or was that your idea, Fenring?
That would be something
your perverse mind would suggest.
- Watch your tongue, girl.
- And what will you do if I don't?
Send me into the desert to die
like that poor boy and his mother?
No one sent them anywhere. They fled.
Despite the Baron's efforts...
...he assures me he did everything he could
to secure them from harm.
You were involved, Father.
I know you were.
Or at least you did nothing to prevent it.
Enough!
There will come a time, Daughter...
...when you will have to shed
this naiveté of yours...
...and learn what it means
to rule an empire.
And when that time comes, Father...
...you may learn to regret it.
It's only another few kilometers,
that's all.
Hurry, we don't have much time.
The sun will soon be up full.
We'll have some shade in here.
If there are any Harkonnen patrols this far out,
they'll have a tough time spotting us.
Such a pity.
A pity that you had to get mixed up
in this business, Doctor.
I'm not mixed up in it, Baron.
I'm the Emperor's servant,
nothing more and nothing less.
So you did not lead them
to that warren of Fremen scum?
That was Idaho's idea.
- He had forged a friendship with them.
- Yes.
We know all about Idaho
and his efforts on the Duke's behalf.
A foolish, desperate gambit.
And where was that Fremen trash
when he needed them, eh?
So, what will you say when the Emperor
questions you about what happened here?
What's your impression, hmm?
The desert is
an indiscriminate executioner, Baron.
I suppose that Bene Gesserit whore...
...and her spawn have found that out,
haven't they?
Be sure he recalls his flimsy denials
when he's face to face...
...with death's sweet smile.
Muad'dib.
Tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
On Caladan we ruled by air and sea, Paul.
But here, on Arrakis,
you need desert power.
- It's calling to you.
- Tell me about the waters...
...tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
It'll be night soon. We'll move on.
Did you get any rest?
Some.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
Try not to slow us down as much tonight.
How is my sister?
I'm having dreams again.
Visions.
Even when I'm awake.
I've seen her, Mother, inside of you.
Even your father didn't know.
Why not?
There wasn't time.
What have you done to me?
- I gave birth to you.
- A freak.
- No, not a freak.
- Then what?
This place is changing me.
It's the spice.
It's in the air we breathe,
in the food we eat.
I can't escape it.
Drink it all.
The best place to conserve water
is in your body.
The stillsuit will do the rest.
If we stay on this dune
we'll reach those mountains a lot sooner.
Is that a good idea?
It's the most direct path.
You all right?
Yes.
Hold on.
That shouldn't have happened.
I was careless about these dunes.
We lost our paracompass.
Can you hear that?
It's a worm!
It must have heard the sand fall.
Run! Just run!
- I can't see it!
- Don't stop!
A thumper?
Someone called it away.
Did you smell it? The cinnamon smell.
The spice.
Everywhere...
...when the worm came.
There had to have been people
for this many plants to survive.
Fremen.
We have to find them.
Most intruders here
regret finding the Fremen.
Don't run, intruders. There is no escape.
I know you.
You're Stilgar...
...the Fremen who came to see my father
with Duncan Idaho.
That was a sloppy crossing you made
from the crash.
You called a worm.
You were watching us?
- All of that time?
- We didn't see you.
- You weren't meant to.
- We're wasting time here, Stil.
- This is the boy Liet told us to seek.
- How can you be sure?
- I say we take their water and move on.
- Be quiet, Jamis.
As you can hear, I have a problem to solve.
My people are cautious and pragmatic.
Good qualities in the desert.
Better sometimes to miss an opportunity
than invite disaster.
Your only value at the moment
is the water in your flesh.
You know the law, Stil.
Yes.
The law.
Tell them to stop hunting my son.
Tell them.
Leave off! Leave the boy alone!
Do you hear me?
Is this the way
you welcome friends of Liet?
Is it?
As leader of this tribe...
...I'm offering the Weirding woman
and her son sanctuary.
No Fremen anywhere will lay a hand on you
while you have my protection.
For how long?
Don't be a fool, woman.
You're fugitives from the Harkonnen.
Don't be fugitives from us as well.
Merciful God!
I've heard of the Weirding ways.
Imagine what a man could do with it.
No doubt we have much
to teach each other.
You can come down, boy!
Your mother has shown her worth.
He won't move unless I say so.
Discipline. Good.
He's here!
He is unharmed.
We are coming down.
Leave me alone.
Made a lot of noise climbing.
He has much to learn.
- Stilgar.
- Can you travel, Jamis?
He surprised me, that's all.
- Of course I can travel.
- Good.
We have now two with us
who are not trained.
In squad lines with flankers.
We have to make Cave of Ridges
before full sun.
Chani, you will be responsible for him.
My name is Paul.
Only until we give you a new one.
Follow me. Do exactly as I do.
Across there is home...
...Sietch Tabr.
We'll be there tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
That must be hundreds of kilometers
from here.
It will be a hard ride.
Sun will be up soon.
Patrols sometimes come this far.
We can't let them see us.
When you give us your stillsuits,
we will recover your water for you.
Here is some food.
Spice.
We don't have delicacies from the cities
like you are used to.
It's fine.
She's the one, isn't she?
The one you've seen in your dreams?
I can tell by the way you stare at her.
I don't know what it means.
Be careful, Paul.
We are new to these people
as they are to us.
Everything we say and do must be careful.
Predicting the future,
then plotting to make it so.
These are superstitious people.
If we are to survive, it will be best
to accommodate their legends.
I'm the steward of the sand.
I am a desert creature.
A desert creature.
Not finished yet!
Still have work to do!
The pre-spice mass.
I am a desert crea...
Spice blow.
Somewhere to the east.
A large field from the looks of it.
We have to send gatherers
before Harkonnen pirates come for it.
You harvest the spice?
For bribes to the Spacing Guild.
It's Liet's wish.
We pay them to keep our skies free
of their satellites...
...so that no one can know
what we are doing here.
You will learn.
Amtal!
I invoke amtal.
Jamis.
What is this?
His way of dealing with what happened
the other night.
That was an accident.
He bested me because there was
witch-force at Tuono basin.
Amtal! It's my right!
We must not interfere.
Jamis has called him out.
You're starting something here
you're going to regret.
- Stilgar.
- You must step back.
If you know what's good for you,
you will find an honorable way...
...to leave this thing alone.
Silence!
I invoke silence.
She's trying to put a spell on me.
If you try that again,
we know it's your witchcraft.
I won't be able to protect you
or the boy anymore.
Come. You can't stop this.
A crysknife, our ritual weapon.
Use it well.
May your blade chip and shatter.
I'm going to bathe this knife
with your blood.
First, you'll have to find my blood.
- Do you yield?
- Yield?
There is no yielding. It's to the death, boy!
- He's never had to kill.
- What?
Then he'd better learn.
Finish. Don't toy with him.
He's bested Jamis.
This didn't have to happen.
It is our way.
Your way?! Killing each other.
No man recognizes leadership
without the challenge of combat.
There is a legend among us...
...that a voice from the out-world
will come.
The Mahdi.
He will hold the key to our future.
It is said that a Bene Gesserit
will be his mother.
A Sayyadina.
Friend of God.
There are rumors about you and your son.
From the city. Liet.
You hope I am that one? That Paul is?
I hope...
...and I fear.
If it's true, your boy will have to
call me out one day...
...to challenge me
for the leadership of the tribe.
The huanui is prepared. It's time.
It's our way.
From water does all life begin.
The flesh belongs to the person...
...but his water belongs to the tribe.
I was a friend of Jamis.
When the hawk plane fell upon us...
...at Hole-in-the-Rock...
...it was Jamis who pulled me to safety.
I was a friend of Jamis.
He taught me...
...that when you kill...
...you pay for it.
Bila-Kayfa!
He sheds tears.
He gives water to the dead.
Jamis carried 33 liters of the tribe's water.
Counted and measured.
Combat water is entrusted to the winner.
Because you fight without stillsuit...
...you may regain the water
you lost fighting.
May you guard it for the tribe,
preserve it against loss...
...be generous with it in time of need.
May you pass it on in your time
for the good of the tribe.
Needs a naming now, Stil.
It's time.
What would you have us call you,
young Atreides?
By what name do you wish Fremen
to know you?
What is the name of that little mouse?
The one in the desert. The one that jumps.
Muad'dib.
Is that the name you wish?
Yes.
Muad'dib.
Wise in the ways of the desert.
Hiding from the sun. Traveling at night.
We call him the "Teacher of Boys".
Muad'dib.
Yeah, a fine choice.
So, from now on
you will be addressed as Muad'dib.
Wait for my signal.
Then you must do exactly as I do.
Your lives will depend on it.
There.
Get ready.
What is that?
The one who will come. Mahdi.
It's the gatherer Stilgar sent
to the spice blow.
Give her some time, Muad'dib.
Liet is dead.
- We found his remains at the spice blow.
- Doctor Kynes is dead?
Harkonnen treachery.
She loved her father very much.
It needs a new dew collector.
Tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
We had rivers of it.
Great flowing veins of water.
From the snows of mountains...
...into lakes so wide
you couldn't see the other side.
Oceans of water.
Our home was on the coast.
Great waves would hurl themselves
against the cliffs.
They used to put me to sleep.
My father had a dream, Muad'dib.
A dream that one day...
...we could change this place...
...make it more like your homeland.
Windtrap.
Plenty of moisture this morning.
My father is at peace.
Muad'dib.
We have thousands of these caches.
Only a few of us know them all.
I know this place.
- No off-worlder has ever seen it.
- I have.
In my dreams.
This is the water we will use
to change the face of Arrakis.
As my father taught us...
...the voice from the out-world will come.
The Mahdi.
We will make a paradise of Arrakis.
And no man shall ever want
for water again.
Just as you said, Stil.
Harkonnen greed for spice
is the most reliable beacon in the universe.
- Reconnaissance team on the ground.
- Ground recon proceed to spice patch.
Anyone else hear that?
We didn't even have to damage
the thopter.
The men will fly it to our caves at Bight.
That was our last communication.
There is no mayday, no evidence of wreckage
when we went to investigate.
That's the third thopter this month!
The patch turned out to be mock spice.
- It was probably a plant to lure them there.
- Fremen scum!
We caught these last night,
a village near the rimwall...
...known to be desert sympathizers.
Mercy, Governor.
We are refugees.
- We need food.
- Liar!
Spies! That's what you are!
Spies for the Fremen scum!
Fremen scum
who raid my spice warehouses!
- Who destroy royal equipment!
- No. We are poor. We have no weapons.
He was trying to dispose of this
when we caught him.
Send words to the filth of the desert!
Tell them what you witness here!
Tell them this is what awaits them!
Mahdi!
Put that away, Feyd, and come here.
I want you to see this.
The latest love letter from your brother.
Mahdil
Appears to be enjoying himself.
The moron's appetite for killing
never ceases to amaze me.
By the time he's finished,
there won't be a population left to rule.
Cheer up, lovely boy.
I merely allow him to brutalize them,
to savage them, until you arrive...
...the handsome Feyd,
to rescue them from the beast, Rabban.
They will be ripe for you, lovely boy.
Feyd, the savior.
There will be cheering in the streets.
You can even give them
your brother's head as a gift, if you like.
And then you will squeeze,
like the grips of a vice...
...so our treasuries become fat
with the profit of spice.
No man recognizes leadership...
...without the challenge of combat.
It is the way.
Call him out!
What do you see...
...Muad'dib...
...when you go away like that?
Where is it you go?
Many places, Stil.
Many roads.
Many choices.
These choices...
...are good or bad?
It's hard to know sometimes.
Either they are good choices
or bad choices.
Aren't you ever afraid, Stil?
Of storms?
Of the future.
The future, Muad'dib, just is.
They're like ghosts! Everywhere!
Need immediate evacuation!
They just keep coming!
We are ready, Muad'dib.
Muad'dib, it's time. We must hurry.
He's waiting, Reverend Mother.
- Who else knows he's here?
- No one.
He made it clear on his arrival
that we should summon you and no other.
The other witches must leave.
As you wish.
This visit is as indiscreet
as it is unexpected.
Let's hope the Emperor's curiosity
isn't aroused.
The Emperor's suspicions
are easily moderated...
...by his dependence on our services.
As you are so fond of reminding us.
The navigators are concerned.
- Concerned?
- They are disturbed about the future.
There is a problem on the horizon.
What kind of problem?
They are troubled by a nexus
they can't fully explore...
...an intersection of events...
...a meeting of countless delicate decisions
beyond which lies a path...
...they cannot see.
And where is this nexus?
Planet Arrakis.
House Harkonnen controls Arrakis now.
The Atreides are dead.
It is not a matter of feuding royal houses.
We sense a higher order interfering.
A misstep could be catastrophic.
Then we understand one another.
Completely.
We'll do what we can.
I thought...
...I felt something.
The spice must flow.
The balance of power must be maintained.
Sayyadina?
I'm awake, Chani.
Has there been any
word, a courier perhaps?
No. The raids are
in the Haga basin.
They won't risk communication until
they are deep across the bled.
- Forgive me, Sayyadina.
- Was there something else?
No.
It's just your skin.
My skin?
We've heard the stories
about off-worlders,
the ones who come
from water planets.
Skin so moist it's like cream.
- Muad'dib's skin is like that.
- Paul?
Muad'dib is still a boy.
I mean, he still has the glow of youth.
Yes.
I say my prayers for his safe return.
We both do, Chani.
The smugglers transport our spice tribute
to the cursed Spacing Guild.
The Emperor never knows.
But bribes are dangerous, Stil.
They have a way of getting larger.
The safe way is the slow way, Muad'dib.
Bribes keep the skies of our sietches clear.
Bribes buy us time.
Something wrong, Muad'dib?
I thought I saw someone I knew.
I'll call them in.
Tell them to hold the smugglers' departure.
No, Stil.
Let them go.
I must have been mistaken.
Gurney.
My father's patience is wearing thin.
These troubles on Arrakis
are proving difficult to manage...
...and our time is running short.
I want you to make arrangements
for a trip to Giedi Prime.
Milady?
The Baron's nephew
is having a birthday celebration.
The Emperor ought to be represented,
don't you think?
I'm in the mood for a party.
Besides, it's time to shed
some of this naiveté.
She is not going!
I'm not going to allow that headstrong,
meddlesome child loose in Babylon.
My God, what a catastrophe
that would be.
The eldest daughter of the Imperial
House ensnared by the likes of Harkonnen
and his dreadful progeny.
Yes, catastrophe indeed.
But perhaps the seducer
could be seduced.
The more we know of the Baron's schemes,
the more we are prepared for the endgame.
Our operatives on Giedi
Prime have limited access.
Your daughter, on the other hand...
has proved quite adept at
intelligence gathering.
Gently chaperoned, I should think
she'd prove quite useful...
once again.
You've heard the voices
from your sietches.
They say the Mahdi has come.
But you...
...the naibs of your tribes
are still cautious. You resist.
But I am offering you the future.
The future as Liet saw it.
- How do you know what Liet saw?
- Because I've seen it.
Here.
And here.
And once we rid Arrakis
of the vile Harkonnen...
...we can complete his dream.
I promise this.
Arrakis will become the paradise
Liet imagined.
You'll never rid Arrakis
with guerrilla raids, boy.
It will take all-out war.
That's why I'm asking you
for hundreds of your best young men.
I want to give them the Weirding way...
...so they can come back to you
and train hundreds more.
So those hundreds
can train hundreds more.
And then hundreds will become thousands!
The Fedaykin.
A force to rival the dreaded Sardaukar.
A force to terrify the Emperor himself!
My father once told me...
...that here on Arrakis...
...one needed desert power to rule.
You are desert power...
...and nothing can stop you...
...if you believe.
So you are the one.
Jessica of the Weirding,
our Reverend Mother Ramallo.
Mapes said you were beautiful.
She also said she pitied you.
I need no one's pity.
That remains to be seen.
There is much talk of you in the sietches.
I hear the people speaking of the Mahdi.
I hear them shout the name Muad'dib.
He is a natural leader like his father.
The men admire his courage.
It will take more than courage
to survive what's coming.
The boy...
...he knows what it is
that's happening here?
He is aware.
You've exploited our legends well.
We had to survive.
And you may...
...for a while.
But remember this:
the very legend which protects you...
...can also destroy you.
- How are you feeling?
- Well.
Tired sometimes.
Healthy.
And growing fast.
I saw the one
they call the Reverend Mother.
Yes. She came from the southern sietch.
- Why?
- To see me.
To see you.
She's Bene Gesserit.
One of our missionaries.
Convenient.
Stilgar says you've learned much.
He's tougher than Hawat ever was.
Chani is happy to see you, I noticed.
Why didn't you marry him, Mother?
Because I loved him.
As long as your father
remained unmarried...
...some of the great houses could still hope
for an alliance through marriage.
We both knew what that meant.
- There were no illusions.
- You would have allowed it?
I would have encouraged it.
Politics.
Yes.
While I was on the hajra...
...I had dreams about this garden.
Except it wasn't here,
it was somewhere else.
Was I there?
Yes.
And there were children...
...playing, very happy.
A wonderful dream.
Do you think it's possible
to love someone enough...
...you'd be willing to give that person up?
I think...
...there are times when it's necessary
to share the one you love...
...with things greater than both of you.
Everything is connected,
one thing to another.
The living and the dead,
the animate and the inanimate.
A system.
All parts functioning to serve the whole.
Smell the air, Muad'dib.
Cinnamon.
The pre-spice mass is below us.
Maybe 100 feet or more, but ripe.
The Maker has left her nest long ago.
Her children have joined together
for survival.
They have grown.
They are losing water now.
It will mix with their waste.
If enough has accumulated...
...a giant bubble of foam
will heave up with tremendous force.
A spice blow.
Trading places with the sands above.
The sun and heat will dry it out and...
...soon...
- Spice.
- Treasure of the universe.
The worm...
...is the spice.
So now you know.
Many of the little makers
will die in the blow.
The rest will swim off
to become Shai-Hulud, the Great Worm.
We may capture a few.
Keep them stunted for Water of Life.
That's enough for now.
When religion and politics
ride in the same cart...
...the whirlwind follows.
You are the Kwisatz Haderach, boy.
The one who can be many places at once.
You are the whirlwind.
It's almost night, Muad'dib.
Time to return to the sietch.
You've been dreaming.
Too impatient, Farok.
You moved too soon.
Try again.
Watch his posture.
Even the slightest change in his breathing
gives you advantage.
Better, Farok. You'll have it soon.
I am Otheym.
These are my brothers
from Sietch Gara Kulan.
We've come to find the one
who calls himself Muad'dib.
You're a long way from your tribe, Otheym.
We've come to join your crusade.
We want to learn the Weirding Way.
We want to become Fedaykin.
- You have the blessing of your naib?
- We do.
- We could fight as Muad'dib.
- I believe you.
Let their waters join with ours.
I must congratulate you
on the perfection of your heir, Baron.
He faces his 100th slave gladiator
in the arena this afternoon.
He appears ready.
Well then,
perhaps we might take this opportunity...
...to conduct our conversations.
There is much to discuss.
Indeed.
If that meets with your approval, Milady.
I am quite entertained here.
Fine.
By your leave, then.
What other house would have
been willing to humiliate itself
so the Emperor could rid
himself of a troublesome duke?
He's been asking
himself that very question.
Are you suggesting that the Emperor
contemplates a move against me?
Speculation is not a
worthy science, Baron.
Better we spend our energy
on what's most important.
The spice must flow.
I must say I've always found
Harkonnen architecture rather...
curious.
Harkonnen patrols have taken more risks...
...coming deeper into the southern regions
than ever before.
Sooner or later our bribes to the Guild
won't be enough to protect us.
Then it's agreed.
We move with the next moons.
When the Harkonnen find this place...
...there must be nothing left
but the wind howling through the rocks.
There is no turning back now.
Subdue the Maker.
The Maker is dead.
The Water of Life.
May Shai-Hulud have mercy on both of us.
When night falls again,
we have to leave this sietch...
...that has sheltered us for so long.
We must go south into the deep desert...
...where the demon Harkonnen
will not pursue us.
But our Reverend Mother
will not survive another hajra.
So that we don't have to make the journey
without her strength and guidance...
...Sayyadina Jessica has consented
to undergo the rites at this time.
This is dangerous and Jessica may fail.
So that we don't lose all, Chani...
...daughter of Liet,
will be consecrated as Sayyadina...
...Friend of God.
I consecrate the daughter of Liet...
...in the Sayyadina.
Here is the Water of Life,
the water that will free your soul.
If you are our Reverend Mother,
the universe will open to you.
Let Shai-Hulud judge now.
You must drink it now.
What's happening to her?
The water is poisoned until she changes it.
This must take its course.
Mother? Mother?
You cannot go there.
That is the place we cannot look.
The place only
the Kwisatz Haderach may go.
You must turn away, Jessica,
or it will drive you mad.
Don't be afraid. I have much to show you.
Here is my life, Jessica of the Weirding,
...and the lives that have come before.
They are yours now.
You are pregnant.
You should have told us.
Holy Mothers!
What have we done?
This changes you both.
Your daughter is in danger.
Take her into your arms.
She must see all that we see.
That is the only way you can save her.
Change the waters, Jessica.
You must change them now.
The plan was perfect in its simplicity
and viciousness.
Of course it was.
You helped your uncle design it,
didn't you?
Duke Leto thought
he was gaining control of Arrakis...
...but he was only being fattened up
for sacrifice.
The kill, Feyd. Tell me about the kill.
Swift and merciless.
The Atreides never had a chance.
The Sardaukar had the palace sealed
within hours.
The Sardaukar.
I sent the final communiqué
to your father myself.
Mother?
Yes?
Mother Ramallo is gone.
But she remains.
You have changed the waters.
Now we know you cannot be false.
Paul?
The Reverend Mother
has changed the Water of Life.
It's now safe for us to drink!
The son and his mother,
the duke's concubine and her son...
...what did you do with them?
Lost in the storm, devoured by the desert.
You found their bodies
and disposed of them?
Never found them.
You never found the bodies?
You're trembling.
I'm afraid.
Of what?
Of you.
You make me see things.
What do you see?
I see us together.
There is a great storm.
I have a child in my arms.
Our child, Muad'dib.
It's not a dream.
I know you, Chani.
I've always known you.
We've sat upon a rock above the sands
and I've eased your fears.
We've caressed
in the darkness of the sietch.
We've grown old together.
History will say that the Fremen
were about to find their messiah.
That Paul Atreides would find his revenge...
...and the world, as we knew it,
would change forever.
The saga of Dune is far
from over.