Arrakis.
Dune.
Wasteland of the Empire...
...and the most valuable planet
in the universe...
...because it is here,
and only here, where spice is found.
The spice.
Without it,
there is no commerce in the Empire.
There is no civilization.
Arrakis.
Dune.
Home of the spice.
Greatest treasure in the universe.
And he who controls it,
controls our destiny.
Father!
This move to Arrakis comes
at a delicate moment for House Atreides.
A test of your father's loyalty
to the Emperor.
You must remember, Paul...
...our society is a tangled web
of competing forces.
Our civilization rests upon
a political tripod...
...a most unstable of structures.
A deceptive balance of power exists
between the Emperor...
...the Congress of Royal Houses, and
the supposedly impartial Spacing Guild...
...with its invulnerable monopoly
on interstellar transport.
Complicated by a feudal trading culture
that turns its...
Dr. Yueh would be disappointed.
Then he'd know how I feel.
It's never easy leaving one's home, Paul.
Think of this as a new adventure,
the adventure of a lifetime.
You call this an adventure?
Leaving our home for some dry speck
of dust in the middle of nowhere?
You're a duke's son.
You have duties, responsibilities.
How could I ever forget?
Every day I have to eat responsibility
for breakfast and duty for dinner.
Sarcasm doesn't become you.
I just want to see my father.
So do I.
The Reverend Mother has arrived.
She wants to see you
before we depart for Arrakis.
You have given him your face, Jessica.
But the father has given him his eyes.
And his courage.
We shall see.
Come here, boy.
Let me have a better look at you.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll do as I say.
I'll be the judge of
what's good for me.
Your mother has taught you many things,
I see.
She tells me you dream.
Your Reverence...
- ...if I could...
- You're dismissed, Jessica.
Since when is it permitted to treat
the Lady Jessica as a common servant?
She was a common servant.
My servant.
And a good one, too...
...until she was 16,
and your father took her.
Now, I would like to hear
about your dreams.
They're just dreams.
About what?
Why don't you tell me?
Do you know what this is?
It is a test, young Atreides.
A test for what?
Put your hand inside and we'll see.
What's in it?
Pain.
I hold the Gom Jabbar at your throat,
young Atreides.
Keep your hand in the box and live.
Remove it and die.
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer.
That's right, boy.
Pray.
I will face my fear,
I will let it pass through me.
And when the fear is gone
there will be nothing. Only I will remain.
No woman child,
ever withstood that much pain.
You are a gifted boy, young Atreides...
...but you have much to learn.
He survived.
You should've warned me.
She was forbidden.
I'm sorry.
Paul! Paul...
You were supposed to have a daughter.
You have hopelessly complicated matters.
An Atreides daughter could've been wed
to the Harkonnen heir.
The feud between the houses
could have been ended.
My duke wanted a son.
You arrogant girl.
Putting his desires above our interests.
How dare you turn your back on
the centuries of our breeding programmes.
I'll pay for my mistakes.
And your son will pay it with you.
We'll do what we can.
He may be worth saving...
...but for the father, nothing.
Good thing you don't play your baliset
as badly as you fight, Gurney-man.
Too bad Duncan isn't here.
- Then I could get a real workout.
- Now you've done it.
Whoa, Gurney-man.
Never submit to anger.
Fast on defense, slow on the attack.
You forgot your first principle, Gurney.
Not likely.
Look down, lad.
Perhaps you'd like to sing soprano
next time I play.
Guess I'm just not in the mood today.
Not in the mood?
Mood is a thing for cattle and women,
young pup.
Mood is not for fighting.
Even with the Weirding ways
your mother teaches you.
It's that old Bene Gesserit witch.
Something she said...
...or did.
The navigator is arriving.
We'll be on our way to Arrakis soon.
It is said that they depend on the spice...
...and that without it, they can't navigate.
It is said.
They used to be human, didn't they?
Until the spice changed them.
I don't think anyone knows for sure.
I've never seen one.
No one has.
It's forbidden, Paul.
So don't endanger
our shipping privileges trying.
All non-Guild personnel,
please secure quarters.
Will Arrakis be as bad as they say, Thufir?
The storms, perhaps.
They can eat the flesh off your bones
as you stand.
The only thing that doesn't fear
an Arrakis storm is the giant worm.
It's not worms I worry about.
Your father is a formidable man, Paul.
Even the Emperor fears him.
I'd sooner cast my fate with him
than trust anything...
...some Bene Gesserit hag said.
Why do you hate them?
The Bene Gesserits?
I don't hate them.
I don't trust them.
I am a Mentat.
I trust logics and statistics, not
mysticism and prophecy.
And so it begins.
The trap is set, the prey approaches.
A glorious winter is about to descend
on House Atreides and all its heirs.
The centuries of humiliation,
visited upon my family...
...will finally be avenged.
But Arrakis was mine!
Shut up, Rabban.
I did what you said, Uncle.
I made the people cover.
I crushed that vile planet.
He said squeeze, brother, not crush.
Rabban aspires to rule House Harkonnen
one day, Feyd.
And yet he can't even rule himself.
Explain our plan, Mentat.
The plan is elegant and vicious, dear Baron.
Of course it is.
I designed it.
In order for the Empire to survive,
the spice must flow.
But the production
has become inconsistent.
In his wisdom, the Emperor decided
only one man is honest enough...
...and loyal enough to be trusted with
restoring the spice production adequately.
Duke Leto Atreides.
Temporarily interrupting
80 years of Harkonnen rule...
...and all the profits that go with it.
I said temporarily, you moron.
It doesn't take long for Duke Leto
to believe he has Arrakis...
...firmly under control.
And then,
at the moment of his greatest confidence...
The traitor strikes.
A traitor? Who?
That remains my little secret for now.
What about the other great houses?
They're sure to protest.
Perverting common wisdom, Nephew,
is a mark of all great conspiracies.
You see, Nephews,
a popular man arouses jealousy...
...and Duke Leto is a very popular man.
The other great houses
will be glad to get rid of him...
...even though they would never admit it.
The spice...
...will flow.
The Emperor will be pleased
and House Harkonnen...
...will be more powerful than ever.
Alone and vulnerable,
at the edge of the universe...
...valiant Duke Leto
will finally come face to face with fear.
When I'm through,
he won't know who to trust...
...not even that Bene Gesserit witch
he sleeps with.
They'll all be turning on one another
like rats in the flood.
By the time the traitor is fully revealed...
...the fate of Atreides
will already be sealed.
My son always says
you have a feline grace, Duncan.
I didn't want to startle you, Milord.
The latest emigration reports.
They fear our regime
will be as bad as the Harkonnens'.
We're losing too many.
Spice hunters, drivers, weather scanners,
dune men, we'll need.
Should I, er, persuade some to stay?
No.
I have something more important
for you to do.
I want you to go into the desert.
The Fremen?
I'm getting reports of hundreds,
perhaps thousands, in villages...
what they call "Sietches".
In the deep desert.
Beyond the mountains.
The Harkonnen sneered
at the desert people.
Hunted them for sport.
- I doubt they'll expect any better from us.
- Then we have to change that.
We're going to need allies here, Duncan.
I want you to seek out their leader...
...this Liet I keep hearing about.
A phantom.
He may not even exist.
He could even be many different men.
Find out.
Negotiate patience so I can demonstrate
our good intentions with deeds.
If I'm lucky, they will judge all of us by you.
You honor me, sir.
I am endangering you and I know it...
...but you're the only one
I can trust with this.
Such a dusty little garrison town.
A testament of the harsh climate
of the place.
What's he doing?
Water seller, Milady.
You need never bother
with the likes of them.
The cistern at the palace
holds 50,000 gallons...
...and it's always kept full.
What's wrong with their eyes?
Those are Fremen, desert people.
It's the spice.
It's everywhere: the air, the food.
By the time a Fremen child is 12
his eyes have turned completely blue.
Guards everywhere.
We didn't have to live like this on Caladan.
Family apartments are in the west wing.
The furniture is being brought up.
What is this for?
An old custom, I'm told.
Guests ceremoniously splash water
on the floor after washing their hands.
They save the squeezings.
Demeaning custom.
Idaho has prepared for us well, Milord.
Duncan?
Where is Duncan? Can I see him?
I have him occupied on official business
for the moment.
You have to be patient.
I've assembled the general staff,
as you requested.
No, don't take it up there.
I want the coat of arms to hang here.
The first thing visitors must see,
this is House Atreides now.
We are not like the Harkonnen.
You will be treated here with respect.
From now on,
we speak the lady's language at all times.
The Shadout Mapes, Milady,
head of household staff.
Mapes, show Milady our apartments.
Make sure she has everything she needs.
I'll join you after the briefing.
This way, Milady.
Come, Paul.
The men are waiting.
Me?
Right now?
It's time you participate it.
I've had the girls sandscrub these walls
to within a millimeter of their frames.
The Harkonnen stench is finally gone.
Built by off-worlders many years ago.
A chapel for the memories of what
they left behind when they came here.
A thousand people
could survive a year on the water...
...it takes to keep this place a month.
And a Harkonnen
never let us forget it, Milady.
Your name, Shadout,
it means well-dipper, doesn't it?
I was raised in the desert sietches,
Noble-born.
Refer to me as Milady, Mapes.
I'm not noble-born.
I am the bound concubine of the duke.
There is no wife?
I'm his only companion,
the mother of his son.
You are Bene Gesserit?
Yes, I know the ancient tongues.
Tell the people, Mapes,
this place belongs to them now.
As long as we rule here...
...the Atreides family
will keep it in trust for them.
Stay there.
Give them back their money.
Go on.
It is a custom, Milady.
This custom stops now.
Do as I said.
Water will never again be sold
at the Atreides' door.
At the end of every meal,
any person who calls at this door...
...may receive a full cup,
free.
Is it possible?
Could it be possible
that she brings the Mahdi?
The thing must take its course.
What about the mining accounts?
The Harkonnen spice operation took...
...10 billion solaris out of here
every year.
Now, does anyone here still think that the
Harkonnen have just packed up and left?
Gurney, I want you to make contact...
...with the smugglers
operating in the deep desert.
Tell them that we'll ignore
what they're doing from now on...
...as long as they make it worth our while.
The Emperor is extremely jealous
of his spice profits, Milord.
It's one thing
to turn a blind eye to smugglers,
it's quite another
to pocket some of their earnings.
Well, then just tell him what we're doing.
Bank the entire amount to his name,
Shaddam IV.
But then deduct it from our taxes
as a legitimate expense.
In other words, cost of doing business.
What?
I would just love to see the Baron's face
when he hears of this.
All the Harkonnen parasites
who got rich taking smuggler bribes...
...will be flushed into the open.
No more graft.
The Emperor cannot deny this.
Not in public, anyhow.
Well done, lad,
well done
Now...
An emperor's daughter must do better.
Worthy to be your first-born?
They tell me her ambitions
tend more to the literary than the political.
Never underestimate the political uses
of an awakened mind, Majesty.
Subterfuge and cunning are often
better allies than a fierce heart...
...and a strong back.
All she lacks is the primacy of our gender.
Then you must marry her well.
Someone with a suitably
pliable personality.
Too bad it won't be that young Atreides.
The most admirable lad, I'm told.
Good union of breeding and training.
We must arrange to send Duke Leto
a token of our love.
He must continue to think of us fondly.
Why did we come here, Father?
And don't just tell me
it's a matter of honor or duty.
There's more to it, isn't there?
I've never lied to you, Son.
We've been entrusted with the most
profitable commodity in the universe.
That alone makes us many enemies.
Then why don't we call them out?
Expose them...
...in front of the Emperor.
What if he's one of them?
This is a hard lesson, Son.
In the world we live in,
self-interest governs all.
The Emperor needs us...
...for the moment, to administer Arrakis,
to make the spice flow.
But he fears us, Paul.
He fears my influence
among the great houses.
If he decides it's in his interests...
...that House Atreides should fall,
he will do nothing to stop it.
He might even...
...invite opportunity to hasten it.
Well then, if you're right,
this place is a trap.
Perhaps.
But knowing there's a trap
is the first step in evading it.
I should've taken
the House Atreides renegade...
...fled to the darkest corners
of the universe.
You're too honorable for that, my love.
No. I'm too fed up.
This endless feud stops here.
The Harkonnen are a rogue clan, Leto.
No matter how much prestige
they try to buy...
...they'll never have the respect
you've earned.
Respect can't buy us peace.
I'd trade it all for a place somewhere,...
...anywhere where we could be alone,
where Paul could be safe.
And all I had to think about
was your happiness.
Maybe then I could finally make...
Please, don't talk about things
that can't be.
You belong to your time,
I was bred to my destiny.
Even if I were able to go back and choose...
...I would change nothing.
One of yours, Turok?
Harkonnen mercenaries.
Save your strength for the desert, Atreides.
Word has already been sent to the palace.
We have people among you.
- Are they trustworthy?
- They are Fremen.
I'll take care of these.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Forgive me, milady.
I was enjoying the morning.
For a moment I could imagine
my wife walking there.
My Suk-conditioning is supposed to rid me
of such unstable versions as hope.
Still, it's all I have left.
We have spies everywhere, Dr. Yueh.
If she's still alive, we'll find her.
Seems almost a sacrilege,
wasting one's water in a land
starved for it.
I'm sorry we drived you here
to this dangerous place.
I came willingly, milady.
Only half the sandcrawlers are operable...
...but we'll have most of the ornithopters
working soon.
That is a harvester factory.
We have about 1,000.
As big as she is,
there are worms in the deep desert
that could swallow one whole.
Why don't we use shields?
Shields are useless in the desert.
Even a simple body shield
will call every worm within 100 kilometers.
Drives them into a killing frenzy.
The imperial ecologist, Milord, Dr. Kynes.
We prefer the traditional term,
planetologist.
I understand that we have you to thank
for our stillsuits.
I hope they fit well.
This is basically a high-efficiency filter
and heat-exchange system.
The skin layer is porous.
Perspiration passes through heat filaments
and salt precipitators.
Water is reclaimed in catchpockets,
which you can draw from this tube.
Properly adjusted, water loss
is kept under 15 milliliters a day.
That's hardly measurable.
That's the point.
You're a Fremen.
I am accepted in both sietch and village.
But I am in the Emperor's employ.
You've worn a stillsuit before?
This is the first time.
Someone adjusted it for you?
No, it just seemed the right way
to put it on, that's all.
Well then...
...the desert awaits.
Maintain 120 degrees southeast, Milord.
Set.
That's where the sandmaster
is concentrating his equipment.
How many men are there
on a mining crew?
As few as possible.
Mining is a perilous adventure at best,
Milord.
Has anyone ever been lost out this far
and survived?
Men have walked out of the nearer zones
by crossing the rock areas...
...where worms seldom go.
Fremen?
Fremen.
There it is.
That's the harvester.
And those are the scouts?
Yes.
Watching for worm sign.
Worm sign?
Wherever there is spice, there are worms.
Always?
They defend the spice sands.
Has there been an effort to wipe them out?
Too much area to cover. Too many worms.
A rich field by the look of the color.
Is that worm sign?
Where's the carryall
to evacuate the harvester?
Worm sign, approximately 40 kilometers.
He's got you.
Estimated intercept, six minutes.
Do they always cut it this close?
It's not standard procedure.
The carryall should be here by now.
- How many men on that harvester?
- Usually 23, Milord.
- Are we sure the worm will attack?
- No doubt about it.
Crew on the harvester,
this is Duke Leto Atreides.
We're coming to take you out.
Cease operations and prepare for evacuation.
Spotters, land to the west.
Prepare to be boarded.
Those spotters only carry four men,
in addition to the crew Milord.
We can only get another two in here.
Paul, you and Gurney can get to
work on the back seats.
We'll jettison them when we land.
I will get in three more.
This is harvester Delta Ajax Niner.
With all due respect Sir, we have almost a full load.
Damn the spice.
We can always get more. Prepare for evac.
That's an order!
Worm sighting! Worm sighting!
10 degrees southwest.
Estimated speed, 40 knots.
We have an approach.
Worm intercept, five minutes.
Sandmaster, this is a direct command
from your duke.
Cease operations
and evacuate the station immediately...
...or I'll cut your ship in two
with a lasgun.
I can hear it.
The worm.
I can hear it coming.
Over here! Over here!
Both of you, over here!
The rest to the spotters!
Run, you sand dogs, run!
Get down and hang onto anything you can.
What are they doing?
Milord, we must go now! Hurry!
Capacity overload.
We need altitude or it'll suck us down.
Capacity exceeds lift capability.
Bless the Maker and his water.
Bless his coming and his going.
May his passage cleanse the world.
May he keep the world for his people.
How about the men we left behind?
- Send a ship to search for them.
- But they were right by the worm...
Send a ship anyway.
When God ordains a man's time to die...
...he directs that man to the proper place.
- What?
- Paul.
I want the pilots from that missing carryall
delivered to me personally.
Someone's going to pay for that waste.
This is a different kind of man.
He risked his life and that of his son
to save the men instead of the Spice.
A leader like that could have commended
fanatic loyalty.
This is my legacy to you, Son.
The greatest wealth in the universe
and the never-ending struggle to defend it.
The ancients used to say
danger and opportunity were...
...often the same thing father.
This is not one of Yueh's
academic exercises, Paul.
On Caladan we ruled by air and sea.
And here we need desert power.
Desert power!
Remember that.
Mahdi, Mahdi.
Leto is growing more popular
with every passing week.
He has ruined our system
of bribes and patronage.
He's been able to maintain the spice quota
despite our sabotage.
Even that mongrel ecologist Kynes
is sending the Emperor favorable reports.
And what do you deduce
from all of this, Nephew?
The longer we wait,
the harder it will be to dislodge him.
Piter, try again, will you?
Leto's continued success makes
the other great houses nervous, Rabban.
We can hear whispers, petty jealousies
that could easily give birth...
...to considerable envy.
Bugger envy!
We have a traitor among them.
I say strike now!
For your approval, Uncle.
The slave is quite a specimen this time,
don't you think, Rabban?
Perhaps Feyd
shouldn't be quite so casual today.
No.
Perhaps my dear brother
might even break a sweat today.
What you fail to understand...
...is that I want Leto to become popular.
I want him to feel secure.
I want him to feel confident.
Confidence breeds distraction.
And that is when one is most vulnerable.
Such a beautiful boy.
Little is known about the giant sandworms
that inhabit the desert regions of Arrakis.
It is known that worms are drawn to the
vibration and noise of mining activity.
However there is no direct evidence linking
desert worms to Spice production.
Needs a new dew collector.
Dew collector?
Chromaplastic.
At night it cools very fast.
In the morning, daylight heats it.
The surface condenses moisture
out of the air...
and it trickles down to keep
the plants alive.
- A simple beauty.
- A meaningless beauty.
In such a godforsaken place.
We deal here with the
law of the minimum.
Unless we learn to live with it,
conditions can never change.
Favorable conditions?
Change the ecology of the planet?
That depends.
On what?
On who the stewart of the desert is.
Perhaps one day the person will
come who will understand,
who will see the future
and know what can be.
The one who will change Arrakis.
The Mahdi.
You asked me to inquire
about the shouting the other day.
The words they were calling out
at your shuttle.
"Mahdi", something like that.
It means messiah.
They have a legend here, a prophecy...
...that a leader will come to them
from off-world.
A boy. The only son of a Bene Gesserit.
To guide them to true freedom.
Messiah?
Paul?
These are, uh, simple people, Milord.
They survive on hope.
Tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
I'm sorry, Milord.
Mapes didn't tell me you were in here.
No wait.
It's fine.
I was tired.
I fell asleep.
You can go on about your work.
Tell me...
...do the cooks use much spice in our food?
The spice is everywhere
on Arrakis, Milord.
Everywhere.
Don't move.
Just do exactly as I say.
It's a hunter-seeker.
They will kill you...
...instantly, if you move.
Listen to me.
The operator, wherever he is...
...can only target movement.
Stay perfectly still.
Don't give in.
Fear is the mind killer.
You're lucky to be alive.
I was its target?
It goes toward movement, that's all.
You could have let it go
and saved yourself.
There is a traitor among you.
Someone close.
Someone very close.
I want him alive!
Hey, you!
They tried to take the life of my son!
He looks local.
- There's nothing to identify him.
- Harkonnen, surely.
- And not working alone...
- Stop it, both of you!
Burn him.
Everything except the hands.
Put some spice in each one...
...and send them to the Baron
on Giedi Prime.
He almost took the life of my son.
Get out, all of you! Out!
You simple ass.
I told you that I wanted
those bastard Atreides to feel secure.
But no, you couldn't wait.
You had to have your own way.
Now your "initiative"
has made them more defensive.
Now what, Piter?
Advancing our timetable
would seem appropriate at this point.
Another blinding burst of insight!
How is it that I am blessed with such
extraordinary counselors as these?
There is, of course,
the slight troop-transport problem.
Our negotiations with the Spacing Guild
are not yet concluded.
Damn the Guild and their navigators.
Even the Emperor can't move without the
blessing of the Spacing Guild, dear Baron.
And what would you suggest,
my most devious Mentat?
Offer an increase in spice royalties...
...payable in advance
from Rabban's own reserves...
You are out of your mind, you...
Get on with it, Piter.
We must try and turn this setback
to our advantage.
Perhaps your incompetence
will prove useful after all...
...and hasten the day
House Atreides must fall.
You're tired, Father.
Yes, I am tired.
The degeneration of the great houses
has worn me out.
Our house hasn't degenerated.
Hasn't it?
Your assassin didn't arrive here
without help.
But who could you suspect?
I can only suspect.
I can't prove...
...and there's suspicion enough
to go around.
It can't be Gurney.
He knew your assassin
would be more valuable alive.
Gurney's impulsive, Father.
He doesn't have that kind of cunning.
Or Yueh's intelligence.
Surely not Yueh?
His Suk conditioning
would drive him mad first.
Never let sentiment
cloud your judgment, Son.
There is someone.
Sooner or later
you must face whoever it is.
So this is how it works.
They sow the seeds of distrust...
...and get us to fear each other.
Learn this lesson well, Son.
If you want to hold Arrakis,
you must be prepared to fight fear with fear.
Fear and power.
That's our cue.
The man in silver
is a stillsuit manufacturer in Carthag.
An inferior product to the Fremen's.
The hard-faced woman next to him
runs an escort service in Arsunt.
Impressive client list, I'm told.
By the fireplace, Lingar Bewt,
water shipper from the polar region.
The man to his right...
A Spacing Guild representative.
How could I miss him?
The man with Thufir is Esmar Tuek,
smuggler, highly successful.
He has fast ships if we need them.
Milady, Milord...
...I was honored by the invitation.
You are always welcome here, Dr. Kynes.
We found the missing carryall, Milord,
hijacked by Harkonnen agents...
...who tried to sell it at a smuggler's camp.
They are now dead.
We are indebted to you, sir.
Milady will see to it
you have everything you need.
It will be my pleasure.
And my honor, Milady.
I understand they lost another harvester
to a worm.
If they keep this up, they won't even be
able to have enough money to buy water.
Gentlemen and ladies, Her Royal Majesty,
Princess Irulan Corrino.
Your Highness, your attendance
is a most welcome delight.
My father sends you his enduring respect
and affection, my Lord Duke.
The Emperor wishes everyone to know
of the confidence he has in House Atreides.
She brings the Emperor's Sardaukar killers
as her bodyguards.
Water customs here are so fascinating...
...don't you think, Your Highness?
When I arrived, my bathing towels
were hurried away almost before I was dry.
To save their squeezings, I assume.
That's a safe assumption.
Nothing about this place is fascinating.
If it weren't for the spice,
no one would bother about it at all.
Fortunately enough,
for a water seller like you, I would guess.
I enjoy watching the flight of birds
here on Arrakis.
Many exist without any water at all.
Carrion eaters, you know, blood drinkers.
A curious adaptation, don't you think?
You mean they are cannibals?
I said they drink blood,
not necessarily the blood of their own kind.
Why not?
One's fiercest competition comes
from one's own kind.
They eat from the same bowl.
It's said that Fremen
drink the blood of their dead.
Isn't that so, Dr. Kynes?
Not the blood, sir.
All of a man's water.
A necessity
when one lives in the deep desert.
The human body is 70 percent water.
Surely a dead man no longer requires it.
At least here is honest merrymaking.
Careful, lad.
That spice beer can go to your head
before you know it.
Play, Gurney.
Let's you and I at least have some peace.
When the son of my beloved duke
orders me to relax...
...then, by God, I intend to do so.
Is that how you really feel, Gurney-man...
...about my father?
Beloved?
You young pup.
If I didn't know better, I would take
those words for an accusation.
It was a simple question.
Your father rescued me
from a Harkonnen slave pit, boy.
He took me into his household,
groomed me as his war master.
The man or woman...
...that raises a hand against him...
...will have it cut off by me,
as a prelude to their death.
I'm ashamed of myself doubting you,
Gurney-man.
That's enough, lad. No more of this.
Gentlemen and ladies,
I use the terms loosely of course.
I, the Baron Harkonnen...
...have decided that the great seal
of our venerable house...
...that confused and ugly Chimera,
the griffin...
...no longer adequately represents
the ambition of our appetites.
Therefore and henceforth, in conclusion
and furthermore, ergo and et cetera...
...our ample and royal self...
...from this day forth,
and throughout the universe...
...we shall no longer be known
as House Harkonnen.
We shall be...
...House Hog.
Now I know why they say
your skill with a knife...
...is exceeded only by your mastery
of the baliset, Gurney Halleck.
Is it Atreides custom
to abandon an honored guest...
...without even the courtesy
of a lame excuse?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Careful.
Spice beer can go to your head
before you know it.
So I've noticed.
You were expecting someone
more delicate, perhaps?
Refined was the word I had in mind,
actually.
There's an ancient saying
I've learned to trust:
Never judge a book by its cover.
We are not all that different, Paul Atreides,
you and me.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I've heard all about the moody Paul...
...the grim Paul,
the angry and unhappy Paul...
...who has been exiled to Arrakis,
well, poor boy...
...one day he will inherit responsibility
for the greatest treasure in the universe.
And a never-ending struggle to defend it.
We both suffer the solitude
of our birthright.
Except that tomorrow you will return
to the comfort of your palaces on Kaitain.
To the confinement of its perfect gardens
and lonely apartments.
To your servants and entourage.
With their slavish flattery
and cautious conversation.
As an heir to an Emperor.
Who damns my mother
for bearing daughters instead of sons.
You're mocking me.
No.
I'm trying to interest you.
Are you gonna dance with me
or just stand there looking confused?
I didn't want to come here, you know.
Being an ornament
of my father's diplomacy...
...is hardly my idea of a good time.
But you turned out to be more complicated
than your reputation.
And I like complicated.
We've been looking for you, Your Highness.
So now you've found me.
- Have you been hurt?
- Be still, Captain.
The Princess has been
under my protection.
Oh, please.
- Gurney, hold.
- Stand down, Captain.
- Gurney.
- I said stand down, Captain!
It's late, Highness. The shuttle awaits.
I am not ready to go.
Your father left strict orders.
You see?
Perhaps we should be the adults here.
Set an example
for our hot-tempered friends.
You are more interesting than you appear,
Paul Atreides.
I hope this won't be our last encounter.
My father will no doubt reward you
for such mindless obedience, Captain.
Father?
Duncan?
Forgive the abrupt arrival, Milord.
But we've taken
a force of Harkonnen infiltrators.
The Fremen found them
in the cave of the shield mountains.
One of the Fremen, Turok,
was badly wounded.
- I rushed him here for treatment...
- But he has died.
This is Stilgar, Milord...
...leader of Turok's tribe.
We've heard many things in the desert
about Leto Atreides.
I hope what you've heard
will be the beginning...
...of a friendship between us.
My people have suffered long
under the rule of such as you.
No, not such as me, nor any of my family.
All that changed
when the House Atreides came to Arrakis.
Stilgar, this is my son, Paul Atreides.
Yes.
We have heard about him as well.
The Fremen want me
to remain with them, Milord.
He fights well.
And he has done his best for our friend.
It will reassure us.
Dual allegiance, Milord,
to you and to their tribe.
There is a precedent.
Liet serves two masters.
Let it be known among your people,
Stilgar, that Duke Leto Atreides...
...honors the sacrifice
that your warrior has made on our behalf.
I wish nothing but peace between us.
We thank you for the gift
of your body's water, Stilgar...
...and accept it in the spirit
with which it was given.
Duncan Idaho...
...your water now belongs to us.
The body of our friend, Turok,
remains with your duke.
His water now belongs to the Atreides.
That is the bond between us.
Mapes? Mapes!
Mapes, who did this? Who?
Traitor.
Who?
Guard dead.
Shields.
The shields.
Gurney!
Yueh?
God forgive me.
I have no choice.
Why?
Because I need to save my wife.
We haven't much time.
The Harkonnen will be in the palace soon.
I'm giving you
the final revenge, Milord...
...for this terrible thing I've done
to you and your family.
You will have your revenge, Milord,
I promise.
Just remember the tooth.
The tooth, Milord.
When you have the Baron face to face...
...remember the tooth.
An Emperor's Sardaukar.
The duke! Where is the duke?
Not in quarters, sir.
We can't find the young master either.
Bastards!
He looks sufficiently paralyzed.
My half of the bargain, Baron.
I promised you the duke, there he is.
Well, it's a delicious sight, Doctor.
Now it's time for your half.
And believe it or not,
I'm a man of my word.
Where is she?
You promised we'd be reunited.
You said you'd free her
if I did what you asked.
Well, I've done it.
So where is she?
Your wife is free, my good doctor.
Completely free.
Free of her mortal coil.
Free of her physical cage.
I've freed her.
I promised you'd be reunited,
and I'm a man of my word.
As now you can see.
You think you've defeated me.
Never trust a traitor.
Not even one you create.
My noble duke, are you enjoying the show?
I hope so.
I kept you alive so you could witness
every precious moment of your betrayal.
What?
Paul.
Oh, the boy.
I don't know, I'd leave them to the desert,
he and that gorgeous woman of yours.
My men left them to explore
the beauty of the sands of Arrakis.
Perhaps they'll see some worms.
We couldn't have all that noble blood
all over our hands, could we?
The Emperor was quite insistent
about that.
Yes...
...your beloved Emperor.
Just goes to show,
never get more popular than the boss.
Unless you intend to sack him.
Did I say that? How impolitic of me.
I must be spending too much time
with that idiot nephew of mine, Rabban.
You won't say anything will you,
my dear man?
Perhaps we should get on with it, then.
Get on with it?
This is Kanly, Piter!
Vendetta!
And I am going to savor
every minute of it.
My family has hated the Atreides
for generations.
They have been the sand in our eyes,
the stink at our meals...
...these arrogant Atreides,
always standing in our way.
I want Leto to appreciate the beauty...
...of what I've done to him.
I want him to know that I,
Baron Vladimir Harkonnen...
...am the instrument
of his family's demise...
...the extinction of House Atreides...
...and the ascendance of House Harkonnen.
The tooth.
What did he say?
Tooth.
What did he say, Piter?
The tooth.
No!
Need you more proof
of what heaven's choice is?
Atreides is dead, and Harkonnen lives!
He's dead.
Father's dead.
- What are you doing?
- We won't survive longer than a few hours in the open.
We have to find shelter.
But Harkonnen patrols.
Worms.
We have to take our chances.
One of ours?
We can't take the chance.
Could be Harkonnen
coming to finish the job.
Hurry! Harkonnen patrol ships
are in the area, approaching fast.
Strap in.
- What is this place?
- A Fremen sietch. A small one.
There's a storm coming.
We can stay here until it passes.
Liet, we must talk.
Rest here.
How did you know where to find us?
Dr. Yueh sent a courier.
Said you were being taken to the bled,
south of the mountain shield.
Milord...
...I'm supposed to give you this.
Harkonnen patrols are in the area.
- They tracked our thopter.
- They called you Liet.
You're the one, aren't you?
The one who's never seen,
the one who may not even exist at all.
Their leader.
I prefer the term guide to leader.
Guiding them?
Until Mahdi comes.
Harkonnen thopters approaching.
Milord.
- You're coming with us?
- No.
- They'll kill you.
- Me?
I'm Dr. Kynes.
I work for the Emperor, you remember?
I'll just say I was your hostage.
Milord, please.
I must remain with the Fremen, Milord,
as I promised your father.
Just hold on.
We can't lose them.
Paul, the storm. We can't go into that.
We have no choice.
Nothing survives one of those storms.
Unless they want to die,
they won't follow us in, will they?
I must not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.
I will face my fear,
and I will let it pass through me.
When the fear is gone
there will be nothing.
Only I will remain.
There is a legend that the night
House Atreides lost Arrakis...
...a star exploded in the skies
above their homeland on Caladan.
But, the saga of Dune was far
from over.
Arrakis.
Dune.
A land so starved for water
a single tear is cherished.
It is here and only here
where it can be found: the Spice.
Greatest treasure
in the universe.
And the neverending cause
for conflict, betrayal, ...
and murder.
No.
Another bad dream, uncle?
No, it's a digestion, that's all.
Miserable food here.
I can't wait to be off
this foul planet.
What are you doing here, boy?
They're dead, uncle.
The Bene Gesserit witch
and her son. Both dead.
We discovered a Fremen siege not far from
where our thopter was supposed to crash.
They've been rescue by this
Atreides snake Duncan Idaho.
The ecologist, Kynes, was with them.
The emperor's man.
We killed Idaho, captured Kynes.
The witch and her son were last seen
driving a thopter into a sand storm.
- You've seen the bodies?
- They are most certainly dead.
You've seen the bodies?
Nothing survives one
of those storms, uncle.
The wind was over 800 kilometres an hour.
Nothing survives.
How long have I been asleep?
Not long.
The storm passed a little while ago.
It was Yueh.
He's the one who betrayed us.
They had his wife.
You should put it on, Paul.
You're the duke now.
We have to get out of here.
I found some supplies
stowed in the compartment by the hatch,
Paracompass, vision goggles, stillsuits.
- But where will we go?
- To find the Fremen.
Fremen?
We're going to need them...
...to take back Arrakis.
How do we know which way to go?
South.
That's into the deep desert.
There were rumors
of sietch communities there.
That's where we'll find the Fremen...
...or die trying.
I'm all right.
It's just the stress. I'm fine.
Please, Your Majesty, please.
You must control your anger.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
Or did you think I would just be
too simple-minded to see the truth?
Leave us alone.
What happened on Arrakis
was beyond my control, Daughter.
An ancient feud between royal houses.
Don't patronize me, Father.
Isn't it enough that you used me?
Used you?
Sending me to the duke
as a token of your support...
...making me a courier
of your esteemed respect...
- ...while you were plotting behind his back.
- Quiet, child.
Or was that your idea, Fenring?
That would be something
your perverse mind would suggest.
- Watch your tongue, girl.
- And what will you do if I don't?
Send me into the desert to die
like that poor boy and his mother?
No one sent them anywhere. They fled.
Despite the Baron's efforts...
...he assures me he did everything he could
to secure them from harm.
You were involved, Father.
I know you were.
Or at least you did nothing to prevent it.
Enough!
There will come a time, Daughter...
...when you will have to shed
this naivet of yours...
...and learn what it means
to rule an empire.
And when that time comes, Father...
...you may learn to regret it.
It's only another few kilometers,
that's all.
Hurry, we don't have much time.
The sun will soon be up full.
We'll have some shade in here.
If there are any Harkonnen patrols this far out,
they'll have a tough time spotting us.
Such a pity.
A pity that you had to get mixed up
in this business, Doctor.
I'm not mixed up in it, Baron.
I'm the Emperor's servant,
nothing more and nothing less.
So you did not lead them
to that warren of Fremen scum?
That was Idaho's idea.
- He had forged a friendship with them.
- Yes.
We know all about Idaho
and his efforts on the Duke's behalf.
A foolish, desperate gambit.
And where was that Fremen trash
when he needed them, eh?
So, what will you say when the Emperor
questions you about what happened here?
What's your impression, hmm?
The desert is
an indiscriminate executioner, Baron.
I suppose that Bene Gesserit whore...
...and her spawn have found that out,
haven't they?
Be sure he recalls his flimsy denials
when he's face to face...
...with death's sweet smile.
Muad'dib.
Tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
On Caladan we ruled by air and sea, Paul.
But here, on Arrakis,
you need desert power.
- It's calling to you.
- Tell me about the waters...
...tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
It'll be night soon. We'll move on.
Did you get any rest?
Some.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
Try not to slow us down as much tonight.
How is my sister?
I'm having dreams again.
Visions.
Even when I'm awake.
I've seen her, Mother, inside of you.
Even your father didn't know.
Why not?
There wasn't time.
What have you done to me?
- I gave birth to you.
- A freak.
- No, not a freak.
- Then what?
This place is changing me.
It's the spice.
It's in the air we breathe,
in the food we eat.
I can't escape it.
Drink it all.
The best place to conserve water
is in your body.
The stillsuit will do the rest.
If we stay on this dune
we'll reach those mountains a lot sooner.
Is that a good idea?
It's the most direct path.
You all right?
Yes.
Hold on.
That shouldn't have happened.
I was careless about these dunes.
We lost our paracompass.
Can you hear that?
It's a worm!
It must have heard the sand fall.
Run! Just run!
- I can't see it!
- Don't stop!
A thumper?
Someone called it away.
Did you smell it? The cinnamon smell.
The spice.
Everywhere...
...when the worm came.
There had to have been people
for this many plants to survive.
Fremen.
We have to find them.
Most intruders here
regret finding the Fremen.
Don't run, intruders. There is no escape.
I know you.
You're Stilgar...
...the Fremen who came to see my father
with Duncan Idaho.
That was a sloppy crossing you made
from the crash.
You called a worm.
You were watching us?
- All of that time?
- We didn't see you.
- You weren't meant to.
- We're wasting time here, Stil.
- This is the boy Liet told us to seek.
- How can you be sure?
- I say we take their water and move on.
- Be quiet, Jamis.
As you can hear, I have a problem to solve.
My people are cautious and pragmatic.
Good qualities in the desert.
Better sometimes to miss an opportunity
than invite disaster.
Your only value at the moment
is the water in your flesh.
You know the law, Stil.
Yes.
The law.
Tell them to stop hunting my son.
Tell them.
Leave off! Leave the boy alone!
Do you hear me?
Is this the way
you welcome friends of Liet?
Is it?
As leader of this tribe...
...I'm offering the Weirding woman
and her son sanctuary.
No Fremen anywhere will lay a hand on you
while you have my protection.
For how long?
Don't be a fool, woman.
You're fugitives from the Harkonnen.
Don't be fugitives from us as well.
Merciful God!
I've heard of the Weirding ways.
Imagine what a man could do with it.
No doubt we have much
to teach each other.
You can come down, boy!
Your mother has shown her worth.
He won't move unless I say so.
Discipline. Good.
He's here!
He is unharmed.
We are coming down.
Leave me alone.
Made a lot of noise climbing.
He has much to learn.
- Stilgar.
- Can you travel, Jamis?
He surprised me, that's all.
- Of course I can travel.
- Good.
We have now two with us
who are not trained.
In squad lines with flankers.
We have to make Cave of Ridges
before full sun.
Chani, you will be responsible for him.
My name is Paul.
Only until we give you a new one.
Follow me. Do exactly as I do.
Across there is home...
...Sietch Tabr.
We'll be there tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
That must be hundreds of kilometers
from here.
It will be a hard ride.
Sun will be up soon.
Patrols sometimes come this far.
We can't let them see us.
When you give us your stillsuits,
we will recover your water for you.
Here is some food.
Spice.
We don't have delicacies from the cities
like you are used to.
It's fine.
She's the one, isn't she?
The one you've seen in your dreams?
I can tell by the way you stare at her.
I don't know what it means.
Be careful, Paul.
We are new to these people
as they are to us.
Everything we say and do must be careful.
Predicting the future,
then plotting to make it so.
These are superstitious people.
If we are to survive, it will be best
to accommodate their legends.
I'm the steward of the sand.
I am a desert creature.
A desert creature.
Not finished yet!
Still have work to do!
The pre-spice mass.
I am a desert crea...
Spice blow.
Somewhere to the east.
A large field from the looks of it.
We have to send gatherers
before Harkonnen pirates come for it.
You harvest the spice?
For bribes to the Spacing Guild.
It's Liet's wish.
We pay them to keep our skies free
of their satellites...
...so that no one can know
what we are doing here.
You will learn.
Amtal!
I invoke amtal.
Jamis.
What is this?
His way of dealing with what happened
the other night.
That was an accident.
He bested me because there was
witch-force at Tuono basin.
Amtal! It's my right!
We must not interfere.
Jamis has called him out.
You're starting something here
you're going to regret.
- Stilgar.
- You must step back.
If you know what's good for you,
you will find an honorable way...
...to leave this thing alone.
Silence!
I invoke silence.
She's trying to put a spell on me.
If you try that again,
we know it's your witchcraft.
I won't be able to protect you
or the boy anymore.
Come. You can't stop this.
A crysknife, our ritual weapon.
Use it well.
May your blade chip and shatter.
I'm going to bathe this knife
with your blood.
First, you'll have to find my blood.
- Do you yield?
- Yield?
There is no yielding. It's to the death, boy!
- He's never had to kill.
- What?
Then he'd better learn.
Finish. Don't toy with him.
He's bested Jamis.
This didn't have to happen.
It is our way.
Your way?! Killing each other.
No man recognizes leadership
without the challenge of combat.
There is a legend among us...
...that a voice from the out-world
will come.
The Mahdi.
He will hold the key to our future.
It is said that a Bene Gesserit
will be his mother.
A Sayyadina.
Friend of God.
There are rumors about you and your son.
From the city. Liet.
You hope I am that one? That Paul is?
I hope...
...and I fear.
If it's true, your boy will have to
call me out one day...
...to challenge me
for the leadership of the tribe.
The huanui is prepared. It's time.
It's our way.
From water does all life begin.
The flesh belongs to the person...
...but his water belongs to the tribe.
I was a friend of Jamis.
When the hawk plane fell upon us...
...at Hole-in-the-Rock...
...it was Jamis who pulled me to safety.
I was a friend of Jamis.
He taught me...
...that when you kill...
...you pay for it.
Bila-Kayfa!
He sheds tears.
He gives water to the dead.
Jamis carried 33 liters of the tribe's water.
Counted and measured.
Combat water is entrusted to the winner.
Because you fight without stillsuit...
...you may regain the water
you lost fighting.
May you guard it for the tribe,
preserve it against loss...
...be generous with it in time of need.
May you pass it on in your time
for the good of the tribe.
Needs a naming now, Stil.
It's time.
What would you have us call you,
young Atreides?
By what name do you wish Fremen
to know you?
What is the name of that little mouse?
The one in the desert. The one that jumps.
Muad'dib.
Is that the name you wish?
Yes.
Muad'dib.
Wise in the ways of the desert.
Hiding from the sun. Traveling at night.
We call him the "Teacher of Boys".
Muad'dib.
Yeah, a fine choice.
So, from now on
you will be addressed as Muad'dib.
Wait for my signal.
Then you must do exactly as I do.
Your lives will depend on it.
There.
Get ready.
What is that?
The one who will come. Mahdi.
It's the gatherer Stilgar sent
to the spice blow.
Give her some time, Muad'dib.
Liet is dead.
- We found his remains at the spice blow.
- Doctor Kynes is dead?
Harkonnen treachery.
She loved her father very much.
It needs a new dew collector.
Tell me about the waters
of your homeland, Muad'dib.
We had rivers of it.
Great flowing veins of water.
From the snows of mountains...
...into lakes so wide
you couldn't see the other side.
Oceans of water.
Our home was on the coast.
Great waves would hurl themselves
against the cliffs.
They used to put me to sleep.
My father had a dream, Muad'dib.
A dream that one day...
...we could change this place...
...make it more like your homeland.
Windtrap.
Plenty of moisture this morning.
My father is at peace.
Muad'dib.
We have thousands of these caches.
Only a few of us know them all.
I know this place.
- No off-worlder has ever seen it.
- I have.
In my dreams.
This is the water we will use
to change the face of Arrakis.
As my father taught us...
...the voice from the out-world will come.
The Mahdi.
We will make a paradise of Arrakis.
And no man shall ever want
for water again.
Just as you said, Stil.
Harkonnen greed for spice
is the most reliable beacon in the universe.
- Reconnaissance team on the ground.
- Ground recon proceed to spice patch.
Anyone else hear that?
We didn't even have to damage
the thopter.
The men will fly it to our caves at Bight.
That was our last communication.
There is no mayday, no evidence of wreckage
when we went to investigate.
That's the third thopter this month!
The patch turned out to be mock spice.
- It was probably a plant to lure them there.
- Fremen scum!
We caught these last night,
a village near the rimwall...
...known to be desert sympathizers.
Mercy, Governor.
We are refugees.
- We need food.
- Liar!
Spies! That's what you are!
Spies for the Fremen scum!
Fremen scum
who raid my spice warehouses!
- Who destroy royal equipment!
- No. We are poor. We have no weapons.
He was trying to dispose of this
when we caught him.
Send words to the filth of the desert!
Tell them what you witness here!
Tell them this is what awaits them!
Mahdi!
Put that away, Feyd, and come here.
I want you to see this.
The latest love letter from your brother.
Mahdil
Appears to be enjoying himself.
The moron's appetite for killing
never ceases to amaze me.
By the time he's finished,
there won't be a population left to rule.
Cheer up, lovely boy.
I merely allow him to brutalize them,
to savage them, until you arrive...
...the handsome Feyd,
to rescue them from the beast, Rabban.
They will be ripe for you, lovely boy.
Feyd, the savior.
There will be cheering in the streets.
You can even give them
your brother's head as a gift, if you like.
And then you will squeeze,
like the grips of a vice...
...so our treasuries become fat
with the profit of spice.
No man recognizes leadership...
...without the challenge of combat.
It is the way.
Call him out!
What do you see...
...Muad'dib...
...when you go away like that?
Where is it you go?
Many places, Stil.
Many roads.
Many choices.
These choices...
...are good or bad?
It's hard to know sometimes.
Either they are good choices
or bad choices.
Aren't you ever afraid, Stil?
Of storms?
Of the future.
The future, Muad'dib, just is.
They're like ghosts! Everywhere!
Need immediate evacuation!
They just keep coming!
We are ready, Muad'dib.
Muad'dib, it's time. We must hurry.
He's waiting, Reverend Mother.
- Who else knows he's here?
- No one.
He made it clear on his arrival
that we should summon you and no other.
The other witches must leave.
As you wish.
This visit is as indiscreet
as it is unexpected.
Let's hope the Emperor's curiosity
isn't aroused.
The Emperor's suspicions
are easily moderated...
...by his dependence on our services.
As you are so fond of reminding us.
The navigators are concerned.
- Concerned?
- They are disturbed about the future.
There is a problem on the horizon.
What kind of problem?
They are troubled by a nexus
they can't fully explore...
...an intersection of events...
...a meeting of countless delicate decisions
beyond which lies a path...
...they cannot see.
And where is this nexus?
Planet Arrakis.
House Harkonnen controls Arrakis now.
The Atreides are dead.
It is not a matter of feuding royal houses.
We sense a higher order interfering.
A misstep could be catastrophic.
Then we understand one another.
Completely.
We'll do what we can.
I thought...
...I felt something.
The spice must flow.
The balance of power must be maintained.
Sayyadina?
I'm awake, Chani.
Has there been any
word, a courier perhaps?
No. The raids are
in the Haga basin.
They won't risk communication until
they are deep across the bled.
- Forgive me, Sayyadina.
- Was there something else?
No.
It's just your skin.
My skin?
We've heard the stories
about off-worlders,
the ones who come
from water planets.
Skin so moist it's like cream.
- Muad'dib's skin is like that.
- Paul?
Muad'dib is still a boy.
I mean, he still has the glow of youth.
Yes.
I say my prayers for his safe return.
We both do, Chani.
The smugglers transport our spice tribute
to the cursed Spacing Guild.
The Emperor never knows.
But bribes are dangerous, Stil.
They have a way of getting larger.
The safe way is the slow way, Muad'dib.
Bribes keep the skies of our sietches clear.
Bribes buy us time.
Something wrong, Muad'dib?
I thought I saw someone I knew.
I'll call them in.
Tell them to hold the smugglers' departure.
No, Stil.
Let them go.
I must have been mistaken.
Gurney.
My father's patience is wearing thin.
These troubles on Arrakis
are proving difficult to manage...
...and our time is running short.
I want you to make arrangements
for a trip to Giedi Prime.
Milady?
The Baron's nephew
is having a birthday celebration.
The Emperor ought to be represented,
don't you think?
I'm in the mood for a party.
Besides, it's time to shed
some of this naivet.
She is not going!
I'm not going to allow that headstrong,
meddlesome child loose in Babylon.
My God, what a catastrophe
that would be.
The eldest daughter of the Imperial
House ensnared by the likes of Harkonnen
and his dreadful progeny.
Yes, catastrophe indeed.
But perhaps the seducer
could be seduced.
The more we know of the Baron's schemes,
the more we are prepared for the endgame.
Our operatives on Giedi
Prime have limited access.
Your daughter, on the other hand...
has proved quite adept at
intelligence gathering.
Gently chaperoned, I should think
she'd prove quite useful...
once again.
You've heard the voices
from your sietches.
They say the Mahdi has come.
But you...
...the naibs of your tribes
are still cautious. You resist.
But I am offering you the future.
The future as Liet saw it.
- How do you know what Liet saw?
- Because I've seen it.
Here.
And here.
And once we rid Arrakis
of the vile Harkonnen...
...we can complete his dream.
I promise this.
Arrakis will become the paradise
Liet imagined.
You'll never rid Arrakis
with guerrilla raids, boy.
It will take all-out war.
That's why I'm asking you
for hundreds of your best young men.
I want to give them the Weirding way...
...so they can come back to you
and train hundreds more.
So those hundreds
can train hundreds more.
And then hundreds will become thousands!
The Fedaykin.
A force to rival the dreaded Sardaukar.
A force to terrify the Emperor himself!
My father once told me...
...that here on Arrakis...
...one needed desert power to rule.
You are desert power...
...and nothing can stop you...
...if you believe.
So you are the one.
Jessica of the Weirding,
our Reverend Mother Ramallo.
Mapes said you were beautiful.
She also said she pitied you.
I need no one's pity.
That remains to be seen.
There is much talk of you in the sietches.
I hear the people speaking of the Mahdi.
I hear them shout the name Muad'dib.
He is a natural leader like his father.
The men admire his courage.
It will take more than courage
to survive what's coming.
The boy...
...he knows what it is
that's happening here?
He is aware.
You've exploited our legends well.
We had to survive.
And you may...
...for a while.
But remember this:
the very legend which protects you...
...can also destroy you.
- How are you feeling?
- Well.
Tired sometimes.
Healthy.
And growing fast.
I saw the one
they call the Reverend Mother.
Yes. She came from the southern sietch.
- Why?
- To see me.
To see you.
She's Bene Gesserit.
One of our missionaries.
Convenient.
Stilgar says you've learned much.
He's tougher than Hawat ever was.
Chani is happy to see you, I noticed.
Why didn't you marry him, Mother?
Because I loved him.
As long as your father
remained unmarried...
...some of the great houses could still hope
for an alliance through marriage.
We both knew what that meant.
- There were no illusions.
- You would have allowed it?
I would have encouraged it.
Politics.
Yes.
While I was on the hajra...
...I had dreams about this garden.
Except it wasn't here,
it was somewhere else.
Was I there?
Yes.
And there were children...
...playing, very happy.
A wonderful dream.
Do you think it's possible
to love someone enough...
...you'd be willing to give that person up?
I think...
...there are times when it's necessary
to share the one you love...
...with things greater than both of you.
Everything is connected,
one thing to another.
The living and the dead,
the animate and the inanimate.
A system.
All parts functioning to serve the whole.
Smell the air, Muad'dib.
Cinnamon.
The pre-spice mass is below us.
Maybe 100 feet or more, but ripe.
The Maker has left her nest long ago.
Her children have joined together
for survival.
They have grown.
They are losing water now.
It will mix with their waste.
If enough has accumulated...
...a giant bubble of foam
will heave up with tremendous force.
A spice blow.
Trading places with the sands above.
The sun and heat will dry it out and...
...soon...
- Spice.
- Treasure of the universe.
The worm...
...is the spice.
So now you know.
Many of the little makers
will die in the blow.
The rest will swim off
to become Shai-Hulud, the Great Worm.
We may capture a few.
Keep them stunted for Water of Life.
That's enough for now.
When religion and politics
ride in the same cart...
...the whirlwind follows.
You are the Kwisatz Haderach, boy.
The one who can be many places at once.
You are the whirlwind.
It's almost night, Muad'dib.
Time to return to the sietch.
You've been dreaming.
Too impatient, Farok.
You moved too soon.
Try again.
Watch his posture.
Even the slightest change in his breathing
gives you advantage.
Better, Farok. You'll have it soon.
I am Otheym.
These are my brothers
from Sietch Gara Kulan.
We've come to find the one
who calls himself Muad'dib.
You're a long way from your tribe, Otheym.
We've come to join your crusade.
We want to learn the Weirding Way.
We want to become Fedaykin.
- You have the blessing of your naib?
- We do.
- We could fight as Muad'dib.
- I believe you.
Let their waters join with ours.
I must congratulate you
on the perfection of your heir, Baron.
He faces his 100th slave gladiator
in the arena this afternoon.
He appears ready.
Well then,
perhaps we might take this opportunity...
...to conduct our conversations.
There is much to discuss.
Indeed.
If that meets with your approval, Milady.
I am quite entertained here.
Fine.
By your leave, then.
What other house would have
been willing to humiliate itself
so the Emperor could rid
himself of a troublesome duke?
He's been asking
himself that very question.
Are you suggesting that the Emperor
contemplates a move against me?
Speculation is not a
worthy science, Baron.
Better we spend our energy
on what's most important.
The spice must flow.
I must say I've always found
Harkonnen architecture rather...
curious.
Harkonnen patrols have taken more risks...
...coming deeper into the southern regions
than ever before.
Sooner or later our bribes to the Guild
won't be enough to protect us.
Then it's agreed.
We move with the next moons.
When the Harkonnen find this place...
...there must be nothing left
but the wind howling through the rocks.
There is no turning back now.
Subdue the Maker.
The Maker is dead.
The Water of Life.
May Shai-Hulud have mercy on both of us.
When night falls again,
we have to leave this sietch...
...that has sheltered us for so long.
We must go south into the deep desert...
...where the demon Harkonnen
will not pursue us.
But our Reverend Mother
will not survive another hajra.
So that we don't have to make the journey
without her strength and guidance...
...Sayyadina Jessica has consented
to undergo the rites at this time.
This is dangerous and Jessica may fail.
So that we don't lose all, Chani...
...daughter of Liet,
will be consecrated as Sayyadina...
...Friend of God.
I consecrate the daughter of Liet...
...in the Sayyadina.
Here is the Water of Life,
the water that will free your soul.
If you are our Reverend Mother,
the universe will open to you.
Let Shai-Hulud judge now.
You must drink it now.
What's happening to her?
The water is poisoned until she changes it.
This must take its course.
Mother? Mother?
You cannot go there.
That is the place we cannot look.
The place only
the Kwisatz Haderach may go.
You must turn away, Jessica,
or it will drive you mad.
Don't be afraid. I have much to show you.
Here is my life, Jessica of the Weirding,
...and the lives that have come before.
They are yours now.
You are pregnant.
You should have told us.
Holy Mothers!
What have we done?
This changes you both.
Your daughter is in danger.
Take her into your arms.
She must see all that we see.
That is the only way you can save her.
Change the waters, Jessica.
You must change them now.
The plan was perfect in its simplicity
and viciousness.
Of course it was.
You helped your uncle design it,
didn't you?
Duke Leto thought
he was gaining control of Arrakis...
...but he was only being fattened up
for sacrifice.
The kill, Feyd. Tell me about the kill.
Swift and merciless.
The Atreides never had a chance.
The Sardaukar had the palace sealed
within hours.
The Sardaukar.
I sent the final communiqu
to your father myself.
Mother?
Yes?
Mother Ramallo is gone.
But she remains.
You have changed the waters.
Now we know you cannot be false.
Paul?
The Reverend Mother
has changed the Water of Life.
It's now safe for us to drink!
The son and his mother,
the duke's concubine and her son...
...what did you do with them?
Lost in the storm, devoured by the desert.
You found their bodies
and disposed of them?
Never found them.
You never found the bodies?
You're trembling.
I'm afraid.
Of what?
Of you.
You make me see things.
What do you see?
I see us together.
There is a great storm.
I have a child in my arms.
Our child, Muad'dib.
It's not a dream.
I know you, Chani.
I've always known you.
We've sat upon a rock above the sands
and I've eased your fears.
We've caressed
in the darkness of the sietch.
We've grown old together.
History will say that the Fremen
were about to find their messiah.
That Paul Atreides would find his revenge...
...and the world, as we knew it,
would change forever.
The saga of Dune is far
from over.