1
00:00:49,299 --> 00:00:53,093
A beginning is
a very delicate time.

2
00:00:54,679 --> 00:00:58,766
Know then, that
it is the year 10191.

3
00:01:00,018 --> 00:01:01,393
The Known Universe is

4
00:01:01,478 --> 00:01:04,605
ruled by the
Padisha Emperor Shaddam IV,

5
00:01:05,440 --> 00:01:06,982
my father.

6
00:01:08,276 --> 00:01:11,570
In this time, the most precious
substance in the Universe

7
00:01:11,654 --> 00:01:13,655
is the spice melange.

8
00:01:14,824 --> 00:01:16,992
The spice extends life.

9
00:01:18,453 --> 00:01:21,872
The spice expands
consciousness.

10
00:01:23,416 --> 00:01:26,460
The spice is vital
to space travel.

11
00:01:27,212 --> 00:01:29,671
The Spacing Guild
and its navigators,

12
00:01:29,756 --> 00:01:33,967
who the spice has
mutated over 4,000 years,

13
00:01:34,219 --> 00:01:36,762
use the orange spice gas,

14
00:01:37,097 --> 00:01:40,349
which gives them
the ability to fold space.

15
00:01:41,392 --> 00:01:42,643
That is,

16
00:01:42,727 --> 00:01:47,189
travel to any part of
the Universe without moving.

17
00:01:48,024 --> 00:01:51,318
Oh, yes.
I forgot to tell you.

18
00:01:52,237 --> 00:01:54,154
The spice exists

19
00:01:54,239 --> 00:01:57,699
on only one planet
in the entire Universe.

20
00:01:58,535 --> 00:02:02,371
A desolate, dry planet
with vast deserts.

21
00:02:03,623 --> 00:02:06,291
Hidden away within the rocks
of these deserts

22
00:02:06,376 --> 00:02:08,877
are a people
known as the Fremen,

23
00:02:09,754 --> 00:02:12,631
who have long held
a prophecy,

24
00:02:12,715 --> 00:02:14,550
that a man would come,

25
00:02:14,926 --> 00:02:19,555
a messiah, who would
lead them to true freedom.

26
00:02:21,516 --> 00:02:24,393
The planet is Arrakis.

27
00:02:25,145 --> 00:02:28,313
Also known as Dune.

28
00:03:55,443 --> 00:03:58,070
A secret report
within the Guild.

29
00:03:59,322 --> 00:04:02,074
Four planets have
come to our attention

30
00:04:02,158 --> 00:04:05,744
regarding a plot which could
jeopardize spice production.

31
00:04:06,663 --> 00:04:09,873
Planet Arrakis,
source of the Spice.

32
00:04:10,750 --> 00:04:14,044
Planet Caladan,
home of House Atreides.

33
00:04:15,046 --> 00:04:18,674
Planet Giedi Prime,
home of House Harkonnen.

34
00:04:19,634 --> 00:04:21,176
Planet Kaitain,

35
00:04:21,469 --> 00:04:24,304
home of the Emperor of
the Known Universe.

36
00:04:26,015 --> 00:04:29,268
Send a third-stage
Guild Navigator to Kaitain

37
00:04:29,352 --> 00:04:32,271
to demand details
from the Emperor.

38
00:04:32,981 --> 00:04:35,190
The spice must flow.

39
00:05:21,904 --> 00:05:22,863
Father?

40
00:05:22,947 --> 00:05:24,865
Irulan, you must leave.

41
00:05:46,429 --> 00:05:50,098
A third-stage Guild Navigator
will be here within minutes.

42
00:05:50,558 --> 00:05:52,642
We felt his presence.

43
00:05:53,186 --> 00:05:55,228
I shall want telepathy
during his visit

44
00:05:55,313 --> 00:05:57,314
and a report
when we're finished.

45
00:05:57,398 --> 00:06:00,192
I am your Truthsayer,
my lord.

46
00:06:01,361 --> 00:06:02,778
He's here, my lord.

47
00:06:31,140 --> 00:06:33,850
The Bene Gesserit witch
must leave.

48
00:06:35,186 --> 00:06:36,478
Leave us.

49
00:06:38,314 --> 00:06:39,815
Yes, my lord.

50
00:06:51,494 --> 00:06:52,994
We are alone.

51
00:07:37,957 --> 00:07:41,209
We have just
folded space from lx.

52
00:07:41,586 --> 00:07:42,711
Yes?

53
00:07:44,380 --> 00:07:46,173
How was your journey?

54
00:07:46,257 --> 00:07:48,592
Many machines on lx.

55
00:07:49,886 --> 00:07:51,720
New machines.

56
00:07:52,054 --> 00:07:53,138
Oh?

57
00:07:53,931 --> 00:07:54,973
Yes.

58
00:07:55,558 --> 00:07:58,018
Better than those
on Richese.

59
00:08:00,062 --> 00:08:02,481
You are transparent.

60
00:08:02,690 --> 00:08:05,775
I see many things.

61
00:08:06,527 --> 00:08:10,238
I see plans within plans.

62
00:08:10,865 --> 00:08:13,909
I see two great houses,

63
00:08:14,410 --> 00:08:18,997
House Atreides,
House Harkonnen feuding.

64
00:08:19,457 --> 00:08:22,834
I see you behind it.

65
00:08:23,085 --> 00:08:24,169
Yes.

66
00:08:24,253 --> 00:08:27,422
You must share with us.

67
00:08:29,091 --> 00:08:31,593
The Atreides House is
building a secret army

68
00:08:31,677 --> 00:08:33,512
using a technique
unknown to us.

69
00:08:33,596 --> 00:08:35,972
A technique
involving sound.

70
00:08:36,599 --> 00:08:39,351
The Duke is becoming
more popular in the Landsraad.

71
00:08:39,435 --> 00:08:41,394
He could threaten me.

72
00:08:41,604 --> 00:08:43,104
I have ordered
House Atreides

73
00:08:43,189 --> 00:08:45,524
to occupy Arrakis
to mine the spice,

74
00:08:45,608 --> 00:08:48,777
thus replacing their enemies,
the Harkonnens.

75
00:08:48,861 --> 00:08:50,362
House Atreides
will not refuse

76
00:08:50,446 --> 00:08:53,406
because of the tremendous power
they think they will gain.

77
00:08:53,491 --> 00:08:55,158
Then, at an appointed time,

78
00:08:55,243 --> 00:08:58,286
Baron Harkonnen
will return to Arrakis

79
00:08:58,371 --> 00:09:01,039
and launch a sneak attack
on House Atreides.

80
00:09:01,123 --> 00:09:02,707
I have promised the baron

81
00:09:02,792 --> 00:09:05,961
five legions of
my Sardaukar terror troops.

82
00:09:06,754 --> 00:09:10,632
So the Harkonnens will
rid you of House Atreides.

83
00:09:11,259 --> 00:09:12,300
Yes.

84
00:09:13,135 --> 00:09:14,928
One small point.

85
00:09:15,763 --> 00:09:17,764
Here it comes.

86
00:09:18,266 --> 00:09:21,268
We, ourselves,
foresee a slight problem

87
00:09:21,352 --> 00:09:23,937
within House Atreides.

88
00:09:24,105 --> 00:09:28,149
Paul. Paul Atreides.

89
00:09:28,693 --> 00:09:32,237
You mean, of course, Duke
Leto Atreides, his father?

90
00:09:32,321 --> 00:09:35,991
I mean Paul Atreides.

91
00:09:36,075 --> 00:09:39,035
We want him killed.

92
00:09:40,663 --> 00:09:43,248
I did not say this.

93
00:09:43,541 --> 00:09:46,209
I am not here.

94
00:09:46,502 --> 00:09:48,003
I understand.

95
00:10:18,242 --> 00:10:22,203
Why would they want
the Duke's son killed?

96
00:10:26,417 --> 00:10:29,544
We must have
a look at Paul Atreides.

97
00:10:30,338 --> 00:10:31,713
On Caladan.

98
00:10:46,854 --> 00:10:49,314
The powerful
Bene Gesserit sisterhoodh

99
00:10:49,398 --> 00:10:50,815
for 90 generations,

100
00:10:50,900 --> 00:10:52,859
has been manipulating
bloodlines

101
00:10:52,943 --> 00:10:55,111
to produce
the Kwisatz Haderach.

102
00:10:55,196 --> 00:10:56,780
A super being.

103
00:10:56,864 --> 00:10:59,491
On Caladan, Jessicah

104
00:10:59,575 --> 00:11:00,992
a member of the sisterhood

105
00:11:01,077 --> 00:11:04,329
and the bound concubine of
Duke Leto Atreides

106
00:11:04,413 --> 00:11:07,374
had been ordered to
bear only daughters.

107
00:11:07,708 --> 00:11:09,626
Because of her love
for the Duke,

108
00:11:09,710 --> 00:11:13,213
she disobeyed
and gave birth to a son.

109
00:11:14,256 --> 00:11:17,258
Paul. Paul Atreides.

110
00:11:25,935 --> 00:11:29,145
Here we are now. Caladan.

111
00:11:29,980 --> 00:11:32,148
And 19 light-years beyond.

112
00:11:32,650 --> 00:11:34,859
Beyond Bene Tleilax.

113
00:11:34,985 --> 00:11:37,028
The training planet
of the Mentats,

114
00:11:37,113 --> 00:11:38,655
the human computers.

115
00:11:38,739 --> 00:11:41,783
Know a Mentat
by his red-stained lips.

116
00:11:42,201 --> 00:11:44,452
There, Arrakis.

117
00:11:44,537 --> 00:11:45,870
Spice Mining.

118
00:11:46,706 --> 00:11:48,832
Carryalls lower
the harvester to the sand,

119
00:11:48,916 --> 00:11:51,626
and lift it off to safety
when a worm attacks.

120
00:11:51,711 --> 00:11:54,546
Worms attack
all rhythmic vibrations.

121
00:11:55,923 --> 00:12:00,009
Weather. See storms'.
No Precipitation.

122
00:12:01,053 --> 00:12:03,930
Never one drop of rain
on Arrakis.

123
00:12:06,016 --> 00:12:09,477
And the Harkonnens are near.
There.

124
00:12:09,729 --> 00:12:12,021
Giedi Prime
and the Baron Harkonnen.

125
00:12:12,314 --> 00:12:13,732
The enemy.

126
00:12:13,816 --> 00:12:16,860
The Baron Harkonnen has sworn
to destroy House Atreides,

127
00:12:16,944 --> 00:12:19,612
and steal the ducal
signet ring for himself.

128
00:12:38,007 --> 00:12:41,342
I know, Thufir, I'm sitting
with my back to the door.

129
00:12:42,887 --> 00:12:46,639
I heard you, Doctor Yueh,

130
00:12:47,016 --> 00:12:48,767
and Gurney
coming down the hall.

131
00:12:48,851 --> 00:12:50,351
Those sounds

132
00:12:51,020 --> 00:12:52,729
could be imitated!

133
00:12:54,940 --> 00:12:56,649
I'd know the difference.

134
00:12:56,942 --> 00:12:59,944
Yes. Perhaps he would at that.

135
00:13:02,865 --> 00:13:05,074
My father sent you
to test me.

136
00:13:05,284 --> 00:13:06,618
Music, then?

137
00:13:06,702 --> 00:13:08,119
No music.

138
00:13:08,454 --> 00:13:10,914
I'm packing this
for the crossing.

139
00:13:11,832 --> 00:13:12,832
Shield practice.

140
00:13:12,917 --> 00:13:13,958
Shield practice?

141
00:13:14,043 --> 00:13:16,544
Gurney, we had
practice this morning.

142
00:13:16,629 --> 00:13:17,670
I'm not in the mood.

143
00:13:17,755 --> 00:13:19,380
Not in the mood?

144
00:13:19,548 --> 00:13:22,008
Mood's a thing for
cattle and love play.

145
00:13:22,092 --> 00:13:23,134
Not fighting!

146
00:13:23,219 --> 00:13:24,719
I'm sorry, Gurney.

147
00:13:25,262 --> 00:13:26,888
Not sorry enough.

148
00:13:37,733 --> 00:13:39,359
What's wrong with Gurney?

149
00:13:39,443 --> 00:13:40,902
He's not faking this.

150
00:13:40,986 --> 00:13:44,572
Now, guard yourself for true!

151
00:14:04,134 --> 00:14:05,593
Is this what you seek?

152
00:14:06,178 --> 00:14:07,637
Good.

153
00:14:07,847 --> 00:14:11,099
The slow blade
penetrates the shield.

154
00:14:11,267 --> 00:14:14,352
But, uh, look down.

155
00:14:16,689 --> 00:14:19,399
We'd have joined
each other in death.

156
00:14:20,442 --> 00:14:23,361
You did seem finally
to get in the mood.

157
00:14:30,870 --> 00:14:33,454
Would you really
have drawn my blood?

158
00:14:33,622 --> 00:14:36,207
If you'd have fought
one whit below your abilities,

159
00:14:36,292 --> 00:14:39,210
I'd have given you
a good scar to remind you.

160
00:14:43,257 --> 00:14:45,133
Things have been
so serious here lately.

161
00:14:45,217 --> 00:14:47,468
Soon we'll leave for Arrakis.

162
00:14:48,345 --> 00:14:49,971
Arrakis is real.

163
00:14:50,848 --> 00:14:53,474
The Harkonnens are real.

164
00:14:55,102 --> 00:14:56,519
Doctor Yueh.

165
00:14:56,645 --> 00:14:59,981
Do you have any information
on the worms of Arrakis?

166
00:15:00,774 --> 00:15:03,776
I've obtained a filmbook
of a small specimen.

167
00:15:04,320 --> 00:15:06,654
Only 125 meters long.

168
00:15:07,698 --> 00:15:08,948
Only?

169
00:15:09,033 --> 00:15:11,075
There have been documented
sightings of worms

170
00:15:11,160 --> 00:15:15,330
as large as 450 meters
in the deep desert.

171
00:15:16,457 --> 00:15:19,334
That's far from where
we'll be in Arrakeen.

172
00:15:20,461 --> 00:15:22,629
The desert belt
and the south polar region

173
00:15:22,713 --> 00:15:24,505
are marked forbidden.

174
00:15:24,840 --> 00:15:26,758
How do the Fremen
survive there?

175
00:15:26,842 --> 00:15:28,968
We don't know much
about the Fremen.

176
00:15:29,094 --> 00:15:32,263
They live in the deep desert,
some of them in the cities.

177
00:15:32,473 --> 00:15:34,599
They have
blue-within-blue eyes.

178
00:15:34,683 --> 00:15:36,309
The eyes.

179
00:15:36,852 --> 00:15:38,227
Yes.

180
00:15:38,646 --> 00:15:41,606
Saturation of the blood
by the spice melange.

181
00:15:42,441 --> 00:15:44,484
Could the spice
affect us in other ways?

182
00:15:44,568 --> 00:15:46,819
Many dangers
exist on Arrakis.

183
00:15:46,904 --> 00:15:47,904
For one,

184
00:15:48,113 --> 00:15:49,906
the Harkonnens would not have

185
00:15:49,990 --> 00:15:53,576
given up their CHOAM Company
contract so easily.

186
00:15:55,204 --> 00:15:57,747
The Harkonnens are
our enemies, yes.

187
00:15:58,874 --> 00:16:01,709
But behind them,
I suspect, is the Emperor.

188
00:16:02,878 --> 00:16:05,296
You'll make
a formidable duke.

189
00:16:10,427 --> 00:16:11,928
Now, remember,

190
00:16:12,846 --> 00:16:15,848
the first step
in avoiding a trap

191
00:16:16,350 --> 00:16:18,309
is knowing
of its existence.

192
00:16:18,394 --> 00:16:21,521
I know,
but if it is a trap

193
00:16:21,605 --> 00:16:22,814
then why are we going?

194
00:16:22,898 --> 00:16:24,899
We have our new army.

195
00:16:25,484 --> 00:16:26,901
Doctor Yueh,

196
00:16:27,319 --> 00:16:29,779
put the weirding module
on him.

197
00:16:34,410 --> 00:16:35,743
Well.

198
00:16:54,013 --> 00:16:55,596
Clear and lock the room!

199
00:16:55,681 --> 00:16:57,974
Detachment, stand down.

200
00:17:06,692 --> 00:17:08,443
Activate a fighter.

201
00:17:27,713 --> 00:17:30,423
Make the range two meters.

202
00:18:17,513 --> 00:18:19,472
Precise control.

203
00:18:49,378 --> 00:18:50,628
Duncan!

204
00:18:52,047 --> 00:18:55,550
Paul, I was just on my way
to say goodbye to you.

205
00:18:56,760 --> 00:18:58,845
I have to go on ahead,
alone,

206
00:18:58,929 --> 00:19:00,388
I won't be seeing you
for a while.

207
00:19:00,472 --> 00:19:02,765
I wish you were
coming with us. Why?

208
00:19:02,850 --> 00:19:04,559
It's something
for your father.

209
00:19:04,643 --> 00:19:06,644
He wants to talk to you.

210
00:19:07,187 --> 00:19:09,730
I'll see you on Arrakis.

211
00:19:11,400 --> 00:19:13,359
May the hand of God
be with you.

212
00:19:13,443 --> 00:19:16,320
May the hand of God
be with us all, Duncan.

213
00:19:32,379 --> 00:19:33,588
Father.

214
00:19:33,755 --> 00:19:36,048
Thank you
for joining me, Paul.

215
00:19:36,717 --> 00:19:40,136
Thufir Hawat has served House
Atreides three generations.

216
00:19:41,597 --> 00:19:45,141
He swears you are the finest
student he has ever taught.

217
00:19:46,727 --> 00:19:49,520
Yueh, Gurney, and Duncan
say the same.

218
00:19:52,274 --> 00:19:53,900
Makes me feel very proud.

219
00:19:53,984 --> 00:19:56,235
I want you
to be proud of me.

220
00:20:08,415 --> 00:20:10,124
I'll miss the sea.

221
00:20:12,753 --> 00:20:15,254
But a person
needs new experiences.

222
00:20:16,423 --> 00:20:18,799
They jar something
deep inside

223
00:20:20,010 --> 00:20:21,844
allowing him to grow.

224
00:20:23,889 --> 00:20:25,556
Without change,

225
00:20:27,184 --> 00:20:30,228
something sleeps
inside us,

226
00:20:32,272 --> 00:20:34,482
and seldom awakens.

227
00:20:38,779 --> 00:20:41,280
The sleeper must awaken.

228
00:21:06,306 --> 00:21:09,934
Arrakis, Dune.

229
00:21:11,019 --> 00:21:13,062
Desert Planet.

230
00:21:16,692 --> 00:21:18,526
I will kill you.

231
00:21:20,320 --> 00:21:22,738
The second moon.

232
00:21:31,039 --> 00:21:33,040
Tell me of your
home world, Usul.

233
00:21:45,554 --> 00:21:47,847
I know she has
come to test him.

234
00:21:48,015 --> 00:21:51,726
No man has ever been
tested with the box.

235
00:21:52,644 --> 00:21:55,688
Tonight, I may lose my son.

236
00:22:20,422 --> 00:22:24,258
Jessica, you were told to bear
only daughters to the Atreides.

237
00:22:24,760 --> 00:22:25,801
Jessica!

238
00:22:25,886 --> 00:22:27,887
It meant so much to him.

239
00:22:28,263 --> 00:22:31,599
You thought only of
a Duke's desire for a son?

240
00:22:32,601 --> 00:22:34,477
Desires don't come
into this.

241
00:22:34,728 --> 00:22:36,187
An Atreides daughter

242
00:22:36,271 --> 00:22:38,272
could have been wed
to a Harkonnen heir

243
00:22:38,357 --> 00:22:40,358
and sealed the breach.

244
00:22:40,609 --> 00:22:43,903
We may lose
both bloodlines now.

245
00:22:45,530 --> 00:22:48,449
I vowed never to
regret my decision.

246
00:22:50,869 --> 00:22:53,120
I'll pay for
all my own mistakes.

247
00:22:53,246 --> 00:22:55,956
And your son
will pay with you.

248
00:22:57,334 --> 00:23:00,086
Arrakis, Dune,

249
00:23:01,129 --> 00:23:03,130
Desert Planet.

250
00:23:04,049 --> 00:23:07,968
Moving.

251
00:23:29,658 --> 00:23:31,826
We'll salvage what we can.

252
00:23:32,327 --> 00:23:34,954
But I can tell you,
dear God,

253
00:23:35,622 --> 00:23:38,290
for the father, nothing.

254
00:23:38,500 --> 00:23:40,501
For the father, nothing?

255
00:23:40,752 --> 00:23:44,213
Did you really think you could
bear the Kwisatz Haderach?

256
00:23:44,297 --> 00:23:46,715
The Universe's super being?

257
00:23:46,883 --> 00:23:49,510
How dare you!

258
00:23:50,345 --> 00:23:52,471
My greatest student.

259
00:23:52,889 --> 00:23:56,517
And my greatest
disappointment.

260
00:24:00,021 --> 00:24:02,565
He's awake.
He's listening to us.

261
00:24:03,692 --> 00:24:06,694
Good! Ready yourself,
young Paul Atreides.

262
00:24:06,778 --> 00:24:08,612
I want to see you
in your mother's chambers

263
00:24:08,697 --> 00:24:10,364
in one-quarter
of an hour.

264
00:24:13,660 --> 00:24:14,785
Paul.

265
00:24:16,079 --> 00:24:18,080
This is very important.

266
00:24:22,878 --> 00:24:25,671
- Kwisatz Haderach?
- The super being?

267
00:24:26,882 --> 00:24:28,883
For the father, nothing?

268
00:24:43,231 --> 00:24:44,356
Vas.

269
00:25:00,081 --> 00:25:03,167
This is the Reverend Mother
Gaius Helen Mohiam.

270
00:25:04,544 --> 00:25:07,087
She's going
to observe you.

271
00:25:10,592 --> 00:25:11,842
Please.

272
00:25:11,927 --> 00:25:13,219
Jessica,

273
00:25:14,262 --> 00:25:16,055
you know it must be done.

274
00:25:16,139 --> 00:25:17,848
Your Reverence.

275
00:25:18,350 --> 00:25:20,392
What does she fear?

276
00:25:21,436 --> 00:25:22,686
What about my father?

277
00:25:22,771 --> 00:25:23,854
Paul,

278
00:25:25,106 --> 00:25:28,776
listen to the Reverend Mother
and do what she tells you.

279
00:25:37,410 --> 00:25:39,787
Now, you,

280
00:25:41,623 --> 00:25:42,998
come here.

281
00:25:44,125 --> 00:25:46,293
She's using the Voice.

282
00:25:47,003 --> 00:25:48,045
No.

283
00:25:48,129 --> 00:25:50,130
Some strength there.

284
00:25:50,590 --> 00:25:51,966
Surprising.

285
00:25:52,759 --> 00:25:55,177
Come here!

286
00:25:55,804 --> 00:25:57,513
Here.

287
00:25:57,806 --> 00:26:00,975
Come here.

288
00:26:13,780 --> 00:26:15,364
Do you see this?

289
00:26:17,826 --> 00:26:20,411
Put your right hand
in the box.

290
00:26:21,580 --> 00:26:22,871
What's in the box?

291
00:26:22,956 --> 00:26:24,123
Pain.

292
00:26:24,207 --> 00:26:25,416
Stop.

293
00:26:26,751 --> 00:26:29,044
Put your hand in the box.

294
00:26:34,634 --> 00:26:37,344
I hold at your neck
the gom jabbar.

295
00:26:37,429 --> 00:26:40,764
This one kills
only animals.

296
00:26:42,017 --> 00:26:44,226
Are you suggesting
the Duke's son is an animal?

297
00:26:44,311 --> 00:26:47,855
Let us say, I suggest
you may be human.

298
00:26:48,356 --> 00:26:52,109
Your awareness may be powerful
enough to control your instincts.

299
00:26:52,193 --> 00:26:53,986
Your instinct will be

300
00:26:54,070 --> 00:26:56,447
to remove your hand
from the box.

301
00:26:57,073 --> 00:26:58,532
If you do so,

302
00:26:59,951 --> 00:27:01,201
you die.

303
00:27:04,414 --> 00:27:06,123
You will feel

304
00:27:08,043 --> 00:27:09,793
an itching

305
00:27:12,505 --> 00:27:13,714
there.

306
00:27:14,716 --> 00:27:19,511
Now, the itching
becomes burning.

307
00:27:20,889 --> 00:27:24,141
Heat upon heat upon heat.

308
00:27:24,225 --> 00:27:25,309
It burns.

309
00:27:25,393 --> 00:27:27,144
Silence! Silence!

310
00:27:27,228 --> 00:27:30,564
- I must not fear.
- Fear is the mind killer.

311
00:27:30,982 --> 00:27:34,276
Fear is the little death that
brings total obliteration.

312
00:27:34,527 --> 00:27:37,196
I will face my fear.
I will permit it to pass

313
00:27:37,280 --> 00:27:40,282
over me and through me.
I must not fear.

314
00:27:40,367 --> 00:27:41,825
You feel
the flesh crisping.

315
00:27:41,910 --> 00:27:43,285
Fear is the mind killer.

316
00:27:43,370 --> 00:27:46,705
Fear is the little death that
brings total obliteration.

317
00:27:46,790 --> 00:27:47,831
I will face my fear.

318
00:27:47,916 --> 00:27:50,501
Flesh dropping off.

319
00:27:51,461 --> 00:27:55,214
Fear is the little death.

320
00:27:55,298 --> 00:27:57,132
I must not fear.

321
00:27:57,425 --> 00:28:01,345
Fear is the little death.
I'm...

322
00:28:02,430 --> 00:28:03,472
The pain!

323
00:28:03,556 --> 00:28:05,391
No! Enough!

324
00:28:08,770 --> 00:28:10,270
Kull wahad!

325
00:28:11,439 --> 00:28:14,108
No woman child
ever withstood that much.

326
00:28:17,445 --> 00:28:22,241
Take your hand out of the box
and look at it, young human.

327
00:28:24,703 --> 00:28:26,036
Do it!

328
00:28:32,419 --> 00:28:34,420
Pain by nerve induction.

329
00:28:34,504 --> 00:28:36,380
A human can resist any pain.

330
00:28:36,464 --> 00:28:39,758
Our test is
crisis and observation.

331
00:28:39,843 --> 00:28:41,552
I see the truth of it.

332
00:28:41,636 --> 00:28:43,512
Could he be the one?

333
00:28:44,097 --> 00:28:45,347
Maybe.

334
00:28:46,141 --> 00:28:48,475
But will he be ours
to control?

335
00:28:50,854 --> 00:28:52,896
Tell me of your
home world, Usul.

336
00:28:56,651 --> 00:28:59,820
Do you know of
the Water of Life?

337
00:29:00,447 --> 00:29:03,407
The bile from the newborn
worms of Arrakis?

338
00:29:03,491 --> 00:29:04,491
I have heard of it.

339
00:29:04,576 --> 00:29:06,410
It is very dangerous.

340
00:29:06,703 --> 00:29:09,913
The Bene Gesserit sisterhood
use it to see within.

341
00:29:11,624 --> 00:29:13,208
There is a place

342
00:29:14,461 --> 00:29:16,503
terrifying to us,

343
00:29:16,963 --> 00:29:18,297
to women.

344
00:29:19,174 --> 00:29:20,632
It is said

345
00:29:21,843 --> 00:29:23,719
a man will come.

346
00:29:24,846 --> 00:29:26,680
The Kwisatz Haderach.

347
00:29:27,932 --> 00:29:30,058
He will go
where we cannot.

348
00:29:32,687 --> 00:29:34,521
Many men have tried.

349
00:29:35,356 --> 00:29:37,232
They tried and failed?

350
00:29:37,609 --> 00:29:39,568
They tried and died.

351
00:29:40,862 --> 00:29:41,862
Jessica.

352
00:29:47,952 --> 00:29:49,912
My son lives!

353
00:29:56,377 --> 00:29:58,629
I sense your
teachings in him.

354
00:29:59,547 --> 00:30:02,090
Ignore the regular order
of training.

355
00:30:02,175 --> 00:30:04,426
His safety
requires the Voice.

356
00:30:04,719 --> 00:30:06,720
I've heard enough
of my safety.

357
00:30:06,805 --> 00:30:08,639
What about my father?

358
00:30:08,932 --> 00:30:10,265
I heard your talking.

359
00:30:10,558 --> 00:30:12,559
You speak as if he were dead.
Well, he's not!

360
00:30:12,644 --> 00:30:13,977
Paul.
Well, he's not.

361
00:30:14,062 --> 00:30:16,647
And he won't die.
Tell me he won't die.

362
00:30:16,731 --> 00:30:18,482
What can be done
has been done.

363
00:30:18,566 --> 00:30:20,234
Mother, tell me!

364
00:30:45,885 --> 00:30:47,886
Mentat Piter De Vries.

365
00:30:47,971 --> 00:30:50,347
Message for
Mentat Piter De Vries.

366
00:30:50,431 --> 00:30:53,183
The Baron is
impatient for Leto's reply.

367
00:30:56,187 --> 00:30:58,355
It is by will alone
I set my mind in motion.

368
00:30:58,439 --> 00:31:01,024
It is by the juice of Sapho
that thoughts acquire speed,

369
00:31:01,109 --> 00:31:03,527
that lips acquire stains,
that stains become a warning.

370
00:31:03,611 --> 00:31:06,488
It is by will alone
I set my mind in motion.

371
00:31:09,617 --> 00:31:11,827
It is by will alone
I set my mind in motion.

372
00:31:11,911 --> 00:31:14,371
It is by the juice of Sapho
that thoughts acquire speed,

373
00:31:14,455 --> 00:31:16,707
that lips acquire stains,
that stains become a warning.

374
00:31:16,791 --> 00:31:19,251
It is by will alone
I set my mind in motion.

375
00:32:22,899 --> 00:32:23,941
My lord.

376
00:32:24,025 --> 00:32:25,233
Piter!

377
00:32:27,153 --> 00:32:29,529
The Atreides will be
leaving Caladan soon, Baron,

378
00:32:29,614 --> 00:32:32,574
and I have here
your answer from Duke Leto.

379
00:32:33,034 --> 00:32:35,118
What does Leto say, Piter?

380
00:32:35,244 --> 00:32:38,038
He wishes to inform you
that vendetta,

381
00:32:38,164 --> 00:32:40,958
as he puts it,
using the ancient tongue,

382
00:32:41,042 --> 00:32:43,835
the art of kanly,
is still alive.

383
00:32:44,128 --> 00:32:47,422
He does not wish
to meet or speak with you.

384
00:32:48,925 --> 00:32:51,385
I've made my peace gesture.

385
00:32:52,428 --> 00:32:55,097
The forms of kanly
have been obeyed.

386
00:32:56,849 --> 00:32:58,892
Bring in Feyd and Rabban.

387
00:33:25,920 --> 00:33:27,754
As you
instructed me,

388
00:33:27,839 --> 00:33:30,048
I have enlightened
your nephews

389
00:33:30,133 --> 00:33:31,383
concerning my plan...

390
00:33:31,467 --> 00:33:32,759
My plan.

391
00:33:34,095 --> 00:33:38,181
The plan to
crush the Atreides.

392
00:33:39,434 --> 00:33:40,726
Feyd,

393
00:33:41,894 --> 00:33:43,770
Rabban,

394
00:33:44,230 --> 00:33:46,231
go quietly.

395
00:33:47,775 --> 00:33:50,902
No other great house
of the Landsraad

396
00:33:50,987 --> 00:33:54,865
must ever know of the
Emperor's aid to the Baron.

397
00:33:55,616 --> 00:33:59,870
The entire Landsraad
would turn against the Baron

398
00:34:01,039 --> 00:34:02,664
and the Emperor.

399
00:34:02,874 --> 00:34:05,042
Put the pick in there,
Pete,

400
00:34:05,960 --> 00:34:09,129
and turn it round
real neat.

401
00:34:29,859 --> 00:34:32,778
You are so beautiful,
my Baron.

402
00:34:33,988 --> 00:34:36,990
Your skin, love to me.

403
00:34:38,159 --> 00:34:41,703
Your diseases
lovingly cared for,

404
00:34:41,788 --> 00:34:43,872
for all eternity.

405
00:34:50,338 --> 00:34:53,215
I will have Arrakis
back for myself!

406
00:34:53,299 --> 00:34:56,760
He who controls the spice,
controls the Universe!

407
00:34:56,844 --> 00:34:59,179
And what Piter
did not tell you

408
00:34:59,263 --> 00:35:02,557
is we have control of
someone who is very close,

409
00:35:02,642 --> 00:35:05,310
very close to Duke Leto.

410
00:35:06,020 --> 00:35:08,522
This person, this traitor

411
00:35:08,606 --> 00:35:12,359
will be worth more to us
than 10 legions of Sardaukar.

412
00:35:12,485 --> 00:35:14,402
And who is this traitor?

413
00:35:15,571 --> 00:35:17,823
I won't tell you
who the traitor is,

414
00:35:17,907 --> 00:35:19,741
or when we'll attack.

415
00:35:20,451 --> 00:35:21,701
However,

416
00:35:22,036 --> 00:35:25,580
the Duke will die before
these eyes and he'll know...

417
00:35:25,665 --> 00:35:28,083
He'll know that it is I,

418
00:35:28,167 --> 00:35:32,129
Baron Vladimir Harkonnen,
who encompasses his doom!

419
00:36:49,624 --> 00:36:52,751
This is what I'll do
to the Duke and his family.

420
00:37:31,832 --> 00:37:34,542
Oh, I'll miss
Caladan so much.

421
00:37:59,527 --> 00:38:00,527
Caladan.

422
00:38:54,665 --> 00:38:57,417
Soon they will
begin to fold space.

423
00:38:58,252 --> 00:39:01,629
Far off in the control rooms
of spice gas.

424
00:39:02,006 --> 00:39:05,008
Traveling without moving.

425
00:41:23,522 --> 00:41:25,398
And now,

426
00:41:25,941 --> 00:41:27,442
the prophecy.

427
00:41:28,861 --> 00:41:31,237
One will come.

428
00:41:32,406 --> 00:41:35,533
The voice from
the outer world.

429
00:41:36,368 --> 00:41:38,578
Bringing the Holy War,

430
00:41:39,413 --> 00:41:40,830
the Jihad,

431
00:41:41,582 --> 00:41:43,917
which will
cleanse the Universe,

432
00:41:44,210 --> 00:41:47,921
and bring us out of darkness.

433
00:42:15,574 --> 00:42:18,034
House Atreides
took control of Arrakis

434
00:42:18,118 --> 00:42:22,413
63 standard days
into the year 10191.

435
00:42:22,873 --> 00:42:24,749
It was known that
the Harkonnens,

436
00:42:24,833 --> 00:42:26,543
the former rulers
of Arrakis

437
00:42:26,627 --> 00:42:29,337
would leave many
suicide troops behind.

438
00:42:30,381 --> 00:42:33,633
Atreides' patrols
were doubled.

439
00:42:45,229 --> 00:42:46,437
Duncan!

440
00:42:49,692 --> 00:42:52,569
What have you discovered
about the Fremen, Duncan?

441
00:42:52,653 --> 00:42:53,903
Tell me.

442
00:42:54,780 --> 00:42:56,281
Why haven't
we heard from you?

443
00:42:56,365 --> 00:42:57,657
My lord,

444
00:42:57,825 --> 00:42:59,576
I suspect so much.

445
00:43:01,495 --> 00:43:03,705
I think they are
the allies we seek.

446
00:43:03,789 --> 00:43:05,582
They are strong, fierce.

447
00:43:05,666 --> 00:43:08,501
They do not give their
loyalty easily or quickly.

448
00:43:08,752 --> 00:43:11,337
As you know,
the Imperium has never

449
00:43:11,422 --> 00:43:13,548
been able to take
a census of the Fremen.

450
00:43:13,674 --> 00:43:15,758
Everyone thinks
that there are but few

451
00:43:15,843 --> 00:43:17,885
wandering here and there
in the desert.

452
00:43:18,178 --> 00:43:19,596
My lord,

453
00:43:20,347 --> 00:43:23,641
I suspect an incredible secret
has been kept on this planet.

454
00:43:24,184 --> 00:43:27,437
That the Fremen exist
in vast numbers.

455
00:43:28,480 --> 00:43:29,772
Vast.

456
00:43:30,399 --> 00:43:34,360
And it is they
who control Arrakis.

457
00:43:40,909 --> 00:43:43,036
Each trooper
will be charged

458
00:43:43,120 --> 00:43:45,538
with responsibility
for preserving water.

459
00:43:45,623 --> 00:43:47,665
Our existence
as an operating army

460
00:43:47,750 --> 00:43:50,793
depends on these following
water-saving procedures.

461
00:43:50,878 --> 00:43:53,379
Remember, water is life.

462
00:43:57,384 --> 00:44:00,637
Why is the shield
not yet up?

463
00:44:00,888 --> 00:44:04,140
Sir, we found and removed
another sabotage device.

464
00:44:04,725 --> 00:44:06,059
I think it'll go up now, sir.

465
00:44:11,148 --> 00:44:14,025
They're finding these
sabotage devices too easily.

466
00:44:25,037 --> 00:44:27,580
House shields activated.

467
00:44:34,713 --> 00:44:36,506
Duke Leto is now here.

468
00:44:36,590 --> 00:44:39,092
Spice mining inspection
to start immediately.

469
00:44:56,819 --> 00:44:58,820
So you are Doctor Kynes.

470
00:44:59,405 --> 00:45:01,114
The Judge of the Change.

471
00:45:01,281 --> 00:45:03,366
And the Imperial
Ecologist, Sire.

472
00:45:03,575 --> 00:45:05,326
Our intelligence informs us

473
00:45:05,411 --> 00:45:08,204
that there's still a strong
Harkonnen presence.

474
00:45:08,372 --> 00:45:10,748
The process of
removal continues.

475
00:45:11,625 --> 00:45:13,459
This is my son, Paul.

476
00:45:14,795 --> 00:45:15,962
Are you a Fremen?

477
00:45:16,046 --> 00:45:18,172
I've been on Arrakis
in the service of the Emperor

478
00:45:18,257 --> 00:45:20,299
long enough
for my eyes to change.

479
00:45:20,384 --> 00:45:22,593
In the service
of the Emperor.

480
00:45:22,678 --> 00:45:24,387
We are in your hands, Doctor.

481
00:45:24,471 --> 00:45:27,181
Your gift of the stillsuits
is much appreciated.

482
00:45:27,266 --> 00:45:30,101
Will you give us an explanation
of their workings?

483
00:45:30,519 --> 00:45:33,688
Well, this is a still suit
of Fremen manufacture,

484
00:45:34,022 --> 00:45:35,606
the most efficient type
on Arrakis.

485
00:45:35,691 --> 00:45:36,733
Basically...

486
00:45:40,863 --> 00:45:42,405
It's all right, Gurney.

487
00:45:43,824 --> 00:45:45,199
Yes, Sire.

488
00:45:46,285 --> 00:45:47,660
Basically,

489
00:45:47,995 --> 00:45:49,787
it's a high-efficiency
filter,

490
00:45:49,997 --> 00:45:51,622
and heat exchange system.

491
00:45:52,458 --> 00:45:54,876
Perspiration passes
through the first layer

492
00:45:55,419 --> 00:45:57,670
and is gathered
in the second.

493
00:45:57,755 --> 00:45:59,672
The salt is separated.

494
00:46:00,007 --> 00:46:03,342
Breathing and walking
provide the pumping action.

495
00:46:04,094 --> 00:46:07,555
The reclaimed water
circulates to catch pockets

496
00:46:07,681 --> 00:46:08,890
from which you can drink

497
00:46:08,974 --> 00:46:12,226
through this tube
around your neck.

498
00:46:13,270 --> 00:46:16,397
Urine and feces are processed
in the thigh pads.

499
00:46:17,065 --> 00:46:19,734
Should you be
in the open desert,

500
00:46:20,486 --> 00:46:22,820
remember to breathe in
through your mouth

501
00:46:22,905 --> 00:46:25,490
and out through
this nose tube.

502
00:46:25,741 --> 00:46:28,201
With a Fremen suit
in good working condition,

503
00:46:28,285 --> 00:46:30,620
life can be sustained
for weeks,

504
00:46:30,704 --> 00:46:33,414
even in the deep desert,
Sire.

505
00:46:35,167 --> 00:46:36,542
My thanks.

506
00:46:37,211 --> 00:46:39,045
With your permission.

507
00:46:41,173 --> 00:46:43,424
You've worn
a stillsuit before.

508
00:46:43,509 --> 00:46:44,801
No.

509
00:46:45,260 --> 00:46:47,553
Your suit is
fitted desert fashion.

510
00:46:47,638 --> 00:46:49,263
Who told you
how to do that?

511
00:46:49,681 --> 00:46:51,057
No one.

512
00:46:51,725 --> 00:46:53,726
It seemed
the proper way.

513
00:46:56,939 --> 00:46:58,314
That it is.

514
00:46:58,398 --> 00:47:01,859
He shall know your ways
as if born to them.

515
00:47:03,862 --> 00:47:05,905
We're wasting time, Sire.

516
00:47:21,630 --> 00:47:24,590
That language?
Translate it.

517
00:47:27,970 --> 00:47:29,595
Very faint.

518
00:47:34,601 --> 00:47:36,102
Harkonnen!

519
00:47:42,276 --> 00:47:44,360
Air speed, zero-five.

520
00:47:45,195 --> 00:47:48,614
Ambient temperature,
300 degrees Kelvin.

521
00:47:49,283 --> 00:47:51,367
Air speed, three-zero.

522
00:47:55,956 --> 00:47:57,957
...35% percent
efficiency.

523
00:48:04,506 --> 00:48:06,048
That's where I told
your sandmaster

524
00:48:06,133 --> 00:48:07,717
to concentrate
the harvesting today.

525
00:48:08,760 --> 00:48:11,137
Southeast,
over the Shield Wall.

526
00:48:13,307 --> 00:48:16,934
Ambient temperature,
350 degrees Kelvin.

527
00:48:18,020 --> 00:48:20,521
Air speed, one-three-zero.

528
00:48:22,482 --> 00:48:25,776
Caution. You've now cleared
protective Shield Wall

529
00:48:25,986 --> 00:48:28,404
and entered open desert.

530
00:48:37,205 --> 00:48:38,956
Will we see a worm?

531
00:48:39,750 --> 00:48:42,668
Where there is spice and spice
mining, there are always worms.

532
00:48:42,920 --> 00:48:43,961
Always?

533
00:48:44,046 --> 00:48:45,171
Always.

534
00:48:45,839 --> 00:48:47,506
Why do they come?

535
00:48:48,467 --> 00:48:50,551
To protect their territory.

536
00:48:51,136 --> 00:48:53,095
Vibrations attract them.

537
00:48:53,263 --> 00:48:55,848
He must be a Fremen
or in with them.

538
00:48:56,516 --> 00:48:58,351
He's studying us.

539
00:48:58,727 --> 00:49:00,978
He's hiding something
about the spice.

540
00:49:01,647 --> 00:49:04,357
Is there a relationship between
the worms and the spice?

541
00:49:06,526 --> 00:49:10,529
As I said, they defend
the spice sands.

542
00:49:12,032 --> 00:49:14,742
As to their relationship
with the spice,

543
00:49:16,286 --> 00:49:17,370
who knows?

544
00:49:33,387 --> 00:49:35,930
My message, it's here.

545
00:49:39,559 --> 00:49:42,019
There are more
enemy bodies coming in

546
00:49:42,104 --> 00:49:44,563
for your inspection,
Doctor Yueh.

547
00:49:49,069 --> 00:49:50,736
Are you all right?

548
00:49:50,988 --> 00:49:52,530
Yes, I'm fine.

549
00:49:52,948 --> 00:49:54,657
Thank you, Thufir.

550
00:49:58,912 --> 00:50:00,371
Dust cloud ahead, Sire.

551
00:50:00,455 --> 00:50:02,289
That's it. Spice mining.

552
00:50:03,417 --> 00:50:05,584
No other cloud
quite like it.

553
00:50:09,006 --> 00:50:10,589
Wormsign?

554
00:50:11,008 --> 00:50:12,133
Is it wormsign?

555
00:50:12,217 --> 00:50:14,593
Yes. Worm. Big one.

556
00:50:15,178 --> 00:50:17,763
You've got sharp eyes.
May I?

557
00:50:21,059 --> 00:50:23,978
Calling Harvester Pad Nine.
Wormsign.

558
00:50:24,438 --> 00:50:25,938
Who calls Pad Nine?

559
00:50:26,023 --> 00:50:27,148
Don't mention the Duke.

560
00:50:27,232 --> 00:50:29,358
This is an un-coded channel.

561
00:50:29,651 --> 00:50:31,861
Unlisted flight
northeast of you.

562
00:50:31,945 --> 00:50:33,904
Wormsign on intercept course.

563
00:50:34,322 --> 00:50:36,907
Estimated contact,
15 minutes.

564
00:50:37,159 --> 00:50:39,618
- Have sighting confirmed.
- Stand by for a fix.

565
00:50:39,786 --> 00:50:41,954
Contact in 16 minutes minus.

566
00:50:42,622 --> 00:50:44,123
Very precise estimate.

567
00:50:44,207 --> 00:50:45,833
Who's on that
unlisted flight?

568
00:50:48,128 --> 00:50:49,920
What happens now?

569
00:50:50,088 --> 00:50:51,047
The carryall will come

570
00:50:51,131 --> 00:50:53,466
and lift off
the spice harvester.

571
00:50:54,801 --> 00:50:56,635
Try to get in close
over the harvester.

572
00:50:56,720 --> 00:50:59,180
You'll find this
interesting, Sire.

573
00:50:59,639 --> 00:51:01,390
They work until
the very last minute.

574
00:51:01,725 --> 00:51:04,435
Spotter control, there's
no sign of the carryall.

575
00:51:04,936 --> 00:51:06,145
It isn't answering.

576
00:51:06,938 --> 00:51:09,231
The worm is
eight minutes away, Sire.

577
00:51:09,316 --> 00:51:11,817
Spotter control, give me
a report by the numbers.

578
00:51:12,110 --> 00:51:13,069
Report One.

579
00:51:13,153 --> 00:51:14,153
No contact.

580
00:51:14,237 --> 00:51:15,404
Report two.

581
00:51:15,655 --> 00:51:16,697
Negative.

582
00:51:16,782 --> 00:51:17,740
Report Three.

583
00:51:17,824 --> 00:51:18,866
Negative, Sire.

584
00:51:18,950 --> 00:51:19,909
Report four.

585
00:51:19,993 --> 00:51:22,244
- No contact.
- Repeat, no contact.

586
00:51:22,496 --> 00:51:24,205
I think they've
got our carryall.

587
00:51:24,414 --> 00:51:26,624
Damn it! Harkonnens.

588
00:51:27,125 --> 00:51:29,251
We're coming down to
take you off the harvester.

589
00:51:29,336 --> 00:51:31,295
All spotters are
ordered to comply.

590
00:51:31,505 --> 00:51:32,671
Ordered by whom?

591
00:51:32,798 --> 00:51:34,215
Duke Leto Atreides.

592
00:51:34,508 --> 00:51:36,425
Yes. Yesh Sire.

593
00:51:36,510 --> 00:51:37,760
How many men do you have?

594
00:51:37,844 --> 00:51:39,428
Full crew, 26 men.

595
00:51:39,888 --> 00:51:42,014
But, Sire, we can't
leave all this spice.

596
00:51:42,099 --> 00:51:43,432
Damn the spice!

597
00:51:43,517 --> 00:51:44,809
Get out of there!

598
00:51:54,361 --> 00:51:56,445
Two men in
each of the spotters!

599
00:51:56,530 --> 00:51:58,114
You, over here!

600
00:51:58,198 --> 00:52:01,033
Run! Run!

601
00:52:07,082 --> 00:52:09,792
I can't see him yet,
but he is very close now.

602
00:52:09,876 --> 00:52:13,129
Damn sloppy.
Really damn sloppy.

603
00:52:13,213 --> 00:52:15,089
Come on, boys.
Come on.

604
00:52:19,261 --> 00:52:20,886
We're going to
be heavy, Sire.

605
00:52:21,429 --> 00:52:22,972
Spice.

606
00:52:24,015 --> 00:52:27,226
Pure unrefined spice.

607
00:52:33,316 --> 00:52:35,943
Here he is!
We've got to go!

608
00:52:45,704 --> 00:52:47,413
Bless the Maker
and his water.

609
00:52:47,581 --> 00:52:49,165
Bless the coming
and going of Him.

610
00:52:49,249 --> 00:52:50,916
May His passing
cleanse the world.

611
00:52:51,001 --> 00:52:53,085
What's that
you're saying?

612
00:52:53,211 --> 00:52:54,461
Nothing.

613
00:53:31,041 --> 00:53:32,917
Gods, what a monster.

614
00:53:41,968 --> 00:53:44,929
Someone is going to
pay for this, I promise.

615
00:53:47,933 --> 00:53:51,101
He's more concerned over
his men than the spice.

616
00:53:51,603 --> 00:53:55,439
I must admit,
against all better judgment,

617
00:53:56,274 --> 00:53:57,900
I like this Duke.

618
00:54:44,406 --> 00:54:47,908
My lady,
the local people,

619
00:54:47,993 --> 00:54:50,703
the maids and servants,
await your inspection.

620
00:54:50,870 --> 00:54:53,038
Hawat has cleared them.

621
00:54:56,209 --> 00:54:57,960
Excuse me, my lady.

622
00:54:58,837 --> 00:55:02,965
The Harkonnens may have
tampered with them medically.

623
00:55:12,309 --> 00:55:14,310
When you said
Harkonnens,

624
00:55:15,812 --> 00:55:19,064
I didn't know you had
so much reason to hate them.

625
00:55:22,569 --> 00:55:24,236
Well, my wife...

626
00:55:26,197 --> 00:55:29,283
But, of course, you...
You didn't know my wife.

627
00:55:31,119 --> 00:55:32,578
The Har...

628
00:55:33,079 --> 00:55:34,580
Forgive me.

629
00:55:34,706 --> 00:55:36,457
They must have killed her.

630
00:55:37,208 --> 00:55:40,085
Please excuse me
if I can't talk about it.

631
00:55:44,841 --> 00:55:48,761
He's holding something back.
Yet.

632
00:55:50,055 --> 00:55:52,222
There's
the imperial conditioning.

633
00:55:53,641 --> 00:55:55,726
Assurance of trust.

634
00:56:02,108 --> 00:56:05,861
The Bene Gesserit motherh
the legend.

635
00:56:06,780 --> 00:56:08,447
Where is your son?

636
00:56:09,491 --> 00:56:12,993
I must warn you.
You are in great danger.

637
00:56:15,830 --> 00:56:17,289
Safe.

638
00:56:33,807 --> 00:56:35,224
Spice.

639
00:56:53,785 --> 00:56:55,911
What is it doing to me?

640
00:57:07,841 --> 00:57:09,508
Second moon.

641
00:57:11,386 --> 00:57:13,846
The sleeper must awaken.

642
00:57:14,097 --> 00:57:16,014
Am I the one?

643
00:57:29,946 --> 00:57:31,864
A hunter-seeker!

644
00:57:32,365 --> 00:57:34,324
It can't get me
if I don't move.

645
00:57:35,368 --> 00:57:37,744
It's too dark in here
for it to see clearly.

646
00:57:54,387 --> 00:57:56,472
I've got
to try to grab it.

647
00:57:57,015 --> 00:58:00,100
The suspensor field will make
it slippery on the bottom.

648
00:58:00,185 --> 00:58:02,227
I must grip it tightly.

649
00:58:04,314 --> 00:58:06,565
Who is operating
that thing?

650
00:58:07,233 --> 00:58:09,568
It has to be someone
in the palace.

651
00:58:10,653 --> 00:58:11,820
I could shout for help,

652
00:58:11,905 --> 00:58:14,072
but it would kill whoever
opened the door.

653
00:58:32,342 --> 00:58:34,301
Hold still.

654
00:58:58,618 --> 00:59:00,494
It would have killed me.

655
00:59:01,663 --> 00:59:05,040
I was its target.
It went to the motion.

656
00:59:05,917 --> 00:59:07,417
Who are you?

657
00:59:07,502 --> 00:59:09,586
I am the Shadout Mapes,

658
00:59:10,380 --> 00:59:12,214
the housekeeper.

659
00:59:12,757 --> 00:59:16,134
I must cleanse
the way between us.

660
00:59:16,803 --> 00:59:20,973
You saved my life, and
we Fremen pay our debts.

661
00:59:21,140 --> 00:59:22,599
A Fremen.

662
00:59:22,684 --> 00:59:24,726
It is known to us

663
00:59:24,811 --> 00:59:27,145
that you've a traitor
in your midst.

664
00:59:27,230 --> 00:59:29,523
Who it is,
we cannot say.

665
00:59:29,816 --> 00:59:32,234
But we are certain
of it.

666
00:59:42,537 --> 00:59:43,829
A traitor.

667
00:59:55,174 --> 00:59:58,218
Set up a sonar probe
immediately.

668
01:00:06,686 --> 01:00:08,353
Harkonnen.

669
01:00:11,941 --> 01:00:14,568
They've tried to take
the life of my son.

670
01:00:18,531 --> 01:00:21,908
Sector 6 through 80
progress reports, Sire.

671
01:00:22,118 --> 01:00:23,702
Take it, Thufir.

672
01:00:26,873 --> 01:00:29,791
Sector 680, copy the 6th, the
summit, the 8th, quadrant over,

673
01:00:29,876 --> 01:00:32,961
the 9th plus 84 circles, weave
the 80 and call the 4th. Copy.

674
01:00:38,176 --> 01:00:42,179
8. Thufir Tawat, Mentat,
Master of assassins.

675
01:00:45,933 --> 01:00:47,934
Uh, the palace
is now secure.

676
01:00:48,978 --> 01:00:52,105
The city of Arrakeen
is under martial law.

677
01:00:52,940 --> 01:00:56,610
We have troops here
headquartered underground

678
01:00:56,903 --> 01:00:59,237
on sub-floors
6 through 10.

679
01:00:59,822 --> 01:01:01,782
The rest of the troops
are stationed in Arrakeen,

680
01:01:01,866 --> 01:01:04,034
and we have some
on the airfield.

681
01:01:04,118 --> 01:01:07,704
Our new army is still
in training, but everything,

682
01:01:07,872 --> 01:01:09,414
everything is shielded.

683
01:01:09,499 --> 01:01:12,626
And with this shielding
we are impenetrable.

684
01:02:05,930 --> 01:02:08,223
Sleep well, my son.

685
01:02:18,609 --> 01:02:21,570
Um, Father,

686
01:02:23,406 --> 01:02:24,781
drugged.

687
01:02:31,247 --> 01:02:34,124
Jessica, what is wrong?

688
01:02:34,333 --> 01:02:36,960
Forgive me,
my beloved concubine.

689
01:02:37,837 --> 01:02:39,629
I should have married you.

690
01:02:40,673 --> 01:02:43,091
Why hold a dream
to ascend to the throne

691
01:02:43,176 --> 01:02:45,135
through
a political marriage?

692
01:02:47,180 --> 01:02:49,139
I should have married you.

693
01:03:13,831 --> 01:03:15,373
What happened?

694
01:03:37,730 --> 01:03:39,022
Yueh!

695
01:03:39,106 --> 01:03:41,066
He sabotaged
the house generators.

696
01:03:41,818 --> 01:03:42,943
We are wide open!

697
01:03:46,948 --> 01:03:49,658
House shield deactivating.

698
01:03:50,117 --> 01:03:53,203
I've destroyed the new army's
weirding modules.

699
01:03:53,496 --> 01:03:55,664
I've brought
House Atreides down.

700
01:03:55,748 --> 01:03:56,998
Why?

701
01:03:57,083 --> 01:04:00,919
I wish to kill a man.
Not you, my dear Duke.

702
01:04:01,629 --> 01:04:03,380
You were already dead.

703
01:04:03,589 --> 01:04:06,091
But you'll get close
to the Baron before you die.

704
01:04:06,592 --> 01:04:09,803
You'll be tied and drugged,
but you can still attack.

705
01:04:10,263 --> 01:04:12,264
You can still attack!

706
01:04:13,349 --> 01:04:15,225
When you see the Baron,

707
01:04:15,601 --> 01:04:18,270
you'll have a new
poison gas tooth.

708
01:04:19,772 --> 01:04:22,941
He'll want you close,
so he can gloat over you.

709
01:04:24,277 --> 01:04:28,446
One bite on this tooth
and a strong exhale...

710
01:04:29,740 --> 01:04:30,740
Refuse.

711
01:04:30,825 --> 01:04:31,992
No! You mustn't!

712
01:04:32,869 --> 01:04:34,494
Because, in return,

713
01:04:34,662 --> 01:04:37,998
I'll save the lives
of your Paul and Jessica.

714
01:04:43,045 --> 01:04:44,504
For Paul.

715
01:04:49,093 --> 01:04:50,093
Ahhh!

716
01:04:59,812 --> 01:05:02,814
When you see the Baron,
remember the tooth.

717
01:05:03,482 --> 01:05:06,526
The tooth! The tooth!

718
01:05:07,820 --> 01:05:11,281
The shield is down!
The shield is down!

719
01:05:13,492 --> 01:05:15,076
Open the doors!

720
01:05:16,078 --> 01:05:17,287
Signals!

721
01:05:19,624 --> 01:05:20,999
Get that shield up!

722
01:05:21,167 --> 01:05:24,085
The shield! The shield!

723
01:05:48,194 --> 01:05:50,862
- The weirding modules!
- Destroyed!

724
01:06:39,495 --> 01:06:42,497
Long live Duke Leto!

725
01:07:05,187 --> 01:07:07,564
The drug was timed.

726
01:07:09,608 --> 01:07:13,278
Dr. Yueh has been
very valuable to us.

727
01:07:15,906 --> 01:07:18,992
What a pity
you must remain gagged.

728
01:07:20,244 --> 01:07:22,454
We can't let
ourselves be swayed

729
01:07:22,580 --> 01:07:24,789
by your witch's voice,
now, can we?

730
01:07:25,708 --> 01:07:28,376
Leto, where are you?

731
01:07:30,296 --> 01:07:32,756
How simple to subdue us.

732
01:07:46,312 --> 01:07:47,979
Goodbye, Jessica.

733
01:07:48,981 --> 01:07:50,982
And goodbye
to your sweet son.

734
01:07:52,318 --> 01:07:54,736
I want to spit
once on your head.

735
01:07:55,446 --> 01:07:57,697
Just some spittle
in your face.

736
01:08:01,619 --> 01:08:02,994
What a luxury!

737
01:08:08,501 --> 01:08:11,169
We were ordered to kill them.
So kill them!

738
01:08:15,925 --> 01:08:18,259
I wish this was Paul.

739
01:08:24,558 --> 01:08:26,643
I knew Yueh's wife.

740
01:08:29,188 --> 01:08:32,941
I was the one who broke
his Imperial conditioning.

741
01:08:37,822 --> 01:08:40,323
I've thought of
many pleasures with you.

742
01:08:42,451 --> 01:08:44,702
It is perhaps
better that you die

743
01:08:45,079 --> 01:08:46,955
in the innards
of a worm.

744
01:08:58,050 --> 01:09:00,552
What are your orders,
Piter?

745
01:09:00,928 --> 01:09:04,055
Take them to the desert,
as the traitor suggested.

746
01:09:05,015 --> 01:09:07,058
The worms will
destroy the evidence.

747
01:09:07,643 --> 01:09:09,894
Their bodies
must never be found.

748
01:09:24,118 --> 01:09:25,827
They're down on this floor
somewhere.

749
01:09:25,911 --> 01:09:26,995
Down there.

750
01:09:46,765 --> 01:09:48,183
Duncan!

751
01:09:53,022 --> 01:09:54,022
Get off!

752
01:09:58,611 --> 01:10:00,904
You wish now
to join your wife?

753
01:10:01,322 --> 01:10:02,947
Is that it, traitor?

754
01:10:03,908 --> 01:10:05,533
She lives?

755
01:10:05,618 --> 01:10:07,160
You wish to join her?

756
01:10:10,956 --> 01:10:12,540
Join her, then.

757
01:10:20,799 --> 01:10:23,092
You think
you've defeated me?

758
01:10:25,930 --> 01:10:30,391
You think I don't know
what I've gained, for my wife!

759
01:10:37,483 --> 01:10:38,816
Take him away.

760
01:11:01,257 --> 01:11:02,840
Yueh's sign.

761
01:11:06,428 --> 01:11:08,263
He's left us stillsuits.

762
01:11:17,022 --> 01:11:19,148
Don't touch my mother!

763
01:11:19,316 --> 01:11:21,067
He's trying the Voice.

764
01:11:21,360 --> 01:11:23,278
The Reverend Mother
said it could save him.

765
01:11:23,362 --> 01:11:26,114
Did you hear a noise
from the little one, huh?

766
01:11:26,615 --> 01:11:29,158
No, I didn't hear
anything.

767
01:11:32,621 --> 01:11:34,205
The little one.

768
01:11:47,970 --> 01:11:49,387
Remove her gag.

769
01:11:49,847 --> 01:11:51,139
Excellent!

770
01:12:08,073 --> 01:12:10,783
There's no need
to fight over me.

771
01:12:21,462 --> 01:12:22,962
A poisoned blade.

772
01:12:31,764 --> 01:12:37,435
First cut my son's bonds.

773
01:12:45,194 --> 01:12:46,611
That's it.

774
01:12:59,666 --> 01:13:01,042
Oh, my God.

775
01:13:11,970 --> 01:13:13,429
It's under control.

776
01:13:42,543 --> 01:13:46,045
Duke Leto Atreides.

777
01:13:49,675 --> 01:13:52,635
Where is
the ducal signet ring?

778
01:13:53,929 --> 01:13:56,514
I must have his ring.

779
01:13:58,976 --> 01:14:00,268
The ring!

780
01:14:03,564 --> 01:14:06,816
He was brought to us
as is, my lord Baron.

781
01:14:08,777 --> 01:14:11,404
You killed the doctor
too soon, you fool!

782
01:14:12,614 --> 01:14:16,033
The doctor, Yueh,
what did he say?

783
01:14:16,869 --> 01:14:18,870
Paul and Jessica safe.

784
01:14:19,496 --> 01:14:21,581
Yes. The tooth!

785
01:14:22,499 --> 01:14:23,875
He's coming around, Baron.

786
01:14:24,168 --> 01:14:25,543
Where's your ring?

787
01:14:26,712 --> 01:14:27,712
Huh?

788
01:14:28,755 --> 01:14:30,089
You do not answer?

789
01:14:30,174 --> 01:14:32,592
Wait! Wait!

790
01:14:32,968 --> 01:14:35,428
You must come closer.

791
01:14:36,221 --> 01:14:39,724
The water of my life

792
01:14:42,186 --> 01:14:43,394
for Paul.

793
01:14:43,854 --> 01:14:47,148
He's crying.
He's crying!

794
01:14:48,192 --> 01:14:50,109
What does that mean,
Piter?

795
01:14:52,905 --> 01:14:55,573
Come closerh Baron.

796
01:15:01,538 --> 01:15:02,580
No!

797
01:15:04,166 --> 01:15:05,583
Jessica!

798
01:15:07,461 --> 01:15:08,878
Leto!

799
01:15:10,214 --> 01:15:12,089
Leto, he's dead!

800
01:15:12,174 --> 01:15:14,091
No, he's dead!

801
01:15:15,469 --> 01:15:16,469
I know.

802
01:15:24,269 --> 01:15:25,937
Am I alive?

803
01:15:28,023 --> 01:15:29,023
I'm alive?

804
01:15:29,107 --> 01:15:30,149
Yes,

805
01:15:31,443 --> 01:15:33,444
you're alive,
my Baron.

806
01:15:34,238 --> 01:15:36,030
I'm alive, eh?

807
01:15:36,615 --> 01:15:42,036
I'm alive!

808
01:15:50,921 --> 01:15:53,130
I can't maintain any altitude.

809
01:15:53,549 --> 01:15:56,008
We'll never reach
the safety of rock!

810
01:16:00,138 --> 01:16:02,014
Maybe that small rock.

811
01:16:02,558 --> 01:16:04,308
Where are we,
do you think?

812
01:16:04,476 --> 01:16:06,227
The south polar regions.

813
01:16:06,687 --> 01:16:10,147
The forbidden area.
Hold on.

814
01:16:19,324 --> 01:16:20,491
Hurry!

815
01:16:23,328 --> 01:16:25,204
Take the stillsuits!

816
01:16:26,957 --> 01:16:28,249
Hurry!

817
01:16:28,333 --> 01:16:30,293
This crash
might bring a worm.

818
01:16:35,549 --> 01:16:36,757
The signet.

819
01:16:36,842 --> 01:16:39,719
A million deaths
are not enough for Yueh!

820
01:17:03,493 --> 01:17:05,202
Where are my feelings?

821
01:17:05,662 --> 01:17:07,496
I feel for no one.

822
01:17:11,877 --> 01:17:13,711
The second moon.

823
01:17:29,144 --> 01:17:32,688
I mean Paul Atreides.

824
01:17:32,939 --> 01:17:35,399
We want him killed.

825
01:17:36,360 --> 01:17:37,401
Why?

826
01:17:37,486 --> 01:17:39,904
Why do they want me killed?

827
01:17:39,988 --> 01:17:42,865
It has to be something
to do with the spice.

828
01:17:43,742 --> 01:17:45,076
But what?

829
01:17:51,458 --> 01:17:55,169
He who controls the spice,
controls the Universe!

830
01:18:03,053 --> 01:18:05,638
This moon holds my future.

831
01:18:18,902 --> 01:18:22,113
Never one drop of rain
on Arrakis.

832
01:18:25,784 --> 01:18:29,328
The sleeper must awaken.

833
01:18:38,171 --> 01:18:40,047
They will call me,

834
01:18:40,465 --> 01:18:42,007
Muad'Dib.

835
01:18:49,349 --> 01:18:52,560
Listen to me. Listen!

836
01:18:53,562 --> 01:18:55,855
You wanted to know
about my dreams.

837
01:18:56,940 --> 01:18:59,358
Well, I've just had
a waking dream.

838
01:19:00,819 --> 01:19:03,612
Do you know why?
The spice!

839
01:19:04,489 --> 01:19:06,407
It's in everything here.

840
01:19:07,325 --> 01:19:08,576
Calm yourself.

841
01:19:08,660 --> 01:19:10,661
Like the Truthsayer drug.

842
01:19:12,456 --> 01:19:13,748
It's a poison.

843
01:19:14,833 --> 01:19:17,668
You knew the spice
would change me.

844
01:19:18,295 --> 01:19:19,837
But thanks
to your teachings,

845
01:19:19,921 --> 01:19:22,256
it's changing
my consciousness.

846
01:19:22,340 --> 01:19:25,009
I see it!
I can see it!

847
01:19:25,927 --> 01:19:27,344
Is he the one?

848
01:19:28,972 --> 01:19:31,223
You carry my unborn sister
in your womb.

849
01:19:31,600 --> 01:19:32,892
He knows.

850
01:19:44,196 --> 01:19:45,529
Father!

851
01:19:49,868 --> 01:19:52,703
Father, I promise,

852
01:19:52,788 --> 01:19:55,581
one day
the sleeper will awaken.

853
01:19:56,541 --> 01:19:58,959
And I will avenge your death.

854
01:19:59,711 --> 01:20:02,421
I will not stop
until I destroy

855
01:20:02,506 --> 01:20:04,673
the Emperor and the Baron.

856
01:20:10,222 --> 01:20:11,430
Father.

857
01:20:27,280 --> 01:20:28,864
Go now.

858
01:20:31,117 --> 01:20:34,995
Take him
to his desert to die.

859
01:20:37,040 --> 01:20:38,415
Go.

860
01:21:09,823 --> 01:21:12,575
Yueh's left the plan
for the weirding modules.

861
01:21:24,254 --> 01:21:26,589
We have to get to
that mountain of rock.

862
01:21:28,300 --> 01:21:29,508
We have entered
the time

863
01:21:29,593 --> 01:21:32,219
when all will turn against us
and seek our lives.

864
01:21:48,153 --> 01:21:50,154
It's further
than I thought.

865
01:21:51,656 --> 01:21:53,324
A worm is sure to come.

866
01:21:55,827 --> 01:21:58,495
I'll plant this thumper.
That should divert it.

867
01:22:27,192 --> 01:22:30,402
Remember,
walk without rhythm,

868
01:22:30,487 --> 01:22:31,946
and we won't
attract a worm.

869
01:22:32,447 --> 01:22:34,073
It will go
to the thumper.

870
01:22:36,201 --> 01:22:37,910
I'm ready.

871
01:23:19,411 --> 01:23:20,911
Faster!

872
01:23:22,789 --> 01:23:24,415
It's deafening!

873
01:24:38,990 --> 01:24:39,990
Ooh!

874
01:24:42,160 --> 01:24:43,786
The spice!

875
01:24:45,663 --> 01:24:47,164
Do you smell it?

876
01:24:47,332 --> 01:24:48,332
Yes!

877
01:24:55,757 --> 01:24:56,757
Paul!

878
01:25:25,662 --> 01:25:27,371
A thumper.

879
01:25:35,713 --> 01:25:38,215
The worm! Spice!

880
01:25:38,591 --> 01:25:40,008
Is there a relationship?

881
01:25:54,065 --> 01:25:57,234
What's happened?
Why did it leave?

882
01:25:58,570 --> 01:26:01,488
Someone started
another thumper.

883
01:26:04,409 --> 01:26:05,868
We're not alone.

884
01:26:35,732 --> 01:26:37,524
Man-carved steps.

885
01:26:37,609 --> 01:26:38,942
Yes.

886
01:26:52,999 --> 01:26:54,958
Such stealth.

887
01:26:55,084 --> 01:26:56,710
I didn't hear them.

888
01:26:56,794 --> 01:27:00,214
Perhaps these are the ones
the Shadout Mapes told us of.

889
01:27:00,298 --> 01:27:01,965
I will take the boy-man.

890
01:27:02,717 --> 01:27:05,093
He shall have sanctuary
in my tribe.

891
01:27:14,729 --> 01:27:18,148
Get back!
She has the weirding way.

892
01:27:20,652 --> 01:27:22,027
Great Gods!

893
01:27:22,779 --> 01:27:25,155
If you can do this
to the strongest of us,

894
01:27:25,990 --> 01:27:29,201
you're worth 10 times
your weight of water.

895
01:27:32,205 --> 01:27:34,998
As the leader of my people,
I give you my bond.

896
01:27:36,000 --> 01:27:38,502
Teach us
this weirding way,

897
01:27:38,962 --> 01:27:41,755
and you both
shall have sanctuary.

898
01:27:41,839 --> 01:27:45,676
Your water shall
mingle with our water.

899
01:27:46,636 --> 01:27:48,637
Then I will teach you
our way of battle.

900
01:27:53,142 --> 01:27:56,478
I give you the word bond
of a Bene Gesserit.

901
01:27:57,021 --> 01:27:58,981
It is the legend.

902
01:28:04,570 --> 01:28:07,531
I am Chani,
daughter of Liet.

903
01:28:09,033 --> 01:28:12,202
I would not have permitted you
to harm my tribe.

904
01:28:13,663 --> 01:28:15,163
From my dreams.

905
01:28:16,082 --> 01:28:18,125
So beautiful.

906
01:28:19,085 --> 01:28:20,210
Come with me.

907
01:28:20,295 --> 01:28:22,379
I'll show you
an easier way down.

908
01:28:40,940 --> 01:28:43,066
You have strength.

909
01:28:43,651 --> 01:28:45,819
You shall be known as Usul,

910
01:28:45,987 --> 01:28:48,780
which is the strength
of the base of the pillar.

911
01:28:49,365 --> 01:28:51,742
This is your secret name
in our troop.

912
01:28:52,535 --> 01:28:55,537
But you must choose
the name of manhood,

913
01:28:55,621 --> 01:28:57,914
which we will
call you openly.

914
01:29:00,918 --> 01:29:03,837
What do you call the mouse
shadow in the second moon?

915
01:29:06,966 --> 01:29:09,760
We call that one Muad'Dib.

916
01:29:11,179 --> 01:29:13,555
Could I be known
as Paul Muad'Dib?

917
01:29:14,432 --> 01:29:16,600
You are Paul Muad'Dib.

918
01:29:18,102 --> 01:29:21,229
And your mother shall be
a Sayyadina among us.

919
01:29:22,106 --> 01:29:23,732
We welcome you.

920
01:29:24,984 --> 01:29:27,778
The dream unfolds.

921
01:29:48,841 --> 01:29:50,008
Moisture!

922
01:29:50,426 --> 01:29:51,593
Wind traps.

923
01:29:52,470 --> 01:29:53,970
Huge ones.

924
01:30:04,857 --> 01:30:09,528
Water.
Millions of decaliters.

925
01:30:10,071 --> 01:30:11,655
A treasure.

926
01:30:11,781 --> 01:30:14,116
Greater than treasure,
Usul.

927
01:30:14,826 --> 01:30:17,869
We have thousands
of such caches,

928
01:30:19,247 --> 01:30:22,124
and only a few of us
know them all.

929
01:30:22,750 --> 01:30:25,001
And when we have enough,

930
01:30:25,711 --> 01:30:29,005
we shall change
the face of Arrakis.

931
01:30:48,860 --> 01:30:50,944
Tell me
of your home world, Usul.

932
01:30:54,323 --> 01:30:56,741
Tell me
of your home world, Usul.

933
01:31:30,526 --> 01:31:33,320
Arrakis!

934
01:31:34,530 --> 01:31:36,948
Rabban! Rabban!

935
01:31:39,076 --> 01:31:41,411
We're knee-deep
in Atreides blood!

936
01:31:41,787 --> 01:31:45,040
We've gutted them!
We've gutted them!

937
01:31:49,504 --> 01:31:52,214
Rabban! Rabban!

938
01:31:53,424 --> 01:31:56,301
I place you
in charge of Arrakis.

939
01:31:56,385 --> 01:31:59,262
It's yours to squeeze,
as I promised.

940
01:31:59,347 --> 01:32:04,184
I want you to squeeze
and squeeze and squeeze!

941
01:32:04,268 --> 01:32:07,103
Give me spice!
Drive them!

942
01:32:07,188 --> 01:32:09,564
Drive them
into utter submission!

943
01:32:09,649 --> 01:32:12,442
Do not show
the slightest pity or mercy!

944
01:32:12,860 --> 01:32:15,612
Never stop! Go! Go!

945
01:32:15,696 --> 01:32:16,863
Show no mercy!

946
01:32:16,948 --> 01:32:18,114
Yes, Baron!

947
01:32:39,095 --> 01:32:40,095
Feyd.

948
01:32:50,439 --> 01:32:54,943
And when we've crushed
these people enough,

949
01:32:55,861 --> 01:32:59,656
I'll send you. Feyd.

950
01:33:04,328 --> 01:33:05,912
Lovely Feyd.

951
01:33:12,670 --> 01:33:14,838
Where's my doctor?

952
01:33:21,470 --> 01:33:23,138
Jessica,

953
01:33:24,974 --> 01:33:27,058
our Reverend Mother
is too old.

954
01:33:28,352 --> 01:33:30,645
She has been calling
through space and time,

955
01:33:30,730 --> 01:33:32,897
for you to come
and let her rest.

956
01:33:34,483 --> 01:33:37,235
She asks
that you pass within,

957
01:33:38,070 --> 01:33:40,155
and become
our Reverend Mother.

958
01:33:41,699 --> 01:33:45,869
If you be a Reverend Mother,

959
01:33:48,039 --> 01:33:51,791
let Shai-Hulud judge now!

960
01:33:55,504 --> 01:33:57,589
The Water of Life.

961
01:34:01,218 --> 01:34:03,720
But what
of my unborn child?

962
01:34:05,306 --> 01:34:08,391
One day,
I will have to do this.

963
01:34:25,451 --> 01:34:27,494
Following the Bene Gesserit
tradition,

964
01:34:27,578 --> 01:34:30,080
the old Reverend Mother
surrendered her life

965
01:34:30,247 --> 01:34:32,415
as she surrendered
her knowledge.

966
01:34:33,918 --> 01:34:38,088
Jessica had successfully transmuted
the poisonous Water of Life.

967
01:34:39,090 --> 01:34:42,175
Every man
who has tried has died.

968
01:34:43,427 --> 01:34:45,220
Am I the one?

969
01:34:45,971 --> 01:34:48,765
The sleeper must awaken.

970
01:34:52,770 --> 01:34:55,230
The tremendous power
of the Water of Life

971
01:34:55,314 --> 01:34:59,359
caused the premature birth
of Jessica's daughter, Alia.

972
01:34:59,652 --> 01:35:01,569
Alia was born
with all the knowledge

973
01:35:01,654 --> 01:35:03,655
and powers of
a Reverend Mother.

974
01:35:19,130 --> 01:35:22,632
Feyd, even though
he's aging,

975
01:35:22,800 --> 01:35:26,136
Thufir is one of the finest
Mentats in the Universe.

976
01:35:27,054 --> 01:35:30,807
And he's mine, Feyd,
all mine.

977
01:35:34,478 --> 01:35:35,478
Try it now.

978
01:35:35,563 --> 01:35:36,563
I will.

979
01:35:36,647 --> 01:35:37,647
Come.

980
01:35:51,495 --> 01:35:53,204
Oh, Thufir!

981
01:35:53,998 --> 01:35:56,833
I see they've installed
your heart plug already.

982
01:35:58,377 --> 01:36:00,795
Don't be angry.
Everyone gets one here.

983
01:36:01,839 --> 01:36:03,757
But this is not
why we're here.

984
01:36:05,176 --> 01:36:07,802
We've brought you
a little cat, Thufir.

985
01:36:09,180 --> 01:36:11,347
You must care for it
if you wish to live.

986
01:36:12,892 --> 01:36:16,853
A poison has been introduced
into your body, Thufir Hawat.

987
01:36:17,688 --> 01:36:21,274
By milking this, this smooth,
little cat body,

988
01:36:21,358 --> 01:36:23,359
you receive your antidote.

989
01:36:23,694 --> 01:36:25,695
It must be done
each day.

990
01:36:28,866 --> 01:36:33,787
All I can see is an Atreides
that I want to kill.

991
01:36:34,580 --> 01:36:37,457
Feyd, no, no.

992
01:36:38,709 --> 01:36:41,044
Thufir's a Harkonnen now.

993
01:36:42,046 --> 01:36:44,047
Aren't you, Thufir?

994
01:36:44,131 --> 01:36:48,009
My Duke,
how I've failed you.

995
01:37:06,237 --> 01:37:08,154
Chani, I love you.

996
01:37:10,241 --> 01:37:11,741
I've always loved you.

997
01:37:37,142 --> 01:37:39,435
The Holy Warriors.

998
01:37:40,521 --> 01:37:42,981
No one ever dreamed
there were so many.

999
01:37:44,608 --> 01:37:48,945
I am Usul. Paul Muad'Dib.

1000
01:37:52,867 --> 01:37:55,034
Our shared enemy,
the Harkonnens,

1001
01:37:55,119 --> 01:37:57,829
are once again
in control of Arrakis,

1002
01:37:58,956 --> 01:38:01,124
Stilgar, your leader,

1003
01:38:01,458 --> 01:38:03,459
has asked me and my mother
to teach you

1004
01:38:03,544 --> 01:38:05,920
the weirding way
to crush the Harkonnens.

1005
01:38:07,673 --> 01:38:09,591
We must do more than this.

1006
01:38:10,467 --> 01:38:14,178
We must totally destroy all
spice production on Arrakis.

1007
01:38:15,764 --> 01:38:19,350
The Guild and the entire
Universe depends on spice.

1008
01:38:20,811 --> 01:38:23,813
He who can destroy a thing,
controls a thing.

1009
01:38:25,149 --> 01:38:27,942
I will take 100 of your
warriors and train them.

1010
01:38:28,652 --> 01:38:31,321
This 100 will train
the thousands that remain.

1011
01:38:32,364 --> 01:38:34,824
When the spice flow stops,

1012
01:38:34,909 --> 01:38:37,535
all eyes
will turn to Arrakis.

1013
01:38:38,162 --> 01:38:40,121
The Baron
and the Emperor himself

1014
01:38:40,205 --> 01:38:42,040
will be forced
to deal with us.

1015
01:38:45,252 --> 01:38:49,714
Arrakis will become
the center of the Universe.

1016
01:38:52,092 --> 01:38:53,176
Orato!

1017
01:38:57,181 --> 01:39:00,725
This obelisk is of
your hardest stone.

1018
01:39:02,686 --> 01:39:03,686
Kick it.

1019
01:39:10,611 --> 01:39:11,611
Hit it.

1020
01:39:17,159 --> 01:39:18,159
Yell at it.

1021
01:39:24,041 --> 01:39:25,458
Break!

1022
01:39:27,711 --> 01:39:30,296
Korba, cut it.

1023
01:39:43,686 --> 01:39:44,686
Move back.

1024
01:40:14,091 --> 01:40:15,883
This is part
of the weirding way

1025
01:40:15,968 --> 01:40:17,510
that we will teach you.

1026
01:40:20,097 --> 01:40:23,599
Some thoughts
have a certain sound,

1027
01:40:24,518 --> 01:40:26,769
that being
the equivalent to a form.

1028
01:40:27,396 --> 01:40:29,522
Through sound and motion,

1029
01:40:29,940 --> 01:40:34,068
you will be able to paralyze
nerves, shatter bones,

1030
01:40:34,486 --> 01:40:38,781
set fires, suffocate an
enemy, or burst his organs.

1031
01:40:39,366 --> 01:40:40,450
We will kill

1032
01:40:40,534 --> 01:40:43,536
until no Harkonnen
breathes Arrakeen air.

1033
01:40:43,662 --> 01:40:46,080
Muad'Dib!

1034
01:40:48,042 --> 01:40:51,127
Chaaksa.

1035
01:40:56,592 --> 01:40:57,800
Stilgar.

1036
01:41:00,512 --> 01:41:01,721
Muad'Dib.

1037
01:41:01,805 --> 01:41:02,805
Hmm?

1038
01:41:02,890 --> 01:41:05,850
- Muad'Dib. Muad'Dib.
- Muad'Dib. Muad'Dib.

1039
01:41:10,230 --> 01:41:12,648
My name is a killing word.

1040
01:41:13,734 --> 01:41:15,318
They are ready to fight.

1041
01:41:15,402 --> 01:41:16,986
Yet in order to lead them,

1042
01:41:17,112 --> 01:41:20,698
I must conquer the worm,
conquer Shai-Hulud.

1043
01:41:30,334 --> 01:41:33,086
Take the kiswa maker hook
of our sietch,

1044
01:41:33,837 --> 01:41:36,089
and ride
as a leader of men.

1045
01:41:52,064 --> 01:41:54,690
Shai-Hulud.

1046
01:42:34,898 --> 01:42:38,401
I must not fear.
Fear is the mind killer.

1047
01:42:46,910 --> 01:42:49,704
Only the very strong ones
travel this deep.

1048
01:42:50,372 --> 01:42:52,915
Usul has called a big one!

1049
01:42:53,417 --> 01:42:56,085
Again, it is the legend.

1050
01:44:34,351 --> 01:44:36,102
Muad'Dib!

1051
01:45:08,885 --> 01:45:12,471
Usul, these are 15
of our finest warriors

1052
01:45:12,889 --> 01:45:15,975
to serve you
as your guard.

1053
01:45:20,939 --> 01:45:22,398
The Fedaykin.

1054
01:45:36,371 --> 01:45:37,371
Now.

1055
01:46:03,648 --> 01:46:07,151
When the spice flow stops,
all eyes will turn to Arrakis.

1056
01:46:07,944 --> 01:46:09,695
The Baron
and the Emperor himself

1057
01:46:09,780 --> 01:46:11,405
will be forced
to deal with us.

1058
01:46:15,410 --> 01:46:17,912
Muad'Dib. Muad'Dib.

1059
01:46:17,996 --> 01:46:19,872
Muad'Dib.
Muad'Dib.

1060
01:46:19,956 --> 01:46:21,499
What happened?
Muad'Dib.

1061
01:46:21,666 --> 01:46:23,542
What happened to you
and your men?

1062
01:46:23,627 --> 01:46:24,919
Muad'Dib!

1063
01:46:25,003 --> 01:46:26,712
What are you saying?
What are you saying?

1064
01:46:26,797 --> 01:46:29,924
Muad'Dib! Muad'Dib!

1065
01:46:31,968 --> 01:46:35,471
He's been repeating that name
ever since we found him.

1066
01:46:35,555 --> 01:46:39,558
Who is this Muad'Dib?

1067
01:46:46,191 --> 01:46:49,068
In the two standard years
that followed,

1068
01:46:49,152 --> 01:46:50,528
Muad'Dib and the Fremen

1069
01:46:50,612 --> 01:46:53,614
brought spice production
to a standstill.

1070
01:46:54,032 --> 01:46:56,700
Fearing for his life,
Rabban did his best

1071
01:46:56,785 --> 01:47:00,037
to hide this fact
from his uncle, the Baron.

1072
01:47:06,837 --> 01:47:10,089
Paul's sister Alia matured
at a frightening rate.

1073
01:47:10,465 --> 01:47:13,509
Her small body harbored
tremendous powers.

1074
01:47:14,511 --> 01:47:17,138
Paul and Chant's love grew.

1075
01:47:22,644 --> 01:47:24,270
We surprised
a band of smugglers.

1076
01:47:24,354 --> 01:47:26,522
Too bad. I thought
they were Harkonnen.

1077
01:47:39,035 --> 01:47:40,202
Gurney!

1078
01:47:43,707 --> 01:47:46,459
You've no need of your weapons
with me, Gurney Halleek.

1079
01:47:47,210 --> 01:47:48,210
Paul.

1080
01:47:50,338 --> 01:47:51,338
Paul!

1081
01:47:51,423 --> 01:47:53,090
Don't you trust
your own eyes?

1082
01:47:53,216 --> 01:47:54,925
They said you were dead.

1083
01:47:57,554 --> 01:47:58,554
They...

1084
01:47:59,514 --> 01:48:00,514
They said...

1085
01:48:06,229 --> 01:48:08,272
Gurney! Gurney! Gurney!
You young pup!

1086
01:48:08,356 --> 01:48:09,315
Gurney!

1087
01:48:09,399 --> 01:48:10,399
You young pup!

1088
01:48:27,667 --> 01:48:29,793
Emperor Shaddam lV,

1089
01:48:29,878 --> 01:48:31,754
you have one last chance

1090
01:48:31,838 --> 01:48:33,839
to take matters
into your own hands,

1091
01:48:33,924 --> 01:48:37,259
and bring the situation
under control on Arrakis.

1092
01:48:37,344 --> 01:48:38,552
What do you mean,
one last...

1093
01:48:38,637 --> 01:48:39,845
Silence. Do not speak.

1094
01:48:39,930 --> 01:48:43,807
Listen. You do not have more
than this one chance.

1095
01:48:44,100 --> 01:48:46,685
I represent the entire Guild
in this matter.

1096
01:48:47,437 --> 01:48:48,687
Our navigators warn you

1097
01:48:48,772 --> 01:48:51,315
that spice production
is in great danger.

1098
01:48:51,399 --> 01:48:53,400
A new Fremen leader,
Muad'Dib,

1099
01:48:53,485 --> 01:48:55,819
has stopped spice mining
on Arrakis.

1100
01:48:56,112 --> 01:48:59,406
Our navigators suggest
he is not of Arrakis.

1101
01:48:59,491 --> 01:49:02,243
No one on the outside world
has been able to see him.

1102
01:49:02,536 --> 01:49:04,620
We do not know
who he is.

1103
01:49:04,829 --> 01:49:06,956
The Harkonnens
cannot stop him.

1104
01:49:07,916 --> 01:49:11,377
Remedy this situation,
restore spice production,

1105
01:49:11,461 --> 01:49:14,463
or you'll live out your life
in a pain amplifier.

1106
01:49:22,472 --> 01:49:23,931
The Emperor will stop him.

1107
01:49:24,015 --> 01:49:25,975
He won't take
the Water of Life.

1108
01:49:26,810 --> 01:49:28,978
That's why
they want me killed.

1109
01:49:29,062 --> 01:49:31,480
They're afraid
I'll take the Water of Life.

1110
01:49:32,649 --> 01:49:36,110
I want 50 legions of Sardaukar
on Arrakis at once!

1111
01:49:36,486 --> 01:49:38,070
50 legions?

1112
01:49:38,196 --> 01:49:39,822
That's our entire
reserves as well.

1113
01:49:39,906 --> 01:49:41,156
This is genocide,

1114
01:49:41,241 --> 01:49:43,284
the deliberate
and systematic destruction

1115
01:49:43,368 --> 01:49:45,703
of all life on Arrakis!

1116
01:49:47,289 --> 01:49:50,791
- The Emperor is coming!
- Chani! Chani!

1117
01:49:53,336 --> 01:49:57,339
You were calling my name.
It frightened me.

1118
01:49:58,300 --> 01:49:59,466
Oh, Chani.

1119
01:50:00,802 --> 01:50:03,012
All the images
of my future are gone.

1120
01:50:05,599 --> 01:50:08,017
I have to drink
the Water of Life.

1121
01:50:08,268 --> 01:50:10,686
No, Paul, please.

1122
01:50:11,146 --> 01:50:12,896
I've seen the men
who have tried.

1123
01:50:13,023 --> 01:50:14,773
I've seen how they died.

1124
01:50:14,858 --> 01:50:18,694
I'm dead to everyone unless
I try to become what I may be.

1125
01:50:21,698 --> 01:50:24,199
Only the Water of Life
will free what can save us.

1126
01:50:30,874 --> 01:50:32,833
I must drink
the sacred water.

1127
01:50:36,129 --> 01:50:37,713
I must go now.

1128
01:51:32,644 --> 01:51:35,938
Hurry. All I see
is darkness.

1129
01:51:36,940 --> 01:51:37,940
Paul.

1130
01:51:40,694 --> 01:51:45,114
I will love you forever.
You are my life.

1131
01:51:55,291 --> 01:51:56,583
You are my life.

1132
01:52:03,174 --> 01:52:05,217
Many men have tried.

1133
01:52:05,802 --> 01:52:07,845
They tried and failed?

1134
01:52:07,971 --> 01:52:09,638
They tried and died.

1135
01:52:18,356 --> 01:52:20,232
The worm is the spice.

1136
01:52:20,316 --> 01:52:22,234
The spice is the worm.

1137
01:52:42,422 --> 01:52:44,506
The worms.

1138
01:53:01,149 --> 01:53:03,484
They're not attacking.
Why?

1139
01:53:22,378 --> 01:53:23,545
Alia.

1140
01:53:25,215 --> 01:53:26,340
Mother.

1141
01:53:28,384 --> 01:53:30,219
It's Paul.

1142
01:53:32,639 --> 01:53:35,474
He's taken
the Water of Life.

1143
01:53:45,568 --> 01:53:49,905
There is a place,
terrifying to us,

1144
01:53:50,698 --> 01:53:51,740
to women.

1145
01:53:52,075 --> 01:53:54,743
This is the place
they cannot look.

1146
01:54:01,751 --> 01:54:04,795
Traveling without moving.

1147
01:54:06,422 --> 01:54:09,007
Now I truly
control the worm

1148
01:54:10,260 --> 01:54:12,052
and the spice.

1149
01:54:13,263 --> 01:54:17,432
And I have the power
to destroy the spice forever!

1150
01:54:47,839 --> 01:54:51,133
Paul.

1151
01:55:01,060 --> 01:55:07,024
Father!

1152
01:55:07,525 --> 01:55:10,485
The sleeper has awakened!

1153
01:55:19,120 --> 01:55:21,121
Muad'Dib.

1154
01:55:28,922 --> 01:55:32,507
Arrakis, Dune,

1155
01:55:34,552 --> 01:55:35,802
Desert Planet.

1156
01:55:37,555 --> 01:55:39,556
Your time has come.

1157
01:55:40,350 --> 01:55:42,184
A storm is coming.

1158
01:55:43,019 --> 01:55:44,519
Our storm.

1159
01:55:46,022 --> 01:55:49,316
And when it arrives,
it will shake the Universe.

1160
01:55:51,861 --> 01:55:55,489
Emperor, we come for you!

1161
01:55:57,492 --> 01:55:59,159
We come for you!

1162
01:56:13,841 --> 01:56:16,635
Long live the fighters!

1163
01:56:16,719 --> 01:56:19,972
Long live the fighters!

1164
01:56:51,295 --> 01:56:52,838
Suspicion confirmed.

1165
01:56:52,922 --> 01:56:54,923
The Emperor's
had Rabban seized.

1166
01:57:37,967 --> 01:57:40,761
Gurney, when the storm hits,
set off the atomics.

1167
01:57:41,971 --> 01:57:44,890
I want an opening through
the entire shield wall.

1168
01:57:46,476 --> 01:57:49,269
Stilgar,
do we have wormsign?

1169
01:57:52,440 --> 01:57:53,857
Usul, we have wormsign,

1170
01:57:53,941 --> 01:57:56,485
the likes of which
even God has never seen.

1171
01:58:52,875 --> 01:58:56,962
Bring in that
floating fat man, the Baron.

1172
01:59:13,229 --> 01:59:15,063
Why have you
brought me here?

1173
01:59:15,231 --> 01:59:18,733
Your Highness,
there must be some mistake.

1174
01:59:19,360 --> 01:59:20,986
I never requested
your presence.

1175
01:59:21,237 --> 01:59:22,237
Ah.

1176
01:59:22,738 --> 01:59:25,073
But your lack of action
demanded it.

1177
01:59:25,158 --> 01:59:27,534
Your dreadful mismanagement,
your bad judgment

1178
01:59:27,618 --> 01:59:30,704
in assigning to Rabban
the governorship.

1179
01:59:31,122 --> 01:59:32,330
You've forced me
to come here

1180
01:59:32,415 --> 01:59:35,000
and set things straight,
personally.

1181
01:59:45,261 --> 01:59:49,222
I am a messenger
from Muad'Dib.

1182
01:59:49,849 --> 01:59:51,641
Poor Emperor.

1183
01:59:52,143 --> 01:59:55,937
I'm afraid my brother won't
be very pleased with you.

1184
01:59:56,022 --> 01:59:57,147
Silence!

1185
01:59:57,440 --> 01:59:59,441
Kill this child.
She's an abomination.

1186
01:59:59,650 --> 02:00:01,651
Kill her. Kill her.

1187
02:00:01,861 --> 02:00:04,738
Get out of my mind!

1188
02:00:04,822 --> 02:00:07,449
Not until
you tell them both

1189
02:00:07,533 --> 02:00:10,577
who I really am.

1190
02:00:12,163 --> 02:00:13,455
Alia,

1191
02:00:15,625 --> 02:00:18,793
daughter of Duke Leto
the Just,

1192
02:00:19,086 --> 02:00:22,297
and the royal
Lady Jessica.

1193
02:00:22,798 --> 02:00:24,007
Sister

1194
02:00:24,926 --> 02:00:28,678
of Paul Muad'Dib.

1195
02:00:28,804 --> 02:00:32,599
Paul's sister?
Paul is Muad'Dib?

1196
02:00:37,563 --> 02:00:39,481
Alia keeps pace
with the storm.

1197
02:00:44,528 --> 02:00:47,489
With the storm, their air
power will be useless.

1198
02:00:48,074 --> 02:00:51,034
On Arrakish
it's desert power.

1199
02:00:51,327 --> 02:00:52,327
Gurney.

1200
02:00:54,121 --> 02:00:55,121
Now!

1201
02:00:55,206 --> 02:00:56,331
Atomics!

1202
02:01:31,909 --> 02:01:37,038
My brother is coming
with many Fremen warriors.

1203
02:01:38,582 --> 02:01:39,749
Impossible!

1204
02:01:39,959 --> 02:01:41,960
Not impossible.

1205
02:01:42,044 --> 02:01:45,338
I told you.
He is here now.

1206
02:01:52,263 --> 02:01:55,432
Father, today
I will avenge your death.

1207
02:02:19,123 --> 02:02:22,250
Emperor, an impassable storm
has descended.

1208
02:02:22,376 --> 02:02:25,462
The Shield Wall has been
penetrated by atomics.

1209
02:02:27,214 --> 02:02:28,548
Release the Sardaukar.

1210
02:02:29,008 --> 02:02:33,553
Baron, give this little
abomination to the storm.

1211
02:02:34,513 --> 02:02:37,098
Wait for my brother, Baron.

1212
02:03:24,480 --> 02:03:25,605
Chaa!

1213
02:04:21,036 --> 02:04:22,036
Cha.

1214
02:04:24,498 --> 02:04:26,082
Wait for my brother.

1215
02:04:32,631 --> 02:04:35,467
Cha!

1216
02:04:39,847 --> 02:04:41,973
Muad'Dib!

1217
02:05:23,265 --> 02:05:28,269
Eee-sah!

1218
02:05:32,066 --> 02:05:33,066
Cha!

1219
02:05:37,863 --> 02:05:39,322
Alia, now.

1220
02:05:39,406 --> 02:05:41,115
Come to meh Baron.

1221
02:06:55,357 --> 02:06:57,025
Muad'Dib!

1222
02:07:42,071 --> 02:07:43,905
Feyd Rautha.

1223
02:07:44,073 --> 02:07:46,741
Emperor Shaddam IV,

1224
02:07:46,825 --> 02:07:48,701
there are Guild Heighliners
above us,

1225
02:07:48,786 --> 02:07:51,245
containing many Great Houses
of the Landsraad.

1226
02:07:51,455 --> 02:07:52,830
Send them back.

1227
02:07:52,915 --> 02:07:54,832
How dare
you speak to me in...

1228
02:07:54,917 --> 02:07:56,793
Stop your speaking.

1229
02:07:58,921 --> 02:08:00,963
You have some idea
of what I could do.

1230
02:08:04,134 --> 02:08:07,011
Don't try your powers on me.

1231
02:08:08,138 --> 02:08:10,431
Try looking into that place
where you dare not look.

1232
02:08:10,516 --> 02:08:12,517
You'll find me there
staring back at you.

1233
02:08:12,601 --> 02:08:14,102
You mustn't speak...

1234
02:08:14,186 --> 02:08:15,353
Silence!

1235
02:08:18,732 --> 02:08:20,566
I remember your gom jabbar.

1236
02:08:21,694 --> 02:08:23,403
Now you'll remember mine.

1237
02:08:23,487 --> 02:08:25,279
I can kill with a word.

1238
02:08:27,783 --> 02:08:30,743
And his word shall carry
death eternal

1239
02:08:31,078 --> 02:08:33,204
to those who stand
against the righteous.

1240
02:08:33,288 --> 02:08:34,706
The righteous?

1241
02:08:34,790 --> 02:08:36,749
There is
a Harkonnen among you.

1242
02:08:39,503 --> 02:08:43,423
Give the Harkonnen a blade,
and let him stand forth.

1243
02:08:43,507 --> 02:08:44,632
If Feyd wishes,

1244
02:08:44,717 --> 02:08:47,051
he can meet you
with my blade in his hand.

1245
02:08:47,136 --> 02:08:48,386
I wish it.

1246
02:08:48,470 --> 02:08:50,471
This is a Harkonnen animal.

1247
02:08:51,432 --> 02:08:53,891
Let me. Please, my lord.

1248
02:08:54,226 --> 02:08:56,144
The Emperor's blade.

1249
02:09:26,675 --> 02:09:29,427
Why prolong the inevitable?

1250
02:09:31,972 --> 02:09:33,347
I will kill you.

1251
02:09:49,156 --> 02:09:50,698
I will kill him!

1252
02:09:57,706 --> 02:09:58,706
Paul!

1253
02:10:00,125 --> 02:10:01,959
I will kill him!

1254
02:10:11,553 --> 02:10:15,181
Who is the little one?
A pet, perhaps?

1255
02:10:16,391 --> 02:10:19,227
Will she deserve
my special attentions?

1256
02:10:26,485 --> 02:10:27,610
Poisoned.

1257
02:10:30,823 --> 02:10:33,658
You see your death.

1258
02:10:34,409 --> 02:10:36,077
My blade will finish you.

1259
02:10:38,622 --> 02:10:41,916
I will bend like
a reed in the wind.

1260
02:10:57,140 --> 02:10:58,140
Chaaksa!

1261
02:11:06,191 --> 02:11:07,733
Muad'Dib.

1262
02:11:08,569 --> 02:11:10,695
Usul no longer needs
the weirding module.

1263
02:11:12,072 --> 02:11:14,949
Muad'Dib had become
the hand of God,

1264
02:11:15,659 --> 02:11:17,869
fulfilling
the Fremen prophecy.

1265
02:11:18,453 --> 02:11:19,537
Where there was war,

1266
02:11:19,621 --> 02:11:22,039
Muad'Dib would
now bring peace.

1267
02:11:22,374 --> 02:11:25,751
Where there was hatred,
Muad'Dib would bring love,

1268
02:11:26,253 --> 02:11:28,588
to lead the people
to true freedom,

1269
02:11:29,381 --> 02:11:32,466
and to change
the face of Arrakis.

1270
02:11:35,971 --> 02:11:37,889
We Fremen have a saying.

1271
02:11:38,974 --> 02:11:41,976
God created Arrakis
to train the faithful.

1272
02:11:43,478 --> 02:11:46,105
One cannot go
against the word of God.

1273
02:12:43,872 --> 02:12:45,831
And how can this be?

1274
02:12:48,377 --> 02:12:51,796
For he is
the Kwisatz Haderach.

