Everyday I spend my time
Drinking wine, feeling fine
Waiting here to find the sign
That I can understand
Yes I am
So everyday I spend my time
Drinking wine, feeling fine
Waiting here to find the sign
That I should take it slow
Off again did he go
To another dimension my mind
Body, soul imprisoned my eye
Probably going ballistic but listen
I'm missing a couple of screws
They ain't never do dreaming true
You been sipping away at the truth
But besides the wisdom I do-do-do
Rolling do, hitting switches,
rolling ditches, blowing kisses
To the, hold the biscuits,
what's the business, Beat the system
cold defendants, Blow the symptoms
go to prison, Go to church and pray
to father Lord forgive us
And only God can judge me
And he don't like no ugly
I look so good most
dykes'll me buddy
Yeah I'm a piece of shit
I know I plead the fifth
I tell her holla if ya need some
The devotion its getting hopeless
Behold it I'm getting closest
My soul is I'm seeing ghosts
A solo is now a poet
Hypnosis overdose on potions
Adjusting to the motions
- And getting out all my emotions
- Everyday..
I spend my time
Drinking wine,
feeling fine
Waiting here to find the sign
That I can understand
Yes I am
So everyday
I spend my time
Drinking wine,
feeling fine
Waiting here
to find the sign
That I should take it slow
This type of shit make a
nigga wanna flip September through August
This type of shit got em busting off
the clipin the middle of the office
And a message to the bosses
The Misfits new outfit is on the bloglist
Gorgeous hoes,
keep the saying that they cost it
For the Porsche's
get em nauseous
Hope they show me in my good shoes
When papa got the brand new bag
Flacko got the brand new Raf,
that's good news
"Hood dudes usually don't look like you"
How it feel to get a deal and come back
And the whole hood look like you?
Screamin', "Pimp Squad, hold it down!"
Can't drive
I'm legally blind
If I live or die,
it's up to me to decide
Shit, niggas coppin' guns like
they legal to buy
The only key to survive and
get a piece of the pie
Is to agree with a lot or
just believe a facade
And I'll be fine just-a drinkin' my wine
I got the love birds chirpin'
at the window
But I don't need love no mo
I'll be fine
Sipping wine
Taking time
Slow
I got the love birds chirpin'
out the window
But I don't need love no mo
I'll be fine
Sipping wine
So everyday I
spend my time
Drinking wine
feeling fine
Waiting here to find the sign
That I can understand
Yes I am
Everyday I
spend my time
Drinking wine,
feeling fine
Waiting here to
find the sign
I don't care if I
ever know.
I got the love birds chirpin' at the window
But I don't need love no more,
oh, no
I'll be fine, sippin' wine
Takin' time slow
I got the love birds chirpin'
at the window
But I don't need love no more,
oh, no
I'll be fine, sippin' wine
Takin' time
slow
Subtitled by Asmita