And I, I wouldn't trade it for the world, world, world
And I, Just so fucking lucky you're my girl, girl, girl
And I, I wouldn't trade it for anything
No, no, no not anything and you
Yeah, I got a brand new Benz
Crazy right, brand new Benz
Got less miles on it than I do friends
Remember when we laid at you and Paige's crib
Was there so long I coulda paid rent
Remember when we couldn't get shit?
Best thing bout being broke is you don't spend shit
Remember that Christmas? We had a wish list
We couldn't afford nothin' but we still get shit ironically
Those were the times I felt the richest
All those times that we spent by the pool girl
Was too broke to even take you to the zoo girl
Maybe it's because I had you girl
Was thinking about when we went to London and Paris
And gave each other times that we cherished
Remember when you saw the Eiffel Tower
And you got so drunk threw up? Yup you were so embarrassed
See those are times I can't let go, I can't let go
Man I hate to see you single in the club looking for kisses and hugs
So you Sipping on XO til I snatch you up like "let's go"
And I, I wouldn't trade it for the world, world, world
And I, Just so fucking lucky you're my girl, girl, girl
And I, I wouldn't trade it for anything
No, no, no not anything and you
Can't nobody do it like, do it like, do it like
My bad for those long long nights, long nights when I left you in the sheets
Sorry for when you had to cry yourself to sleep
Tried to count on me and I made you count sheep
Sorry when you put your faith in me I was unfaithful, disgraceful, distasteful
Yeah I know you're not supposed to hate cake and eat it too
Crazy how these hoes always kept my plate full
What about the emails you hacked in?
I know we hate to live in the past-tense
It's been weird since I went out west and did an album with No I.D and ain't came back since
Now we the best in the city, I rep for the city
That's about the time that you left for the city
You and all your girls moved to NY,
I shoulda' known now how you watch sex and the city
I know we ain't close but, I gotta focus on blowing up
I know I promised that I'd be there, and really did I ever show up?
I know I wasn't honest to ya girl
Almost broke every promise to ya girl, Brought problems to your world
And you said "how could you just lie to me? I thought you'd die for me?"
I was scared you'd find somebody who would treat you like they're supposed to
You the type niggas get close to, get close to, and then propose to
And when thanksgivings come around,
I ain't tryna bring hoes through to momma
So it's back to the drama,
"No I don't know that number"
"Why the hell you text it?"
Heartbreak hotel man, with no exit just checked in
Young and living reckless
And I, I wouldn't trade it for the world, world, world
And I, Just so fucking lucky you're my girl, girl, girl
And I, I wouldn't trade it for anything
No, no, no not anything and you
Can't nobody do it like, do it like, do it like
I can't imagine myself without you
I need a whole lot of help without you
Me and my granny both agree
Damn you're such a G I'll hold you down forever, B
And I, I wouldn't trade it for the world, world, world
And I, Just so fucking lucky you're my girl, girl, girl
And I, I wouldn't trade it for anything
No, no, no not anything and you
Can't nobody do it like, do it like, do it like
My bad for those long long nights, long nights