Hello.
We're here with a woman who alleges
to be my mother.
I don't buy it for a minute.
But this is how we'll find out.
I have proof.
You have films.
I have films and I have a certificate.
You have the films that I'm happy.
Oh, yes. Well, because you doubted it for so long.
You knew that I was gonna doubt it later,
so you filmed me being happy.
No, I thought that if you filmed children,
and you had happy children
and then you filmed it--
- Exposure!
- Who knew when you were going to grow up
and say, "I'm very unhappy,"
and "That's a fake film," that I made it up.
This is getting so ugly so fast.
You have to try to concentrate
on the fact that you did have,
sometimes, good times.
I know that I did!
I had a very good time.
See how you yelled?
At your mother?
What about Todd?
Do you like Todd better than me?
No. It's just that you're different.
- Every child is different, so--
- I don't buy this.
You never bought anything that I said, so...
Okay, what does he get in the will and what do I get?
Oh, I'm not gonna tell anybody that.
If we lived together, we would argue.
Yes.
It's possible.
How long has it been done for?
I'm done for.
Ugh!
Fucking criminy!
I'm gonna go help my mother pack.
My mother is performing a show in Connecticut.
I tried to stop her,
but that is like throwing yourself in front of a...
Oh, what are those called?
Not tiramisus.
Tsunami. See?
She's "Tsu-Mommy."
And I threw myself in front of Tsu-Mommy,
and it didn't work.
She loves doing it when she's doing it,
but afterwards, she was laying on the floor, so...
But in a good, dignified, movie star way.
Mother and I live next door to each other,
separated by one daunting hill.
I usually come to her.
I always come to her.
Mommy!
Mommy, I'm home!
Hello!
Where--
look, you cannot keep that phone.
It's ridiculous.
That's from the early '90s, when they first invented cell phones.
- But I--
- That was one of the originals.
I don't want to buy a new one.
The old phone works fine.
Just dandy.
- It's horrible.
- Oh! There she is.
- Look. Look at all the--
- Do you know how to do it?
- No. No one knows how to use those anymore.
That is a beautiful puff.
Thank you for the beautiful soufflé.
- I love it.
- Is it good?
You want to sing with me?
Debbie, what do you wear in the show?
A very heavy beaded dress.
It is quite beautiful.
It's beautiful,
but it weighs more than she does.
It does weigh--
it does weigh about 50 pounds.
- But it's so beautiful.
- Worth it!
Now, that's-- that's Elizabeth's.
This belonged to...
I bought that at Elizabeth Taylor's auction.
- I won it.
- This is when-- during her muumuu phase.
Yeah. Well, it's pretty, really.
Look.
It has a drag queen element.
Oh, now, just do what your mother says.
It makes life easier.
As if.
- Yeah.
- All right.
You remember me? I'm your mother.
- I remember.
- Tammy, Tammy...
I keep you very close, so--
constant reminder.
Is this for the show?
I forgot I had it.
That's what's good about losing your memory
is there's so many surprises in the world.
I have found some things work.
Not enough.
There's never enough Listerine.
I'm gonna go fill it. I'm just gonna go fill it.
Remember, we had a relative that drank Listerine...
- She was an alcoholic.
- ...and 18 bottles of vanilla.
- Okay.
- That's it. That's all.
Okay, look.
Turn around this way because your rear end
is to the camera.
Oh, my God.
I don't like not knowing what's happening.
- I worry a little.
- That's very sweet.
I worry what the show costs you.
That's all. I know you like to do it.
I have caught up with a few people in age.
Whoa!
But they're in bed and you're doing a show.
Like George Burns says,
I'm gonna stay on stage until I drop dead.
And then I'm gonna have myself stuffed,
like Trigger,
and then I'll put me in a museum.
- That's nice.
- Do you like that?
Or we could just leave this house...
I totally understand why she's doing it,
and it makes me nervous.
She'll forget she's not 35.
You know, it doesn't make sense to her
that her body isn't cooperating.
And she just thinks if she ignores it,
it'll go away.
Everything in me
demands that my mother be as she always was,
even if that way is irritating.
She just can't change.
That's the rule.
And she's fucking with me.
Age is--
it's horrible for all of us,
but she falls from a greater height.
Debbie's light goes to the ears.
- Yes or no?
- Yes.
Okay. You know, all this stuff
is, like, blocked in your template.
And I think I only got nervous once
when I performed for the Queen of England.
I went over with Bob Hope to do a show,
and I did get a little nervous there.
The crown, the jewels kind of threw me a little bit.
But as a rule, I don't--
I don't get nervous.
I just have a good time.
I've been doing this my whole life.
You know, I started performing when I was 16.
Will you know your set already and everything?
Oh, yes, I'm all set.
I carry my script in my beat-up folder.
You can see how beat up.
And all the edges are all worn out.
And if you can make people smile a little,
laugh a little,
just enjoy themselves for a moment...
It's not "Macbeth," you know.
How are you tonight?
You're such a nice, attractive audience.
Now, you don't mind if I come out, do you?
See, I like to visit with you.
Otherwise, I'm stuck up there.
I've seen my act. Good evening.
I used to go out in the audience.
I used to do that.
I used to wear a girdle, too,
and I don't do that anymore.
So, it's like the old days, in a way,
but I'm like the old days, so...
Can you do me a favor while you're down there?
Yeah?
- You see that toe?
- Uh-huh.
That has to come around.
That...
See that? It has to go to the--
- Underneath?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm pulling
your leg, huh?
I have to do it. Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, Kevin is gonna do, like, an introductory thing.
Five minutes, yeah.
Yeah. So, when do you want him to start?
When?
But David's already asked me this.
Oh, he did? He didn't tell him, though.
- Now.
Go!
Oh!
I look around and I see all you nice men.
You're very sweet. I'm sure you're nice.
It's just that if there's a nice guy around,
I'm not gonna find him.
- You remember Eddie Fisher?
- Yes.
Carrie told me, "Mommy, doesn't--
doesn't it start to look like Eddie's the good one?"
After Eddie, I married again.
He was very rich, too. That was helpful.
I thought that was very nice.
But then I found out, after we were married,
he was a gamble-oholic, and he lost all of his money.
I should have married Burt Reynolds.
I wouldn't have to change my last name.
And we could share wigs.
So, I thought, I'll bring along
some of my first movies.
We had a lot of fun in those days.
Now, this is my one little hit.
It's called "Tammy."
Here we go.
Start over again.
Maybe something will come out.
People were loving it. That was so awesome.
Okay, we're going this way, though.
Great.
Good.
Okay.
And...
one more.
Okay.
Boom!
- Debbie, that was amazing!
- It wasn't easy.
Debbie, that was...
It is very frustrating for her,
because inside, my mom is the same person.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for having me.
And she doesn't want to retire.
She does not want to retire.
You were great.
Performing gives her life.
It feeds her in a way that family cannot.
That's why I think it-- we've always been frustrating.
Because... it's not--
people aren't cooperative,
audiences are.
When you're her, they are.
Where are you? Come here. Come on.
Come on. Junie, don't you want to see the kid?
Come on, sing it for your old mother.
Besides, I have to retire soon.
I had been singing in my mother's act since I was about 13.
Would you sing my favorite for me?
It's for Junie and Jerry.
Don't say no.
Just sing right out.
Whoo!
My mother wanted to be able to groom me
for show business.
The biggest thing I did that broke my mother's heart
was not do a nightclub act.
My mother would say, "Do drugs.
Do whatever you need to do.
But why don't you sing?"
That was my big rebellion.
Carrie's daddy, Eddie, had a great voice, you know.
Really beautiful voice.
I guess she doesn't want to be Eddie
and she doesn't want to be Debbie.
She wants to be Carrie, so she'll do it her way.
I love that voice.
Isn't that a great voice?
I wish I had it.
Take a bow, take a bow, take a bow.
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
That's not bad for a 15-year-old, is it?
So, this is the compound.
It was built by Robert Armstrong, who was in "King Kong,"
who said, "'Twas beauty killed the beast."
I've lived in this for--  let me see--
20 years.
This is the lobby.
This is where early mornings are spent
with people who drink coffee.
And there's a hummingbird nest.
Look how teeny.
This is the bathroom.
It has, as a lot of bathrooms should,
a player piano in it.
This is Bette Davis when she lived here.
This is my suitcase, Robert.
Oh.
Ugly children portraiture.
They did this thing in the last century
where they dressed boys in girls' clothing.
He looks like Ross Perot in red.
Shia LaBeouf as a Dutch underage prostitute.
And Richard Dreyfuss
as a young girl wielding a rose.
Richard likes that.
Now, this just happens to be probably an unhappy woman
that looks like Kevin Spacey.
They sold this on the Internet
as a Princess Leia sex doll.
Maybe this.
There's no way of accounting for it.
My daughter, Billie.
My brother and myself.
And Billie.
And my mother and Judy Garland.
And my friend, Charlie, at the dentist
with his mouth widely displayed.
My house-- I love it.
It's like scavenger hunting.
And my mother--
there's part of it she kind of tolerates.
"Well, this is just Carrie's thing."
This is the opposite of the house that I grew up in.
The house we lived in was very grand
when I was growing up.
It was marble and glass.
Cold.
And there was just too much air in it.
Family-wise, we didn't grow up with each other,
we grew up around each other.
You know, like trees.
My mother, she worked a lot.
And then Harry, her husband at the time,
he was the original fancy-man, rich guy.
It was a prototype life.
We were getting ready for a photoshoot
all the time.
And that's what Todd and I shared.
Todd and I had a shared history of weirdness.
Yes?
Who is it?
- Come in.
- Hi! I just wanted to say hi.
She brought her chicken in. Speaking of science fiction.
- Hello.
- We've never met.
And this is Nugget.
He travels everywhere with her.
He goes everywhere with me 'cause he's my emotional wellness chicken.
And he's just--
We're gonna get him a service tag
so he can be a service chicken.
I have to drive everywhere currently...
- With a harness.
- ...because they won't let chickens fly.
What? Yeah.
- He's my boy.
- That's right.
Sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt you.
No, I was just telling the poster story.
In fact, I was telling her the only reason why we bought this house
was so I could hang my posters somewhere.
So, I decided I would tell a story on this wall.
My mother made this movie called "Singin' in the Rain," down there,
and that's an original "Singin' in the Rain" poster.
Then she went on to do "Tammy and the Bachelor,"
where she sings the song "Tammy."
Then she makes a movie with Frank Sinatra called "The Tender Trap."
And in this-- while she's making this movie,
Frank Sinatra says, "Now, Debbie, whatever you do,
do not marry a singer, whatever you do."
So, she goes right out and marries the singer, my dad, Eddie Fisher.
Then my dad ran off with Elizabeth Taylor
and became a producer on "Cleopatra."
Then my dad goes on and marries Liz,
and of course they make the movie "BUtterfield 8."
So, that's the story of my life
in a certain amount of posters.
Do you know what's funny, is Debbie,
when she first came in here, she went,
- "How can you allow this?"
- Right, too many Debbie posters.
"To many Debbie posters. Where's your stuff?" She's just so awesome.
And I was like, where else am I gonna put your stuff?
Or what else are we gonna do with it?
Sooner or later, it's got to get up on the wall.
Now, when I was younger, "2001: A Space Odyssey" came out
and I was very influenced by how amazing that movie was.
And then, all of a sudden, you know,
Carrie does this little picture called "Star Wars"
she thought was gonna be a B-movie.
I went to the screening with her over at Fox,
and she was hiding in the back with me
'cause she thought it was gonna be a cheesy film.
We are at a lap dance.
Come on, do it a little more.
In the front, the whole thing.
A celebrity lap dance,
which is where celebrities of all shapes and ages
sign autographs for cash prizes.
It's sort of like going to a strip club,
except they don't stuff cash in your underwear.
But that's kind of it.
It's Carrie Fisher, everybody!
Carrie! Carrie!
Hi there. How are you doing?
- Good to meet you.
- That is great.
We'll get a photo later.
- It's a pleasure to... "meat" you.
- Meet me.
- All right, thank you!
- Thank you so much.
Well, she's always been my favorite on "Star Wars" since I was a little kid.
I had a crush on her since I was, like, eight years old.
So, I'd just like to see her, you know?
That's awesome!
That doesn't really look like me in a way.
- Show me where.
- Right up here.
There? How we go...
- Where do you want it?
- Right here.
- Nice and big.
- Yes, sir.
There you go. Thank you.
- I really like your overall look.
- Thank you.
That goes without saying.
Thank you. I like your outfit on you.
- Thank you.
- No bra, though.
I'll remember that next time.
- Hey there.
- Hello.
So, this is one of these things
that we go to at least once a month.
They're kind of a mini Comic-Con.
Carrie resisted these lap dances for years,
but it's amazing!
You see these thousands of people that are behind me here?
Okay, so, they line up at 9:00 in the morning,
they'll stay here until 9:00 at night
just to have two seconds with Carrie.
Yeah, actually, Liz and Matt, please.
- Liz and Matt.
- Yes.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Don't cry. Don't cry.
- Stop it, stop it.
- It was--
- It probably won't sink in for a while.
She's, like, my idol.
- Is she?
- Yeah.
How come?
She just epitomizes a strong woman
who speaks her mind,
doesn't care what anybody else thinks.
And I wish I was more like that.
All right, here we go!
Let's go!
There you go.
Here we go!
They love...
They love you.
Yes. They love her, and I'm her custodian,
and I'm as close as you're gonna get.
She's me and I'm her.
I mean, they talk to me like I'm Princess Leia
who happens to have had all these, you know,
difficult experiences to go through,
and that's like me fighting for the Force.
It's nice. They're nice.
Oh, something's unplugged. I can see it.
I thought this case was top priority.
I was on three episodes of this show
where I played a very pivotal character for the lead character,
and so I've been to a lot of "Knight Rider" conventions.
And when I went there, I realized how much I loved this car,
and I said, "I got to have it."
I think it's important that you, you know,
marry inside the entertainment race.
And, you know, that's an important thing
because people don't get it.
I think you could-- my family, in particular,
could overwhelm most people.
It wasn't just my mother that was super famous.
People forget my dad was a world-class singer.
He had more consecutive hits than the Beatles
and Elvis Presley combined.
At one time, he had 65,000 separate fan clubs.
He had an exclusive contract with Coca Cola.
He was the "Coke Kid."
...T.V.'s even more fun
with a bottle of Coke in hand.
They gave him a percentage of the Pasadena bottling company proceeds.
I mean, he had it made for life.
All he had to do was behave a little bit.
My dad and mom, they were cute as hell together,
and they had the cutest little kids together,
and they were the couple of America.
Obviously, the studio loved that setup.
You know, you put the two of them together,
it's one heck of a marketing tool.
I think my mother really was in love with my father
in a naive, young person way.
First love.
And I think that was the last time
that she ever really experienced that.
- There.
- She's here?
Yeah, outside there.
Hey, Dwight!
Mama! Let's go that way, though.
You look beautiful.
You're wearing the same shoes as I am.
- No, you gave me these.
- I know.
- You don't remember?
- No, I do.
I leave messages.
I know, that's the greatest thing.
- I leave messages on here.
- I wish there was one.
- "I'm here."
- "Go away."
"If you want to come in, come in through the front door."
"It's not a rainy day.
It's my day to be quiet and alone."
Alone is good.
I have to go to my meeting now,
but I just wanted to say hello.
I love you.
I love--  oh, oh, oh, oh.
- I love you.
- I don't know where you're going.
I'm coming up.
And look, our shoes are the same.
- Sing the song.
-  I don't want to go
"I'll be around."
I think I'm my mom's best friend
more than a daughter.
My mother really wants me to be an extension
of her wishes, an extension of her.
And to a great degree,
far more sometimes than I ever would want to,
I know what my mother feels and wants.
And there's a lot of it.
I share everything with my daughter.
That's right.
Especially the check.
- Especially the what?
- Check.
She pays for everything.
Oh, that's-- it's not true.
She gets furious when I bring up...
That's me.
My mother's always liked the idea
of living in the compound.
It's actually turned out pretty good.
She's been there a very long time,
and they have obviously survived
the decades of being there together.
Remember my 17th birthday party
when you lifted your skirt up in front of...
- all those people...
- I did not lift my skirt.
- ...including that guy Michael?
- It twirled up!
And you weren't wearing any underwear.
Well!
Carrie wrote the movie "Postcards From the Edge"
about her relationship with my mother,
and in the movie, they end up having an argument
through two characters--
Shirley MacLaine and Meryl Streep.
I'm going to kill myself.
Don't say that even in jest, Suzanne.
I was very unhappy back then.
I was just a mess.
And some of the things that are in the movie happened.
- Any idea what she's taken?
- Pills, sir.
- Demerol,
Percodan, and cocaine.
- Give me her vitals.
Todd:
Carrie at this point
was famously into drugs.
- Suzanne?!
- And my mother was not real happy about it.
There was anger, true anger there.
I never said you were a monster.
You don't say it, but you feel it.
Somehow you lay the entire blame for your drug taking on me.
I do not! I do not, Mother.
I took the drugs. Nobody made me.
Carrie and I started getting high together
when we were about-- I was 15.
We used to smoke weed together and we had a lot of fun.
And then, you know, she moved on to other things,
and I didn't.
When I would stop, she would keep going.
I knew something was the matter with me.
I went too fast.
I was too much.
And I was embarrassed of it.
The drugs I liked were painkillers.
They calmed me down.
I just couldn't--
I couldn't handle it.
I didn't know what "it" was.
Manic depressive is a disease.
Now, that was not diagnosed then,
so nobody kind of knew what was going on with Carrie.
When she was 13, her personality changed.
So it's a constant battle
that takes all of us
to assure her that she's loved,
and that won't get her.
Hard. Yeah, it's hard.
That's the hardest part.
It's Christmas here in China on the Wall,
and we're headed toward the top.
Come with us.
Join us on a walk on the Wall.
Come on, everybody!
We look like we're tired! We're having a ball!
I have two moods.
Roy is Rollicking Roy,
a wild ride of a mood!
Wow, some of that methamphetamine released itself,
and the brain slid and there was some trapped
methamphetamine from my father.
It's melting from the heat.
Pam is Sediment Pam,
who stands on the shore and sobs.
One mood is the meal,
the next mood, the check.
Where am I in all this? I have no idea.
Because I feel like it's a little mood relay, you know?
I'm Pam now.
See, if Roy got this cold...
he wouldn't let him stop it.
'Cause Roy is bigger than all of it.
But I just fit snugly
into the mood pocket that is Pam.
I don't have any choice.
I don't dictate the ride.
Look, the blue one, I think, is probably better,
but this is crazier.
It's important to know.
That is very nice sweater.
Those are good folk art colors.
That's what you are-- folk art.
Okay, see? That's not bad.
And a person wearing this would then have a room...
like this!
We met--
Debbie and Eddie bought a house
two doors down from where I lived.
I was 11 when they first moved in, I think.
She was pregnant with Todd.
- Debbie worked a lot...
- Yeah.
...so she wasn't there, so, you know,
it's like you take what you can get, really.
And if you can't have Debbie Reynolds...
No, we wanted her.
Here's the deal-- Carrie at two
was more interesting than anyone I've ever known.
Todd was a very happy child, very easygoing.
But we weren't made with each other in mind.
No, you were very different.
I was jealous of that.
It was simpler for him for some reason.
Yeah.
Also, he didn't--
you suffered from the divorce.
You had an attachment to your dad,
but he wasn't around much.
And then Elizabeth Taylor--
Oh, God.
In a scandal that's gripping Hollywood and the nation,
Eddie Fisher leaves America's sweetheart, Debbie Reynolds,
for her friend and neighbor, Elizabeth Taylor.
Something I had never seen was all the paparazzi.
Liz, over here!
It was very dramatic.
I want to get out. Now.
And your mom was quite dignified and quiet.
I haven't even been informed. I just got off the airplane.
I will not contest it, no.
All of a sudden, there were photographers
on your front yard or on the sidewalk.
Don't remember it.
Coming out of the driveway,
they took your picture in the car.
I don't remember it. I don't remember it.
- I don't want to remember it.
- Yeah.
No, I do remember it.
I'm sure that was very stressful.
I know I didn't like that.
They were trampling me and Todd to get to her,
so the sensation was that she belonged to them.
My mom did say about her-- she said, "That's a sad child,"
and that's after, I think, the divorce.
She had this sadness,
and then Harry Karl was in the picture.
We were supposed to call him "Daddy Harry."
Yeah, that was gonna happen.
He was just a mass of noises and monograms.
You have to remember this.
There was an intercom, and he would start calling,
"Carri-i-e.
To-o-dd.
Hone-e-y."
"Honey" was Debbie's name.
You know, he owned shoe stores, so that didn't interest us.
Nothing about him was interesting
until we found out about the hookers.
Oh, God.
And here he comes now,
industrialist and philanthropist,
a celebrity in his own right, Harry Karl.
- And look who's with him-- Carrie and Todd.
Harry Karl walked into the perfect, ready-made family,
and he seems like a great setup.
- There's Mommy.
- There's Mommy, yeah.
Loving, caring, loved Carrie and I,
but we don't know at the time that he has serious problems.
We don't know that
he is a compulsive gambler.
We don't know that he's
a compulsive drinker.
It was a disaster
in the making,
and it was really a disaster
when my mom came home one day
and saw
the foreclosure notice
on the front door
of one of the biggest houses
in Beverly Hills.
At the end
of the rainbow
We were both about to enter a new era of reality.
Little did we know what's really going on at that exact moment
is Harry Karl is gambling away all of our money
and Harry and Debbie were divorcing.
That was the tail end of Carrie and I,
our innocence as children.
- Okay, let's go.
- All right, let's go.
We're going to see Debbie.
Ma?
Aw, I'm so happy to see you.
How are you?
I'm good. How are you feeling?
Shitty. Pretty bad.
Truly, you look so beautiful.
You have to believe me.
I'm dizzy, and I think I caught it from you.
Here, you want some oxygen?
Yes! That's the ultimate hostess.
You're offered water, soft drinks, oxygen.
- Here.
- I'm taking it.
Carrie, maybe you've had enough oxygen.
- What?
- Maybe you've had enough.
She seems very, you know, coherent,
and she looks wonderful, but she seems fragile.
And, um...
She's good at seeming good.
- That's the thing.
- Yes, that's correct.
She's definitely the lightest version
of Debbie I've ever seen.
Um...
That would be a good way to put it.
Yeah, Debbie Light.
Holler "uncle"!
You're tuckered, Molly! Why don't you quit?!
Sure, I'm tuckered, and I might give out, but I won't give in!
How could anybody say I'm down?
Look, I'm blinking!
Somehow, my mother is unsinkable.
- Maybe here!
That "Unsinkable Molly Brown" stuff is her.
No place, but there come a time
'cause nothing nor nobody wants me down
like I wants me up!
The idea that my mother is now older
and she's more frail, and I'm trying to see
what that feels like, but I still don't feel it
because she's still who she is inside.
She went to school at MGM,
where they trained you how to behave,
and so it's in her consciousness
to be at her best at all times.
Howdy, everybody.
Welcome.
Glad to see you're here at last.
And she's a fan before she was ever a star.
When she went to MGM,
she was enamored like anybody would be.
My God, there's Clark Gable.
And I have pictures of her with Gary Cooper.
You can see she's got stars in her eyes.
Who wouldn't?
And she's still a fan to this day.
But let me just say that Debbie Reynolds
is a self-proclaimed movie-oholic
and has an enormous Hollywood memorabilia collection.
Altogether, the costumes and props
are worth millions dollars,
so this is sort of your nest egg.
Yes, this is-- I put all the money I could save
after all my husbands, and I bought costumes.
This is Marilyn Monroe's subway dress.
Wow.
My mother's passion for collecting
started when they were auctioning off
the back lots of MGM and all the contents.
The idea that this stuff was going to be scattered
to the four corners of the Earth
was unconscionable to her,
so she took it upon herself to say, "I'm going to save it."
This is Liz Taylor's stool, makeup stool from "Cleopatra."
This chandelier back here is called a "girandole."
It's from "Marie Antoinette" and "Camille."
In the end, she was successful in amassing
the world's largest collection of Hollywood memorabilia,
and so she wanted to build a museum.
- This is from "Molly Brown."
- That's right.
People are always amazed when they come to Hollywood
and there's no museum of film history.
I've tried.
It's just that no one seems to be interested
that's in the business.
The public, the fans are interested, I'm interested.
We, for decades, struggled to build this museum.
It was impossible to believe that this wasn't gonna happen.
But we couldn't find a partner who shared her vision.
Deal after deal fell through.
- "The Wizard of Oz."
That's Judy Garland's.
Chokes me up now.
You know, here we are-- we'll talk about this
in another 10 years, I'll get choked up.
Nobody wants to see their mother's heart broken,
and we saw it.
When we had
the first two auctions,
it was very traumatic for my mother.
We sold the Marilyn Monroe subway dress
from "The Seven Year Itch" for $6.2 million.
The truth is the collection was sinking her financially.
We had debt because we had borrowed money to get a lot of this stuff,
and we don't have a museum.
We were done.
In one week, I have to go
and start rehearsals in London
for "Star Wars Seven...ty-two."
I'm concerned because my mother is not feeling well.
But I'm trying to let go.
It's like the--
It's like I should be trying to let go of my daughter
instead of trying to let go of my mom.
So, everything is backward.
My question is, if you die when you're fat,
are you a fat ghost?
Or do they go back to a flattering time?
So now you got to pick it up.
I'll go to 30, but then you have to let me go!
- Almost there!
- Let me go! Let my people go!
That's all you're gonna get.
Oh! Okay, now cool down. Keep it going.
Oh, I've been doing this for a year.
Lucasfilm, they make them report on my weight.
They take measurements.
I mean, it's-- it's intense.
- She loves it.
- I've learned to love it.
I hate to break this conversation,
but the gift for George Lucas's daughter,
is it her birthday?
Oh, the gift.
It's three months late for his birthday.
No, it's the birthday of the daughter, so--
- No, it's his. It was his.
- Oh, his birthday.
Okay, all right.
All right, I found a place that wraps
and does all the lovely things, and I'll be back.
Forward and back.
Back. There you go.
Shoulders. Where are the shoulders?
California.
- We're going this way.
- Even if it's a lie.
No, there is no way-- no, that's the one thing--
that is my Waterloo.
After your exercise class,
what you need to do is smoke a cigarette.
You hear that noise, Carrie? That's what we have to do.
Clear the house.
He's bossy.
Don't clear it today. Clear it tomorrow.
Every day.
We keep trying.
Here we go.
So, what's on the agenda?
Let's go shopping.
Inner health and well-being you can now buy.
How much is the little watch up there?
There's a man with his penis and a fat woman.
"Prepare to meet thy God."
- Uh-oh. When?
- When?
Okay, and... action.
Look at all this.
I'm having a crisis of joy.
Ooh!
What's nice here is the lighting.
Ah!
They're doing a film.
Do you know who Debbie Reynolds is?
- Of course!
- She's my mother.
- Debbie Reynolds?
- Yeah, so--
- No.
- Yes.
So, you know who Eddie Fisher is?
- Of course I know Eddie--
- Okay, that's my father.
Oh, and I'm in "Star Wars." You know that movie?
Yes, of cour--
I'm Princess Leia. Yes! This.
Oh! I need a picture!
Well, you're getting a picture, look.
Look, they want--
Am I getting a picture with Princess L--
take one and then you can send it to me.
My son will go ballistic!
So, was it good to see the "Star Wars" gang again?
Anybody you have history with, it's interesting
to see them after a while or not--
I've seen Harrison and Mark over the years.
You sort of run into one another in the cafeteria,
the celebrity cafeteria.
And they-- you know, we all just look more melted.
Did you always want to be an actress?
No, I wasn't running around saying, "I want to be an actress."
You know, I think you got exactly the same eyes as your mother,
- and your chin's a little bit like hers, too.
- No, it isn't.
I only did "Shampoo" because I was hanging around the set,
and they-- you know, I mean, almost.
I was a type.
That was when Debbie wanted me to use the word "screw"
instead of "fuck,"
and Warren had to come over and convince her.
Can't we just, uh, be friends?
You want to fuck?
And "Star Wars" came out when I was 20.
I met Paul the next year, and, boom.
Suddenly, I'm with the people
that are the best at what they do,
the best actors and the best directors.
And that was fun and scary to be around that.
It was all a surprise.
It all happened very fast and very soon.
Carrie, someone's here!
Hey, fuckface!
- Coming!
- Where are you?!
- Oh, my God.
- Who the fuck is this?
Home at last. It's Gary, our son.
Where are we going?
We're going into the bedroom, as per usual.
So how's the new "Star Wars" going?
- I'm not allowed to answer that.
- Oh, that's right, you can't.
Close your eyes.
- Can I open them?
- Yeah.
That's the only part of the "Happy Birthday" song
- that I've been able to learn.
That is what we sing now.
Oh, my God.
That is filthy.
Look it, that's his dick that's keeping the time.
- As it can do.
- It's a second-hand dick.
- It's so beautiful.
- Isn't it great?
- But I can really keep it?
- You can really keep it.
You know, I was thinking it's very funny
that we're running into each other in London, too,
because so many things happened to us here in London.
I remember you had a boyfriend and you were a virgin,
and you didn't want him to know you were a virgin.
So I helped you out
as a friend.
- He relieved me of the--
- The burden.
Burden of my...
- What is that called?
- Virginity.
- No, no, no, but-- hymen.
- Oh, the hymen.
I took the pressure off your hymen.
My hymen was a burden to me.
But that's what a real friend does.
- That really is.
- But it was funny.
They always say sex-- sex can ruin a friendship,
but we were young enough where it didn't.
- No, it was--
- I bet now it would.
No, it wouldn't. No.
Swear to God, my mother,
she offered for me to have sex with this guy Albert,
and she would supervise...
- Albert and I having sex.
- Actual having sex?
- Actual having sex.
- Walking you through it.
Yeah, because she apparently has some tips on that.
"You take the staff of life and the grapes."
Oh, God.
For some reason, I have to tell you this.
The first time I saw test-- like, this is a tour
of the first times of genitals for me,
just endless tour.
Harry-- we all slept in the room with them,
and Harry slept in this top.
And he would go to the bathroom.
So, here we go.
- Now, we're all there.
- Oh, God.
Why?
- Ugh.
- And here comes Dumbo.
I'm seeing the grapes, where they would be.
This angry slather of balls.
That is a horrible story.
He was so awful.
Actually, Eddie turns out to be one of the better ones.
- Oh, my God, what a bar.
- I know.
You know, we can kind of laugh and everything,
but I remember you would look forward to seeing your father
or talk, and he would let you down, like,
over and over and over again.
And so, I always felt like, God, what a prick.
And I was so stupid about it, though.
Yes, you were. And you didn't see it coming.
You were an open-faced sandwich.
Like, "Yeah, I'm right here."
- There we go. There's a good title.
- And, bam!
"The Open-Faced Sandwich."
But he suddenly did make more appearances.
He came and stayed with me. He came to me.
And he said, "I need, like,
$5,000, $10,000
for clothes."
I said, "I don't have it.
And he went, "You don't have it?!"
And he now points to my house.
"You don't have it?!"
And I said, "Dad...
...you're a singer, not an actor.
Don't make a scene."
At that time, he was kind of like
a guy who used to be famous,
a sort of washed-up, you know, um...
you know, lounge act.
It just makes me cringe
when you think about stars that aren't stars anymore.
- Yeah.
- It's humiliating.
Todd, you said you could sing like your father.
Oh, yeah.
When Eddie left,
I was, like, a year old.
One of the first times I really connected with my father
was after I shot myself in the leg in New York.
It was the first time I had really heard from my dad.
He never had called me before in my life.
I was like, "Wow, that's unusual."
But, you know, I had to shoot myself in the leg
to get him to make me a call.
I have not been
the best father in the world.
I still have that guilt of not putting in
a certain amount of time that I thought I should have.
All I had in my head for years and years and years was
making sure that I had my drugs.
Well, my dad started off very early
with crystal meth.
It all started with him saying,
"God, I just can't do this show. I'm so sick."
And this doctor was there, and he said, "Look, I got a shot."
And he gave him this shot, and, man, he went out there
and sung his heart out.
And he was like, "That's incredible!"
He was being told it was vitamin shots.
That same doctor was giving it to President Kennedy
and to J. Edgar Hoover,
and a lot of very prominent people
were taking these same drugs
until everybody realized what it was.
But then it's too late, now, isn't it?
People that get into drugs generally make stupid choices.
If you look at my dad's life, he got stuck on stupid
and ended up blowing his career.
Puff Daddy.
You want a beverage?
My father, the way that I had
a relationship with him, finally,
was I became his parent,
and that was the way to have the relationship.
It's very important.
And so I got to know him
as there was less of him to know.
Was I always funny?
You know what?
I used to be funny for you.
'Cause I thought if I was really funny
that you would want to be around me all the time.
I would make myself wonderful for your return.
See? And it finally paid off.
I wanted to be your best girl,
and that's-- I had tough competition.
Yeah. Well, you know, if your competition
to be best girl with you is Elizabeth Taylor,
well, I don't think I'm gonna do well with that one.
But I think I'm funnier than Elizabeth Taylor.
Anyway, that's always been a goal.
You love me?
I love you.
You're loveable.
So, here we are, approaching the third auction
of my mother's collection.
Unfortunately, my mother just fell
because she was dizzy walking into her bathroom.
When we saw her, we were all in horror
because we were like, "Wait a minute.
You know, you could have broke your neck or be dead right now."
I fainted.
I went plummeting to the ground.
And I hit a rock or-- you know, in my bathroom.
And it was 12:00 at night,
and it just bruised everything.
But-- I know, I'll do the interview like this!
But the subject never came up
to cancel the auction.
You know, I suspect she's going to show up
to the parties and act like
nothing's wrong, which is what she does so well.
Here we are.
Here we are, here we are.
Oh, this is murder.
You ready to come up? I've got your arm.
- Good evening!
- I'm Princess Leia's mother.
I'm wondering now, you're about to be done with the third--
Final. It's the end of an era,
but we hope that the public enjoy all these fabulous things.
What is it about show business
that connects the two of you
when you're not on a red carpet?
We are always on a red carpet.
We have red carpets at home, connecting our homes.
We are not people with personas.
This is everything that came out of my mother,
right here, these two.
- Ugh.
- That doesn't sound good.
That doesn't sound very good.
Well, it's a good thing.
I'll ask one more question.
Sold.
475 to paddle number 1073.
My mom, she's having second thoughts
about the Rat Pack costumes.
She said, "I think I want to keep them."
She personally collected these outfits.
Debbie went to Peter Lawford.
And he was like, "Why in the hell do you want
my underwear and socks
and my outfit?"
And she's like, "I want the whole ensemble,
and I want it for the museum.
I had a dream last night.
I say it's a vision.
I say it's someone speaking to me,
that I should not sell the boys.
When I worked with Frank, he called me "sweetie."
"Come on, sweetie, sit over here."
So, I don't want to sell,
and I have to be here
and I have to be happy about it,
so I have to have happy things in my head.
I love having my ghosts
and I love having my memories.
It's like you have a friend forever.
It makes me smile when I even just say their names.
Sold, 650 to paddle 6000.
At the time, the Hollywood Heritage Museum
did not have the funds or the property
of the Hollywood current museum
as it says in the catalogue,
so, with that in mind,
we're going to sell lot number 235.
Opening bid?
20,000. Joe has the bid at 20,000.
20,000, the opening bid.
$22,500.
Is that a bid, sir? Or are you just-- yep.
25,000. Thank you.
25,000.
Gentleman on the aisle at 25,000
for the Charlie Chaplin--
- 27,500.
Next would be 30,000.
Going once, going twice,
selling for $27,500.
The dog will not leave,
so do you want him to lie down?
Um, he's okay there.
But I'm gonna sort of face that way a little bit.
'Cause I just-- I look so bad.
I don't want to face direct.
No, you're gonna talk to me...
- Oh, good, good.
- ...but I was gonna stand right here.
Now...
is the hair in one place?
- The hair?
- It's one place.
Okay, there we are.
The hair looks very good.
Okay, how are you-- by the way, how are you doing?
Well, it's not my best day, but that's all right
because we've had other days that are worse.
Have we?
I'm happy to be here.
First thing I want to ask you about
is how many years were you under contract at MGM?
I was at MGM from 1948...
through "How the West Was Won."
We made a lot of pictures at MGM,
and I had a wonderful time.
I had a wonderful time.
I had... youth, you know.
I had-- I was just a kid.
I didn't know anything,
and they taught me everything.
Can we talk a little bit about your brother
and just a little bit about Texas?
- Because, um...
- If you like.
- Is that okay?
- Sure.
Oh, hi, Carrie!
You're going?
I'm going.
Go to bed.
Yes, go to bed.
Say good night to everybody.
Good night to everybody.
Will you come back and visit us?
No, no, no. She's got to go to bed.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
The alarm! She's locked in now!
Wait, Carrie!
I have no idea what the alarm is.
Oh, my God.
I-I have no--  I have no idea...
Now the police with come?
I suppose.
Michael?
Try 985-3193 or something.
I don't remember ever...
I don't remember ever, ever turning this alarm on.
It wasn't my day.
That's it!
- Yay!
- Ohh!
Debbie, while you're here,
can you just tell us about the shoes and stuff?
Okay.
This is Judy Garland's shoe.
Well, was, of course.
They look small, don't they?
Mm-hmm.
They would fit me.
Do you think they fit you now?
She wore 5 1/2.
I'll get that for you.
- Sorry.
- Okay.
I think we should end it at the end of this.
Okay, yeah.
'Cause I think everything's going wrong.
Okay.
And this...
is...
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Chaplin.
Come on.
Thanks, Debbie.
- Come on.
- You got it?
Mm-hmm.
Dwight!
Do you want to go to Vegas?
I know Dwight does.
Dwight always wants to go to Vegas.
And they get very excited.
Come on, it's hard to take both of them.
Come on, Dwig.
We are going to do Vegas
with my mother.
I didn't know it until my daughter told me.
It's absurd.
If you're going to retire, you retire.
She retires and books an engagement in Vegas,
and then says, "Come help me."
I don't believe that that's the last one.
This is all against
doctor's orders, now,
as if any orders apply to Debbie.
But everyone ends up in Vegas.
You know, if my mother's unhappy,
it lives on my grid,
so I both want to
and have to help my mother.
She was very good to her mother,
and her mother didn't deserve it.
Debbie deserves it.
When Debbie got into show business,
obviously it was a big difference in your lives,
but did you like it?
Mm-mm. I think it's phony.
Your mother never knew what it was,
and we went in blind.
And did you encourage her to go in?
No. In fact, I've tried to get her out of it.
What did Grandpa think of show business?
Eh, he thought it was a crazy way to make a living.
Well, what do you wish that she would have done?
She wanted to be a gym teacher. You know that.
You think she would have been happier doing that?
I think it would have been more normal.
But she loves what she's doing, let's face it.
Loved it all, and still does.
- Yeah, she does.
- Yeah.
God gave her brains, but He didn't put 'em up here,
He put 'em down in her ankles.
This is the view of the whole-- this is Vegas.
I've been coming here since the '60s,
but this will be probably the finale.
I'm not feeling that well,
and so, to be well enough to do my whole show,
I asked my children if they would come up and relieve me.
"Carrie says, 'Mother,
you know I started in your act
at 14 years of age."
Who talks like that?
"Todd comes onstage and the family banters."
I don't want to make fun of it,
'cause it's sweet and she wrote this.
Then she sings "This is a Lovely Way to Spend an Evening"
and "Tammy."
I hope it works out well.
And the song that she's picked, for me-- perfect.
The only way you make it through life is to fight.
You don't get there the easy way.
If you feel sorry for yourself
and you let yourself go down
you will drown.
Why don't we get you out of there--
Just-- see that doorway down there?
No, I know where to park it.
- Okay.
- How about we walk you...
- ...and then we'll...
- Well, first I want to--
I'll take care of your cart.
- Okay.
- She goes out the opposite.
- Well.
- I was trying to get you out the easy--
I know. I saw where you were going.
I was trying to get the stuff.
- I'll take care of this.
- I've got it.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Here's Debbie!
Welcome to the South Point Hotel.
I look what?
- Good!
- Oh, thank-- oh!
Beautiful.
She says I look all right.
Do I look all right back there?
Down here, I look like a hooker.
This is it, you know. You folks came at the right time.
This is my last weekend ever to be in show business.
- I'm gonna be...
- Aww.
I've got to retire.
Come on, say-- wish me luck.
Yeah, "Good luck, Debbie! Yeah."
I enjoyed making that--
- I'll never say no...
- Uh-oh.
To you
You know my daughter.
Whatever you say I'll do
If you ask me to wait...
Carrie Fisher.
...for a lifetime
You know I'll gladly wait
For a lifetime or two
Just to look at you...
Ah!
I'll smile
If you say be glad
I'll weep
'Cause I'm bipolar...
Today is tomorrow
If you do too much blow...
I'll stay
Or I'll go
But I'll
Never say
No.
My daughter.
Nice to see you.
Oh, likewise.
- Please don't retire.
- Oh, no, it's time.
- So beautiful.
- I love you.
- Bye-bye.
Great show.
Thank you.
Hi. How are you doing?
Bye-bye.
Good night.
Hi, Alexis.
This is Donald calling for Debbie.
She's not gonna be able to do that tomorrow.
I'm gonna put her on
so you can hear how her voice is.
Hold on one second.
Okay.
- She's not there?
- No.
Hello, Alexis?
This is Debbie.
If I can't speak,
I don't know a reason to try to do a recording.
Why don't we just forget about this till I'm well?
I'm sorry to bother you with it.
Sorry to bother the both of us.
Anyway, Carrie says I should stop saying that.
I'm sorry.
But I am sorry. Bye.
So, just when we thought she'd stay home for a while,
my mom gets this big lifetime achievement award,
and she's right there back in the spotlight.
Actress Debbie Reynolds will be the recipient
of this year's Screen Actors Guild Lifetime Achievement Award.
The ceremony will be broadcast live
from the Shrine Auditorium in Hollywood, California.
She was already making up speeches in her head.
You know, she's like...
Her thing is sort of like, "Well, I'm--
finally, they're..."
But she doesn't say that.
But they haven't been--
they haven't lavished her with awards.
Yep, you sit at your seat, just next to your mom here.
That would be terrific.
Here we go.
Debbie Reynolds, Lifetime Achievement Award.
Carrie Fisher, standing in for Debbie Reynolds.
Todd, I-- Todd, I stayed overnight.
I was-- yeah.
She doesn't feel well.
She feels like shit.
Then let's do that.
Let's let her not be there at the table, and lay down...
That doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
I'll find out, but it doesn't matter.
Oh, how much time would she have to sit at the table?
We're gonna need some kind of place for her to lay down.
Yeah. Sure.
Okay, so if there's just, like, anything
that's not embarrassing.
We'll make an area for her.
Got it. We'll-- we'll--
- we can make this work.
- She's like...
Yeah.
It's okay, Carrie.
We can make this work. We've done it before.
They're gonna set aside, like a little area for her...
so she can do it, you know.
I know.
Give Debbie my best, all right?
Hi, Mama.
I passionately, passionately
am going to marry you while you're sleeping tonight.
And by the morning, I will have taken all your money.
No, I want your bedroom cleared.
Except for me because I'm your favorite!
Oh.
I'm sorry. God damn it.
I know.
Well, please, could--
is there any way you could go to sleep...
now?
Okay, I'll get off the phone with you.
I'm-- I'm coming home.
I like Christmas.
I like the lights.
My mom...
she is Christmas.
She's something special.
- Wait, did you get drinks?
- Yeah, perfect.
Seriously, though, you secretly want something.
I know you do.
You know, I could do a pretty good Streisand.
Your voice is beautiful.
Thank you.
Um...
I should have been a pair of ragged claws
scuttling across the floors of silent seas!
You know what would be so cool?
To get to the end of my personality...
and just, like, lay in the sun.
Oh, I have to watch a little of this.
I'm sick of myself.
Smile.
I love this movie.
I love every lyric.
Are you okay, Carrie?
Mmm.
That's how I've gotten through a lot of it...
- is abstract it...
- Mm-hmm.
...so that it's not happening to me.
It's...
I just-- I'm a, um...
type of bird.
I'm manic right now. I didn't know if you've...
And I haven't been for a while.
It'll go out of style soon,
and then I'll just be quirky.
Ohh!
Careful, all right?
I make my own blends.
Okay, you just kind of...
- Fun tonight.
- It's more than fun.
It's-- it's magical,
and things will start happening now
that you want to have happen.
You are fucking amazing.
I'm fuckin' amazing!
I know.
Yeah, later, because they...
I know...
Is she moving at all?
Todd, you've got to get her out.
You can't push her or you don't get nothin'.
If you push, and then she gets mad, you can't have that.
That's the worst thing that could happen,
so you've gotta just kind of act like...
The show has started.
And I'd like to accept this award on behalf
of every dog on Earth.
Jodie Hattaway!
Can you go check and just tell us anything?
Yes, I will be happy to.
Does she realize that we're gonna miss the show?
Of course.
Should I go and, like, ,hustle her out?
Your mom or Debbie?
Here comes the old lady. I'm very sorry.
Yay!
We're here, Mom, right here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
So, hello, gorgeous.
Who said that?
I want to tell you all
what fun it is to go out on the town.
Have a good time.
Thank you.
I just want to say...
Your segment.
What is my award? Now I can't even think.
You're getting the Lifetime Achievement Award.
Life-- well, that's the thing, see?
I get upset, so I can't remember anything.
It's an achievement that you even got here.
That's the real achievement.
This is the what award?
Lifetime Achievement.
- But...
- Screen Actors Guild.
- But it's on the prompter.
Carrie, was the prompter big enough?
The prompter is huge.
I just want to know what it is.
Like, in real life right now,
like we're talking here--
we're talking, and we're just saying.
We're just saying it's the SAG Lifetime Achievement Award.
It's just called
a Life Achievement--
like S-A-G?
SAG Lifetime Achievement Award.
Screen Actors Guild.
- SAG. SAG.
- SAG. Lifetime.
You don't really have to say it, I don't think.
- I have to say it.
- I'm not worried about that.
I just want to really know--
She's gonna set it all up for you.
I just really want to know what it really is.
Right now, I just blanked out.
It's the biggest honor in your industry.
- It is?
- It's a big deal.
- I mean, it actually is.
- It is!
No, it is. It's the biggest honor.
Do you have enough air on you back there?
You know, you keep asking me questions.
- Did you--?
- I don't need any questions.
Don't ask you questions. Okay.
I'm just trying to stay, uh, level,
like I'm-- I'm-- I'm, uh...
Don't talk to us. Just relax.
Just breathe.
If you could slow down just a tiny,
tiny, tiny little bit.
I know you're being coached.
Vomiting is a possibility.
I know.
Best of all, don't-- don't--
I don't-- no, I'm not.
I know.
- Ohh.
- Okay, here we go.
Looks like I'm going onstage.
Please welcome Carrie Fisher.
Okay.
Uh...
I am very close to this year's
Screen Actors Guild Life Achievement Award honoree.
Hey!
Gary, look, there's your mommy.
I found it difficult to share my mother
with her adoring fans...
She's nervous as hell, isn't she?
She has lived two lives...
I mean, she was throwing up leading into this.
I'm sure Carrie's flipping out.
I am proud to present
the Screen Actors Guild Life Achievement Award
to my mother, Debbie Reynolds!
Ahh!
Thank you. Thank you.
I want to thank the Screen Actors Guild
for awarding me with this tonight.
It's very unexpected.
And, you know, I've been in the business now...
...66 years.
And, uh, my favorite movie was "Singin' in the Rain."
Well, I did mention-- did I say that? Yeah.
And I had a good time making that picture,
wearing myself out.
God gave us talent, so we're very fortunate.
We all are.
What we do best, believe in it.
And of course, we-- we do that of course,
and my favorite movie was "The Unsinkable Molly Brown,"
and I had a lot of fun doing that.
Thank you.
In that movie, I got to sing
a wonderful film-- uh, song,
called, uh, "I Ain't Down Yet."
Well, I ain't.
Thank you all very much for this wonderful award.
Thank you.
Coming up-- Ethan Hawke,
Patricia Arquette, Rashida Jones, Andy Samberg,
and, with a special tribute, Liev Schreiber.
- How was it?
- It was fine.
- Fine.
- Were you nervous at all up there?
- Um, yes, but not for--
- I was nervous. I was nervous!
When did you not get nervous?
You seemed like you settled down.
Well, no, it wasn't that I--
the whole evening, to me, was wonderful.
And there's no business like show business.
- Tonight--
- You know what?
I have to say something.
Everything about it is appealing.
Something that the traffic will applaud.
Everything. No, seriously, everything,
well, the traffic will allow.
- Nowhere can you get...
- That happy feeling.
When you're stealing--
and I don't mean, you know, out-and-out stealing...
An extra bow.
Extra bow.
But there's no people like show people.
There are people like show people.
- Nah, it's true.
- Now, that's true.
Well, the smiling when they're low...
- ...us schizophrenics are like that.
- Oh, really?
- So, they're like show people.
- Really?
If they offered you another Life Achievement Award, would you do it?
Now, I can't be funny about tonight.
It's too special.
- Okay.
- It was a special night.
But that was a good question, though.
Could you handle another life achievement award?
'Cause they're gonna see that you did one,
and they're gonna want to do--
That's right, the floodgates are open.
I can't answer it, because...
it's too special,
and I won't be here then.
I will have gone on.
So it's very important for this moment--
For the big life achievement.
You don't get a chance
to have a moment like this very often.
It's not like any moment.
It's its own special moment.
Yeah! "Ever since this world began."
All right, we have to stop,
as my therapist likes to say.
Say good night, George.
Can't you say, "Good night, George,"
and I'll say, "Good night, Gracie"?
That's not original, Mother.
Oh, I know, but it shouldn't be.
It should be just simply funny.
It's slightly amusing to you.
Why continue working so hard?
Say good night.
Good night,
and thank you for joining us here
around our family "herth"-- "harth."
Hearth!
You know I loved you.