( music playing )
Carrie Fisher:
Hello.
We're here with a woman
who alleges
to be my mother.
I don't buy it
for a minute.
But this is how
we'll find out.
Debbie Reynolds:
I have proof.
Carrie:
You have films.
Reynolds:
I have films and I have
a certificate.
Carrie:
You have the films
that I'm happy.
Reynolds:
Oh, yes. Well, because
you doubted it for so long.
Carrie:
You knew that I was
gonna doubt it later,
so you filmed me
being happy.
Reynolds:
No, I thought that
if you filmed children,
and you had happy children
and then you filmed it--
- ( Carrie laughs ) Exposure!
- Reynolds: Who knew when you
were going to grow up
and say, "I'm very unhappy,"
and "That's a fake film,"
that I made it up.
Carrie:
This is getting
so ugly so fast.
( Reynolds laughs )
You have to try
to concentrate
on the fact
that you did have,
sometimes, good times.
Carrie:
I know that I did!
I had a very good time.
Reynolds:
See how you yelled?
At your mother?
Carrie:
What about Todd?
Do you like Todd
better than me?
( Reynolds sighs )
No. It's just that
you're different.
- Every child
is different, so--
- Carrie: I don't buy this.
Reynolds:
You never bought anything
that I said, so...
Carrie:
Okay, what does he get
in the will and what do I get?
Reynolds:
Oh, I'm not gonna
tell anybody that.
Carrie:
If we lived together,
we would argue.
Reynolds:
Yes.
It's possible.
( music playing )
¶ Just in time ¶
¶ I found you
just in time ¶
¶ Before you came,
my time ¶
¶ Was running low ¶
¶ Mm, I was lost ¶
¶ The losing dice
were tossed ¶
¶ My bridges
all were crossed ¶
¶ Nowhere to go ¶
¶ Now you're here ¶
¶ And now I know
just where I'm going ¶
¶ No more doubt or fear ¶
¶ I've found my way ¶
¶ But love came
just in time ¶
¶ You found me
¶ And changed
my lonely life ¶
¶ That lovely day ¶
¶ Yeah! ¶
( music continues )
Carrie:
How long has it
been done for?
I'm done for.
Ugh!
Fucking criminy!
I'm gonna go help
my mother pack.
My mother is performing
a show in Connecticut.
I tried to stop her,
but that is like throwing
yourself in front of a...
Oh, what are those called?
Not tiramisus.
Tsunami. See?
She's "Tsu-Mommy."
And I threw myself
in front of Tsu-Mommy,
and it didn't work.
She loves doing it
when she's doing it,
but afterwards, she was
laying on the floor, so...
But in a good, dignified,
movie star way.
Mother and I live
next door to each other,
separated
by one daunting hill.
I usually come to her.
I always come to her.
( dog barking )
Mommy!
Mommy, I'm home!
Reynolds:
Hello!
Where--
look, you cannot
keep that phone.
It's ridiculous.
That's from the early '90s,
when they first invented
cell phones.
- But I--
- That was
one of the originals.
I don't want to buy
a new one.
The old phone works fine.
Just dandy.
- It's horrible.
- Oh! There she is.
- Look. Look at all the--
- Do you know how to do it?
- No. No one knows how to use
those anymore.
Reynolds:
That is a beautiful puff.
Thank you for
the beautiful soufflé.
- I love it.
- Carrie: Is it good?
Reynolds:
¶ Delicioso! ¶
You want to sing
with me?
Fisher Stevens:
Debbie, what do you
wear in the show?
Carrie:
A very heavy
beaded dress.
It is quite beautiful.
It's beautiful,
but it weighs more
than she does.
( laughs )
It does weigh--
it does weigh
about 50 pounds.
- But it's so beautiful.
- Worth it!
Now, that's--
that's Elizabeth's.
This belonged to...
I bought that
at Elizabeth Taylor's
auction.
- I won it.
- This is when--
during her muumuu phase.
Yeah. Well,
it's pretty, really.
Look.
It has a drag queen
element.
Oh, now, just do
what your mother says.
It makes life easier.
As if.
- Yeah.
- All right.
You remember me?
I'm your mother.
- I remember.
- ¶ Tammy, Tammy... ¶
I keep you very close, so--
constant reminder.
Carrie:
Is this for the show?
Reynolds:
I forgot I had it.
That's what's good
about losing your memory
is there's so many
surprises in the world.
I have found
some things work.
Not enough.
There's never
enough Listerine.
I'm gonna go fill it.
I'm just gonna go fill it.
Remember, we had a relative
that drank Listerine...
- She was an alcoholic.
- ...and 18 bottles
of vanilla.
- Okay.
- That's it. That's all.
Okay, look.
Turn around this way
because your rear end
is to the camera.
Oh, my God.
I don't like not knowing
what's happening.
- I worry a little.
- Reynolds: That's very sweet.
I worry what
the show costs you.
That's all.
I know you like to do it.
I have caught up
with a few people in age.
Whoa!
But they're in bed
and you're doing a show.
Like George Burns says,
I'm gonna stay on stage
until I drop dead.
And then I'm gonna
have myself stuffed,
like Trigger,
and then I'll put me
in a museum.
- That's nice.
- Do you like that?
Or we could just leave
this house...
Carrie:
I totally understand
why she's doing it,
and it makes me nervous.
She'll forget she's not 35.
You know, it doesn't
make sense to her
that her body
isn't cooperating.
And she just thinks
if she ignores it,
it'll go away.
Everything in me
demands that my mother be
as she always was,
even if that way
is irritating.
She just can't change.
That's the rule.
And she's fucking with me.
Age is--
it's horrible
for all of us,
but she falls
from a greater height.
- ¶ Good morning ¶
¶ We've talked
the whole night through ¶
- ¶ Good morning ¶
- ¶ Good morning to you ¶
¶ Good morning,
good morning ¶
¶ It's great
to stay up late ¶
¶ Good morning,
good morning ¶
¶ To you ¶
¶ When the band
began to play ¶
¶ The stars
were shining bright ¶
¶ Now the milkman's
on his way ¶
¶ It's too late
to say good night ¶
¶ So, good morning,
good morning ¶
¶ Sunbeams
will soon smile through ¶
¶ Good morning,
good morning ¶
¶ To you, and you,
and you, and you ¶
¶ Good morning,
good morning ¶
¶ We've gabbed
the whole night through ¶
¶ Good morning,
good morning to you ¶
¶ Nothing could be grander
than to be in Louisiana... ¶
Man: Debbie's light
goes to the ears.
- Yes or no?
- Man #2: Yes.
Man: Okay.
You know, all this stuff
is, like, blocked
in your template.
( indistinct chatter )
( crew chattering )
And I think I only
got nervous once
when I performed
for the Queen of England.
I went over with Bob Hope
to do a show,
and I did get
a little nervous there.
The crown, the jewels
kind of threw me a little bit.
But as a rule, I don't--
I don't get nervous.
I just have a good time.
I've been doing this
my whole life.
You know, I started
performing when I was 16.
Stevens:
Will you know your set
already and everything?
Reynolds:
Oh, yes, I'm all set.
I carry my script
in my beat-up folder.
You can see how beat up.
And all the edges
are all worn out.
And if you can make
people smile a little,
laugh a little,
just enjoy themselves
for a moment...
It's not "Macbeth,"
you know.
How are you tonight?
You're such a nice,
attractive audience.
Now, you don't mind
if I come out, do you?
See, I like
to visit with you.
Otherwise,
I'm stuck up there.
I've seen my act.
Good evening.
Reynolds:
I used to go out
in the audience.
I used to do that.
I used to wear
a girdle, too,
and I don't do that
anymore.
( laughing )
So, it's like
the old days,
in a way,
but I'm like
the old days, so...
( laughs )
Can you do me a favor
while you're down there?
Yeah?
- You see that toe?
- Uh-huh.
That has to come around.
That...
See that?
It has to go to the--
- Underneath?
- Yeah.
( laughs )
Thank you.
I'm pulling
your leg, huh?
I have to do it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, Kevin is gonna do,
like, an introductory thing.
Five minutes, yeah.
Yeah.
So, when do you
want him to start?
When?
But David's already
asked me this.
Oh, he did?
He didn't tell him, though.
- Now.
Go!
- ( band playing )
- ( cheering and applause )
Oh!
( cheering and applause
continue )
I look around
and I see all you nice men.
You're very sweet.
I'm sure you're nice.
It's just that if there's
a nice guy around,
- I'm not gonna find him.
- ( laughter )
- You remember Eddie Fisher?
- Crowd: Yes.
Carrie told me,
"Mommy, doesn't--
doesn't it start to look like
Eddie's the good one?"
( laughter )
After Eddie,
I married again.
He was very rich, too.
That was helpful.
I thought
that was very nice.
But then I found out,
after we were married,
he was a gamble-oholic,
and he lost all of his money.
I should have married
Burt Reynolds.
I wouldn't have to change
my last name.
( laughter )
And we could share wigs.
- ( rim shot )
- ( cheering )
So, I thought,
I'll bring along
some of my first movies.
We had a lot of fun
in those days.
¶ "Babba dabba dabba dabba,"
said the chimpee to the monk ¶
¶ "Babba dabba
dabba dabba dabba,"
said the monkey to the chimp ¶
¶ All night long
they'd chatter away ¶
¶ All day long
they were happy and gay ¶
¶ Swinging and singing
in a honky-tonky way... ¶
Now, this is
my one little hit.
It's called "Tammy."
Here we go.
¶ I hear the cotton-- ¶
Start over again.
Maybe something
will come out.
( laughter )
¶ I hear the cottonwoods ¶
¶ Whisperin' above ¶
¶ Tammy, Tammy ¶
¶ Tammy's in love ¶
¶ Tammy's in... ¶
¶ Love. ¶
( cheering and applause )
- ( music playing )
- ( cheering continues )
People were loving it.
That was so awesome.
Okay, we're going
this way, though.
Great.
Good.
Okay.
And...
one more.
- ( groans )
- Okay.
- Boom!
- ( clapping )
- Man: Debbie,
that was amazing!
- It wasn't easy.
Man #2:
Debbie, that was...
Carrie:
It is very frustrating
for her,
because inside,
my mom is the same person.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for having me.
Carrie:
And she doesn't
want to retire.
She does not
You were great.
¶ Wah-oh! ¶
¶ Why do I feel
like a feather? ¶
¶ Why do I sing
in a crowd? ¶
¶ Why, when it's clear,
lovely weather ¶
¶ Why is my head
in a cloud? ¶
¶ It's that... ¶
Carrie:
Performing gives her life.
It feeds her in a way
that family cannot.
That's why I think it--
we've always been frustrating.
Because... it's not--
people aren't cooperative,
audiences are.
When you're her,
they are.
- ( applause )
- ¶ Where are you? ¶
Whoo-hoo!
Where are you?
Come here. Come on.
Come on.
Junie, don't you
want to see the kid?
Come on, sing it
for your old mother.
Besides,
I have to retire soon.
Carrie: I had been
singing in my mother's act
since I was about 13.
Would you sing
my favorite for me?
It's for Junie
and Jerry.
- Don't say no.
- ( band playing )
Just sing right out.
Whoo!
Carrie:
My mother wanted
to be able to groom me
for show business.
¶ When you're weary ¶
¶ Feeling small ¶
¶ When tears are in ¶
¶ Your eyes ¶
¶ I will dry them all... ¶
Carrie:
The biggest thing I did
that broke my mother's heart
was not do
a nightclub act.
¶ Oh, when times
get rough... ¶
Carrie: My mother would say,
"Do drugs. Do whatever
you need to do.
But why don't you sing?"
¶ Like a bridge... ¶
Carrie:
That was my big rebellion.
¶ Over troubled water ¶
¶ I will lay me down ¶
¶ Like a bridge over... ¶
Reynolds:
Carrie's daddy, Eddie,
had a great voice, you know.
Really beautiful voice.
I guess she doesn't want
to be Eddie and she doesn't
want to be Debbie.
She wants to be Carrie,
so she'll do it her way.
¶ I'm gonna ease
your mind ¶
¶ I will ease your mind! ¶
( applause )
I love that voice.
Isn't that a great voice?
I wish I had it.
( applause continues )
Take a bow,
take a bow,
take a bow.
Man:
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
That's not bad
for a 15-year-old, is it?
( music playing )
Carrie:
So, this is the compound.
It was built
by Robert Armstrong,
who was in "King Kong,"
who said, "'Twas beauty
killed the beast."
I've lived in this for--
let me see--
20 years.
This is the lobby.
This is where
early mornings are spent
with people
who drink coffee.
And there's
a hummingbird nest.
Look how teeny.
This is the bathroom.
It has, as a lot
of bathrooms should,
a player piano in it.
This is Bette Davis
when she lived here.
This is my suitcase,
Robert.
Oh.
Ugly children portraiture.
They did this thing
in the last century
where they dressed boys
in girls' clothing.
He looks like Ross Perot
in red.
Shia LaBeouf as a Dutch
underage prostitute.
And Richard Dreyfuss
as a young girl
wielding a rose.
Richard likes that.
Now, this just happens to be
probably an unhappy woman
that looks like
Kevin Spacey.
They sold this
on the Internet
as a Princess Leia
sex doll.
Maybe this.
There's no way
of accounting for it.
My daughter, Billie.
My brother and myself.
And Billie.
And my mother
and Judy Garland.
And my friend, Charlie,
at the dentist
with his mouth
widely displayed.
My house-- I love it.
It's like
scavenger hunting.
And my mother--
there's part of it
she kind of tolerates.
"Well, this is just
Carrie's thing."
This is the opposite
of the house that
I grew up in.
( projector whirring )
The house we lived in
was very grand
when I was growing up.
It was marble and glass.
Cold.
And there was just
too much air in it.
Family-wise, we didn't
grow up with each other,
we grew up
around each other.
You know, like trees.
My mother,
she worked a lot.
And then Harry,
her husband at the time,
he was the original
fancy-man, rich guy.
It was a prototype life.
We were getting ready
for a photoshoot
all the time.
And that's what
Todd and I shared.
Todd and I had
a shared history
of weirdness.
( dog barking )
Yes?
Who is it?
- Come in.
- Hi! I just wanted to say hi.
She brought her chicken in.
Speaking of science fiction.
- Hello.
- We've never met.
And this is Nugget.
He travels everywhere
with her.
He goes everywhere with me
'cause he's my emotional
wellness chicken.
And he's just--
We're gonna get him
a service tag
so he can be
a service chicken.
I have to drive
everywhere currently...
- With a harness.
- ...because they won't
let chickens fly.
- ( clucking )
- What? Yeah.
- He's my boy.
- That's right.
Sorry.
I didn't mean
to interrupt you.
No, I was just telling
the poster story.
In fact, I was telling her
the only reason why we
bought this house
was so I could hang
my posters somewhere.
So, I decided I would
tell a story on this wall.
My mother made this movie
called "Singin' in the Rain,"
down there,
and that's an original
"Singin' in the Rain" poster.
Then she went on to do
"Tammy and the Bachelor,"
where she sings
the song "Tammy."
Then she makes a movie
with Frank Sinatra called
"The Tender Trap."
And in this--
while she's making
this movie,
Frank Sinatra says,
"Now, Debbie, whatever you do,
do not marry a singer,
whatever you do."
So, she goes right out
and marries the singer,
my dad, Eddie Fisher.
Then my dad ran off
with Elizabeth Taylor
and became a producer
on "Cleopatra."
Then my dad goes on
and marries Liz,
and of course
they make the movie
"BUtterfield 8."
So, that's the story
of my life
in a certain amount
of posters.
Hickland:
Do you know
what's funny, is Debbie,
when she first
came in here, she went,
- "How can you allow this?"
- Right, too many Debbie
posters.
"To many Debbie posters.
Where's your stuff?"
She's just so awesome.
And I was like,
where else am I gonna
put your stuff?
Or what else
are we gonna do with it?
Sooner or later,
it's got to get up
on the wall.
Now, when I was younger,
"2001: A Space Odyssey"
came out
and I was very influenced
by how amazing that movie was.
And then,
all of a sudden,
you know,
Carrie does
this little picture
called "Star Wars"
she thought was gonna
be a B-movie.
I went to the screening
with her over at Fox,
and she was hiding
in the back with me
'cause she thought
it was gonna be
a cheesy film.
( R2-D2 beeping )
( beeping continues )
( music playing )
Carrie:
We are at a lap dance.
Come on,
do it a little more.
- In the front,
the whole thing.
- ( dog barks )
Carrie:
A celebrity lap dance,
which is where celebrities
of all shapes and ages
sign autographs
for cash prizes.
It's sort of like
going to a strip club,
except they don't stuff cash
in your underwear.
But that's kind of it.
Woman:
It's Carrie Fisher,
everybody!
- ( cheering )
- ( woman #2 chanting )
Carrie! Carrie!
Hi there.
How are you doing?
- Good to meet you.
- That is great.
( laughs )
We'll get a photo later.
- It's a pleasure to...
"meat" you.
- Meet me.
- All right, thank you!
- Thank you so much.
Well, she's always been
my favorite on "Star Wars"
since I was a little kid.
I had a crush on her
since I was, like,
eight years old.
So, I'd just like
to see her, you know?
( gasps )
That's awesome!
That doesn't really look
like me in a way.
- Show me where.
- Right up here.
There?
How we go...
- Where do you want it?
- Right here.
- Nice and big.
- Yes, sir.
¶ And that's
my big old signature. ¶
There you go.
Thank you.
- I really like
your overall look.
- Thank you.
That goes
without saying.
Thank you.
I like your outfit on you.
- Thank you.
- No bra, though.
( laughs )
I'll remember that
next time.
- Hey there.
- Hello.
Abe Gurko:
So, this is
one of these things
that we go to
at least once a month.
They're kind of
a mini Comic-Con.
Carrie resisted
these lap dances for years,
but it's amazing!
You see these thousands
of people that are
behind me here?
Okay, so, they line up
at 9:00 in the morning,
they'll stay here
until 9:00 at night
just to have two seconds
with Carrie.
Yeah, actually,
Liz and Matt, please.
- Carrie: Liz and Matt.
- Yes.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Don't cry. Don't cry.
- Stop it, stop it.
- Liz: It was--
- Matt: It probably
won't sink in for a while.
She's, like, my idol.
- Interviewer: Is she?
- Yeah.
How come?
She just epitomizes
a strong woman
who speaks her mind,
doesn't care what
anybody else thinks.
And I wish I was
more like that.
( music playing )
Photographer:
All right, here we go!
Man:
Let's go!
There you go.
( camera clicking )
Carrie:
Here we go!
( crowd chatter )
They love...
Gurko:
They love you.
Yes. They love her,
and I'm her custodian,
and I'm as close
as you're gonna get.
( laughs )
She's me and I'm her.
I mean, they talk to me
like I'm Princess Leia
who happens to have had
all these, you know,
difficult experiences
to go through,
and that's like me
fighting for the Force.
( laughs )
It's nice.
They're nice.
Oh, something's unplugged.
I can see it.
K.I.T.T.:
I thought this case
was top priority.
( engine revs )
( K.I.T.T. speaking )
I was on three episodes
of this show
where I played
a very pivotal character
for the lead character,
and so I've been to a lot
of "Knight Rider" conventions.
And when I went there,
I realized how much
I loved this car,
and I said,
"I got to have it."
I think it's important
that you, you know,
marry inside
the entertainment race.
( laughs )
And, you know,
that's an important thing
because people
don't get it.
I think you could--
my family, in particular,
could overwhelm
most people.
( camera clicks )
Todd:
It wasn't just my mother
that was super famous.
People forget my dad
was a world-class singer.
He had more consecutive hits
than the Beatles
and Elvis Presley combined.
At one time, he had 65,000
separate fan clubs.
( applause )
( orchestra playing )
¶ My eyes sing to you ¶
¶ My... ¶
Todd:
He had an exclusive contract
with Coca Cola.
He was the "Coke Kid."
...T.V.'s even more fun
with a bottle of Coke
in hand.
They gave him a percentage
of the Pasadena bottling
company proceeds.
I mean, he had it made
for life.
All he had to do
was behave a little bit.
Betty Johnson:
¶ I want Eddie Fisher ¶
¶ For Christmas... ¶
Todd:
My dad and mom, they were
cute as hell together,
and they had
the cutest little kids
together,
and they were
the couple of America.
Obviously, the studio
loved that setup.
You know, you put
the two of them together,
it's one heck
of a marketing tool.
I think my mother
really was in love
with my father
in a naive,
young person way.
First love.
And I think that was
the last time
that she ever
really experienced that.
¶ Wouldn't it be heaven
to find... ¶
- There.
- She's here?
Yeah, outside there.
( dog barks )
Hey, Dwight!
Mama!
Let's go that way, though.
You look beautiful.
You're wearing
the same shoes as I am.
- No, you gave me these.
- I know.
- You don't remember?
- No, I do.
I leave messages.
I know,
that's the greatest thing.
- I leave messages on here.
- I wish there was one.
- "I'm here."
- "Go away."
"If you want
to come in, come in
through the front door."
"It's not a rainy day.
It's my day to be
quiet and alone."
Alone is good.
I have to go
to my meeting now,
but I just wanted
to say hello.
I love you.
I love--
oh, oh, oh, oh.
- I love you.
- I don't know
where you're going.
I'm coming up.
¶ I'm coming up. ¶
And look, our shoes
are the same.
¶ I'm... ¶
- Sing the song.
- ¶ I don't want to go ¶
¶ I'm coming up ¶
¶ One of these days,
you will see me ¶
- ¶ I don't know the song ¶
- ¶ I'll be around... ¶
"I'll be around."
Carrie:
I think I'm my mom's
best friend
more than a daughter.
My mother really wants me
to be an extension
of her wishes,
an extension of her.
And to a great degree,
far more sometimes
than I ever would want to,
I know what my mother
feels and wants.
And there's a lot of it.
I share everything
with my daughter.
That's right.
Especially the check.
- Especially the what?
- Check.
She pays for everything.
Oh, that's--
it's not true.
She gets furious
when I bring up...
¶ Money. ¶
That's me.
¶ I'm enraged
last night ¶
Both:
¶ Like breathing out
and breathing in ¶
¶ I am completely independent
and content before... ¶
Todd:
My mother's always
liked the idea
of living
in the compound.
It's actually turned out
pretty good.
She's been there
a very long time,
and they have
obviously survived
the decades
of being there together.
Remember
my 17th birthday party
when you
lifted your skirt up
in front of...
- all those people...
- I did not lift my skirt.
- ...including
that guy Michael?
- It twirled up!
And you weren't wearing
any underwear.
Well!
Todd:
Carrie wrote the movie
"Postcards From the Edge"
about her relationship
with my mother,
and in the movie,
they end up having an argument
through two characters--
Shirley MacLaine
and Meryl Streep.
I'm going to kill myself.
Don't say that
even in jest, Suzanne.
Carrie:
I was very unhappy
back then.
I was just a mess.
And some of the things
that are in the movie happened.
- Any idea what she's taken?
- Woman: Pills, sir.
- Demerol,
Percodan, and cocaine.
- Give me her vitals.
Todd:
Carrie at this point
was famously into drugs.
- Suzanne?!
- Todd: And my mother
was not real happy about it.
( exhales )
There was anger,
true anger there.
I never said
you were a monster.
You don't say it,
but you feel it.
Somehow you lay
the entire blame for
your drug taking on me.
I do not!
I do not, Mother.
I took the drugs.
Nobody made me.
( projector whirring )
( chatter )
Todd:
Carrie and I started
getting high together
when we were about--
I was 15.
We used to
smoke weed together
and we had a lot of fun.
And then, you know,
she moved on to other things,
and I didn't.
When I would stop,
she would keep going.
Carrie:
I knew something
was the matter with me.
I went too fast.
I was too much.
And I was embarrassed
of it.
The drugs I liked
were painkillers.
They calmed me down.
I just couldn't--
I couldn't handle it.
I didn't know
what "it" was.
Reynolds:
Manic depressive
is a disease.
Now, that was
not diagnosed then,
so nobody kind of knew
what was going on with Carrie.
When she was 13,
her personality changed.
So it's a constant battle
that takes all of us
to assure her
that she's loved,
and that won't get her.
Hard.
Yeah, it's hard.
That's the hardest part.
( chorus singing )
It's Christmas
here in China on the Wall,
and we're headed
toward the top.
Todd:
Come with us.
Join us on a walk
on the Wall.
¶ Follow
the yellow brick road ¶
Chorus:
¶ So I'm offering
this simple... ¶
( music playing
on radio )
Come on, everybody!
( music continues )
Chorus:
¶ He's making a list
and checking it twice ¶
¶ Santa Claus
is coming to town ¶
¶ He sees you
when you're sleeping... ¶
We look like we're tired!
We're having a ball!
¶ With the little tin horns
and little toy drums... ¶
Carrie:
I have two moods.
Roy is Rollicking Roy,
a wild ride of a mood!
Wow, some of
that methamphetamine
released itself,
and the brain slid
and there was some trapped
methamphetamine
from my father.
Woman:
¶ Jingle bells,
jingle bells ¶
¶ Jingle all the way... ¶
- Carrie: Listen to the music.
- ( music distorting )
It's melting
from the heat.
( distorted music
continues )
Carrie:
Pam is Sediment Pam,
who stands on the shore
and sobs.
One mood is the meal,
the next mood,
the check.
( TV playing )
Where am I in all this?
I have no idea.
Because I feel like
it's a little mood
relay, you know?
I'm Pam now.
( clears throat )
See, if Roy
got this cold...
he wouldn't let him
stop it.
'Cause Roy is bigger
than all of it.
But I just fit snugly
into the mood pocket
that is Pam.
I don't have any choice.
I don't dictate the ride.
( music playing )
Look, the blue one, I think,
is probably better,
but this is crazier.
It's important to know.
Stevens:
That is very nice sweater.
Those are good
folk art colors.
That's what you are--
folk art.
Okay, see?
That's not bad.
And a person wearing this
would then have a room...
like this!
We met--
Debbie and Eddie
bought a house
two doors down
from where I lived.
I was 11 when they
first moved in, I think.
She was pregnant
with Todd.
- Carrie: Debbie
worked a lot...
- Yeah.
...so she wasn't there,
so, you know,
it's like you take
what you can get, really.
And if you can't have
Debbie Reynolds...
No, we wanted her.
Freiberg:
Here's the deal--
Carrie at two
was more interesting
than anyone I've ever known.
Todd was a very happy child,
very easygoing.
Carrie:
But we weren't made
with each other in mind.
Freiberg:
No, you were very different.
Carrie:
I was jealous of that.
It was simpler for him
for some reason.
Yeah.
Also, he didn't--
you suffered
from the divorce.
You had an attachment
to your dad,
but he wasn't
around much.
And then
Elizabeth Taylor--
- Carrie: Oh, God.
- ( Freiberg chuckles )
Reporter: In a scandal
that's gripping Hollywood
and the nation,
Eddie Fisher leaves
America's sweetheart,
Debbie Reynolds,
for her friend and neighbor,
Elizabeth Taylor.
Freiberg:
Something I had never seen
was all the paparazzi.
( reporters shouting )
Liz, over here!
Freiberg:
It was very dramatic.
I want to get out.
Now.
Freiberg:
And your mom was
quite dignified and quiet.
( reporters overlapping )
Reynolds:
I haven't even been informed.
I just got off the airplane.
I will not contest it, no.
Freiberg:
All of a sudden,
there were photographers
on your front yard
or on the sidewalk.
Carrie:
Don't remember it.
Freiberg:
Coming out of the driveway,
they took your picture
in the car.
Carrie:
I don't remember it.
- I don't want
to remember it.
- Yeah.
No, I do remember it.
I'm sure that
was very stressful.
I know
I didn't like that.
They were trampling me
and Todd to get to her,
so the sensation was that
she belonged to them.
My mom did say about her--
she said, "That's a sad child,"
and that's after,
I think, the divorce.
She had this sadness,
and then Harry Karl
was in the picture.
We were supposed
to call him "Daddy Harry."
Yeah, that was
gonna happen.
He was just a mass of noises
and monograms.
( both chuckle )
Carrie:
You have to
remember this.
There was an intercom,
and he would start calling,
( gravelly voice )
"Carri-i-e.
To-o-dd.
Hone-e-y."
"Honey"
was Debbie's name.
Freiberg:
You know, he owned shoe stores,
so that didn't interest us.
Carrie:
Nothing about him
was interesting
until we found out
about the hookers.
( laughs )
Oh, God.
And here he comes now,
industrialist
and philanthropist,
a celebrity
in his own right,
Harry Karl.
- And look who's with him--
Carrie and Todd.
- ( applause )
Todd: Harry Karl
walked into the perfect,
ready-made family,
and he seems like
a great setup.
- There's Mommy.
- There's Mommy, yeah.
Todd:
Loving, caring,
loved Carrie and I,
but we don't know at the time
that he has serious problems.
We don't know that
he is a compulsive gambler.
We don't know that he's
a compulsive drinker.
It was a disaster
in the making,
and it was really a disaster
when my mom came home one day
and saw
the foreclosure notice
on the front door
of one of the biggest houses
in Beverly Hills.
Reynolds:
¶ At the end
of the rainbow ¶
¶ There's happiness ¶
¶ And to find it,
how often I've tried... ¶
Todd:
We were both about to enter
a new era of reality.
Little did we know
what's really going on
at that exact moment
is Harry Karl
is gambling away
all of our money
and Harry and Debbie
were divorcing.
That was the tail end
of Carrie and I,
our innocence as children.
( projector whirring )
- Okay, let's go.
- All right, let's go.
We're going
to see Debbie.
Ma?
Reynolds:
Aw, I'm so happy to see you.
How are you?
Freiberg: I'm good.
How are you feeling?
Reynolds:
Shitty. Pretty bad.
( camera clicks )
Reynolds:
Freiberg:
Truly, you look
so beautiful.
You have to believe me.
Carrie:
I'm dizzy, and I think
I caught it from you.
Reynolds:
Here, you want some oxygen?
Carrie: Yes!
That's the ultimate hostess.
You're offered water,
soft drinks, oxygen.
- Reynolds: Here.
- Carrie: I'm taking it.
Carrie, muffled:
Freiberg:
Carrie, maybe you've had
enough oxygen.
- Carrie: What?
- Maybe you've had enough.
She seems very,
you know, coherent,
and she looks wonderful,
but she seems fragile.
And, um...
She's good
at seeming good.
- That's the thing.
- Yes, that's correct.
She's definitely
the lightest version
of Debbie
I've ever seen.
Um...
That would be
a good way to put it.
Yeah, Debbie Light.
( birds chirping )
- ( grunting )
- Boys: Holler "uncle"!
( sputtering )
You're tuckered, Molly!
Why don't you quit?!
Sure, I'm tuckered,
and I might give out,
but I won't give in!
How could anybody
say I'm down?
Look, I'm blinking!
( spits )
Todd:
Somehow, my mother
is unsinkable.
- Maybe here!
- ( shouts )
Todd:
That "Unsinkable Molly Brown"
stuff is her.
No place,
but there come a time
'cause nothing
nor nobody wants me down
like I wants me up!
Todd:
The idea that my mother
is now older
and she's more frail,
and I'm trying to see
what that feels like,
but I still don't feel it
because she's still
who she is inside.
( music playing )
Todd:
She went to school
at MGM,
where they trained you
how to behave,
and so it's
in her consciousness
to be at her best
at all times.
Howdy, everybody.
Welcome.
Glad to see
you're here at last.
And she's a fan
before she was ever a star.
When she went to MGM,
she was enamored
like anybody would be.
My God,
there's Clark Gable.
And I have pictures of her
with Gary Cooper.
You can see she's got
stars in her eyes.
Who wouldn't?
And she's still a fan
to this day.
( applause )
Oprah Winfrey:
But let me just say
that Debbie Reynolds
is a self-proclaimed
movie-oholic
and has an enormous Hollywood
memorabilia collection.
Altogether,
the costumes and props
are worth
millions dollars,
so this is sort of
your nest egg.
Yes, this is-- I put
all the money I could save
after all my husbands,
and I bought costumes.
This is Marilyn Monroe's
subway dress.
Wow.
Todd:
My mother's passion
for collecting
started when they were
auctioning off
the back lots of MGM
and all the contents.
The idea that this stuff
was going to be scattered
to the four corners
of the Earth
was unconscionable
to her,
so she took it
upon herself to say,
"I'm going to save it."
This is Liz Taylor's stool,
makeup stool from "Cleopatra."
This chandelier back here
is called a "girandole."
It's from "Marie Antoinette"
and "Camille."
In the end, she was
successful in amassing
the world's largest collection
of Hollywood memorabilia,
and so she wanted
to build a museum.
- This is from "Molly Brown."
- That's right.
Man:
People are always amazed
when they come to Hollywood
and there's no museum
of film history.
Reynolds:
I've tried.
It's just that no one seems
to be interested
that's in the business.
The public,
the fans are interested,
I'm interested.
We, for decades,
struggled to build
this museum.
It was impossible to believe
that this wasn't gonna happen.
But we couldn't find a partner
who shared her vision.
Deal after deal
fell through.
- "The Wizard of Oz."
That's Judy Garland's.
Chokes me up now.
You know, here we are--
we'll talk about this
in another 10 years,
I'll get choked up.
Nobody wants to see
their mother's heart broken,
and we saw it.
When we had
the first two auctions,
it was very traumatic
for my mother.
We sold the Marilyn Monroe
subway dress
from "The Seven Year Itch"
for $6.2 million.
The truth is the collection
was sinking her financially.
We had debt because
we had borrowed money
to get a lot of this stuff,
and we don't have
a museum.
We were done.
- ( water flowing )
- ( birds chirping )
Carrie:
In one week,
I have to go
and start rehearsals
in London
for "Star Wars
Seven...ty-two."
I'm concerned
because my mother
is not feeling well.
But I'm trying to let go.
It's like the--
( scoffs )
It's like I should be trying
to let go of my daughter
instead of trying
to let go of my mom.
So, everything is backward.
( music playing )
Carrie:
My question is,
if you die when you're fat,
are you a fat ghost?
Or do they go back
to a flattering time?
So now you got
to pick it up.
I'll go to 30,
but then you have
to let me go!
- Almost there!
- Let me go! Let my people go!
That's all
you're gonna get.
Oh! Okay, now cool down.
Keep it going.
Oh, I've been doing this
for a year.
Lucasfilm, they make them
report on my weight.
They take measurements.
I mean, it's--
it's intense.
- She loves it.
- I've learned to love it.
Gurko:
I hate to break
this conversation,
but the gift
for George Lucas's daughter,
is it her birthday?
Oh, the gift.
It's three months late
for his birthday.
No, it's the birthday
of the daughter, so--
- No, it's his. It was his.
- Oh, his birthday.
Okay, all right.
All right, I found
a place that wraps
and does
all the lovely things,
and I'll be back.
( mouthing words )
- ( Carrie humming )
- Trainer: Forward and back.
Back.
There you go.
Shoulders.
Where are the shoulders?
( humming continues )
California.
- We're going this way.
- Even if it's a lie.
No, there is no way--
no, that's the one thing--
that is my Waterloo.
After your exercise class,
what you need to do
is smoke a cigarette.
You hear that noise, Carrie?
That's what we have to do.
Clear the house.
He's bossy.
Don't clear it today.
Clear it tomorrow.
Every day.
We keep trying.
Here we go.
Gurko:
So, what's on the agenda?
Carrie:
Let's go shopping.
Inner health and well-being
you can now buy.
How much is
the little watch up there?
There's a man
with his penis
and a fat woman.
"Prepare to meet thy God."
- Uh-oh. When?
- Gurko: When?
Okay, and... action.
Look at all this.
I'm having
a crisis of joy.
Ooh!
What's nice here
is the lighting.
- Woman: Ah!
- ( laughs )
They're doing a film.
Do you know who Debbie
Reynolds is?
- Of course!
- She's my mother.
- Debbie Reynolds?
- Yeah, so--
- No.
- Yes.
So, you know
who Eddie Fisher is?
- Of course I know Eddie--
- Okay, that's my father.
Oh, and I'm in "Star Wars."
You know that movie?
Yes, of cour--
I'm Princess Leia.
Yes! This.
Oh! I need a picture!
Well, you're getting
a picture, look.
Look, they want--
Am I getting a picture
with Princess L--
take one
and then you can
send it to me.
- ( humming )
- My son will go ballistic!
( music playing )
Stevens:
So, was it good to see
the "Star Wars" gang again?
Anybody you have history with,
it's interesting
to see them after a while
or not--
I've seen Harrison and Mark
over the years.
You sort of run
into one another
in the cafeteria,
the celebrity cafeteria.
And they-- you know,
we all just look more melted.
Stevens:
Did you always want
to be an actress?
No, I wasn't
running around saying,
"I want to be an actress."
You know, I think you got
exactly the same eyes
as your mother,
- and your chin's
a little bit like hers, too.
- No, it isn't.
I only did "Shampoo" because
I was hanging around the set,
and they-- you know,
I mean, almost.
I was a type.
That was when Debbie wanted me
to use the word "screw"
instead of "fuck,"
and Warren had to come over
and convince her.
Can't we just, uh,
be friends?
You want to fuck?
Carrie:
And "Star Wars" came out
when I was 20.
I met Paul the next year,
and, boom.
Carrie:
Suddenly,
I'm with the people
that are the best
at what they do,
the best actors
and the best directors.
And that was fun and scary
to be around that.
It was all a surprise.
It all happened
very fast and very soon.
Stevens:
Carrie, someone's here!
Hey, fuckface!
- Carrie: Coming!
- Where are you?!
¶ I'm rooting ¶
Both:
¶ For the one I love ¶
¶ To find me ¶
¶ Today ¶
¶ Toda-a-y! ¶
( dog barks )
- Oh, my God.
- Who the fuck is this?
Home at last.
It's Gary, our son.
Where are we going?
We're going
into the bedroom,
as per usual.
So how's the new
"Star Wars" going?
- I'm not
allowed to answer that.
- Oh, that's right, you can't.
Close your eyes.
¶ Ha-a-a-a... ¶
- Can I open them?
- Yeah.
That's the only part
of the "Happy Birthday" song
- that I've been
able to learn.
- ( Dunne laughs )
That is what we sing now.
Oh, my God.
That is filthy.
Look it, that's his dick
that's keeping the time.
- As it can do.
- It's a second-hand dick.
- ¶ They called me
second-hand dick ¶
- ¶ Second-hand dick. ¶
- Dunne: It's so beautiful.
- Isn't it great?
- But I can really keep it?
- You can really keep it.
You know, I was thinking
it's very funny
that we're running into
each other in London, too,
because so many things
happened to us here in London.
I remember
you had a boyfriend
and you were a virgin,
and you didn't want him
to know you were a virgin.
So I helped you out
as a friend.
- He relieved me of the--
- The burden.
Burden of my...
- What is that called?
- Virginity.
- No, no, no, but-- hymen.
- Oh, the hymen.
I took the pressure
off your hymen.
My hymen
was a burden to me.
But that's what
a real friend does.
- That really is.
- But it was funny.
They always say sex--
sex can ruin a friendship,
but we were young enough
where it didn't.
- No, it was--
- I bet now it would.
- No, it wouldn't. No.
- ( laughs )
Swear to God,
my mother,
she offered for me
to have sex with
this guy Albert,
and she would supervise...
- Albert and I having sex.
- Actual having sex?
- Actual having sex.
- Walking you through it.
Yeah, because she apparently
has some tips on that.
"You take the staff of life
and the grapes."
- ( laughs )
- Oh, God.
For some reason,
I have to tell you this.
The first time I saw test--
like, this is a tour
of the first times
of genitals for me,
just endless tour.
Harry-- we all slept
in the room with them,
and Harry slept
in this top.
And he would
go to the bathroom.
So, here we go.
( whistles )
- Now, we're all there.
- Oh, God.
Why?
( whistles )
- Ugh.
- And here comes Dumbo.
I'm seeing the grapes,
where they would be.
This angry
slather of balls.
( both laugh )
That is a horrible story.
He was so awful.
Actually, Eddie
turns out to be one
of the better ones.
- Oh, my God, what a bar.
- I know.
You know, we can kind of
laugh and everything,
but I remember
you would look forward
to seeing your father
or talk, and he would
let you down, like,
over and over
and over again.
And so, I always felt like,
God, what a prick.
And I was so stupid
about it, though.
Yes, you were.
And you didn't
see it coming.
You were
an open-faced sandwich.
Like, "Yeah,
I'm right here."
- There we go.
There's a good title.
- And, bam!
"The Open-Faced Sandwich."
But he suddenly did make
more appearances.
He came and stayed with me.
He came to me.
And he said,
"I need, like,
$5,000, $10,000
for clothes."
I said,
"I don't have it.
And he went,
"You don't have it?!"
And he now points
to my house.
"You don't have it?!"
And I said, "Dad...
( chuckles )
...you're a singer,
not an actor.
Don't make a scene."
At that time,
he was kind of like
a guy who used to be
famous,
a sort of washed-up,
you know, um...
you know, lounge act.
It just makes me cringe
when you think about stars
that aren't stars anymore.
- Yeah.
- It's humiliating.
Stevens:
Todd, you said you could
sing like your father.
Todd:
Oh, yeah.
¶ Oh, my papa ¶
¶ To me, he was
so wonderful ¶
¶ Never there ¶
¶ Oh, my papa ¶
¶ To me he was so dear ¶
¶ Time and again
when he would take me
on his knee ¶
¶ And with a smile ¶
¶ He'd change my tears
to laughter ¶
Eddie:
¶ Oh, my papa ¶
¶ So funny,
so adorable... ¶
Todd:
When Eddie left,
I was, like, a year old.
One of the first times
I really connected
with my father
was after I shot myself
in the leg in New York.
( gunshot )
It was the first time
I had really heard from my dad.
He never had called me
before in my life.
I was like,
"Wow, that's unusual."
But, you know, I had
to shoot myself in the leg
to get him to make me
a call.
I have not been
the best father
in the world.
I still have that guilt
of not putting in
a certain amount of time
that I thought I should have.
All I had in my head
for years and years
and years was
making sure that I had
my drugs.
( music playing )
Todd:
Well, my dad
started off very early
with crystal meth.
It all started
with him saying,
"God, I just
can't do this show.
I'm so sick."
And this doctor
was there, and he said,
"Look, I got a shot."
And he gave him this shot,
and, man, he went out there
and sung his heart out.
And he was like,
"That's incredible!"
He was being told
it was vitamin shots.
That same doctor was giving it
to President Kennedy
and to J. Edgar Hoover,
and a lot
of very prominent people
were taking
these same drugs
until everybody
realized what it was.
But then it's too late,
now, isn't it?
People that get into drugs
generally make stupid choices.
If you look at my dad's life,
he got stuck on stupid
and ended up
blowing his career.
Carrie:
Puff Daddy.
You want a beverage?
( mutters )
Carrie:
My father,
the way that I had
a relationship with him,
finally,
was I became his parent,
and that was the way
to have the relationship.
It's very important.
Carrie:
And so I got to know him
as there was less
of him to know.
Was I always funny?
You know what?
I used to be funny
for you.
'Cause I thought
if I was really funny
that you would want
to be around me
all the time.
I would make myself
wonderful for your return.
See?
And it finally paid off.
( chuckles )
Carrie:
I wanted to be
your best girl,
and that's-- I had
tough competition.
Yeah. Well, you know,
if your competition
to be best girl with you
is Elizabeth Taylor,
well, I don't think
I'm gonna do well
with that one.
But I think I'm funnier
than Elizabeth Taylor.
Anyway, that's
always been a goal.
( chuckles )
You love me?
( softly )
I love you.
You're loveable.
( chatter )
( piano music playing )
Todd:
So, here we are,
approaching the third auction
of my mother's collection.
Unfortunately,
my mother just fell
because she was dizzy
walking into her bathroom.
When we saw her,
we were all in horror
because we were like,
"Wait a minute.
You know, you could
have broke your neck
or be dead right now."
I fainted.
I went plummeting
to the ground.
And I hit a rock or--
you know, in my bathroom.
And it was
12:00 at night,
and it just bruised
everything.
But-- I know, I'll do
the interview like this!
Todd:
But the subject
never came up
to cancel the auction.
You know, I suspect
she's going to show up
to the parties
and act like
nothing's wrong,
which is what she does
so well.
Here we are.
Carrie:
Here we are,
here we are.
Reynolds:
Oh, this is murder.
You ready to come up?
I've got your arm.
- Woman: Good evening!
- I'm Princess Leia's mother.
( laughter )
I'm wondering now,
you're about to be
done with the third--
Final.
It's the end
of an era,
but we hope
that the public enjoy
all these fabulous things.
What is it
about show business
that connects
the two of you
when you're not
on a red carpet?
We are always
on a red carpet.
We have red carpets
at home, connecting
our homes.
We are not people
with personas.
Todd: This is
everything that came
out of my mother,
right here, these two.
- Ugh.
- That doesn't sound good.
That doesn't sound
very good.
Well, it's a good thing.
George Pennacchio:
I'll ask one more question.
- ( gavel pounds )
- Sold.
475 to paddle number 1073.
My mom, she's having
second thoughts
about the Rat Pack
costumes.
She said, "I think
I want to keep them."
She personally collected
these outfits.
Debbie went
to Peter Lawford.
And he was like,
"Why in the hell do you want
my underwear and socks
and my outfit?"
And she's like,
"I want the whole ensemble,
and I want it
for the museum.
Reynolds:
I had a dream last night.
I say it's a vision.
I say it's someone
speaking to me,
that I should not
sell the boys.
¶ And all at once
it seems so nice ¶
¶ The folks are throwing
shoes and rice... ¶
Reynolds:
When I worked with Frank,
he called me "sweetie."
"Come on, sweetie,
sit over here."
So, I don't want to sell,
and I have to be here
and I have to be happy
about it,
so I have to have
happy things in my head.
I love having my ghosts
and I love having
my memories.
It's like you have
a friend forever.
It makes me smile
when I even just
say their names.
Auctioneer:
Sold, 650 to paddle 6000.
At the time,
the Hollywood Heritage Museum
did not have the funds
or the property
of the Hollywood
current museum
as it says
in the catalogue,
so, with that in mind,
we're going to sell
lot number 235.
Opening bid?
20,000.
Joe has the bid
at 20,000.
20,000,
the opening bid.
$22,500.
Is that a bid, sir?
Or are you just-- yep.
25,000.
Thank you.
Gentleman on the aisle
at 25,000
for the Charlie Chaplin--
- Man: 27,500.
- Auctioneer: 27,500.
Next would be 30,000.
Going once, going twice,
selling for $27,500.
The dog will not leave,
so do you want him
to lie down?
Stevens:
Um, he's okay there.
Reynolds:
But I'm gonna sort of face
that way a little bit.
'Cause I just--
I look so bad.
I don't want
to face direct.
Stevens:
No, you're gonna
talk to me...
- Oh, good, good.
- ...but I was gonna
stand right here.
Now...
is the hair in one place?
- Stevens: The hair?
- It's one place.
Okay, there we are.
Stevens:
The hair looks very good.
Okay, how are you--
by the way, how are
you doing?
Well, it's not my best day,
but that's all right
because we've had
other days that are worse.
Have we?
I'm happy to be here.
First thing I want
to ask you about
is how many years were
you under contract at MGM?
I was at MGM
from 1948...
through
"How the West Was Won."
We made a lot
of pictures at MGM,
and I had
a wonderful time.
I had a wonderful time.
I had... youth,
you know.
I had--
I was just a kid.
I didn't know anything,
and they taught me
everything.
Can we talk a little bit
about your brother
and just a little bit
about Texas?
- Because, um...
- If you like.
- Is that okay?
- Sure.
Oh, hi, Carrie!
¶ I'm not here. ¶
Reynolds:
You're going?
I'm going.
Go to bed.
Yes, go to bed.
Say good night
to everybody.
Good night
Stevens:
Will you come back
and visit us?
Reynolds:
No, no, no.
She's got to go to bed.
( mouthing words )
( chuckles )
( alarm blaring )
Stevens:
Oh, no! Oh, no!
( laughing ) The alarm!
She's locked in now!
Wait, Carrie!
I have no idea
what the alarm is.
Carrie:
Oh, my God.
( alarm continues )
I-I have no--
I have no idea...
Oh, my God.
Now the police
with come?
I suppose.
Michael?
Try 985-3193
or something.
I don't remember ever...
I don't remember ever,
ever turning this alarm on.
¶ Just one
of those things ¶
¶ Just one of those
fabulous things. ¶
It wasn't my day.
- ( alarm continues )
- ( dog barks )
- ( alarm stops )
- Stevens: That's it!
- Yay! ( clapping )
- Carrie: Ohh!
Stevens: Debbie,
while you're here,
can you just tell us
about the shoes and stuff?
Okay.
This is Judy Garland's shoe.
Well, was, of course.
They look small,
don't they?
Stevens:
Mm-hmm.
They would fit me.
Do you think
they fit you now?
She wore 5 1/2.
Stevens:
I'll get that for you.
- Sorry.
- Man: Okay.
I think we should end it
at the end of this.
Man:
Okay, yeah.
'Cause I think
everything's going wrong.
Okay.
And this...
is...
¶ We're off
to see the Wizard ¶
¶ The wonderful
Wizard of Oz. ¶
Thank you.
( kisses )
Chaplin.
Come on.
Stevens:
Thanks, Debbie.
- Come on.
- Stevens: You got it?
Man:
Mm-hmm.
( dog barks )
Carrie:
Dwight!
Do you want to go
to Vegas?
I know Dwight does.
Dwight always wants
to go to Vegas.
And they get
very excited.
Come on, it's hard
to take both of them.
Come on, Dwig.
Carrie:
We are going to do Vegas
with my mother.
I didn't know it
until my daughter told me.
It's absurd.
If you're going
to retire, you retire.
She retires and books
an engagement in Vegas,
and then says,
"Come help me."
I don't believe that
that's the last one.
( sirens wailing )
Carrie:
This is all against
doctor's orders, now,
as if any orders
apply to Debbie.
But everyone ends up
in Vegas.
You know,
if my mother's unhappy,
it lives on my grid,
so I both want to
and have to
help my mother.
She was very good
to her mother,
and her mother
didn't deserve it.
Debbie deserves it.
( projector whirring )
Carrie:
When Debbie
got into show business,
obviously it was
a big difference
in your lives,
but did you like it?
Maxine Reynolds:
Mm-mm. I think it's phony.
Your mother never knew
what it was,
and we went in blind.
And did you encourage her
to go in?
No. In fact, I've tried
to get her out of it.
( laughing )
What did Grandpa think
of show business?
Eh, he thought
it was a crazy way
to make a living.
( chuckling )
Well, what do you wish
that she would have done?
She wanted
to be a gym teacher.
You know that.
You think she would have
been happier doing that?
I think it would have
been more normal.
But she loves
what she's doing,
let's face it.
Loved it all,
and still does.
- Carrie: Yeah, she does.
- Yeah.
God gave her brains,
but He didn't put 'em
up here,
He put 'em
down in her ankles.
This is the view
of the whole--
this is Vegas.
I've been coming here
since the '60s,
but this will be
probably the finale.
I'm not feeling
that well,
and so, to be well enough
to do my whole show,
I asked my children
if they would come up
and relieve me.
Carrie:
"Carrie says, 'Mother,
you know
I started in your act
at 14 years of age."
Who talks like that?
"Todd comes onstage
and the family banters."
I don't want
to make fun of it,
'cause it's sweet
and she wrote this.
Then she sings
"This is a Lovely Way
to Spend an Evening"
and "Tammy."
I hope
it works out well.
And the song
that she's picked,
for me-- perfect.
¶ I'll never say no
to you ¶
¶ Whatever you say,
I'll do ¶
¶ If you ask me to wait
for a lifetime ¶
¶ You know
I'd gladly wait ¶
¶ For a lifetime
or two ¶
¶ Just to look at you. ¶
( coins clinking )
Reynolds:
The only way you make it
through life is to fight.
You don't get there
the easy way.
If you feel sorry
for yourself
and you let yourself
go down,
you will drown.
Todd:
Why don't we get you
out of there--
Just-- see that
doorway down there?
No, I know
where to park it.
- Okay.
- How about we walk you...
- ...and then we'll...
- Well, first I want to--
I'll take care
of your cart.
- Okay.
- She goes out the opposite.
- Well.
- I was trying to
get you out the easy--
I know.
I saw where
you were going.
I was trying
to get the stuff.
- I'll take care of this.
- I've got it.
- All right.
- Thank you.
( quiet chatter )
- ( band playing )
- Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen.
Here's Debbie!
( cheering and applause )
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to
the South Point Hotel.
I look what?
- Woman: Good!
- Oh, thank-- oh!
Woman #2:
Beautiful.
She says I look all right.
- ( applause )
- Do I look all right
back there?
( laughter )
Down here,
I look like a hooker.
- ( laughter )
- ( band playing )
This is it, you know.
You folks came at
the right time.
This is my last weekend ever
to be in show business.
- I'm gonna be...
- Audience: Aww.
I've got to retire.
Come on, say--
wish me luck.
Yeah, "Good luck,
Debbie! Yeah."
¶ Good times
and bum times ¶
¶ I've seen 'em all ¶
¶ And my dear,
I'm still here ¶
¶ Plush velvet
sometimes ¶
¶ Sometimes pretzels
and beer ¶
¶ But I'm here ¶
¶ I was a kid
with dreams and pluck ¶
¶ One-third was talent,
two-thirds luck ¶
¶ I saw some dreams
disappear ¶
¶ But I'm here... ¶
- ( applause )
- I enjoyed making that--
- Carrie: ¶ I'll never
say no... ¶
- Uh-oh.
¶ To you ¶
Reynolds:
You know my daughter.
¶ Whatever you say
I'll do ¶
¶ If you ask me
to wait... ¶
Carrie Fisher.
¶ ...for a lifetime ¶
¶ You know
I'll gladly wait ¶
¶ For a lifetime
or two ¶
¶ Just to look
at you... ¶
Ah!
( laughs )
¶ I'll smile ¶
¶ If you say be glad ¶
¶ I'll weep ¶
¶ 'Cause I'm bipolar... ¶
( laughter )
¶ Today is tomorrow ¶
¶ If you do
too much blow... ¶
- ( laughter )
- ¶ I'll stay ¶
Both:
¶ Or I'll go ¶
¶ But I'll ¶
Both:
¶ Never say ¶
¶ No. ¶
( cheering and applause )
Reynolds:
My daughter.
( applause and cheering
continue )
Nice to see you.
Woman:
Oh, likewise.
( indistinct chatter )
- Please don't retire.
- Oh, no, it's time.
- So beautiful.
- I love you.
- Bye-bye.
Great show.
Thank you.
Hi. How are you doing?
Bye-bye.
Good night.
( music playing )
Donald on phone:
Hi, Alexis.
This is Donald
calling for Debbie.
She's not gonna be able
to do that tomorrow.
I'm gonna put her on
so you can hear
how her voice is.
Hold on one second.
Debbie on phone:
Okay.
- She's not there?
- Donald: No.
Hello, Alexis?
This is Debbie.
If I can't speak,
I don't know a reason
to try to do a recording.
Why don't we just forget
about this till I'm well?
I'm sorry to bother you
with it.
Sorry to bother
the both of us.
Anyway, Carrie says
I should stop saying that.
I'm sorry.
But I am sorry.
Bye.
Carrie:
So, just when we thought
she'd stay home for a while,
my mom gets this big
lifetime achievement award,
and she's right there
back in the spotlight.
Reporter:
Actress Debbie Reynolds
will be the recipient
of this year's
Screen Actors Guild
Lifetime Achievement Award.
The ceremony
will be broadcast live
from the Shrine Auditorium
in Hollywood, California.
She was already making up
speeches in her head.
You know, she's like...
Her thing is sort of like,
"Well, I'm--
finally, they're..."
But she doesn't say that.
But they haven't been--
they haven't lavished her
with awards.
Yep, you sit at your seat,
just next to your mom here.
That would be terrific.
Carrie:
Here we go.
Man:
Debbie Reynolds,
Lifetime Achievement Award.
Carrie Fisher, standing in
for Debbie Reynolds.
¶ Follies... ¶
Todd, I--
Todd, I stayed overnight.
I was-- yeah.
She doesn't feel well.
She feels like shit.
Then let's do that.
Let's let her not be there
at the table, and lay down...
That doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
I'll find out,
but it doesn't matter.
Oh, how much time
would she have to sit
at the table?
Carrie:
We're gonna need some kind
of place for her to lay down.
Yeah. Sure.
Carrie:
Okay, so if there's
just, like, anything
that's not embarrassing.
Woman:
We'll make
an area for her.
( Carrie whispering )
Got it.
We'll-- we'll--
- we can make this work.
- She's like...
Yeah.
It's okay, Carrie.
We can make this work.
We've done it before.
( Carrie crying )
They're gonna set aside, like,
a little area for her...
so she can do it,
you know.
( crying continues )
I know.
Woman:
Give Debbie my best,
all right?
Carrie:
Hi, Mama.
I passionately,
passionately
am going to marry you
while you're sleeping
tonight.
And by the morning,
I will have taken
all your money.
( Gurko laughs )
No, I want
your bedroom cleared.
Except for me
because I'm your favorite!
Oh.
I'm sorry.
God damn it.
I know.
Well, please, could--
is there any way
you could go to sleep...
now?
Okay, I'll get off
the phone with you.
I'm-- I'm coming home.
( music playing )
Carrie:
I like Christmas.
I like the lights.
My mom...
she is Christmas.
She's something special.
- Wait, did you get drinks?
- Yeah, perfect.
Seriously, though,
you secretly want something.
I know you do.
( audience laughs on TV )
Carrie:
You know, I could do
a pretty good Streisand.
¶ You're a funny girl ¶
¶ That's me ¶
¶ I keep them
in stitches ¶
¶ Doubled in half ¶
¶ And though I may be all ¶
¶ Wrong for the guy ¶
¶ I'm good for a laugh. ¶
Your voice is beautiful.
Thank you.
Um...
( groans )
I should have been
a pair of ragged claws
scuttling across the floors
of silent seas!
You know what would
be so cool?
To get to the end
of my personality...
and just, like,
lay in the sun.
( music playing on TV )
Oh, I have to watch
a little of this.
I'm sick of myself.
Smile.
¶ I'm crazy about ya... ¶
Carrie:
I love this movie.
I love every lyric.
¶ I can't do
without ya... ¶
Woman:
Are you okay, Carrie?
Mmm.
That's how I've gotten
through a lot of it...
- is abstract it...
- Woman: Mm-hmm.
...so that it's not
happening to me.
It's...
I just--
I'm a, um...
type of bird.
( laughing )
I'm manic right now.
I didn't know if you've...
And I haven't been
for a while.
¶ Than be
hap-hap-hap-happy... ¶
It'll go out of style soon,
and then I'll just
be quirky.
¶ ...else! ¶
( cheering and applause )
- ( bangs )
- Carrie: Ohh!
( gasps )
Careful, all right?
( chuckles )
¶ Makes me so exquisite... ¶
I make my own blends.
Okay, you just kind of...
- ( vocalizes )
- ( woman laughs )
- Fun tonight.
- It's more than fun.
It's-- it's magical,
and things
will start happening now
that you want
to have happen.
( laughing )
You are fucking amazing.
- ( all laughing )
- I'm fuckin' amazing!
Man:
I know.
Yeah, later,
because they...
( continues indistinctly )
Woman:
I know...
( chattering )
Billie:
Is she moving
at all?
Alexis:
Todd, you've got
to get her out.
You can't push her
or you don't get nothin'.
If you push,
and then she gets mad,
you can't have that.
That's the worst thing
that could happen,
so you've gotta just
kind of act like...
The show has started.
And I'd like to accept
this award on behalf
of every dog on Earth.
Carrie:
Jodie Hattaway!
Can you go check
and just tell us anything?
Yes, I will be happy to.
Billie: Does she realize
that we're gonna
miss the show?
Of course.
Should I go and, like,
hustle her out?
Woman:
Your mom or Debbie?
Here comes the old lady.
I'm very sorry.
Woman:
Yay!
We're here, Mom,
right here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
So, hello, gorgeous.
Who said that?
I want to tell you all
what fun it is
to go out on the town.
Woman:
Have a good time.
Reynolds:
Thank you.
I just want to say...
Todd:
Your segment.
What is my award?
Now I can't even think.
Todd:
You're getting the Lifetime
Achievement Award.
Life-- well,
that's the thing, see?
I get upset, so I can't
remember anything.
It's an achievement
that you even got here.
Todd:
That's the real
achievement.
This is the what award?
Billie:
Lifetime Achievement.
- But...
- Screen Actors Guild.
- Todd: But it's on
the prompter.
Carrie, was the prompter
big enough?
The prompter is huge.
I just want to know
what it is.
Like, in real life
right now,
like we're talking here--
we're talking,
and we're just saying.
Billie:
We're just saying it's the SAG
Lifetime Achievement Award.
It's just called
a Life Achievement--
like S-A-G?
SAG Lifetime
Achievement Award.
Screen Actors Guild.
- SAG. SAG.
- Billie: SAG. Lifetime.
You don't really
have to say it,
I don't think.
- I have to say it.
- I'm not worried about that.
I just want
to really know--
Todd:
She's gonna
set it all up for you.
I just really want to know
what it really is.
Right now,
I just blanked out.
Billie:
It's the biggest honor
in your industry.
- It is?
- It's a big deal.
- I mean, it actually is.
- All: It is!
Billie:
No, it is.
It's the biggest honor.
Todd:
Do you have enough air
on you back there?
You know, you keep
asking me questions.
- Did you--?
- I don't need
any questions.
Don't ask you questions.
Okay.
I'm just trying
to stay, uh, level,
like I'm-- I'm--
I'm, uh...
Todd:
Don't talk to us.
Just relax.
Billie:
Just breathe.
Carrie:
If you could
slow down just a tiny,
tiny, tiny little bit.
Reynolds: I know
you're being coached.
Carrie:
Vomiting is a possibility.
Reynolds:
I know.
Best of all,
don't-- don't--
I don't--
no, I'm not.
I know.
- Ohh.
- Okay, here we go.
Looks like
I'm going onstage.
Announcer:
Please welcome
Carrie Fisher.
( music playing )
Okay.
Uh...
I am very close
to this year's
Screen Actors Guild
Life Achievement Award
honoree.
Gurko:
Hey!
Gary, look,
there's your mommy.
Carrie:
I found it difficult
to share my mother
with her adoring fans...
She's nervous as hell,
isn't she?
Carrie:
She has lived
two lives...
Gurko:
I mean, she was throwing up
leading into this.
I'm sure
Carrie's flipping out.
I am proud to present
the Screen Actors Guild
Life Achievement Award
to my mother,
Debbie Reynolds!
Ahh!
( music playing )
( cheering )
( mouthing words )
- Reynolds:
Thank you. Thank you.
- ( cheering )
I want to thank
the Screen Actors Guild
for awarding me
with this tonight.
It's very unexpected.
And, you know, I've been
in the business now...
( deep breath )
...66 years.
And, uh, my favorite movie
was "Singin' in the Rain."
Well, I did mention--
did I say that? Yeah.
And I had a good time
making that picture,
wearing myself out.
God gave us talent,
so we're very fortunate.
We all are.
What we do best,
believe in it.
And of course, we--
we do that of course,
and my favorite movie was
"The Unsinkable Molly Brown,"
and I had a lot of fun
doing that.
- ( applause )
- Thank you.
In that movie,
I got to sing
a wonderful film--
uh, song,
called, uh,
"I Ain't Down Yet."
- Well, I ain't.
- ( chuckles )
Thank you all very much
for this wonderful award.
( cheering and applause )
- ( music playing )
- Thank you.
Announcer:
Coming up-- Ethan Hawke,
Patricia Arquette,
Rashida Jones, Andy Samberg,
and, with a special tribute,
Liev Schreiber.
( chatter )
- How was it?
- It was fine.
- Fine.
- Were you nervous
at all up there?
- Um, yes, but not for--
- I was nervous. I was nervous!
When did you not
get nervous?
You seemed like
you settled down.
Well, no,
it wasn't that I--
the whole evening,
to me, was wonderful.
And there's no business
like show business.
- Tonight--
- You know what?
I have to say
something.
Everything about it
is appealing.
( laughter )
Something that
the traffic will applaud.
Everything.
No, seriously,
everything,
well, the traffic
will allow.
- Nowhere can you get...
- Woman: That happy feeling.
When you're stealing--
and I don't mean, you know,
out-and-out stealing...
An extra bow.
Extra bow.
But there's no people
like show people.
There are people
- Nah, it's true.
- Now, that's true.
Well, the smiling
when they're low...
- ...us schizophrenics
are like that.
- Oh, really?
- So, they're
like show people.
- Reynolds: Really?
If they offered you another
Life Achievement Award,
would you do it?
Now, I can't be funny
about tonight.
It's too special.
- Okay.
- It was a special night.
But that was
a good question, though.
Could you handle another
life achievement award?
'Cause they're gonna see
that you did one,
and they're gonna
want to do--
That's right,
the floodgates are open.
I can't answer it,
because...
it's too special,
and I won't
be here then.
I will have gone on.
So it's very important
for this moment--
For the big
life achievement.
( chuckles )
You don't get a chance
to have a moment
like this very often.
It's not like any moment.
It's its own special moment.
( chatter )
( laughter )
- ( piano music playing )
- Man: "The man that won you."
¶ The man
that won you... ¶
"Has run off
and undone you."
¶ Has run off
and undone you ¶
- "The great beginning."
- ¶ The great beginning ¶
- "Has seen a final ending."
- ¶ Has seen a final ending ¶
- "Don't know what happened."
- ¶ Don't know what happened ¶
- "It's all a crazy game."
- ¶ It's all a crazy game ¶
Yeah! "Ever since
this world began."
¶ Ever since
this world began... ¶
Carrie:
All right, we have to stop,
as my therapist
likes to say.
Debbie:
Say good night, George.
Can't you say,
"Good night, George,"
and I'll say,
"Good night, Gracie"?
Carrie:
That's not original, Mother.
Reynolds:
Oh, I know,
but it shouldn't be.
It should be
just simply funny.
It's slightly amusing
to you.
Carrie:
Why continue
working so hard?
Reynolds:
Say good night.
( Carrie laughs )
Good night,
and thank you
for joining us here
around our family "herth"--
"harth."
( Carrie laughing )
Hearth!
Reynolds:
You know I loved you.
( music playing )
¶ Love is a thing ¶
- ¶ A sting ¶
- ¶ Aah! ¶
¶ That brings
a reason for livin' ¶
¶ Love is a fling ¶
¶ There's never any doubt ¶
¶ Love will unhinge ¶
- ¶ And singe... ¶
- Man: Ow!
¶ And cringe
the weak and the hearty ¶
- ¶ Love is a binge... ¶
- ( man hiccups ) Yeah.
¶ That pushes logic out ¶
¶ Love has a way
of catching ¶
¶ A person unaware ¶
¶ No rhyme or reason ¶
¶ Any time or season ¶
¶ A blight, a fright ¶
¶ A thief in the night ¶
- ¶ Love is a noose... ¶
- ( man groans )
¶ A ruse,
no use to try ¶
¶ To resist it ¶
¶ Love is a thing ¶
¶ That no one
can live without ¶
¶ Love ¶
¶ Has a way
of catching hold ¶
¶ Like a cold ¶
¶ No rhyme or reason ¶
¶ Any time or season ¶
¶ A blight, a fright ¶
¶ A thief in the night ¶
- ¶ Love is a word... ¶
- ( man whispering )
¶ A word I've heard ¶
¶ Referred to in whispers ¶
¶ Love's girls and boys ¶
¶ Making noise ¶
¶ And after dark,
in some respects ¶
¶ It's just a bundle
of sound effects ¶
- ¶ Well, it's a wheeze... ¶
- ( man coughs )
- ¶ A sneeze... ¶
- ( man sneezes )
- ¶ A pop, a cop ¶
- ( pop, whistle blows )
- ¶ A crow ¶
- ( bird squawks )
¶ A chicken and a dove ¶
¶ And they can hand it out,
give it out ¶
¶ None of us
could live without love ¶
¶ Love is. ¶