Crab cakes.
Your favorite.
Trying to bribe me,
Mr. Martinez?
It's not a bribe.
It's a hot meaI.
Fryer's still leaking.
How's your girlfriend?
He said he was
going to fix it.
I tell him, but he keeps
blaming everything on me.
If you downgrade us,
he's gonna fire me.
See you tomorrow.
Flynn.
He wants to see you.
Hey.
Flynn.
Can I just say something?
If this is about
the crab cakes-
It's not.
Seems your resume
failed to mention
a certain 11 months in jaiI
four years ago.
You've done
a good job here.
But we have a responsibility
to the public trust,
and you broke that trust.
I guess I did.
Hi.
Are you expecting someone?
Yeah.
Oh.
Are you bribing me?
Well, yeah, okay.
All right, it's a little bribe.
# If I had the time to solve
the mystery of your crime #
# you know I would #
# If I had to shape the form
of your mechanicaI design #
# you know I would #
Oh, my God.
What are you doing to me?
You can't play this song.
Don't tell me
you don't like this song.
Turn it off.
Really?
All right.
Don't move out.
I already moved out.
Please.
Take the keys.
No, I don't
need the keys.
I have another copy of them.
You can keep them.
After two years,
you know what I know about you?
I know two things
about you:
You take steroids
for dust mites.
It's for my allergies.
And you grind your teeth
when you sleep.
That's why
you get headaches.
That is-
that is not-
that's not true.
You know me. That's not true.
I've told you tons of stuff.
Nat called.
I told you-
He said he's your father.
He's pretty chatty for a dead man.
I- I never said he was dead.
Yes, you did.
Well, he's dead to me, so...
Your name's not even Flynn.
Yes, it is.
All right,
Flynn's my last name.
Hey, hey.
Maggie, I don't know
what kind of stupid stories
he's been telling you,
but whatever it is,
it's got nothing to do with us.
It's him.
He's toxic.
What did he want?
He called to borrow money,
right, collect?
I bet he was
reaI charming too.
That's how he works.
He pulls you in.
He makes you
feeI sorry for him.
And before you know it,
he's in your pocket.
Don't talk about him like that.
What?
He called to say
he was dying, Richie.
He isn't dying,
and don't call me Richie.
Why would he say he's dying
if he isn't dying?
Because it's the only card
he has left to play.
You don't understand.
He isn't dying.
He's Iying.
Like father,
like son.
I'll take the boat.
Flynn.
It's good to see you.
So welcome to my casbah.
Here.
You like boats.
I taught you to motor a boat.
Yes?
No.
Of course,
out on the harbor.
That was Uncle Al.
Al was in Rikers
from that chop shop deaI.
No, it was Al.
You're right.
You don't look sick.
Thank you.
You're llstenlng to...
One second.
WNJ, New Jersey's home
to the tlcket glveaway.
The flrst caller
who gets through
wlll wln two tlckets
to the sold-out 50 Cent concert.
Golng to the flrst caller
to say, "I love WNJ. "
Caller, you're on the alr.
Thls Is Nat Santos,
and I love WNJ.
Congratulatlons, Nat.
You just won two tlckets
to the sold-out 50 Cent concert.
Hold on.
We'll get your Info.
Congratulatlons.
Can we get your name
and where to send the tlckets?
Yes, Nat Santos,
P.O. Box 981,
Atlantlc Clty.
Thank you.
Well...
Santos, huh?
It's one of my aliases.
They have restrictions
on how many times you can call in.
Don't shake your head.
Know what I can scalp
these tickets for?
Cut my overhead
for a month.
So you sit here all day
trying to win
freebies off the radio now?
When did you know me
to sit around?
I got things to do.
How about you?
Stlll behavlng yourself?
Yeah, I'm trying.
Two tlckets golng out
to the flrst caller
who can correctly Identlfy
thls band.
Duran Duran.
Spandau Ballet.
Is It Spandau Ballet?
Spandau Ballet Is correct.
You just won
two tlckets to the-
You're right.
What am I doing here, Nat?
I can't remember the last time
you called me Dad.
You told me you were dying.
You're obviously fine.
So what is it you need me for?
Want me to help you rig a bingo game
at a golden age club?
That's so mean.
I don't do bingo anymore.
Since when?
Since...
you get out.
I got a rotten egg
inside my head.
It's a tumor.
Malignant,
inoperable, and growing.
It's preoccipitaI,
is the medicaI
mumbo jumbo.
Sorry.
Me too.
You hungry?
I could use
a cup of coffee.
Let's go.
So what are you
up to these days?
Are you working?
Yeah,
I'm a health inspector.
Really?
Is that good?
How do you do that?
Well, I'm the guy who makes sure
there's no mouse turds in your salad
when you go to a restaurant.
That's good.
What? This is the coffee?
Yeah.
Help yourself.
I need you to drive me
to New Mexico.
There's a treatment
down there,
some kind of experimentaI
holistic thing.
They dunk you in mud,
do chanting.
I don't know.
They need volunteers,
so I get a freebie.
Maybe it's
a waste of time,
but I figure,
what the heck?
Won't take
more than a week, tops.
A week?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I'm not taking you.
Why can't you
drive yourself?
Drive myself?
This thing's
messing with my vision.
Why can't you get
somebody else?
Don't you have any friends?
None that I don't owe money to.
So take a plane.
You got all those vouchers.
Why don't you use them?
Doctor says altitude's bad
also for my brain.
Makes for swelling.
Turn in here.
I want to show you something.
Hey.
Hey, Nat.
Morning.
Meet my son.
What a thrill.
Nice to meet you.
Barney's been storing it for me
in his humidor.
It keeps it soft.
Here,
try it on.
Hm?
What do you
think it's worth?
I don't know.
Take a guess.
Nothing.
This is one of four jackets
worn by Steve McQueen
in The Great Escape.
Where'd you get this?
Bert Kruger.
You probably
don't remember him.
He had car dealerships
when you were a kid.
Kruger Motors.
No.
Your mother worked there.
Anyway,
he won the jacket
in some charity raffle.
He gave it
to your mother.
She left It behlnd
when we broke up.
I was going to sell it,
but then I thought, "No,
"I keep it for Flynny.
If he wants,
after I die, he can sell it. "
It's a nest egg.
It's a bribe.
It's a jacket.
A nice jacket.
Looks good on you,
don't you think?
Thanks, Marty.
I have to know,
are you my wheeI man or what?
Jeez.
You know, you're really
putting me on the spot here.
I mean, I got a job.
I got commitments.
I only brought
an overnight bag.
The fact is,
I don't want you to do this.
I need you to.
I need to make things
copasetic between us.
I know I've been
a terrible father.
It's not a thing
I can ignore.
Sometimes,
for no particular reason,
life hauls off and knocks you flat,
slams you so hard against the ground,
you think that all your insides are busted.
But if you look for something
to replace what's broken,
if you're lucky, you can find it.
You're all I have.
You really
got a brain tumor?
You think I'd kid around
about a tumor?
I do.
Come on.
Just say yes.
All right.
You're the one.
You're pure,
pure flame.
I'll drive you.
Blood is thick.
All right.
Know what I'm saying?
You behave.
And these glue traps
are just plaln gross.
Hlgh technology arrlves
wlth the push-
Thing you do now
is try and forget it.
How, Pa?
How you gonna
forget somethlng llke that?
What I'm trylng to say Is,
now and then,
for no good reason
a man can figure out, life will just...
haul off
and knock hlm flat,
slam hlm agaln'
the ground so hard
It seems llke
all hls Insldes Is busted.
And you start looking around
for something good
to take the place
of the bad.
As a generaI rule,
you can find it.
Think you packed enough?
CooI, no?
New regulations
at the airlines
say you got 60 days
to pick up unclaimed baggage.
After that...
# You belong to me #
This is the good stuff.
Louis Vuitton.
You're not
golng to be sorry.
I got this
so totally worked out.
And you don't have to dip
in your pocket for a thing,
zlp, zllch,
not a crouton.
This trip's on me,
ever last pillow chocolate.
That is good news.
Of course.
I got us set up
in five-star places.
Wait'll you see.
You're going
to be shocked and awed.
Let's go.
What zip code
did you park in?
Oh, here's our ride.
Are you shittin' me?
Free wheels and gas
for a year.
AII I have to do
is drive 1,000 miles a month.
No way.
No, no, no.
Why not?
No, I'm not
getting in there.
I'm not
getting in that.
Don't be a snob.
No.
You know what?
You are completely insane.
You're gone.
Going, going, gone.
Get in the car.
Don't-
don't put that there.
Put that over here.
No, don't put that on.
That stinks.
What about your Maggie?
Is it serious?
'Cause she's
answering your telephone.
It is.
Don't do what I did.
Don't let go
of something speciaI,
'cause, in my experience,
it comes along once.
Okay.
Thanks for the advice.
She dumped you, right?
Yeah, I'm psychic.
Turn in here.
We need to make a stop.
What, you got to take a piss?
No, make a right.
I got a surprise.
Just make a right.
What kind of surprise?
We just got on the road.
I was feeling good.
Little trim, a spruce-up,
get back on the highway.
I don't need a little trim.
I promise you,
these women are good,
and it's not
going to cost a dime.
What the heck?
They don't have their license?
Big deaI.
They're about to be
very good at what they do.
Mm.
Yeah.
There you go.
Yeah, Nat is one
of our favorites.
He's up for anything.
Oh, yeah?
He let me put his hair
in a Mohawk last summer.
No.
I bet it was great
growing up with a dad like that.
Yeah.
You know, if it wasn't for Nat,
I wouldn't be here.
Tuition's reaI pricey.
What, he paid your tuition?
Not exactly.
But he knew
a guy whose wife
was having a hard time
getting knocked up,
so your dad thought of me,
if you know what I mean.
I'm afraid to ask.
He sold my eggs.
Got me enough
for a new car too.
Yep, Nat's the bomb.
Sherry, what have you done?
So much better.
You like it?
Yeah, yeah.
Tips.
All around excellent service.
30 free minutes.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
I'm crazy about you.
Okay.
Good?
They only do
one haircut here, huh?
I always knew you had big hair.
Women; they take care
of everything for me.
They're saints.
Flynn.
There's a good one.
What was that for?
Are you trying to blind me?
It's for my wallet.
When's the last time
I had a picture of you?
My mug shot.
Does that thing
even work anyway?
Three box tops and $1.20
post and handling, of course.
Oh.
30 days unlimited airtime.
It's promotionaI.
Take a couple.
Hey, let me
ask you a question.
Yeah?
When was the last time
you actually paid for something?
You know how much
I'm out-of-pocket
in the last six months?
50 cents.
$900, and I've wanted for nothing.
Rent, food, sundries,
entertainment, even.
That works out
to under $5 a day.
Well, if you stopped eating,
you'd cut it down to three.
Do you know how many people
could do what I'm doing?
You may see
a curious old person,
but I see
a good-looking older guy
who's making the system
work for him.
I do quite well,
you know, in my modest way.
It's sort of monkish.
AII I need is my bowI.
I go from village to village,
tapping with my stick.
Who taught you
how to drive?
You're a terrible driver.
You're a lot like me.
Nat.
- Hey.
- Huh?
- You all right.
- Yeah.
Food.
Let's eat.
Who planned this route?
It's like an EKG.
It's worked out exactly.
We do a trip down memory lane,
plus there's an IHOP and a Chevron station
every 300 miles.
I get free gas.
It's the best
of all possible worlds.
Let's go.
Every day's my birthday,
'cause I got a guy
who does drivers licenses.
Watch.
Welcome to IHOP.
Thank you, darling.
Is Jones on the grill?
Oh, God, no. He died years ago.
No. Enough said.
May he rest in peace.
We'll have
a window booth.
Window booth.
You might not remember Jonesy.
WonderfuI Reuben sandwich.
Thank you.
What's the most
expensive dish you have?
Chicken combo.
It's $11.99.
He'll have two.
Yes.
Ma'am?
Mm-hmm.
Right here.
Oh.
Thank you.
Make a wish.
Nah-
Grab the bone.
I don't do that stuff.
Come on.
No, it's voodoo stuff.
Nobody's thinking about it.
Grab the bone.
I'm not superstitious.
I wish I could run across
my own private beach
and jump in the ocean.
What about you?
You wanted a boat.
I used to want
a lot of things.
Altoona.
We had good times here.
Are you serious?
This was our turf.
Father and son.
You want to know
the last time I called you Dad?
It was right here in Altoona.
I said, "Thanks, Dad,"
right after they found me
guilty of grand larceny.
I took my eye off the ball.
Definitely, I did.
I was willing
to do the time.
You had a record.
You would've done
ten years.
And then you hired that clown
impersonating a lawyer.
And he guaranteed
I'd get off.
Everybody said he was tops.
Hey, look at me.
11 months, a week,
and 3 days at Rahway, Dad.
# Many happy returns of the day to you #
# Many happy returns #
# Happy birthday #
# Many happy returns
from IHOP #
That's all right.
Thank you.
Which one's
the birthday boy?
That's me.
Thank you.
Well, Happy Birthday.
All right, thanks.
Don't mention it.
Happy Birthday.
Can I pick them or what?
Wow.
Whose house is it?
Our new best friend.
His name's Nobody,
and su casa's our casa.
For-sale listings
in 2,700 counties.
I don't know why I was thinking
you might spring for a moteI.
Let's go.
Oh, hey,
I'm not going in there.
Why not?
It's empty.
I'm an ex-con,
and it's illegaI.
Whoop.
Huh?
Let's check out
the bed sltuatlon.
I hope they got a firm rack.
These doggies are tired.
Sweet dreams.
I'm just going to go
sleep in the car.
Yeah, sleep in the car.
Hl, thls Is Maggle.
Please leave a message.
Hl, are you there?
I'm on the road...
with my father.
I think I'm going to be gone
a few days.
You were right.
It hurts me
to say this,
but the only person
who really knows me is him.
And that scares the hell out of me.
Anyway...
I don't know.
Maybe it's too late.
But even If you hate me,
I want you to know
who you're hatlng.
The thlng Is,
I'm not from Canada.
I was born In Secaucus,
New Jersey.
I don't have
any brothers or sisters.
I grew up
without a mother
because my father
drove her away.
I-
Promotlonal perlod ended.
To purchase addltlonal mlnutes,
press 7.
Hello?
Nat!
I got a gun!
Whoa.
Richie.
Don't call me Richie.
Flynny.
Always good
to see you.
Oh.
I slept
like a polar bear.
So good.
I need coffee.
There's a wonderfuI moteI
83 miles away.
Comps on coffee
and Danlsh.
The 7-Eleven.
Or we could
buy a cup now.
We're doing
so good here.
Let's not blow it
on luxury items.
Come on.
Perfect.
Take it easy.
Lovely.
And It Is just
the safest nelghborhood.
Hi.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Wish you could, darling.
The house is wonderfuI.
We like it.
The fact is,
my partner and I
are looking for something
a little more feng shui-ish.
The house Is wonderful,
though, Isn't It?
Vaulted celllngs.
Take it easy, honey.
It's the first place we've seen.
It's got everything.
Thank you.
Yikes.
We escaped.
Last time I drove
across country,
it took me four days.
Did I tell you that?
No.
A lifetime ago.
Four perfect days.
We wound up on a beach
in Mexico, freezing.
White sand,
clear blue water,
your mother looking up at me
like I was the one.
That's when I asked her
to marry me.
Then we did it,
twice, maybe three times.
Yeah, shake your head.
These are memories.
You'll see what it's like
when things stop happening on command.
Half mast.
I'm not even dead yet.
What are you saying,
you're impotent?
I'm saying, I can't get it up
most of the time.
Since when?
Since...
Uh, it's hard to say.
Couple of years,
maybe five.
Well, have you tried
taking those pills?
They're junk.
They don't work.
Where'd you buy them,
off a fruit truck?
What difference
does it make?
They don't work.
I don't work.
Clock's ticking.
One last frolic
is not going to stop that, is it?
Use this for the gas.
The Sweet'N Low people
will pick it up.
Be back in a flash.
Room service, please.
Room servlce.
How may I help you?
Yes, we'd like to order up some brunch,
my wife and I.
What room, please?
Room 120.
All rlght.
Thank you so much.
Please hold.
Yes, I'll wait.
Thank you.
Sir.
Could you leave the tray
outside the door?
My wife is under the weather,
and I'm trying
not to disturb her.
Thank you so much.
May I add the tip
to the check?
Sure.
There. That's for you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir.
Please.
Thank you.
Hl, thls Is Maggle.
Please leave a message.
Hey, it's me.
Are you there?
Are you there? Are you there?
Okay, another confession.
Um, thls Is...
Thls Is a llttle trlcky.
I'm gonna-I'm gonna tell you
a story, okay?
Here we go.
My father
drove a beat-up Mustang
wlth 150,000 mlles on It,
about the tlme a sane person
buys a new car.
But not him.
He rents a new Mustang,
strips it, and swaps the parts
with his hunk of junk.
Then he returns the rentaI,
complains it's a lemon,
and gets his $69 back.
But guess what.
Thls tlme,
they nailed him.
And guess what else.
My name was on the lease.
Okay?
You can guess the rest.
All right.
I'm going to call you back.
I'm thinking
about those lobster dinners
we pinched from that place
up in Bar Harbor.
Could you forget the taste,
the flavor,
the freshness?
It was like the ocean.
Eat something.
You can't
live on coffee.
I'm tired.
You're depressed.
Anybody in your situation's
got to feeI like junk.
The trick is to take your mind
off getting dumped.
Every obstacle
is an opportunity.
Think about it this way.
You have a clean slate.
No girI.
No job.
No nothing
to hold you back.
How did you know
about my job?
You sent that letter
to the health department?
The whole thing
was beneath you.
You got me fired.
I did you a favor.
You want to spend the next
30 years punching a clock?
Huh?
Things are out there.
Hm?
Life is out there.
One day,
you're going to say thank you.
Thank you, Dad.
Oh, it was nothing.
What's wrong?
Come on, Flynn.
Don't be so serious, huh?
What are you dolng?
What am I doing?
I'm spending the night
in a room
that you're paying for.
And then tomorrow,
I'm on the first train,
bus, or pickup truck
the hell out of here.
Yeah.
Your mother and I got married
in a HoJo's.
They wanted $800
for the banquet room.
Back then,
good for me,
I was able to swing a deaI
with the night manager.
We had a tastefuI,
low-key ceremony in the lobby
for $50.
Who knew the difference?
Who could tell
the difference?
Flynn?
I'm going to go
have a drink...
Meet some people,
have some fun.
Hi. Bill and Betty Richmond.
Hi.
Hey.
Thank you.
Sounds like a shindig.
I wouldn't know, sir.
Good blazer.
I had one
almost like it.
Different buttons.
Brooks Brothers.
Sears.
Solid store.
Good return policy.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Ah, shooting the breeze.
I must say, that's some
serious hair you got there.
When's the last time
you cut it?
Nine years.
That's really something.
Actually, another 13 inches,
and I beat the county record.
Good for you.
Of course, Dory Jensen's got
the state sewn up at 5'2".
Oh, hair is important.
I'm a fan.
I've always had good hair.
It's nice we can share that.
From back east?
Brooklyn.
Queens.
Do you mind if I go inside
and have a cocktaiI?
I'm thirsty.
Sales of teeth-bleaching kits
brighten...
Up 2.8%
in the last quarter,
while psoriasis ointment
dried up substantially...
up 5.5%.
And finally,
in our laxative department,
I'm pleased to announce that
back orders have loosened up.
Who is that?
You're kidding, right?
No.
That's the new CEO.
Wow, he's so boring.
Jesus.
I don't think
we've met.
Rick Carlson.
Sales rep of the year.
Of course.
Kudos, Rick.
You put us all to shame.
Thank you very much.
I didn't catch your name.
Richie Flynn.
What office
are you in, Flynn?
Topeka.
Oh, you work
with Tim Webber then?
T- Bird?
I like to think
he works with me.
You know, that bastard
hasn't even shown up yet.
Too cheap to buy a suit.
With the bonus
he got last year,
he got buy us all
brand-new suits
and maybe a little bit
of plastic surgery
for that wife of his.
Yeah, but she's
a nice person.
Nice ain't got
nothing to do with it.
Woof.
That's right.
This is the good stuff.
Thank the little woman for that.
She put this whole thing together.
But between you and me,
that's the only thing
she put together
in the last three weeks.
Honey?
Excuse me.
Say hello
to Rlchle Flynn.
He's in Webber's office.
My wlfe, Clalre.
WonderfuI. Thank you.
Congratulations.
Oh, yes.
Are these hybrid tea roses
in the centerpieces?
Well, yes.
Brilliant.
Thank you for noticing.
Thank you for making
a beautifuI thing tonight.
Thank you so much.
The whole thing,
it's so well done, you know?
It's my pleasure.
Do you garden?
I do.
Me too.
Oh, that's nice.
I like to grow things.
Oh, do you cook?
I do.
# Do you remember #
# the very first night
of September #
# Love was
changing the minds #
# of pretenders #
# while chasing
the clouds away #
# Our hearts are ringing #
# in the key
that our souls were singing #
# as we dance
in the night #
# Remember #
# how the stars
stole the night away #
Hey, here's Webber.
Hey.
See that jackass over there
danclng wlth my wlfe?
Yeah.
You know hlm?
Never seen him
before in my life.
Hold this.
# My thoughts
are with you #
# holding hands
with the heart #
# to see you #
Whoa, whoa,
whoa there, buddy.
Who the hell are you?
This is Tim Webber,
your "boss. "
Oh!
Whoa,
wait a minute.
Why are we fighting?
We're not fighting yet,
buddy.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
You all right?
I'm not all right, no.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Richie.
I don't know
who you are.
Webber has no idea
T- Bone,
I'm Rich-
I'm gonna
knock your teeth out, paI.
Let me.
Excuse me.
Can we step aside?
Step aside, please.
This man
is under my orders.
Nat Santos,
county health department.
Apologlze
for the tlmlng,
but we're in the midst
of an undercover investigation
of the premises,
which has severaI outstanding
health code violations.
Are you telling me
you send this guy here
to drink our booze
and make the moves on my wife?
I ought
to kick your ass.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, let's just call the cops.
Sure, call 'em.
And while you're dialing,
I'm going to go ahead
and shut this party down.
Are you in charge here?
No.
Rick, your wife did
kind of put this together, huh?
Great, why don't you
come with me.
Let's go have a look
at the kitchen.
Yeah.
Yeah, let's go.
So I'm showing
114 degrees here.
That's 10 degrees
below my standards,
20 degrees below
most restaurant standards.
That good enough
for you?
Uh.
No, it isn't.
It's not good enough
for me either.
Throw that out, please.
You ever had
a foodborne illness?
Have you ever launched
stomach contents north?
Have you had vomit
come up at high velocity?
It's a hideous situation
in the end.
Give me diarrhea
over vomit any day.
I am not
liking the look of this.
What is going on?
Why is he on the floor?
Honey, relax, okay?
Give me a minute.
Accumulation of unidentified
organic matter,
harborage,
or conditions conducive...
to vermin.
Do you know
what this is?
Is it poop?
I'm going
to go check the buffet.
Not the buffet.
These are decent people.
Give them a break.
I've seen him shut people down
over a chafing dish.
Could I talk to you
for one second?
I'll tell you, you know,
a little cash wouldn't hurt.
The entire agency is corrupt.
Everybody knows that.
No problem.
No problem, buddy.
Yeah, thanks.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
What a nice guy
he was.
Get in.
I should've left you there.
But you didn't.
I should have.
Hl, thls Is Maggle.
Please leave a message.
It's me again.
I don't know
if he's dying.
But If he Isn't,
I'm golng to klll hlm.
You know, I was a hustler,
a petty scammer.
As far back as I can remember,
that's what I dld.
That's what we dld,
and we were good at It.
Stlll are.
I'll call you back.
Put this on.
No, no.
Please.
I'm not cold.
There's something
I need to show you.
A '63 Corvair,
best car I ever drove.
First time I got nookie
was in this car.
Well, similar.
Stand by the car.
I want a picture
of the both of yous.
Why? You got nookie in that car.
That's gross.
No, for my wallet.
Let's go.
If I can't drlve one,
I can take a plcture.
Say, "Holy moly, guacamole. "
Nlce.
Looks good, huh?
Welcome to Cactus Vlllas,
a self-contalned communlty
for the sunset years.
Now, after-
Welcome.
Hi.
After my 90-mlnute
sales presentatlon,
we invite
each one of you active seniors
to spend the weekend
In one of our phase one
mountaln vlew unlts.
Nice one.
Now, If you'll look at my dlagram here,
the phase one units
are on the west side of the property.
Each unlt contalns a kltchen
and elther one or two bedrooms
decorated In Its own unlque style.
This is good.
Ooh.
I taught you that.
It was Uncle Al.
Uncle Al,
Uncle Al, blah, blah.
He hated my cat,
so I kicked him out.
Did you know
that the question mark-
What question mark?
The symboI,
the question mark,
like at the end of a sentence,
it's a question.
Like in grammar?
Yeah.
It was originally
a hieroglyphic symboI
which came from the view
of the ass of a cat
as it's walking away from you.
Explain.
Well, because when a cat
walks away from you,
you feeI insecure;
you're unsure of yourself; it's doubt.
I see.
A question mark.
You mean like the thing,
the taiI-
Yeah, you look at it,
you see the taiI.
And then the-
Pfft.
Pop.
The a-hole.
The asshole.
Well, sounds like Al.
Dubious a-hole.
What do you got
against Al?
You'll have
to ask him.
He taught you
everything else you know.
All right, left or right?
Which way, left or right?
Left.
Left or right?
Left. Left.
Here's the house.
Pull in here.
Do you know
this person?
Yes, I do.
Think back.
Dolores Jones.
She won a beauty contest.
You had the hots for her;
I sensed it.
Yeah, she was my babysitter.
Yes. She moved here.
We stayed in touch.
I thought you and I could
stop in for a visit.
You're older now.
Maybe you could,
you know-
how you say in English?
SeaI the deaI.
Why is it guys with E.D.
can't stop talking about sex?
What's wrong?
You got something
against fornication?
Hey.
Hey!
Look at you.
You're early.
I was just about
to take a dip.
There you are.
Time stands still.
Here he is.
Skinny Flynny?
Look who filled out.
He's gun shy.
Come on in.
I was just about
to make some cocktails.
Put your bags anywhere.
Not there.
Over there.
This is reaI nice.
Oh, don't be polite.
You know I never stay
in one place too long.
Isn't that right, Nat?
We got ants
in our pants.
Yes, we do.
Come on out.
Before we take off,
how about a dalqulrl?
Absolutely.
So, Flynny,
last thing I heard,
you were selllng
washers and dryers.
Oh, I know.
You're shutting down restaurants.
Yeah, didn't work out.
How about grabbing the rum
and topping off these drinks?
Sure.
And I am going to go
put some clothes on.
Oh, no argument.
Never.
Uh-oh.
Hey, sorry.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Oh, he will.
Comfortable?
That's my motto.
CooI, no?
I told you
I would set us up.
Don't hold back.
No, thou shalt not perish
by plague or by famine yet.
So shalt thou perish
by pestilence,
so why bother shaving?
You're so weird.
I'm gonna catch some rays
by the pooI.
Why don't you take her someplace
nice and buy her a cocktaiI.
Here, for later.
Oh, no.
A glow-in-the-dark condom?
They're extra large,
jumbo.
They're glow-in-the-dark,
for God's sake.
Check for pinholes.
Might be Chinese.
Ooh. Ouch.
Look at you.
Scheherazade.
She could wln
a beauty contest
as we speak.
Yeah, well, you're not so bad
yourself there, Daddy.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Okay, sugar shorts,
let's hit the road.
Let's do it.
Hold down the fort.
I'm gonna clean the kitchen.
Perfect.
So...
I take you're not
still babysitting.
Why, do you need one?
Mm, from time to time, yeah.
So what are you doing?
This and that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Got my notary's license.
Did you?
Mm-hmm.
Congratulations.
Well, it was Nat's idea.
He's so thoughtfuI.
Remember when he got me
that pink briefcase
when I graduated high schooI?
Yeah, I also remember
he didn't pay for it.
It was still nice.
All right.
You used to have
the most pitifuI crush on me.
I did not.
I was your dream girI.
Yeah, all right,
you were.
Remember when I used
to give you those bubbles baths?
Vaguely.
You still take baths?
Mm-mm.
Showers.
Uh-huh.
With other people?
Sometimes lots of people.
Of course, there was always
a guard watching.
There's no guards here, Flynny.
You never did it with Nat...
Uh-oh.
Did you?
Oh...
That was a-
that was a no, right?
Right.
Though, I can't say
I didn't think about it.
Mm.
Just never met a man who was
so in love with his wife.
I used to sit
on my front porch
and watch them dance
in the living room.
I can't say,
If thlngs weren't dlfferent,
I wouldn't have...
The man deserved
a little love and affection.
Why?
Because of the way
she treated him.
What are you talking about?
He drove her away.
He didn't drive her away.
Yes, he dld.
I don't know what he told you,
but she left him for another man.
What?
That candy-ass that she
used to work for at the car dealership.
What, Kruger?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
She did not.
I would've known.
Everybody in the town knew, Flynn.
Nearly broke that man in two.
You were just a kld.
And of course, Kruger
moved on to greener pastures.
And, you know...
She died.
Probably shouldn't have told you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Your coffee, ma'am.
Hey.
Ow!
Are you all right?
Hey, can we get
some napkins here?
Oh.
What happened?
He very nearly
burned me to death.
Please, ma'am, anything that we
can do to solve the problem,
we'll be more than happy to.
There is.
And you will be
hearing from me.
You will.
And it will not be
for a refill.
He saw it.
Did you see it?
Yes, yes.
Would you take me home?
What are you, kidding?
Get a lawyer.
I didn't-
So I got my Mercedes with a trip and a slip
at the supermarket last year.
This?
This ought to be worth 5 grand
and maybe a new wardrobe.
Well, in that case,
you don't mind if I ask
for my 20 dollars back, do you?
Nat!
What are you doing?
What are you doing, man?
Guys?
Sensory dep.
It's so soothing.
It's better
than meditating.
Hi, baby.
Wah!
Hm.
Hey.
Nighty-night, Flynny.
Comfy?
Hi.
Hey.
I got that mattress
from that sexuaI harassment thingy,
from Price Breakers
last summer.
A Sealy Posturepedic.
The good stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Nice, huh?
It's nice and springy.
Yeah, it's a wonderfuI mattress.
Mm-hmm.
He's not here, you know?
He's on the couch.
I know.
Okay.
I'm verklempt.
You are one of the most exciting women
I've ever been this close to,
and normally, I'm a guy
who does what comes next,
but in this case,
at the end of the day,
it's too late.
No, it's not.
It is.
I have an idea.
How about I give you
a supply of calling cards,
30 minutes, including
weekends and holidays?
I already have
2,000 free minutes.
Wow.
Is this because I'm dying?
This is because
you're a good man.
I used to be.
You still are.
Dolores?
Yeah, baby?
I would deny you nothing,
but this is not going to happen,
I promise you.
It's a fruitless effort.
Are you giving up that easy?
Oh.
Oh...
You think this is easy,
for me to embarrass myself
this way?
You should go.
No.
Why?
The pink briefcase.
I've never heard it spoken of
in that way before.
You gave it to me
for my high schooI graduation.
That was a souvenir
of friendship.
I...
I didn't even pay for it.
You're going
to pay for it now, buddy.
Mm.
Oh, Nat!
Dolores.
Oh, Dolores.
Whoa, golly.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Boom, boom, boom,
let's go back to my room.
I'll give you another try.
You know, don't like good-byes,
no tears, no sighs.
Thank you.
Mighty hunter drive?
What do you say to a chow-down
after a hard day's night?
Pancakes,
sausage patties,
maple syrup!
You worked up
an appetite, huh?
Mm-hmm.
How come you never
told me about Kruger?
Did I tell you
he owes me $2,000?
That's what I lent him
to open his first car lot,
$2,000.
And he stiffed me.
You know how many showrooms
Kruger has as we speak?
23.
And still, I haven't seen
dime one of my investment.
He's not an honorable man.
No, no, Kruger and Mom,
Kruger and Mom.
How could you not tell me?
Tell you what?
Oh, come on.
Make a wish?
What was yours, running naked
on the beach again?
Nah.
I already got mine.
I wish you weren't sick.
You on a diet?
It's my cake.
It's for you.
Thanks.
So how you going
to stick it to him?
What do you mean?
Well, that's what
we're here for, isn't it?
Get back at Kruger?
How'd you put that together?
I'm your son,
aren't I?
Let me in on it.
Eh.
I have to do this by myself.
I want to help.
Meet me at Dogtown, noonish.
Welcome to Kruger Motors.
Beauty, isn't she?
4.6- liter V8 engine,
320 horses.
Interested in a test drive?
No, thanks.
I have a meeting with BK.
Nat Flynn.
He's very busy today.
It could be a while.
I'm early.
Is there a place to sit,
maybe some tea?
Thanks.
Nat.
Bert.
Sit down.
Thanks.
Long time, no see.
Not long enough.
A lot of spilt milk under the bridge
for the both of us, I'm sure.
How's your family?
Children and your wife?
They're great.
Bert junior must be
in college by now.
Michigan.
Yeah, your alma mater.
Kudos.
Let's get down to it, Nat.
Sure.
Nice-looking boy.
He's all rlght.
No chick magnet, not like us.
First time they handed him
to met at the hospitaI,
I got scared.
What am I going to do
with a screaming, red-faced kid?
But three seconds later,
I was in love with him.
I wish I hadn't felt that way.
It should've been you, Bert.
Look, Nat-
I understand you've got
a beautifuI thing here,
terrific family, new career.
I'm not here to upset
any of that.
AII I care about is him.
I want him to have something,
a nest egg for when I'm gone.
I haven't been able
to do that for him, but you could.
Or we have to do this in court.
And then it's a public thing.
How do I know
that in six months,
you're not going to show up
on my front porch, Nat?
I'm not going to be here
six months from now, Bert.
Look, check with
my oncologist.
His number's on the back,
if you want.
What about the kid?
He doesn't know.
At this time of my life,
the last thing I want is
to tell him I'm not his father.
He may be a disaster,
but he's all I've got.
It pains me to say this,
but there's something
wrong with him, Bert.
I believe it.
It's my fault.
You don't look sick, Nat.
You haven't
changed at all.
Sam impeccable
sense of timing.
You know today's the day I announce
my candidacy for mayor.
Of course,
you knew that already.
Got us a suite.
You going to tell me
what happened, or what?
I've thought about this day so long,
worked it out in my head,
and it was nothing.
No big deaI.
I talked.
He listened.
He game me the money.
That's it.
Well, that's good, right?
You should be happy.
You got your $2,000 back.
My money plus 30 years
compounded interest
adjusted for inflation.
$150,000.
What is this?
You got $150,000
in a plastic-
did you steaI this?
He gave it to me,
and I promise you,
he's not coming after it.
Why would he
give you $150,000?
He thinks
he's your father.
Why does he
think he's my father?
He took a test.
I sent him
his own DNA,
said it was yours.
Well, how'd you
get his DNA?
Short, curly pubic hair.
I don't know.
Ask Dolores.
Oh, that's-
that's disgusting.
She's a friend.
Top of the menu, right?
What do you say
we throw the map away
and detour down to Vegas?
What stays there
stays there.
Yeah, all right.
What's wrong,
mopey face,
hangdog mopey face?
Why would
he just roll over?
Well, what else
was he going to do?
I had him boxed in.
He's running for mayor.
You think his wife
and spin doctors
want you
on the campaign poster?
Thanks.
No, it's just,
he was with Mom.
Is that right?
So when exactly
did that start?
I don't know.
Was it before I was born?
I try not to worry about things
I can't do anything about.
Excuse me?
The thing is,
we hit the jackpot, you and me.
You play your cards right,
you never have to punch a clock.
You can start up
something permanent with this.
It's a nest egg.
Are you shitting me?
Are you kidding?
I know how you feeI,
but these last days have been
the best time for me in a long time.
Oh. Oh, jeez.
I wanted us to get
to know each other again, and we did.
No, you're right.
You're right, you're right.
I admit it.
For some reason,
I was starting to enjoy
sitting in that stupid car
with you all day.
But that's worth nothing now,
because you're a liar.
How could you think
that it wouldn't matter to me
to know who my father is?
Hello?
Hey.
Give me a straight answer.
You're not even dying,
are you?
The X-ray is from
a friend of mine at the zoo.
It's the skull bone
of a gorilla.
All right, well,
maybe you're not my father,
but ever morning, I wake up,
I look in the mirror,
and I feeI sick to my stomach
because I thlnk I'm turnlng out
to be just llke you.
Stick a knife in my heart.
What's wrong?
Where you going
with the money?
What are you doing?
So glve me a number.
How much more
is this going to cost me?
I don't want your money.
Why have you come?
I wanted
to get a look at you.
to get a look at you too.
You're not
what I expected.
But then again, I bet Nat painted me
as the bad guy too, didn't he?
Something like that.
Look,
I already have a son.
But I might be willing to make
an arrangement with you.
Not out in the open, of course.
But I could get you a job in sales.
We're opening
a new dealership in Reno.
So you're my father.
I suppose we ought to get
a legitimate blood test.
I got to assume
Nat's hustling me.
Why'd you pay him?
Guilt.
Pity.
I wanted hlm to feel
llke he'd pulled off
something big
for once in his life.
You know,
a big score.
Look...
after the election,
you get in touch with me.
I really have
to be getting back.
Okay, can I ask you a question?
Did you love her?
You know
what women are like.
You say something
in the heat of the moment.
Do you mean it?
They think it's forever.
Honey?
You're keeping some
very important people waiting.
Can you see your way out?
Saw my way in.
Serlously, I wlll turn
the mlc over to Tom.
Tom, what do you have to say
about Bert Kruger?
He's a man of honor and Integrlty,
despite being
a used car salesman.
It would be
my honor to support him
as the next mayor
of this city,
especially if I get the discount
on that new Caddy.
You got it, Tom.
Just kidding, Bert.
Hi, everybody.
I'll be reaI quick.
I just wanted
to say a few words
about the man I've just
discovered is my father,
Mr. Kruger.
Dad...
I just wanted to say how great
it is to finally meet you
and to see what I've been
missing all this time.
I was in jaiI.
And about that $150,000
that you paid to get rid of me,
I don't want it.
I hate bribes.
Hold it!
Mr. Kruger, slr,
you've just been accused
of paying hush money
to an ex-con
who claims to be your son.
Do you have any comments, sir?
Yes, this is dirty tricks
by Terrance Bissen, my opponent.
Is that a deniaI, sir?
It's a categoricaI deniaI.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Did you give him the money?
How could you do that?
What have you done?
You gave back $150,000.
Am I rlght?
Did you give him the money?
Yes or no?
Come on.
You ralsed me
better than that.
Vegas,
here we come.
Hey, Nat?
How about we head down
to L.A. after?
I want you
to meet Maggie.
Nat?
Hi.
I'm in a hospitaI
in Albuquerque.
It's Nat.
And it turns out,
this is the first time in his life
he's telling the truth.
And...
he's dying.
He really is dying.
So...
That's...
what I wanted to tell you.
Bye.
Hello?
Hi.
Could I get another tapioca, please?
You've got a sweet tooth.
I do.
Closer.
Let me feeI your face.
I'm sorry.
We did good, though.
We got copasetic.
We're not done yet.
Come here.
Get me out of here.
Hi.
Thanks for coming.
Well, nobody ever
flew me first class before.
I do what I can.
Your mustache.
You want me
to grow it back or what?
I won this place in a card game
a long time ago.
I figured,
one day, you'd come here
and bring the girI of your dreams,
like I did.
Oh,
somebody's been here.
I don't remember the place
being such a dump.
We were a family once.
You wanted a boat?
Thank you.
Just so you know,
if I could do it again,
I'd have been more like a dad,
tossed a ball, pitched a tent,
taught you to drive.
You did teach me to drive.
Come on.
Uncle Al-
No, you did. You did.
In the parking lot behind
St. PauI's Church when I was 11.
You're right.
How could I do
a thing like that?
Come on.
There's something
we got to do.
Well, I spent my whole life
wanting a different kind of a father,
one who would look after me
instead of me looking after him.
And instead,
I got this infantile,
irresponsible,
uncivilized, cheap,
jive-talking bullshit artist.
And now that
I'm rid of you,
here...
Here I am
wanting you back.
It's typicaI.
Oh, and you'd be
happy to know that urn was free
with $5 of gas.
I'm gonna miss you, Dad.
We're sinking.
Oh, come on.
What do we do?
Hey, grab that metaI cup
right there.
It's coming in fast.
BaiI, baiI,
baiI, baiI!
Why don't you row?
BaiI!
You got to be shitting me, Nat!
Row!
Oh, what did I do?
Oh, my God.
Help!
It's not funny.
Ah!
# And if I had the time to solve
the mystery of your crime, #
# you know I would #
# If I had to shape the form
of your mechanicaI design, #
# you know I could #
# But I've been up and down
the lanes to lose #
# the memory of your name,
the sword #
# taken from this stone #
# Put it in the lake #
# But I mended up
my heart #
# and I have nothing more
than bones to break #
# But I said #
# I do believe #
# on the endless roads
you weave #
# You may climb #
# You may fall #
# You could spend your lifetime
on the wall #
# I don't mind #
# If I had the hand to take
the blood out of the sand #
# or make it dry #
# And if I knew about
all the secrets of the earth #
# I won't ask why #
# Well, I've been
in and out of windows #
# just trying
to find a doorway #
# I've broken off the marble #
# that has
weighed upon my shoes #
# But I mended up my heart #
# and I've nothing
more than time to lose #
# But I said #
# I do believe #
# on the endless roads
you weave #
# You may climb #
# You may fall #
# You could spend your lifetime
on the wall #
# I don't mind #
# If I could look within #
# the endless tales
upon your skin #
# would I go blind? #
# If I could carve your face
upon an unfamiliar place #
# would I be kind? #
# But I've seen visions
of a ghost #
# that stand upon
the record sleeve #
# of all my faded dreams #
# that I've broken
at the seams #
# But I mended up
my heart #
# and I've nothing more
than sorrow on the brain #
# But said #
# that I do believe #
# on the endless roads
you weave #
# You may climb #
# You may fall #
# Spend your lifetime
on the wall #
# But I don't mind #
# I don't mind #
# Don't mind #