(Engine hums)
(Brakes squeak)
Hey. You.
Come on, l seen
that sleeping act before.
You know your ticket
ran out the last stop.
How much to San Francisco?
2.25.
(Bell tinkles)
Yes, three days.
So it's three days she's gone.
Where do you get off keeping it
from the police 72 hours?
l didn't want it to get around,
Mr Johnson, that's all.
People talk.
Stella's a good girl, really she is.
- l don't want them to talk.
- Well, we'll find what took her.
Why not give it till morning,
Johnson?
Stella'll show up.
OK. Till morning.
You oughta know, Mr Judd. Cood night.
- Cood night, Johnson.
- Cood night.
Way down this week, Pop.
Nobody plays it
when Stella not around.
Yeah, l guess not.
You don't think she might have
done something to herself?
Not Stella.
Back in New York, l handled
31 suicide cases, personally.
Everything from poison to jumping
in front of the Flatbush subway.
Stella's not the type.
- Here's your receipt.
- Thanks, Atkins.
l'll be seein' ya.
Cup of coffee, please.
lt's after ten, we're closed up.
And a hamburger: well done,
with onions, mustard, relish...
What else you want on that,
the whole state of California?
- What's the population?
- l'll fix you something.
(Sighs)
- Cigarette?
- No, thanks.
Never touch them.
(Bell tinkles)
l knew you'd be back.
OK.
- l'm back.
- Well, here y'are, young man.
Stella!
You...
You're OK.
l'm hungry.
Right away, Stella, right away.
You don't know what it's been like
since you went.
You won't go away, Stella,
will you, again?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Room's waiting for you.
l paid him not to touch a thing.
You wanted it like that, didn't you?
- (Bell tinkles)
- And you'll come back to your job,
everything just like it was,
'cept you'd never been away.
That's just how it'll be.
After a long rest.
You sure look run out.
So what?
One look at him
and l knew he wasn't any good.
- l knew...
- You make me sick.
He's finished his coffee. Co on.
That was the best hamburger
l never ate.
Sorry, come back later...
l mean tomorrow.
- l'm closing up.
- How much?
- lt's OK.
- lt's not OK.
He got his coffee,
let him pay for it.
Five cents.
(Cash register dings)
(Coins scrape)
(Cash register slams shut)
(Cash register dings)
(Chirruping)
- Cood evening.
- Uh-huh?
- Professor Madley, please.
- Professor Madley?
He won't be here till tomorrow.
- Oh.
- Maybe Mr Ellis could help you.
- Ellis?
- The Professor's assistant.
He registered this morning.
Oh, Ellis! Oh, yes.
What's his room number?
216, but he's not in just now.
Of course, he's getting tuned.
- Tuned?
- To the other world.
He always does that
before the Professor comes in.
- ls that so?
- Oh, sure.
l'll wait for Ellis in his room.
- That's against the rules.
- Don't worry, it's all right.
(Clock chimes)
(Door creaks)
(Croans)
- Mr Ellis, l presume.
- Yes.
My name is Stanton.
- Eric Stanton.
- Never heard of you.
Professor Madley's an old friend.
- When was that?
- The good old days.
How old?
Old enough to be good.
Oh. Drink?
My favourite brand.
Oughta be, l got it
out of your bureau drawer.
(Laughs) Help yourself to everything
as long as you're a friend
of the Professor's.
- From my cradle days.
- Then do the Professor a favour.
Lend-lease him thirty dollars.
- Thirty dollars?
- Do him half a favour. Fifteen.
(Chuckles)
What's so funny?
Tell me, l'd like to laugh too.
l came up to put the bite on you.
Now let's hear how you laugh.
- You can't sleep here.
- Wait a minute.
Consult the spirit of my friend
the Professor. What's he say?
l know what the manager says:
one more guest, one more dollar.
l haven't got enough for my own bill.
- Then the extra dollar won't matter.
- Don't take your shoes off.
l've enough to aggravate me.
Don't worry.
- l'll get you out of it.
- What with? You're broke.
l gotta have fifteen dollars
by noon tomorrow,
or lose the hall downstairs
and my deposit,
besides being kicked out of here.
What about the Professor's spooks?
Don't they come through
with an advance sale?
Sure, if there's nobody to stop them,
but a certain woman in this town
don't believe in spooks,
and what she says goes
for the rest of the women.
She's not only the daughter
of the former mayor,
who donated a new organ
to the church,
but the President
of the Ladies' Auxiliary.
Against such a combination,
not even l could sell one ticket.
Co charm her.
Miss Mills will have no truck
with me, not even on the phone.
- Well, let's sleep on it.
- l said no.
We're in this thing together.
Naturally, l'll sleep here.
- Stands to reason.
- What stands to reason?
You are in trouble, man.
l've got to pull you out of it.
- Have you got any toothpaste?
- ln the bathroom.
Hope you like my brand!
(Birdsong)
Cood morning.
- Your mistress, please.
- Who?
Miss Clara Mills.
l'm Clara Mills, and we're not
buying anything, either.
l am here to speak
on the behalf of the dead.
Walton's respected deceased
are having a rendezvous tonight
at the Walton Hotel.
There's nothing to discuss,
l told you that on the phone.
- Now don't call again, Mr Ellis.
- Oh, l'm not Mr Ellis.
l'm not a part of the spook act
down at the hotel. l'm Eric Stanton.
Would you listen to me for a minute?
- Out with it, l'm busy.
- So is Professor Madley.
Appointments with the dead
from coast to coast.
Yet this soul of generosity
finds time to drop in on Walton
to deliver a message of hope.
For money. He's a charlatan.
A fraud.
Not the Professor Madley.
Pretending to commune with the dead.
Now, look... He and Ellis are just
a couple of struggling artists
like fortune-tellers,
or a vaudeville team.
l won't let the poor, gullible people
of Walton be fooled.
lf my father were alive, these fakers
would never have gotten a licence.
- Your father?
- Abraham Mills was a real mayor.
He wouldn't have let frauds
take advantage of honest people.
What if Mayor Mills would like
to make another speech,
or tell you something?
Suppose he's...
Suppose you leave right now!
Suppose l do.
But don't forget, the curtain goes up
tonight at eight o'clock.
Birds of a feather. Well,
they won't hatch anything here.
Trading on people's sacred feelings.
Everything that's dear held up
to ridicule by frauds in a trance,
rapping on a table.
We won't have any of the cheap,
vulgar tricks of spiritualism here.
You think l'm wrong?
l think he's right.
But how can he be?
June, don't be taken in
by his glib manner.
He meant it: just two people
trying to make a living.
Why can't they make an honest living?
(Chuckles) Are we to judge?
Well, it's too late now, there's
nothing we can do about it.
- Yes, there is.
- What?
We can buy two tickets.
lf we go, everybody else will.
Shall l call the hotel?
l'll think about it.
We thank thee, O Lord, for our daily
bread and our many blessings. Amen.
- Doughnut?
- (Cash register dings)
No, thanks.
- Like to make a few extra dollars?
- How?
Push these tickets to your customers.
- l'll give you twenty per cent.
- Sure. What are they for?
A spook meeting tonight, featuring
the one and only Professor Madley.
- No.
- Why not?
lf the Ladies' Auxiliary
don't want 'em, l don't want 'em.
Don't worry about the women. They
wouldn't miss hearing Abraham Mills.
- Mills?
- The Professor's bringing him back.
- With a message.
- l don't believe in it.
What's the difference?
You can still make some money.
No, l don't wanna get mixed up
in anything.
- (Cash register dings)
- Pop?
- Coffee, please.
- Right away.
(Bell tinkles)
Here he is, Professor,
your old friend, Eric Stanton.
Old friend? l don't recall.
- Buffaloes. Connectity.
- Sorry, l still can't remember.
- Let me see.
- Relax, Professor. We've never met.
Last night in my room, you said...
- And you never met him?
- Clad to meet you now, Professor.
Delighted, Mr Stanton.
All the signs point to a prosperous
association. Dollar signs.
l've sold a batch of tickets already.
- Couple of beers, please.
- OK, comin' up.
l heard from my assistant here
that you really work wonders.
- Congratulations on your success.
- We'll have sell-out after sell-out.
Well, OK.
l never believed you could talk
Miss Mills into buying tickets.
l just had a call from her sister
to reserve a couple.
They're coming over to get a message
from their old man. Right, Professor?
Ah, yes, l had a visitation from him
on US Route 101 .
He definitely arrives tonight.
What do you say, Pop?
Now do you believe it?
He definitely arrives tonight, sir.
He better arrive tonight,
he's your main attraction.
Er, dig up the vital facts, Ellis.
Who is Mills,
and why does he want to come back?
- OK, see you later.
- Wait, leave me one of these.
Pop, let me hang this up in here
and l'll give you a couple of tickets
to the best show in town.
All right, go ahead.
- There you are.
- Eric, you've got a great calling:
spook promotion.
- Like to back that up with a fin?
- Oh, gladly.
l hope to see you in my room later.
l have a fine collection of friendly
spirits there, Scotch ancestry.
(Bell tinkles)
(Cash register dings)
There you are, Stella.
- (Cash register dings)
- Thank you.
Have you any idea what the deceased
Mr Mills is going to say tonight?
Why?
They thought a great deal of him
around here.
You wanna be careful.
Thanks.
(? Kay Kyser and his Orchestra:
Slowly)
? Slowly
? l opened my eyes
- ? Hazy with mist
- (Cash register dings)
? Slowly
? My lips realised
? They had just been kissed
? Slowly
- Beer, please.
- ? You stirred in my arms
? Thrilling me so
That the only record in that box?
- l like it.
- He knows what you like.
That's for his wife to worry about.
- What does he do?
- He's from New York.
New York.
He came out here to stay,
to get his health back.
How'd he lose it?
Workin' too hard, l guess.
He used to be a big man back there,
on the police force.
Would you like to come to the show?
You askin' me?
? The moon came in through... ?
Here.
Never mind.
- What's the matter?
- l don't go places alone.
OK.
- Here.
- Was that four beers?
Three beers and a cup of coffee.
(Cash register dings)
(Bell tinkles on door)
You have just heard
the spirits of citizens of Walton
who have gone on before us,
who've returned tonight through me.
Returned to tell you how happy
they are in their eternal reward.
But now, my good friends of Walton,
we come to our last experiment,
for which l must have your undivided
attention and sincere concentration.
l feel a strange vibration
coming over me.
The vibration of a spirit
who has remained troubled,
who has found no peace or contentment
since he departed.
Abraham Mills.
l can feel his troubled spirit
trying to get through from beyond.
Yes, Abraham Mills,...
- l can hear you.
- Would you mind moving over?
Yes, Abraham Mills.
- Like it?
- Oh, yes, very much.
You're troubled
because your daughter Clara
has lost practically
everything you left her.
The bonds, orange groves.
You can't understand how she could
have trusted that man...
that man...
(Whispers) John Martin! John Martin!
John Martin,
who came here after you passed on and
talked her into selling everything.
Why didn't she ask
the police for help
- when he ran away with the money?
- Come, Clara.
You'll find peace only when you know
that Clara will guard
the last of the inheritance
for herself and her younger sister.
$25,000 in stocks.
l'm sorry,
l shouldn't have made you come.
(Applause rings out in other room)
Cee, that was awful mysterious.
How he knew everything.
- Say, can l ask you a favour?
- Sure. What?
- You know the Professor, don't you?
- Sure l do.
l'd love to have my fortune told.
D'you think he'd do it if you asked?
- l can tell it better myself.
- Where're we going?
Your horoscope's up there.
l'd like a drink.
OK, you're on. Where do we go?
l know the place.
(? Dance-hall music)
(Chattering)
l like the way you talk.
l like the way you dance.
(Applause)
Here, sir, two bourbon.
- Who ordered them?
- Do you want them?
OK.
Thanks.
- You said you'd tell my fortune.
- Well,...
Er, you don't belong
in a one-armed joint.
- No?
- Not a girl like you.
You've got style. Beautiful style.
You inherited that.
Your father was a leading citizen.
Rich.
(Sniggers)
- He trusted people too much.
- And?
Your mother...
Well, her line seems to run out.
Don't scare me! She runs
a boarding house in San Diego,
and my old man came
from a long line of drunks.
(Chuckles)
Anyway, there's a man in your life.
You just met him.
Tomorrow, he goes to San Francisco,
and you're gonna lie awake at night,
unable to forget.
And what can l do about it?
(? Band strikes up)
(Waves crash)
Listen to that.
The sound of far-off places.
(Waves crash)
Do you like the sound of the ocean?
l like the way you talk.
No.
That's OK for kids, but not for me.
Not any more.
Where are you from?
What has that got to do with it?
OK, don't tell me.
l'm from New York.
- Now you know.
- Er...
What do you do
when you don't tell fortunes?
l help make 'em for others.
l passed actresses,
directors, producers,
through a publicity mill l ran:
they came out famous.
Their names in all the papers.
- You know people like that?
- l know all people in all places.
Like 21 , the Stork Club: that's where
you belong, smothered in mink.
l can see you there.
Do you see me with a ring on my
finger? Somebody to give me a home?
Sure. Sure.
Now, look...
last night, l made up my mind.
That's the way l want it.
He didn't see it that way,
so l walked home.
At night. Miles before l got a ride.
Was plenty tired when l got in, too.
You saw me.
- But when l make up my mind...
- Forget about last night.
You talk different, sure,
but you drive just like the rest.
Well, you got the wrong girl.
Yeah?
(Struggles)
No!
Tomorrow, you're going.
- Where does that leave me?
- You'll go with me.
What on? You got into town with one
dollar in your pocket. You're a fake!
Why, you little gyp!
Dealing a buck out
of the cash register, and calling...
Co on. Co on back
to your one-armed joint
and wait for somebody
to come and marry you.
(Church bells)
(Window squeaks)
Coming, Eric?
Yeah, l'm coming.
Professor's waiting. lt never
felt so good getting out of town.
Even with the bills all paid.
Don't smile,
your face looks better without it.
- See ya downstairs.
- OK.
Top of the mornin', my boy. Hop in.
- Cood morning.
- Cet in.
- l'm not going.
- Not going? What's wrong?
Nothing. You go ahead, l'll meet you.
We need you for advance publicity.
San Francisco's tough on spooks.
- Hit 'em like the earthquake.
- When l feel like it.
l made it clear when l took this job,
you can't tie me down.
lt cramps my style.
l work best when a certain feeling
comes and right now, l don't have it.
- Cenius.
- Eric, my boy, you're an artist.
- Have a bus ticket on the firm.
- Never mind that.
Well, you'll always find your
favourite brand in my bureau drawer.
(Footsteps)
- lt's about time you showed up.
- (Bell tinkles)
(Bell tinkles)
My bus leaves in fifteen minutes.
You got a nickel?
l... l just came back
to say l'm sorry about last night.
- (? Kay Kyser and his Orchestra)
- Save it.
- Nothing else you want to say?
- No.
- Don't give me that act.
- What act?
- You know what l mean.
- (Bell tinkles)
Hello.
So long... for good!
(Bell tinkles)
What bit him?
Just trying to make his bus, l guess.
? Slowly
? You stirred in my arms
? Thrilling me so... ?
- Well, in or out?
- Skip it.
(Engine hums)
This finishes it.
You'll never see me again.
Coodbye.
Coodbye!
Oh!
Always leave 'em laughing.
You again.
- Whaddya want?
- l wanna talk to you.
OK, talk.
Don't give me that smile.
OK, l don't smile.
l thought you had something to say!
- Doesn't that say it?
- l heard that kinda talk before.
Cood night.
l never said it before. To anybody.
Ever.
l'll marry you, Stella,
if that's what you want.
You? You don't kid me.
l'm not kidding.
- Last night, you...
- Last night, l didn't know you.
What made you tick.
l know you now. l know why l couldn't
pull out of here this morning,
or get on that bus.
l can't get away without you,
and l'm not going without you.
- What's in it for me?
- You said you wanted that:
a ring on your finger.
That isn't enough. What goes with it?
l want a home.
l'll get it for you.
What with, one dollar in your pocket?
Twelve and a half thousand dollars.
Where would you get
twelve and a half thousand dollars?
What's the difference,
as long as l get it?
How? You gonna murder somebody?
- Talk sense.
- Steal it?
- Listen.
- Well, l don't know you!
You know one thing.
We're gonna get married.
Once l get the cash.
Maybe you'll get me in trouble.
l don't wanna get in trouble.
You won't, not the way l'll get it.
l'm not even telling you how.
You just sit tight and wait for me.
That's the deal.
You'll keep it.
Maybe l will.
(Strains of church organ from within)
(Church organ grows louder)
A very good performance, Miss Mills.
Please, go on.
Beethoven never sounded so good.
- l wasn't playing Beethoven.
- No?
Why, sure, it was Brahms. The old
boys do sound alike, don't they?
l mean, in spots.
- What spots?
- The way they begin and end,
sometimes in the middle,
like the piece you were playing.
lt wasn't anything,
l was just improvising.
lf Brahms didn't write that,
you wrote him one better.
That was beautiful.
lt was classical, it was inspiring.
You know,
you belong in Carnegie Hall.
Now, look, you can't stay angry
at me forever, not two full days.
Wait a minute. What about
living up to the place we're in?
And the music you play here?
So when a guy says he's sorry,
the least you can do is forgive him.
All right, l forgive you.
- Friends?
- l hardly know you.
(Chuckles) Don't worry about that,
we'll fix it right away.
lt's a good thing word didn't come
through from New York this morning.
l get the chance to stay another day,
square things
with you and your sister.
Tell me, what is there to do in this
town to make time pass till tomorrow?
- That's up to you, isn't it?
- What do you do?
Oh, there's plenty
to occupy your time here.
The movies, dancing,
the beach isn't far.
They'll tell you at the hotel.
You still think l tried to hurt your
sister. l didn't mean to, really.
l only meant to help the Professor.
That's happened before. l try to help
somebody, somebody else gets hurt.
That's the way it's been all my life.
Of course. You live by impulse.
You never bother to think if you're
following the right or wrong impulse.
l see you don't stop at music,
you read too.
Don't you?
l haven't opened a book
since l left school. They're phoney.
- So are some people.
- At least they're alive.
- So are books.
- You come to a part you don't like,
you can turn the page,
but try it on people.
Try it on life.
l'll tell you something about
yourself. You're scared to live.
That's why you bury yourself
in books and music.
l think you ought to respect my ways
as l respect yours.
Only l live and you don't.
All the things you look down on
are the things that make up life.
What things?
Little things. A game of bowling,
or a swim at night...
(Bell)
Or a dance.
A kiss. Stuff with bubbles.
l bet you never had a drink.
- That doesn't mean anything.
- Not by itself, it doesn't.
But you add up all the little things,
that's what makes up life.
Maybe you're the one
that's scared, not l.
How come?
You don't know what you want,
that's why you're scared.
That's why you keep running
after every little thing.
That's quite a mind you have there,
Miss Mills.
You mean for a girl in a small town?
Must be the books, huh?
Must be.
lf you didn't know me so well,
l might ask you something.
- You'd probably say no, though.
- Probably.
So there's really no use in asking.
Well, why don't you ask me anyway?
Will you have dinner with me tonight?
Well, l, l don't think l can.
You see?
You're afraid to step out
of your tower.
No, no, no, that isn't it.
Your sister?
- Of course not.
- Then what are you afraid of?
l'm not afraid. Why should l be?
Yeah, why should you be?
l'll pick you up at seven.
At seven.
Two, please.
Don't you ever see anything through?
When it's worth it.
We've had a dinner you didn't like
and saw a movie you didn't like.
- What's next?
- Dancing?
All right. Let's not miss any of the
things that make up your happy life.
(Chattering, music)
Well, here's to your first Scotch.
(Clinking)
How do you like it?
lt tastes like soap.
lf this is what all
your little things add up to, l...
l don't think it's very much.
Did you learn to play Beethoven
in one night? No.
Then don't expect
to learn this in one night.
l don't think you enjoy it either.
- Because you don't.
- But l want to, that's why l came.
Frankly, why did you ask me?
No special reason.
You happen to interest me.
ln what way?
l can't define it.
Maybe it's your charm.
Maybe it's your talent.
Ever think of a career?
- Maybe?
- And?
No. No, l know my limitations.
One shouldn't set a limit
on what one can do.
Mr Stanton, that sounds
as if it came out of a book.
And not a very good one!
There goes that mind again.
Shall we turn the page and dance?
Oh, it's been an awfully long time.
l'll lead you.
(? Dance-hall music)
You're doing fine.
Thank you.
(Music stops, applause)
(Whispers) Hey, ditch him
and l'll meet you afterward.
(Whispers) l don't cheat on a date.
(Music starts up again)
(Chirruping)
There's still one more little thing.
Don't worry, l'm not going
to kiss you goodnight
and make you unhappy.
Unhappy?
Don't you take too much for granted?
No. One kiss
goes a long way with you.
You need a guy who will take it
the same way,
who will give you a marriage with
all the trimmings, home and kids.
Who'll walk to church with you
every Sunday and listen to you play.
Save all your ''Cood nights'' for him.
What makes you think
l wanted you to kiss me?
Didn't you?
(Door slams)
(Bell tinkles)
(Cash register dings)
- Short of help this morning, huh?
- Kinda.
- She always come in this late?
- Sometimes.
Why d'you want to know?
Just thought maybe
she'd skipped out on you again.
No, she won't do it.
She promised me she won't.
- (Bell tinkles)
- Stella!
Mornin', Stella.
(Sighs) Cood mornin'.
Whew! Sure could use some coffee.
l got something special for you.
l waited for you last night.
Until after three.
That's nice.
Where were you?
Around.
- With that guy?
- Oh, leave me alone, it's too early.
Here y'are.
- Mm, thanks.
- Where d'you get the watch?
You like it?
Cet me some hash. Cood and brown.
l said some hash.
You get this last night?
Wait till we're married, then ask me.
Till then,
l don't have to tell you a thing.
We're as good as married.
(Chuckles)
You're dropping out of circulation.
From now on, when you go out,
it'll only be with me.
You've got a steady date,
with Miss Mills.
l'm only doing that for you.
- Lot of good l'm getting out of it.
- You will in a couple of days.
OK, couple of days,
but that don't mean forever.
(Bell tinkles)
Morning, Mr Judd.
Cood morning, Stella.
(Bell tinkles)
Hello.
With my compliments.
- Thank you.
l'm leaving tomorrow
and l wanted to say goodbye.
Coodbye, Mr Stanton.
We're going to pick up a few things.
Can we take you anywhere?
Anywhere you say.
- Can three of us get in there?
- l think so. You go ahead.
Thank you.
(Engine starts, revving)
Nice town. Hate to leave it.
- Expect to go far?
- Maybe.
Maybe l'll be back.
And maybe l won't.
lt depends.
On what?
On what there is to come back to.
l... l'll be just a minute.
What would you come back for?
June.
l gathered as much.
Let's be frank, shall we?
My cards are on the table,
Miss Mills.
l want you to leave June alone.
We don't know who you are
or where you come from.
- What do you do?
- Nothing.
That's frank, at least.
l'm sure you'll be interested to know
l have no bank account, either.
l thought so.
Your hand is showing, Miss Mills.
You've got a trump card: money.
- And because l haven't any, you...
- lt has nothing to do with money.
June has quite enough,
even without my share.
Your share?
Yes, she'll get that too. l want her
to be happy, that's all l care about.
lt's all hers, whatever l have.
ln San Francisco, Mr Stanton,
where no-one can touch it.
Not until she meets the right man.
Well, maybe l'm not
the right man after all.
And you won't see her again?
Suppose we leave that up
to the one concerned.
(Engine starts)
- There you are.
- Thank you.
Wonderful. Just wonderful.
lf l've accomplished nothing else,
at least l've made you like
one of the little things l like.
l have my little secrets, too.
Bet you think all l do is read
big, heavy books, don't you?
But l don't.
For years, l've been saving
ads out of magazines.
Sometimes, l...
l feel like l'm the girl in the ads,
softly alluring, full of grace,
gowned by Schiaparelli.
lf l had money,
l'd dress you like the ads.
Take you to New York,
at least to San Francisco.
You'd have that Schiaparelli gown.
lt isn't that important.
lt would be when l took you
to the nightclubs, the theatre.
The concerts. D'you ever hear
the San Francisco Symphony Orchestra?
Mm-hm. On the radio.
Whaddya hear on the radio?
A lot of noise.
But when you see 'em up on the stage,
all dressed up with their fiddles
and their horns,
ten thousand people waiting for
the music to begin. That's a concert.
Particularly when Toscanini conducts,
as he is tomorrow afternoon.
Toscanini?
Yeah.
And you know what? After the concert,
l'll get him to listen to you play,
see who's right about your talent,
you or me.
- You know Arturo Toscanini?
- l'll make it my business to.
We can leave for San Francisco in the
morning, make it in plenty of time.
No.
Your sister?
Yes.
You gotta do everything she says?
No, but l...
Well, l guess after tonight,
it's goodbye.
l guess it is.
Anyway, there are a few things
to remember.
lt could've been wonderful.
(Softly) Mm-hm.
lf l were another guy, the right guy,
it could've gone on like this,
night after night.
Just the two of us.
A fire, hot dogs, wine.
Martinis.
Wonderful martinis.
Coulda been a dream.
- A beautiful dream.
- You and l together.
New York and San Francisco.
Mm-hm.
Cetting you all those things
in the ads.
Coing everywhere together,
to the concerts,
to hear the famous people play.
Becoming famous yourself.
Creat career.
''Miss June Mills,
the finest talent of them all.''
''Woman Of The Year.''
(Chirruping)
(Knocking)
(Knocks louder)
- (Stella) Who is it?
- Eric. l have to see you right away.
(Stella) lt can wait till tomorrow.
lt's important.
(Stella) OK, l'm listening.
l can't talk to you like this.
(Stella) l can hear you.
Open up, what are you afraid of?
- Oh, pipe down, will ya?!
- (Window slides shut)
You wanna wake everybody up?
Whaddya want?
l came to tell you l can't
go through with it like l planned.
lt'll take too long.
l knew it. You didn't stand a chance.
That isn't it.
Look, you know how l feel about you.
You've gotta believe in me,
have confidence in me.
l want you. l'm nuts about you.
That wasn't the deal.
Well, what of it? l'll get you that
home and everything you wanted.
l can do it. l've got ideas
that work and pay off big.
Come on,
let's get out of here, tonight.
l'm taking no chances.
- Now listen to me, Stella...
- l stick to a deal.
Satisfied there's nobody here?
Now beat it.
(Ringing)
- Yeah?
- 'Eric?'
Yeah.
'l'm so glad. l was afraid
you might have already left.'
- Who is this?
- June.
Eric, l'm going with you.
To San Francisco?
To the concert, on the nine o'clock
train. We'll pick you up.
We?
Yes, Clara's going along too.
She had to go to San Francisco anyway
to take care of some business,
and thought she might as well
do it a week early.
'Clad to have her along.'
Thank you, Eric. We'll be right over.
(Traffic roars)
- Wanna wait here?
- No, l'll go in with you.
- Do you mind?
- Not at all.
Mills, number seventeen.
Yes, Miss Mills. Clara and June
Mills. Joint ownership.
Either one of you sign here.
What's the rent on a box?
Four dollars a month,
but there's none available now.
We might have some vacancies
next month.
- l need one now.
- Put whatever you want in our box.
l might need it when you're home.
Come on, June.
Have you a telephone directory?
Yes, right around the corner.
- This way?
- Yes.
Thanks.
(Dialling)
- The gentleman went to the phone.
- Thank you.
- Creat luck, l found him in.
- Who?
Somebody very important. Might have
a great effect on your career.
- Who is he?
- Wait till you meet him.
l told him we'd be over right away.
Co ahead.
l want to make a call from here.
- l'll meet you after the concert.
- We wouldn't think of it.
- Eric asked you to go with us.
- Sure, you're going.
Meet us at two-thirty sharp
in front of the auditorium.
Two-thirty.
- Cood luck.
- Thanks, we'll need it.
(Traffic)
(Car horns)
There is no concert.
l suppose you know that.
- He knew it all along.
- Cetting us up here, pretending...
- He had to.
- Why?
Any better way of getting June
out of Walton?
- There, we didn't have a chance.
- What chance?
- To get married.
- Married?
Sure. Here's the evidence.
''Certificate Of Marriage.''
June...
you don't know what you've done!
l do.
l'll have the whole thing annulled.
No, you won't, Clara.
l know what l want.
This isn't as sudden as you think.
Well, what's the verdict?
l hope you'll be very happy.
Thank you.
l suppose the next thing to say
is ''Shall we be friends?''
We could be, if you make June happy.
Sure l will. Right from the start.
What are your plans?
Well, l'd like to go home first
and get a few things together.
Then we'll go some place
for a little while, right, Eric?
OK, back to Walton.
First, l'd like to try another bank.
l wanna put this
in a safe deposit box.
Don't wanna take any chances carrying
it around. l've a few valuables too.
- Why don't you put it in our box?
- lt's in your name.
l'll put it away for you.
l always thought of it that way,
didn't l, June?
Yes, dear.
l said to myself ''When June gets
married, this will be her home.''
''l'll give it to her and her husband
to do with as they please.''
lf l am to stay on,
it'll be as a guest.
A guest in June's home.
Assuming, of course, that l'm wanted.
- Of course we want you with us.
- Absolutely. Here, have some more.
No.
lt's time for a guest
to say good night.
Cood night.
Cood night, Clara.
l'll be up in a minute.
- (? Kay Kyser and his Orchestra)
- ? ls that the smile?
(Car revs)
? Slowly
Won't you even have a drink with me?
l got a date.
- ? Smiling above
- Can l walk you home?
l said l got a date.
- ? That's when
- Cood night, Stella.
Don't forget to lock the door.
- (Bell tinkles)
- ? l was in love ?
- Stella?
- Yeah?
You're going to San Francisco
tomorrow.
Am l?
Tomorrow, l'll have that money.
All of it.
- Meet me up there and then...
- How do l know you'll have it?
l'm going to San Francisco
with her to get it.
Well, l won't. And she won't either.
Oh, yes, she will.
lt's her honeymoon.
- Her what?
- Yeah.
l married her... this afternoon.
lt was the only way.
Congratulations(!)
Now, listen,
we're really not married.
- (Music stops)
- We'll be divorced in no time.
l haven't even kissed her.
ln fact, l can have it annulled.
- (Sighs) Cood night!
- (Bell tinkles)
Now wait a minute!
What do you want?
She's your wife, not me.
l don't run around with married men.
l did it for you,
to get you what you wanted.
Now keep your part of the deal.
Oh, sure, but she's got
the ring on her finger.
She's not so dumb.
- Well, l'm not a dope, either!
- (Engine starts)
Sugar? Cream?
No.
Co ahead, say it.
l have nothing to say, Eric.
l'm waiting for you.
Well, l'm sorry.
Maybe l shouldn't
have stayed out that late.
All of sudden, there l was,
a married man.
l had to go out for a drink.
By the time l got back in,
you were asleep.
Why did you go to that girl
in the diner?
- What girl?
- Clara saw you.
- You mean she went out after me?
- Yes, she told me this morning.
Well, that's fine. Clara told you.
What's she gonna do? Follow me around
everywhere l go? Check up on me?
She's been running your life up to
now, and she better stay out of mine.
l was angry with her too, at first,
but she means well.
Yeah? Then why did she tell you?
So you could have a good time
worrying?
l didn't worry.
Until that...
that man came to see you.
What man?
He's with the police.
Wants to ask you something.
Ask me what?
About that girl.
She was found murdered.
Stella?
Yes. Yes, that was her name.
Eric...
what did she mean to you?
Does Mr Judd know?
Judd?
He's downstairs waiting.
- Mr Judd.
- Congratulations, Mr Stanton.
l just heard you were married.
- My best wishes to you, Mrs Stanton.
- Thank you.
Well, our church organist
certainly surprised us all.
Married in San Francisco
and not in the church.
lt certainly saves time, doesn't it?
Cives one the chance to get back the
same night for a nice family dinner.
- And after that, where d'you go?
- We retired.
Everybody?
l locked the door myself.
Mm-hm.
Well, l'll check up on a few things.
- Ah, mind if l go with you?
- Not a bit.
Thank you.
How did it happen? Who did it?
l don't know yet.
The Chief of Police called me this
morning and asked me to help.
He appointed me Special lnvestigator.
- You know, it's strange.
- What is?
That a man doesn't spend
his wedding night at home.
- Did Clara tell you?
- No, she didn't say anything.
l saw you around myself.
(Engine starts)
Out the way, folks. One side, please.
Hi, Mr Judd.
One side, please, one side.
Outta the way.
- Hello, Mr Judd.
- Johnson.
Hello, Pop.
You can sit down now.
- Thanks for coming, Mr Judd.
- Chief.
Coroner was here. He'll send in
his report as soon as possible.
ln the meantime, however,...
here's what he said.
''She was killed by a blow
on the left temple.''
''Weapon undetermined.''
''Probably a lead pipe.''
''Time of death
between three and four a.m.''
- Find the weapon?
- lt's not in here.
Who's she?
She lives downstairs, Mr Judd.
Says someone ran out of here
late last night.
She found the girl's watch
under the step this morning.
Cuess he must've dropped it.
What did he look like?
Oh, l don't know, mister.
lt was so dark, l couldn't see him.
Just as l went to close the window,
l saw him running down the street.
How d'you know it was a man you saw?
- l didn't say it was.
- Then it was a woman?
- No!
- Then it had to be a man.
l guess it was.
A man always took her home.
- Who?
- l don't know.
l saw him come up.
And once, l saw him.
Which one did you see last night?
Oh, l can't say
if it was them, honest!
Can l go now, mister?
l should be down in the store.
Please?!
l don't like to stay in here.
You can go.
So can you, Pop.
l don't need you right now.
Let me stay, Mr Judd.
- lt's her room.
- lt was her room, Pop.
She was a good girl, wasn't she,
Mr Judd? She never meant bad.
Everybody liked her.
Yes. Everybody.
- Your name?
- Atkins.
l gave my statement to the Chief.
- What do you do?
- You know me, l operate jukeboxes...
- And slot machines.
- Only in Nevada, where it's legal.
Now, look, l already said
what l had to to the Chief.
l'm not answering any more questions.
What makes you think
l'm gonna question you?
l know how cops work.
How do they work, Mr Atkins?
Well, you're supposed to show me.
Perhaps we'd better go in there.
- lf you don't mind.
- No, l don't mind.
Here's his statement, Mr Judd.
Check his alibi.
- There's a phone in the store below.
- Right away.
Sit down.
Now,...
let's get down to facts, Mr Atkins.
You've got my alibi right there.
Don't believe me? Why don't you
wait till the Chief gets back?
l'm not interested in your alibi.
l'd like to know
when you gave her this watch.
When?
Why don't you ask if l gave it her?
- l know you did.
- You don't.
l told you l know how cops work.
l don't believe you know how l work,
Mr Atkins.
- Those kid gloves?
- Certainly.
l don't like to mess up
any case l'm on.
You gave her the watch, didn't you?
- No.
- You did.
- You gave her the watch.
- (Judd) You gave her the watch.
- (Atkins) No.
- You did. You gave her the watch.
- (Smacking)
- (Atkins) No.
(Smacking, Atkins groans)
- You gave her the watch.
- (Atkins groans)
All right, let's pick it up.
What about you and Stella?
Well, l've known her for a long time.
l used to board at her mother's home
down San Diego.
l... didn't have any money then,
so l couldn't marry her.
Skip the romance.
Last night, you picked her up
at 10.1 5.
You were with her until two.
What happened in between?
(Atkins) We had dinner...
We drove down to the beach.
(Judd) You got there, didn't you?
(Atkins) Yeah, yeah.
She said she'd marry me.
(Judd) Then you brought her home,
came up to kiss the bride.
No, l didn't. l left right away.
(Atkins) You see,
when Stella was murdered,
l was in a motor court just outside
of Clenolden. That's 100 miles away.
How do you know what time
Stella was murdered?
The coroner's report.
lt says around four.
Oh, you know
l couldn't have murdered her.
Sit down.
- You gave her the watch, didn't you?
- No.
Time l went home.
(Judd) Just for the record,
so we can clear that up.
Doesn't make you any more guilty
if you did give it to her.
You quarrelled, you took it back,
then you lost it on the way down.
No, l never gave her any jewellery.
- Come on, Mr Atkins, admit it.
- No.
- Admit you were generous, just once.
- No!
- Admit it.
(Smacking, Atkins groans)
(Shuffle, thud)
- Mr Stanton.
- Look, you don't try that on me.
l wouldn't think of it.
l just happen not to like his face.
Mr Judd, his alibi's OK.
The Liddell Motor Court in Clenolden
said he checked in at 2.30.
All right, Mr Atkins, you may go now.
l knew his alibi'd hold up.
You got the watch?
l didn't say you could go,
Mr Stanton.
- Sit down.
- You can't ask me anything
or hold me without charges.
You seem to be an expert
on loopholes.
Perhaps you could tell us
who might've murdered the girl.
Could've been anybody. Atkins, maybe.
- lt isn't Atkins.
- Pop? He was stuck on her.
Perhaps.
- Or was it a woman? Clara Mills?
- Or the woman downstairs.
- Or you, Mr Stanton?
- Or you, Mr Judd?
A splendid deduction.
The possibilities are many, and all
quite interesting, don't you think?
ln a cold-blooded sort of way, sure.
- You still aren't helping us.
- lt's your case.
But you're involved in it,
more than you realise.
- Now, look...
- l'm looking.
The facts, they're all against you.
You came into town
for no obvious reasons.
Of course, you weren't
going elsewhere.
Meet a young lady,
spend some time with her,
then you come up here.
The woman downstairs saw you.
Then you meet another young lady
and marry her.
On your wedding night, you walk the
streets looking for lady number one.
How do we know you didn't wait
for her until...
l didn't.
You're an expert, Mr Stanton.
You know the exact value
of a man's word against facts.
- Are you accusing me?
- Not yet.
Perhaps after we find the weapon.
However, l wouldn't plan on any
out-of-town honeymoon just yet.
We might need you any moment.
Cood day.
What are you packing for?
- You're not going away now, are you?
- Yes, l am.
June, l won't let you go with him,
not after that girl was murdered.
- l'm going, Clara.
- How can you?
Why throw yourself away on someone
who's not worth it?
He isn't worth it.
lt's no use, there's no happiness
in it. l've been through this.
lt's not the same thing, Clara,
please try to understand.
l do understand.
Once l believed in someone, too.
No matter what people said,
l believed in him.
You don't know what he meant to me.
What all of his lies and broken
promises and dishonesty did to me.
l can't let you ruin your life too.
June, he went out after another woman
the night of your marriage!
Maybe you're right,
but l can't let it end now.
l must give us every chance.
l hardly know him yet.
We've said so little,
we're practically strangers.
- Together, maybe he'll change.
- He won't change.
Maybe not,
but at least l'll have tried,
done everything l could.
(Door opens outside)
Coodbye, Clara.
- There's a train in a half-hour...
- Forget about the honeymoon.
l'm beating it alone.
l'll make better time.
You're running away?
What do you want me to do?
Stick around here? Cet framed?
And my face punched in.
You bet l'm running away.
Won't it look bad if they want you?
That's for Mr Judd to figure out.
lf he wants to pin it on me,
he'll have to find me first.
Where will you go?
What do you want to know for?
Cos l wanna go with you.
You'll need me to get the money
in San Francisco.
Who asked you for money?
You'll need it.
You mean you're giving me the money?
No. No, l'm not giving it to you,
it belongs to both of us.
All right, but when this thing
blows over, l'll pay it back to you.
- Very well. l'll get the car.
- No. And we can't take the train.
Or the bus, either.
Judd'll have them all watched.
We've gotta get on the highway
without being seen.
We'll hitchhike to San Francisco.
And no luggage.
lt's gotta look as if we were
just out taking a walk. Come on.
(Train)
Cood evening.
- ln and out, out and in.
- l'm sorry.
One room right after the other. Can't
even wait till the room's ready.
l never saw such a rush.
Everybody getting married.
What a dump!
lt isn't so bad.
Tired?
Maybe l am.
Waiting for something to happen.
Nothing's going to happen.
(Tap screeches)
Shut it off, will you?
l thought you might like a drink.
l sure would... but not that.
There's a bar downstairs
and we have a little money left.
Whaddya want me to do,
walk right into his arms?
- He probably isn't after you at all.
- Not much!
He must've sent a description of me
to all the papers.
Maybe we missed an edition.
Couldn't be in the papers, it's too
early. There's no need to be afraid.
Sure! Murder rap's nothing(!)
Let's just go home,
so he can pin it on me.
- l didn't say we oughta go home.
- You didn't, but you meant it.
The room's not good enough!
Why don't you go and tell me,
you're sorry you ever came?
But l'm not sorry, l wanted to.
Why? So you could drive me nuts
with that quiet way of yours?
- Eric...
- Why'd l bring you anyway?
l don't need your dough.
Wouldn't have to hang around
this dump.
lf l'd been alone,
l could've kept on going.
Maybe l will.
(Faint dance-hall music)
(Music grows louder)
Double Scotch, thanks.
Better make it a single.
- l'll settle for a beer.
- Better make up your mind, mister.
lt is made up. A beer.
(Cash register dings)
(Running water)
(Key turns in lock)
Eric?
- Yes.
- (Water stops)
Could you give me a towel, please?
They're on the bed.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Eric, would you get me my coat?
lt's in the closet.
Here.
l, er, thought l'd bring you
one of these.
Thank you.
And this.
Help you pass the time.
That's very sweet of you.
Ah, l thought it would say it better
than l could that...
(Sighs) l'm sorry.
Just nerves, l guess.
l understand.
All l mean is there's nothing in it
for you. You oughta go home.
- No.
- Why do you waste your money on me?
l'm not wasting my money.
lt's yours, as well. l don't care
what you do with it.
Burn it, tear it up,
do anything you want.
You take it easy.
l only meant it for your sake.
lf you had any consideration at all,
you wouldn't even mention money!
OK. But anytime you want to,
you can always pull out.
They'll fix you up with a divorce,
just for the asking.
Tell them how l lied to you,
married you for your money.
- l'm wanted for murder...
- You didn't murder that girl!
- Maybe l did. You didn't ask me.
- l knew you didn't.
- What do you know about me?
- All l know is that l love you!
l love you, Eric, l love you!
(Sobs)
l could talk for the rest of the
night about my batting average.
How many times l've struck out.
Even when l hit a home run,
it isn't any different.
Like the time in New York,
just before l came west.
l'd started a publicity office.
Like always,
it was great at the beginning.
A guy comes along,
wants to buy the business.
Offered me eight thousand bucks.
l took it.
We had a big celebration that night.
ln a couple of hours,
l'd lost half of it back.
To him and his friends.
l knew the dice were loaded,
but l couldn't prove it.
Anyway, l came west.
Chicago for a while.
Then Omaha.
Las Vegas. That's where l dropped
the other half of the dough.
When l was kicked off of that bus
at Walton,
l only had one dollar left.
And then...
Ah, but why go on?
l want to know everything about you.
lt all adds up to only one thing.
A washout.
That's what you're looking at.
A complete washout at 30.
Yeah, l'm finished OK.
- You're not finished, Eric.
- Sure l am.
l'm tired.
Like l was a million years old.
With a million jobs behind me.
And girls.
Chances l never followed up.
Eric...
did you care very much for... Stella?
l don't know.
l guess l did.
l even promised her l'd marry her.
l can't figure it out now.
Woulda lasted a couple of weeks.
Maybe less.
Anyway, that's all gone.
Just as if it died with her.
Yeah, that's over, too.
Up in smoke,
like everything in my life.
My school, the publicity game.
Easy come, easy go.
l got everything by talking fast
in a world that goes for talk.
And l end up with exactly nothing.
Perhaps we can find what you want
when this has all cleared up.
lf it's cleared up.
Eric...
wouldn't it look better not to run
away, to go back to Walton?
Sure, and go back to the chair.
Or is it the gas chamber
in California?
lf you're innocent,
there's nothing to worry about.
Maybe that's the way it works
in your books,
but even as a kid, l always got
beaten up for something l didn't do.
That's when l learned to run away
before it was too late.
You're tired.
Come, lie down.
(Sighs)
Tomorrow, we'll go
wherever you want to go.
June,...
why don't you just go on home?
We're married. Remember?
Besides, l... l wanna be with you.
Why?
l need you, Eric.
You need me?
Yes. You're my husband.
And l'm your wife.
(Whispers) Right out of a book.
Again.
Yes.
Out of a book.
''We were born to tread the earth
as angels,
to seek out heaven
this side of the sky,
but they who race alone
shall stumble in the dark,
and fall from grace.''
Co on. Sounds good.
''Then love alone
can make the fallen angel rise.''
''For only two together
can enter paradise.''
Four-and-a-half-minute eggs.
l certainly married a man
with a peculiar taste.
You can still get out of it.
Promise you'll never say that again.
OK, l promise.
lt's ten o'clock.
- The bank just opened.
- Let's go.
(Man shouts outside)
(Man) Cet your morning papers here!
Cet your papers!
Early edition papers!
Papers! This morning's papers!
Paper, sir?
You wait here, l'll be right back.
Shine, sir?
- Papers here! This morning's papers!
- All right.
Papers! Early edition papers!
Morning papers here!
Papers!
- Mrs Stanton?
- Yes?
Could you come with us, please?
(Car horns, engine revs)
(Brakes squeak)
(Car horn)
(Siren)
Here.
But l ain't finished yet!
Now let's be sensible.
We've been here for hours.
(Clanging)
Tell us where he is.
We're bound to find him soon.
(Clanging)
Mrs Stanton,
you're not helping him or yourself.
Cetting mixed up in this murder
as an accessory after the fact.
lf he doesn't wanna come back,
he must have a reason.
What reason
could an innocent man have?
- Assuming he's innocent.
- He is. He could never have done it.
How can you say that?
You know very little about him.
He came into town a total stranger
and within a week, he married you.
All to his credit, of course.
But why this trust in him?
A man who went out to see another
woman the night of your marriage.
That's between the two of us.
Ask Miss Clara Mills to come in.
Miss Mills, please.
June.
Sit down, Miss Mills.
ln your sworn statement,
you identified this envelope,
found in your safe deposit box,
as the one Mr Stanton gave you.
Would you please repeat that
for your sister?
Yes.
This is the envelope he gave me
after they were married.
Why did he want you to put it away?
He said it contained
something valuable.
Mm-hm.
Would you care to see your husband's
valuable property?
A blank piece of paper.
Why would a man want to put a blank
piece of paper in your deposit box?
l'll tell you.
lt gives him the excuse to open
the box, to steal your money.
No, he wouldn't. Whatever he did,
he did because he was confused.
He knew what he was doing.
He wanted that money so he could
run away with that girl.
- But he didn't.
- No.
He made the mistake
of coming back a married man.
She didn't want
anything to do with married men.
They argued and he killed her.
You're only assuming that.
You have no proof.
All right. But why shield
a man who lied to you
and wanted to steal from you,
when you have positive proof
that he married you for your money?
He didn't lie to me. And he isn't
guilty, l know he isn't.
He only ran away because he had to.
He's always had to run away,
all his life,
even as a child, when he was beaten
for things he didn't do.
He won't come back because of you.
You won't give him a chance,
you only think the worst of him!
Trying to make him guilty of murder
when he didn't do it!
l tell you he didn't do it!
He didn't do it! (Sobs)
Take her home now.
(Bawls)
You're responsible
she doesn't leave the house.
(Continues to cry)
lt's not the same, Mr Judd.
l think l'll sell the place.
(Bell tinkles)
Hello, Pop.
Some coffee, please.
l knew you'd be back.
Yeah.
Well, drink your coffee and we'll
go down to the Chief of Police.
Thanks.
Enjoy San Francisco?
Sure.
- How come you didn't go after me?
- l didn't have to.
And how come there wasn't a word
about Stella's murder in the papers?
- Why are you holding it back?
- Professional reasons.
And was it for professional reasons
you beat up Atkins?
When all the time
you knew he was innocent?
You don't seem to appreciate
my methods, Mr Stanton.
Frankly, no.
That's what brought me back.
You know, l got worrying about you
in San Francisco.
About me?
Yes, Mr Judd.
You know, you oughta stay home nights
with your bad health.
Not walk the streets.
Like the night you said you saw me
looking for Stella.
More coffee, Pop.
You weren't strong enough to keep
on working on the New York force.
Why are you working so hard
on this case?
- Maybe you better slow down.
- Don't you worry about me.
l'm OK.
l said l wanted more coffee, Pop.
Cet it.
l don't worry about you, Mr Judd.
Not anymore.
Not since l called a friend of mine
in the DA's office in New York.
He assured me you were in
perfect health when you left there.
They retired you from the force after
you ruined another man's health.
Almost killed him,
in a routine investigation.
They would've sent you up,
if you hadn't had such a good record.
That was before you started
to enjoy your work too much.
Wearing gloves, you know.
And l checked up on...
That's enough.
Save it for the Chief.
There y'are, Pop.
Oh, you remember that watch?
The one with the three diamonds
that belonged to Stella?
- Find out who bought it for her?
- Perhaps.
You made your fatal mistake, Judd,
when you had June arrested.
Oh, you scared me at first,
all right,
but then l stopped,
and l began to think.
And l kept right on thinking
about that watch,
and l started a little
routine investigation of my own.
The result is the Walton police
will get a wire from San Francisco.
They'll know who bought it
tomorrow morning,
unless you admit it tonight.
Shall we go?
Oh, l came in a police car,
they're outside.
l thought it'd be more convenient.
Sit down.
You don't mind if l finish my coffee?
You're insane.
The police are right outside.
Perhaps l am insane.
Perhaps this might've been
the perfect crime
if l hadn't dropped the watch.
But l doubt it.
- There's always some slip.
- Yeah, there always is.
You understand.
You know what she was like.
You couldn't get away
from her either.
Two years l came in here
and drank coffee.
Just to get a look at her.
Day after day for two years.
lnsane, perhaps.
Those evenings when she went out
with other men,
while l was waiting for her
in the shadow of the porch...
Remember three nights ago,
when you brought her home,
and kissed her?
l was standing there.
lnsane, perhaps.
Night before last,
when she was out with Atkins,
after he left, l went up.
When she told me she wouldn't wait
any longer for my wife to divorce me,
that she was going to marry that
slot-machine operator the next day,
l hit her.
Unfortunately,
l didn't remember my ring.
Cet out of the way, Mr Stanton!
l'm gonna kill him!
He murdered Stella!
(Bell tinkles)
Let's go.
(Clicking)
(? Kay Kyser
and his Orchestra: Slowly)
(Sobs)
You gotta forget it, Pop.
No, l'll never forget Stella.
You will.
l felt the same way myself, until...
Well, you'll find yourself, Pop.
? They had just been kissed
Eric?
? The moon came in through
? My room above
- Where to?
- Home.
? l suddenly knew
? That l was
? ln love ?