Previously on Fallen...
When God created Man, a jealous Lucifer
mounted a great rebellion|in Heaven.
His army of angels was defeated,
and forever banished from Paradise.
These angels, the Fallen,
abandoned Lucifer,
choosing to live on Earth
among the pleasures of humans.
They took mortal wives,
and fathered abominations...
children called Nephilim.
They have the powers|of angels,
but the souls of men.
Angry, the Creator flooded the Earth,
killing the Nephilim and
driving the Fallen into hiding.
He sent the Powers, fierce warrior angels,
to hunt those that survived the Flood.
But there was hope
for the Fallen in a prophecy:
A Nephilim would be born,
who would redeem them
So the fallen watched...
and waited.
I'm not afraid
of the Powers.You?
of anything.
I'm going to put
an end to this.
I'm not running
from them anymore.
Nephilim...
you face warriors of Heaven.
We fought in the greatest war
in the history of creation...
and won.
Do you really think
you stand a chance against us?
Hello, Mazarin.
So, who wants
to die first?
This can't be.
That's exactly what Nathaniel said, moments
before I was dusting him off my boots.
Your, uh, scar's healing up.
Looks good... ish.
It is our mission to cleanse
the Earth of your kind,
and those that spawned you.
We will not abandon it.
We don't have to fight.
Just turn around and leave.
- If you do that, no one has to die.
- Oh, come on. Someone always has to die.
That's part of the fun.
Kill him.
Kill him!
I yield.
Duly noted.
What the hell
did you just do?
- He yielded.
- And?
There's a line that
I'm not going to cross.
And as long as you're with me,
you're not going to cross it either.
I'm not with you.
You're with me.
Listen to me. This Light Bringer,
he better be everything that you promised,
because I am running out of reasons
to hang around you.
Let go of me.
Come on.
The Light Bringer knows
everything about you, Aaron.
Who you are, where you came from.
You can learn it all.
We just have to get to him first
and I'm just trying to do
everything I can
to make sure you do.
You're free now.
Hurry, someone's coming.
Still out, Camael?
How did I make fire come
out of me like that?
- It just happened. I wasn't even trying.
- You don't need to, sweet cheeks.
It's instinct.
You don't have to be taught
how to use your powers.
The angel side of you already knows.
But your feeble, little human mind
gets in the way.
You just got to let go, let
the angel side take over.
You can't just let it take over.
That's like freeing a wild animal
that has no sense of..
good or evil, right or wrong.
You are so dramatic.
Well what about you, huh?
You just do whatever you feel like?
You don't care about
what you say who you hurt?
It's just how the good Lord made me.
I'm being true to my nature.
You should try it sometime.
What is that noise?
Is something wrong?
I think the car is about done.
What'd you do to it?
Human-made
piece of crap!
Well, never mind, we're going
to have to foot now, anyway.
Where are we going?
Yeah, see those mountains over there?
That is where we're going
to find the Light Bringer.
This is turning out
to be a really bad day.
Leave me.
I need to speak to the Creator.
Nothing in the year since I've taken over
the Powers is what I've accomplished.
Under my command,
we've remained faithful.
We've continued and will continue
to pursue the abominations,
until they stain your planet no longer.
Is that what you perceive
your mission to be, Mazarin?
Michael.
Camael?
Oh, God. What have they done to you?
- Hold still, Camael.
- No.
Yes, you have to take
the healing, you have to.
- What?
- Aaron...
We must find Aaron.
What?
It would be a whole lot easier
if we could just fly there.
But I don't have any wings, genius.
I don't know how to fly.
Hey, guys, can I help you with anything?
You bet you can.
We wanted to see if we
could get some camping gear.
You headed up to the mountains?
You seem like an outdoorsy kind of a gal.
Do you ever play
any... indoor sports?
Sorry, he doesn't
get out much.
You might need something
warmer than that. Come on.
Listen, I don't how we're going to pay
for this stuff. I'm running out of cash.
- Where did you get that?
- Remember that waitress from the diner?
Yeah.
Remember that line
you told me not to cross?
- Yeah.
- I crossed it.
But, in my defense, it was
before you told me not to.
Is that your boyfriend? Not the guy with
the French fries, the other one.
Why?
No reason. He's cute.
Yeah. I know.
So, is he your boyfriend or not?
I'm not sure.
Lesbian.
Had to be.
Will you get over it?
Everybody gets rejected sometimes.
Not me. Nobody rejects me, ever.
Well, I know you think you're
God's gift to women, but,
I just don't see it. Sorry.
Oh, you don't, do you?
If I turned it on, sweetheart, you
wouldn't know what to do with yourself.
The only reason I haven't is because
the Redeemer's sweet on you.
- Ignore him.
- You can't ignore me. It's impossible.
They lose a little something when
they get cold, don't they?
Hey guys, come on, let's go.
How much further?
We won't get there
till tomorrow morning.
Ariel...
I'm dying.
- Don't say that. I can...
- You can give me
a little more time.
More strength.
That is all.
Perhaps this is what I deserve.
I clipped many an angel's wings
when I led the Powers.
I clipped yours.
At least you didn't use angelfire.
Not on you, Ariel.
Sorry, I haven't seen her.
Are you sure?
Take another look, she's probably
traveling with a boy around her age.
Are you sure you haven't seen her?
Look, if she was in here,
I don't remember her, all right?
Sorry I couldn't have been more help.
Hey, Scott, it's Deborah. Would you mind
coming by the store for a little while?
There's this guy...
This is the last time
I'm going to ask you nicely.
When was the girl here
and where did she go?
Lord Michael,
mightiest of angels,
he who cast the rebels from Heaven.
That'll be enough of that, Mazarin.
On your feet. Let's speak as equals.
The Powers need guidance, Michael.
Aren't you meant to guide them?
Isn't that your charge?
I'm not sure I'm worthy.
The Powers were instrumental
in squashing Lucifer's rebellion.
You and your clan killed more rebels
than the rest of the clans combined.
That was not a compliment.
The rebellion tested us all.
For the first time,
we were given free will,
the ability to chose not only who
we fought for, but how we fought.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I'm trying to tell you that the Powers
earned an exile as well.
Not so different from the Fallen.
Exile?
But...
But we remained faithful.
Which is why you were
given a noble mission...
to protect Earth against
threats to the Divine Plan.
And are we wrong?
Are we not meant
to destroy the Nephilim?
Is this boy really
who Camael says he is?
That's for you to decide.
There's at least one threat to the
planet of which you are certain.
Azazel.
To defeat him...
you may very well need the help of the
boy you've been trying so hard to kill.
You know, Azazel,
you're not doing that right.
Yes, I know I'm not
doing it right, Gabe.
You sure that doesn't go over there?
Gabe, I've just realized what
I'm supposed to do with this,
and you're not going
to like it.
Can't we just play
with these sticks instead?
Why am I doing this?
I don't even sleep.
You're no fun.
Try it.
- I don't know how.
- You did it earlier.
Look, the angel inside of you
already knows how to do it.
The trick is to tap into that
knowledge without letting it take over.
- Go on, give it a shot.
- No.
Come on, just try it.
Picture it in your mind, okay?
- I can't.
- Yes, you can. Hey...
Focus.
Okay.
Okay, great. Now just picture the flame
jumping from your hand into the fire.
All it takes is just a little nudge.
- I did it.
- Told you.
So you really don't
want to be redeemed?
Ever?
Heaven's just not for me. That's all.
It's not all sitting around on clouds,
playing harps and all that crap, you know?
So how much further to this Day Lighter,
or whatever you call him?
Light Bringer.
I don't know how much
further, sweetheart.
I didn't get the most
precise directions.
- So you don't even know where we're going.
- We're in the right general area.
And from what I understand, it's damn
near impossible to miss the place.
Why were you imprisoned?
None of the other Fallen
were, right? Just you.
I'm not just any other
Fallen, sweetheart.
- I used to lead them.
- You led them?
Almost straight to Hell. It was my idea
to come to Earth, you know?
We made a decent team,
Lucifer and me, but it was a
temporary alliance from the start.
I never wanted to take over
Heaven like he did.
I was fighting for the right to leave it.
- Where are you going?
- To take a leak.
To take a leak?
- I thought angels didn't take leaks.
- I'll figure something out.
Aaron, are you sure we can trust him?
Azazel? Yeah.
- I mean, he saved our lives twice.
- Yeah, but...
Yeah.
But it doesn't seem like
he's fighting to protect us,
as much as he just likes to fight.
Well, at least
he's on our side.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
I just hope you're not looking for answers
so hard, you can't see anything else.
waffles, whipped cream, syrup.
- He's dreaming.
- Yeah, I know.
Sounds like his dreams
are a lot better than mine.
What are they like,
your dreams?
It's the same one...
over and over again.
I'm fighting some kind of war,
except I don't even know...
whose side I'm on.
I'm just kind
of walking around,
and cutting down everyone
in front of me.
It's like I'm some kind
of monster or something.
You're not a monster.
- It's just a dream.
- What if it's not a dream?
What if that's the real me?
That's all of this,
that's the dream.
Funny, I've been afraid that
I'm the one who's dreaming.
Like, I'm going to wake up any minute
and find myself back in Lukas' attic.
You know,
I thought about you all the time.
I still can't even
believe that you're here
Right next to me.
I'm sorry.
No, you're beautiful.
Vanity is a sin,
Azazel.
If the Creator hadn't wanted
me to admire myself,
he wouldn't have made me so pretty.
- How are we  progressing?
- You'll have him tomorrow.
Good. I knew if anyone could
come through for me, it would be you.
I'm the only one who would
and the only one who could.
Which brings us to your
part of the bargain.
When this is over, I want my freedom.
- I'm never going back  to that pit again.
- I see.
You're concerned that I'm going to
renege on my agreement
and imprison you again.
You should learn to be
more trusting, Azazel.
- It's good for the soul.
- Too bad I don't have one.
Azazel, is that you?
Gabe, come on, wake up, boy.
- Oh, thank God I found you.
- Found me?
I'm lost, I walked off the trail two
days ago. I have no idea where I am.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I am now.
Hey, look, I haven't eaten in a
long time, you got any extra food?
Yeah, we have plenty of food.
Thanks. I can't tell you how
much I appreciate this.
Nephilim may have the powers of angels,
but your biology is mostly human,
unfortunately for you.
Ariel, this is the site
of Anane's redemption.
- I was wondering when you'd show up.
- Azazel is free.
And he's with your Nephilim.
You're not taking me back there.
Grasic's dead. It's the Redeemer I want.
Naughty.
You're okay.
- Who is that guy?
- That's the man who kidnapped me.
Look at all this stuff.
These are pretty cool.
You know, if I hadn't have come galloping
to your rescue, both your heads
would be mounted on a
wall somewhere by now.
No.
He said he wanted Aaron alive.
He knows that you're the Redeemer.
Wake up.
Who are you?
You with the Order, huh?
Answer me!
Aaron, stop it!
What do you people want from me?
What do you think we want?
We want redemption.
Did you really think your powers
can only be used on the Fallen?
His power wasn't meant for you.
It was meant for us.
That's not true. You can send
anyone you want to Heaven,
whether they deserve it or not.
Yeah.
Yeah, whether they worship
graven images or not,
whether they covet their neighbor's
wife, if they repent or not.
I would never use my powers like that.
The stench of death
is all over you, my friend.
You don't have
long left, do you?
I have a brain tumor,
that's why I need you.
I've done a lot of bad things in my life,
things that can never be forgiven,
but you can pardon me,
you can keep me from going to Hell.
You can wash me clean of my sins.
Please, please.
Sorry.
- I can't do that.
- No.
No. You're going to have
to pay for what you've done.
You just killed him.
- Why would you do that?
- He was dying anyway.
He kidnapped your girlfriend, sold her,
he was trying to use you to get a
bunch of sinners into Heaven.
Leave him.
He's nothing to us.
Aaron...
- this is wrong.
- I know.
I don't know why Azazel is free,
or what he's doing
with the Redeemer.
I served under Azazel.
Locking him up was the only
good thing you Powers ever did.
Mazarin, take to the sky. Scout ahead.
Look for any traces of angel activity.
Sachael, come with us.
We don't take orders
from you anymore, Camael.
You will. That is the only way
we're going to do this.
Is it always going to be like this?
I don't know if I can do this, Aaron,
all this running
and fighting and killing.
I don't like it either.
Part of you must.
I've seen it... when you fight.
Sometimes it looks
like you're enjoying it.
Just like Azazel.
I'm nothing like Azazel.
Why are we doing this anyway? What is it
you want to learn from this Light Bringer?
Maybe he can tell me
more about where I come from.
Why I have all these visions and
all these dreams, and why I have all
this anger inside of me,
and just what it means to be the Redeemer.
Maybe he can tell me who I am.
Aaron, no one can
tell you that.
You need to decide
for yourself who you are.
Then you should try to ve up to that.
- There it is.
- This is it?
Yeah, that's where |you're going.
- You sure this is the place?
- Have I ever lied to you?
- This isn't for you.
- Why can't you come?
This isn't about us, Aaron.
Aaron, this doesn't feel right.
Don't go in there.
I have to.
Hello?
Anybody here?
You'll have to forgive me.
I wasn't expecting
you so soon.
I've waited a long
time to meet you.
- Are you the Light Bringer?
- I am.
- And you're Aaron Corbett, the Redeemer.
- How do you know|my name?
This meeting, like your birth,
was foretold to me long ago.
So it is true.
You did write
the prophecy about me.
Yes.
You've come here
looking for answers,
to learn where you come from, so that you
can better understand where you're going.
I have so much
to tell you, Aaron.
I can help you learn the truth,
if you're strong enough to face it.
Are you?
Yes...
I am.
How are you doing
back there?
I would not have had
your wings removed, Camael.
That was Mazarin's
doing, not mine.
I remember, Sachael.
He's a good soldier,
you know that,
but your desertion broke his heart.
Might want to get comfortable, love.
This might take a while.
What is this place?
It's a monastery,
or rather, it was.
It hasn't been
used in decades.
In fact, you're the first living soul
I've seen here in years.
People don't often
find their way here.
Not unless they're
seeking me out.
Now you must be very tired.
Maybe you'd like to sit down?
So do you really
know everything about me?
Hardly.
But I am very curious to hear
what you know about yourself,
or what you believe you know.
Well, I know that
my father is an angel.
And my mother is dead.
Does that disturb you, knowing that
your father allowed your mother to die?
He didn't allow|her to die.
He killed her.
Is that how you view your conception?
As murder?
Isn't that what it is?
The Fallen know that a human
can't survive a Nephilim's birth.
Our mothers die
the second we're born,
and we're left alone, to spend the rest
of our lives running from the Powers.
It's selfish
and it's cruel,
and the truth is,
I don't know if any of the Fallen
are truly worthy of redemption.
We should have
left him behind.
He's a liability.
The Nephilim won't trust us without
Ariel and Camael. We need them.
I don't blame you for being angry,
but the way you look
at your mother's death,
it does her a great disservice.
What do you mean?
You paint her as a... a victim instead
of the martyr she truly was.
I loved her very much.
You... You loved her?
Yes, Aaron.
I'm your father.
I know how
you must be feeling.
There were times when
I really need a father.
Where were you?
I was here,
waiting for you.
I couldn't have
raised you, Aaron.
For your own protection you need to
remain hidden until you came of age.
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you.
You have no idea how sorry.
I just hope that you can
find it in your heart to forgive me.
To forgive you?
I can feel it when a Fallen
wants redemption,
and I have never
felt it as strongly
as I do right now.
Is that what you want?
From me to send you
back to Heaven?
You are the Redeemer.
And when the time is right,
when you
are absolutely certain that I have
atoned for my sins,
yes, perhaps you will
return me to Paradise.
And that is when you will have
fulfilled your destiny.
So that's what
all of this is about?
That's why I have
all this power?
Just so I can redeem you?
All the Fallen must return
to Heaven, Aaron.
That's the prophecy.
But if I don't return
to Heaven myself, then...
then it was... all for nothing.
From the moment I took up arms
against the Creator
to the day that I had my vision that
foretold your coming...
Oh, I denied it at first,
but after I thought about it,
it made perfect sense...
that this Redeemer
would come from a Fallen
that needed forgiveness most.
The one who started it all.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am nothing but what you see
before you, Aaron.
A fallen angel,
the Bringer of Light...
Your father.
I want to know your name.
I have so many names.
More than I can even
remember myself.
But the one
the Creator gave me...
is Lucifer.
No.
Yes, Aaron.
I am Lucifer Morningstar, first of
the Fallen, and you are my son.
I don't believe you.
Yes, you do.
You know it's true.
You can feel it.
- My blood has been crying out to you.
- Get away from me!
Stay away!
Aaron.
Don't come any closer.
I am not the son
of the Devil.
And I am not what
you believe me to be.
Please, let me
make you understand.
I do understand.
I finally understand what all of these
dreams have been trying to tell me.
Dreams?
I see myself as evil.
I see myself as a monster,
like you.
Whatever you think I am,
please give me the chance
to convince you otherwise.
Or strike me down now.
I shall make no move
to stop you.
My fate is entirely
in your hands.
I knew you would make
the right decision.
You always do.
Ariel.
Azazel did this.
I can smell him.
Azazel is a force
of nature.
He will never change.
But realigning with Lucifer?
After all it's cost us?
Lucifer?
Lucifer is involved
in this?
He wants the Redeemer.
He used Azazel to get him.
Can Lucifer use this boy
to return to Heaven?
Why do you think I've been trying
so very hard to protect him?
I've been trying to prevent
this very thing from happening.
Azazel got to Aaron
because of you.
He's in Lucifer's hands now
The world as we know it
may be about to end...
because of you.
Do you know why
I rebelled, Aaron?
It's because you wanted
to take over Heaven,
steal it from the Creator.
As they say, history is written
by the winners.
You know, the truth is...
I only wanted the freedom
to choose my own destiny.
But it is not better to reign in Hell
than it is to serve in Heaven.
I didn't construct Hell
to be a haven
for the Creator's rejects.
But when more of them started to come
to me instead of Heaven...
You assumed the Creator gave up on them.
Yes.
Humans love to disobey.
None of it's true, then?
All of the horrible things you're
supposed to be responsible for?
They're all lies?
No.
No, I'm not saying
I'm perfect.
But your arrival tells me
that I have atoned.
More than that,
I know it in my heart.
When all the angels
have reunited in Heaven,
then we can restore the Earth to the
reflection of Paradise it was meant to be.
You could bring us all
back together.
And what if I don't?
Well, you've seen the signs...
war, famine, pestilence, death.
It's all around us.
These are the End Times, Aaron.
The Day of Judgment is coming.
And only you can stop it.
How long is he going
to be in there for?
As long as it takes.
As long as what takes?
For him to accept the truth.
What truth?
Is he going to be all right?
The truth hurts.
Sometimes it hurts more than others.
I'm going in there.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you, sweetheart.
No, of course you wouldn't.
You wouldn't do anything
unless there's something in it for you.
Is this Light Bringer
the one who freed you?
Is this why you brought
Aaron over here?
You've got me all figured out,
don't you, sweetcheeks?
Yeah, I made a deal with him.
And deals with him don't come cheap.
What are you talking about?
You can speak every
conceivable language.
You don't even understand what you know.
What is "Light Bringer" in Latin?
Lucifer.
Right.
Aaron put his faith in you.
He's a fool.
I'm coming, too.
I can smell him, Vilma.
Hello?
Aaron?
Who's that?
Lucifer.
So you're telling me that
in order to save Earth
I have to send the Devil
back to Heaven?
I told you, I haven't
been the Devil in ages.
It was my vision of you
that inspired me to leave Hell
and serve my penance on Earth.
Just like any of the Fallen.
Just like the ones
you've already redeemed.
Their sin was the same as mine
and you found them worthy.
Aaron...
we all deserve forgiveness
if we truly want it.
You can't deny what your body
is telling you.
Ok.
Ok?
I'll do it.
Oh, thank you, son.
Thank you.
Give me your hand.
I saw you. I saw the things
you've done.
I saw what you really are.
No. No, you...
you saw me as I was.
I want to trust you.
I do.
But I can't.
Please, Aaron.
I'm your father.
I came here...
looking for answers.
Like you were just going to say some
magic words
and all of a sudden, my life would just
make sense.
But I don't care what the prophecy says.
I don't care what anybody
tells me to do.
I know what feels right
and I know what doesn't.
And this feels wrong.
I can't redeem you.
I won't.
Il gran rifiuto.
I'm going home now.
No, Aaron.
You're not going anywhere.
Where are we?
No! No! No!
Just finished.
You're safe now.
This was my punishment...
an eternity without you.
But you came back to me,
thank God.
No! No!
Lukas, you can't do this to me.
Maybe this is Heaven after all.
Where are we?
The monastery
is where I broke through, Aaron.
My portal to Earth.
I'm not able to leave
its grounds, but...
I am allowed certain
comforts of home here.
To enter these walls
is to enter Hell itself.
This is Hell?
Yes.
This is my dominion.
And you,
like these poor souls,
are now a prisoner here.
But I am offering you
something that the rest of my guests
would do anything to have.
A way out.
Send me home, son,
to Paradise.
So you can take over?
Is that what you want?
No.
I won't let you.
And if I have to spend
an eternity in Hell
to make sure that you never get there,
that's a sacrifice
that I'm willing to make.
How noble of you.
But...
what of the lovely
Ms. Rodriguez?
She entered the monastery
looking for you.
But she found...
something else.
Where is she?
She's in my care.
And she will remain there
until you do
what you were born to do.
I don't believe you.
This is another one
of your lies.
Is it?
Look down there.
I knew, Vilma.
Vilma!
I always knew
that we'd end up together.
It's not the Redeemer
you belong with.
It's me, Vilma.
There were times
when you were happy with me.
Do you rember?
You'll be happy again.
She can't hear
or see you, Aaron.
Just look at her.
An eternity as a prisoner
of that twisted old man.
It's one thing
to sacrifice yourself, Aaron.
But are you willing to damn
the woman you love?
Wipe these runes away.
If I brush away
those markings,
then I'll condemn myself
to eternal torment.
If I don't...
I'll condemn you.
Go.
Thank you.
Just go.
Well...
the esteemed Dr. Grasic
just earned himself
an upgrade in his damnation.
You couldn't
keep her here.
You can't keep anyone here.
You don't have
that kind of power.
Hell is a choice that we make.
The only real
prisoner here is you.
You're so smart.
I tried to be nice,
I tried intimidation, and now
I have to resort to force.
Then go ahead.
Kill me.
I'm not afraid.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Did you find
what you were looking for?
You sent Aaron to his doom.
You knew!
He trusted you.
You can help him.
You have to, Azazel.
I know you can.
Why would I?
You know what it's like
to be held against your will.
This is your chance
to make up for everything
that you've done wrong.
Take it.
Please, Azazel.|Please.
Do it!
Do it or what?
Or I'll kill you.
I was thinking about it!
I was on the fence!
But then you had to go
and ask me so politely.
I think I have
some time to kill.
You're right, Aaron,
I can't keep you here in Hell.
But I can persuade you
to be reasonable.
And this time, don't expect Azazel
to come to your rescue.
Azazel knew what you wanted.
He was in on this.
Of course he was.
So,
it comes down to this.
If you stand against me,
you stand alone.
I am the most powerful angel
that was ever created.
Do you really believe
that you can beat me?
The angel in me is just as powerful
as you are.
But my humanity
makes me stronger.
Really?
You've been defeated before.
And once is enough.
Not bad for a girl.
You know, I hate
hurting pretty girls!
But something about you
really pisses me off.
Run!
Camael.
I thought you were dead.
Let's see if we can fix that.
This is where it ends.
Azazel, no!
Azazel.
Mazarin!
5,000 years ago,
I put you in chains.
Will you return willingly?
Never!
Then you leave me no choice
but to fight you to the death.
Now you're speaking
my language!
Let's do this!
Man to man!
You are my son!
You were born to help me
destroy the Creator,
and by God you are going
to live up to that!
Surrender, my son.
The prophecy.
I don't care
about the prophecy.
I care about my destiny!
This is my life!
I'm taking control of it.
I'm sorry, son.
I never meant for it
to end like this.
Go ahead!
Say it!
Go to Hell!
Aaron!
Gabe.
Let's get out of here.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
Kill me!
Give me a warrior's death.
You know you want to.
No, Azazel.
I follow the Creator's orders.
Not yours.
Ariel.
Ariel...
Long time no see.
Don't do it.
No, you're going back.
Then how about
a kiss good-night?
I'm so glad
you're all right.
Camael!
You're alive?
What happened to you?
Did you...
Did you see him?
Aaron...
did you meet... Lucifer?
I sent him back to Hell...
where he belongs.
It's too late for me.
I'm not going
to let you die.
I'd never considered...
that your powers
would apply to me.
I've taken
so many lives, Aaron.
I've killed so many.
I... I have not earned
my redemption.
If anyone's earned
their redemption, Camael,
it's you.
And I'm going
to send you home now.
Good-bye, Camael.
Good-bye...
my friend.
I'll be watching you...
Nephilim.
Forgive me.
You are indeed the Redeemer
of the prophecy.
It's over.
All of it.
You're going to stop
killing the Fallen,
the Nephilim.
Find yourself
a new mission.
Noooo!
No!
Your sentence was to remain here
until Judgment Day, Azazel.
But the Redeemer
has defeated Lucifer.
So that day may never come.
Well, I'm nothing
if not patient, Mazarin!
We'll just have to wait
and see, won't we?
So what happens now?
Well, Aaron,
that's really up to you.
There are still a lot of Fallen
who need redemption, right?
Yes, but everything's different now.
They can come out of hiding.
You no longer have to risk your life
trying to track them down.
They can come to you.
So you can do whatever you want.
So...
what do you want to do?
Yeah, what's next?
I want to go home.
Will you come with me?
Anywhere.