When God created man,
a jealous Lucifer
mounted a great
rebellion in heaven.
His army of angels
was defeated
and forever banished
from paradise.
These angels, the fallen,
abandoned Lucifer,
choosing to live on earth
among the pleasures of humans.
They took mortal wives
and fathered abominations,
children called Nephilim:
by the power of angels
with the souls of man.
Angry, the Creator
flooded the earth,
killing the Nephilim and driving
the fallen into hiding.
He sent the Powers,
fierce warrior angels,
to hunt those who
survived the flood.
but there was hope
for the fallenn a prcy.
A Nephilim would be born
who would redeem them
and return them
to paradise.
So the fallen watched...
and waited.
Tom?
Lori?
Tom? Lori?
Come, Nephilim!
Meet your death!
Huh.
Oh, man, that was wicked.
Oh...
Hey, buddy.
Oh, hey, hey,
stop, come on.
All right, come on, come on.
Hey, a little lighter
on the noise, okay?
I got
a killer headache.
Surprise.
Hey,
Happy Birthday!
Don't let it go out.
I got it.
Okay.
We got it.
Here it is.
There you go.
Make a wish.
Yay.
Nice.
Thank you, Lori.
Thanks, Tom.
Wow. Um, you guys
didn't have to do this.
Didn't have to?
It's your 18th birthday.
It's like the start
of a whole new life.
Yeah. And we'll
have a party tonight,
but we just wanted
to, uh, to--
how happy we are
that you were born,
that last three years
you've been with us
have been just wonderful.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I mean, yeah.
Thanks a lot.
Now, you know
the Corbett tradition.
Birthday boy gets
to pick dinner,
so what'll it be?
Um, well, if it's
not too much trouble,
maybe Tom can make
his spaghetti sauce?
Yeah. Yeah?
Of course not.
It's no trouble.
I'll make it
extra-special.
It already is, hon.
Okay. All right.
Well, um, I got to get
to work, so...
we'll see you,
and save your appetite.
Maybe after the party,
we can work on the Caddy.
Cool.
All right.
That was very nice of you,
and brave.
I can talk him out of it.
I'll tell him we're
out of the ingredients.
No, no, I'm actually, uh...
I'm beginning to like
Tom's sauce.
Or at least
get used to it.
How'd you get to be
such a good kid, huh?
I got to get Stevie up.
So enjoy your breakfast,
and happy birthday.
How's it taste?
this just arrived
he said it wa urgent
it's late You may go now
But you have another meeting
it's no t neccessary for you to be here
I'll see you tomorrow
what was that
just the wind
we're on the eighty-first floor
Hello, Fallen.
Verchiel.
You look like you were
expecting someone.
Who was coming
to visit you, Samchial?
No one, Your Worship.
Look we find you,
lying to us.
What's that in your hair?
Is it gray?
I think you've been
hanging around these monkeys
for too long.
Did you really think
that you could hide yourself
behind all this magic?
I mean, what good are runes
when you show yourself
by your actions?
It's very sloppy.
Maybe you're sick
of this realm.
Or maybe you actually feel
remorse for your actions,
and you've decided
to turn yourself in.
I have paid for my transgressions.
You've paid?
Being exiled to this planet
is far from payment
for what you did, my friend.
Your kind has yet
to be punished.
By whom? You and your
fanatic followers?
You're not enacting
the will of the Creator.
You're on your own crusade
to destroy those
whom you know were loved
more by the Creator.
Silence!
Prepare yourself
for your judgment, Fallen.
Yaah!
Only the Creator can judge.
Wait!
Oh! You fool!
He was hiding something,
and you destroyed it!
Mom, let it go.
There are plenty
of kids out there
who call their parents
by their first names.
Besides, Dr. Jonas says
that it's common
for older adopted children,
and it doesn't mean
that Aaron's
not bonding with us.
No, Mom, Tom and I don't
need a second opinion.
We're happy working
with Dr. Jonas.
Besides, Aaron trusts him.
Oh! It's okay, Stevie. Sorry.
I-- No, it's okay.
I just touched Stevie
without telling him.
And I think you're wrong
about forcing Aaron
to call us Mom and Dad.
You know,
he's been through more
than you or I
could ever understand.
Oh, here he is now, Mom.
Yeah.
She wants to wish you
a Happy Birthday.
Hey, Marge--
Grandma.
A white button-down shirt,
slacks, and loafers.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Okay. I will.
Okay. Thanks. Bye.
She wanted to make sure
I was dressed right
to meet
the school recruiters.
Oh, well, I officially
apologize for my mother again.
It's no big deal.
Don't sweat it.
So, you're legal now.
Are you sure you don't
want to play hooky today?
We could go and vote,
enlist in the Army,
or--ooh--you could see
an "R"-rated movie.
No, thanks anyway.
I got a big test in math,
and I got to practice
for the meet on Saturday.
Oh. Headache.
You're not doing
any dumb jock stuff
like starving yourself
for the wrestling meet?
Uh, with my metabolism,
I don't have to.
Lucky dog.
Hey, bro.
How's it going?
Hey.
You're the only one
that--
- he does that with.
- He does that with.
Well, Stevie and I have
an understanding. Right, bro?
Oh, hey, Stevie, leave
Aaron's ring alone.
That's okay.
He can play with it.
Hey, Stevie,
I got to get going.
I'm gonna hand you over
now, okay?
Hey, Stevie, Mama's gonna
take you from Aaron, okay?
Oh, no. It's okay.
We got to let Aaron
get to school, right?
Yeah, we're gonna have
some fun today,
aren't we? Hmm?
Hey, no,
it's a good thing
that he responds so well
to you, right, kiddo?
Yeah. You go to school.
We're fine.
I told you. I don't know what
you're talking about
we know youre master
was part of a system
that protects the fallen angels
and their offspring
where are the records?
She knows nothing.
Dispose of her.
wait wait
sometimes I woould see hime
he would stand in front of the
markings. on the wall
show me where
here
He has hidden them
behind the runes.
You have done well.
We have no more
need of you.
Very clever, Samchial.
The abominations--we can
track them down and des--
What's that?
It's North America.
It looks
like Massachusetts.
Damn him!
He rigged it.
You think?
Samchial's
not alone in this.
He was expecting
someone else.
Find out who it is,
and let me know
before the others do.
Corbett-hole.
Lay off, Lockhart.
I got a headache.
You weren't at weigh-in
this morning.
Yeah, I got in late.
I was 162.
What, are you losing weight?
Better bulk up if you want
to compete in the 166 class.
No, I'm good.
I'm shooting for your level.
I mean, I'm good at 166,
but I'm gonna be great
at 157,
so you watch your butt,
"Corbutt,"
'cause I'm coming for you.
I'll eat you alive.
Someone screw
with your locker, Brady?
Yeah, real funny.
You think they'd get
tired of the same joke.
Here.
For a jock,
you're almost human.
And for a geek,
you're almost, uh...
Ah, you're just a geek.
Why do you put up
with that nose wipe?
Ah, leave him alone,
Peter.
Just trying
to help you out.
It's bad enough
you're a foster kid,
but hanging out
with losers like that,
it's bad for your rep.
Catch my drift, Corbett?
Corbot.
Don't even think it.
That is way
out of your league.
Hey.
Hi.
Ouch. That had
to hurt, huh?
I got to get to class.
Wrestling is
the art of strategy.
Do not think
about your first move.
Think about how you're gonna
get to your fifth move.
Okay, mat time.
Situational drills.
Pinning combinations.
Partner up.
Wrestling is
the art of leaders.
Genghis Khan
chose his generals
by their wrestling skill.
And at the regionals,
we're gonna show everybody
what kind of leaders we are.
Uh, Corbett, partner up
with Lockhart.
You're gunning
for state champ.
Gotta give you a challenge.
Got what it takes,
Corbett-hole?
How's the headache?
Still there.
Good. Make it easier
to take you down.
Thanks for the love.
Couldn't hold
the half nelson.
Weak, Corbett, weak.
You're gonna have to do
much better on Saturday.
Mat work.
Pinning combinations.
Partner up.
Hey, Brady.
Saw you in the shower
today, buddy.
Doesn't look good.
Yeah, shouldn't you be
in the girls' locker room?
Come on, Peter,
let me go.
"Come on, Peter,
let me go."
"Peter, oh, please,
don't hurt me."
Can we be intelligent
about this?
Whoa! You're saying
Peter's not intelligent?
Aren't you guys tired of
kicking the crap out of me?
Not yet.
Lay off, Lockhart.
Whoa, it's
the orphan boy.
Yeah, poster boy here
for birth control.
You challenging Lockhart
after he trounced you today?
Didn't you learn your
lesson in gym today,
Corbett-hole.
I guess not.
Aaron,
what are you doing?
Lay off, Corbett!
You're choking him!
He's choking him.
Let him loose, Corbett!
You're choking him!
Lay off him!
Aaron, come on, let him go.
He's just a jerk.
Man, lay off!
You're choking him!
Come on, let him go.
Lay off him!
It's your birthday?
Yeah. Yeah.
I heard what you did
for David Brady in the gym.
I think it's cool.
It was stupid.
I, uh, I lost control.
I could have hurt him.
Well, it's just
I promised Tom and Lori
that I wouldn't
fight anymore.
Who?
Oh, they're my parents.
Oh!
I'm sorry. They're-- Yeah.
They're my parents.
They're-- Actually, they're
my adoptive parents.
Yeah. I heard
you're adopted.
So am I.
You are?
Yeah.
My mom died
when I was born,
and my aunt
raised me.
And when she died,
I moved up here
to live with my
other aunt.
Wow.
That's--
That's so cool.
What?
No, no, no.
Not that you're an orphan.
That's not what I meant.
I'm an orphan too.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it
that way.
It's okay.
It's just,
uh, you, uh--
You know
your biological family.
You don't?
No.
I was, uh, placed
in foster care
when I was born.
Sorry.
What are you gonna do
for your birthday?
You having a big party?
No, I'll probably
just, uh,
hang out
with Tom and Lori,
and Stevie.
He's their son.
That probably sounds
really, uh, dorky,
spending my 18th birthday
with my family.
No. It sounds
really wonderful.
Vilma, come here.
I got to go.
Happy birthday.
So, water conservation.
Three basic goals:
Increase the amount
of groundwater,
keep the unpolluted
waters clean
and clean up
the polluted waters,
and decrease our own
personal use.
Americans use 60 gallons
of water each per day.
That's five times more
than any European.
Now, when you're
brushing your teeth,
do you let
the water run,
or do you turn the shower on
before you get into it,
let it run, getting warm,
or run the water
for a while
before you get
a glass of water,
wash just a few things
in the laundry machine?
Okay, this material will
be on next week's test.
Homework tonight, Chapter 3,
and answer the questions
in the back.
Mr. Corbett,
before you go,
I know you have a--
a lot of offers
from colleges,
based upon
your wrestling,
but I don't want you
to neglect your
academic achievements.
I have a friend who's
recruiting for Cornell.
He's looked
at your records.
He's impressed, and he
wants to meet with you.
Now, I know it may
be as much money
as a sports scholarship,
but I think you should
listen to his offer.
Okay. I will.
Thank you, Mrs. Baker.
Aaron, you're a smart boy.
You're talented.
Kids like you,
they're destined for a fate
greater than being
an ex-wrestling champ.
Make something of yourself.
Can I help you?
The boy,
the one who just left.
Aaron Corbett?
Yes. Thank you.
Is there a problem?
Not anymore.
He's really mean.
He's nice to me.
Yeah, like a spider,
and you're the fly.
Maybe I'm the spider,
and he's the fly.
I think he's cute.
Come on, class.
Take your seats.
Open up your textbooks
to Chapter 5.
Run. Disappear.
Run!
They come! Run!
Run! Danger.
Leave this place.
Run.
Danger. Run.
Run!
Danger!
Get home...
get some sleep...
and everything
will be okay.
Ah, kids today.
Drink, drugs.
Shouldn't be driving.
Angels?
Nephilim.
Come on,
come on, come on.
Hey.
Hey, you.
Hold, it, hold it.
Stop, stop, stop!
Hold it! Now wait a minute,
wait a minute,
wait a minute!
Oh, my.
He's come.
The Punisher.
what shall we do?
They've come to kill us
don't worry my beloved
I'll proctect you.
They won't find you
But the signs show...
You must come with me
Father, no. What are you doing?
No please.
You have your Nephilim.
I've kept my part
of the bargain.
Please, father. No.
How could you do this?
Then you will live,
Grigori.
For now.
Papa?
Papa!
Lori?
Aaron!
Stevie?
Aaron, Aaron, Aaron.
Love you, love you,
love you.
Okay, play now with Gabriel?
Aaron scared?
Aaron okay?
I swear, if I hear
one more word from you,
I'm gonna scream.
Aaron?
Hey, you're home early.
Everything all right?
Yeah, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I think
I'm just, uh...
I think I'm coming
down with something.
Oh, you're pale.
Oh, and you're feverish.
Yeah, I just, uh...
I just need to rest.
Are you sure?
Can I make you something?
No, no. I'm fine.
I'm just gonna,
um, go upstairs.
Okay.
Hey, wait for Gabriel!
Gabe is not talking to me.
Gabe is not talking to me
Aaron angry at Gabriel?
Gabriel did
something wrong?
Shut up.
Please, just shut up.
I'm losing it.
This can't be happening.
Aaron angry.
Gabriel knows why.
It's a...dream.
It's...hallucinations
from a fever.
Maybe I...hit my head
too hard in gym class.
Gabriel took, chewed up
couldn't stop.
Gabriel sorry.
Aaron, please forgive.
Please.
Gabe will never
chew socks.
It's not about
the damn sock.
I know, but I promise
I will never chew socks.
Please be quiet
for a second.
Is everything okay up there?
Gabriel fine.
Aaron act funny.
We're good--
I mean, I'm good.
Okay.
Inside.
Yeah, but I thought maybe
a quick game of fetch.
Animals and people aren't
supposed to talk to each other.
Dogs are dogs,
and humans are humans.
Aaron talk to Gabe
all the time.
Gabe talk
to Aaron all the time.
I know that,
but there's a difference
between talking to
and understanding, Gabe.
I'm--I'm arguing with a dog.
This is crazy.
I'm--I'm crazy.
They're, uh...
They're gonna lock
me away, Gabe.
Aaron scared
Gabriel talk?
Gabriel no talk.
No talk?
No talk.
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna sleep this off.
When I wake up,
everything's gonna be fine.
Yeah, and we'll celebrate
your birthday tomorrow.
Okay.
Can't wait.
We're gonna have
cake and ice cream.
It's gonna be
a lot of fun.
Stop talking.
there is no mercy
for abominations!
There is no mercy for Nephilim!
Aah!
Hello.
No more talking?
Okay.
Good boy.
All right, buddy,
let's get you some food.
Good.
Love, love, love food.
Oops.
Gabriel talked.
I think
I'm going crazy.
Have you told
Tom and Lori?
No. No. Um...
You know, they've been
so nice to me,
and, uh...
now I've got to tell them
that they've adopted a schizo.
There are a lot of other
things besides schizophrenia
that would explain
these symptoms.
You and I have been
meeting for seven years.
We've gone through some
pretty tough situations in foster care,
so I--I think we can get
through this one all right, okay?
Good.
All right, then.
Reality check.
Out of the Heavens rained down,
who angrily were saying:
"Who is this...
that without death goes through
the Kingdom of the people, dead"
So what did I just say?
It's from Dante's Inferno.
We read it last year
in Language Arts.
The fallen angels are angry
because Dante's in hell
but he's not dead.
Did you, um, read
this book in Italian?
No.
Non conosco l'italiano.
But you're speaking it now.
No. Ora non sto parl--
parlando.
Holy crap.
D-Do you see
what I mean?
Amazing.
Wait a minute.
..."whose fire in his eyes
"reaches further
than her heart.
"Will the flame
of the heart die
in the flames
of the fire?"
The woman thinks
of the living,
whose fire in his eyes
reaches further
than her heart.
Will the flame
of the heart die
in the flames of the fire?
Or something like that.
Hey, you live
like an onion,
with your head
in the ground.
An onion?
What does that mean?
Um...it means...
It means holy crap.
What?
I--I don't know, Aaron.
I don't know.
I've heard of people
who have suffered
a head trauma.
Others get brain lesions.
Well, I did have
a bad headache.
And suddenly, they--they
understand other languages.
I always just thought
it was urban myth.
Repeat this string
of numbers to me backwards:
11, 5, 8, 12, 14.
14, 12, 8, 5, 11.
Adds up to 50.
That's right.
And you understand
animals as well.
So, is Gabe
saying anything?
Gabe?
A lady poodle
peed right here.
Um...
A poodle
peed on your carpet.
Well, now,
that's impossible.
The label said the odor
will be gone in a week,
and absolutely no one--
Gabe told you that?
Damn.
Aaron, are you...
having any other symptoms?
I mean, are you
experiencing nausea, vomiting?
No.
I'm fine.
Just...weird.
Weird.
Yeah, well, that--
That is the word
for it.
I'm gonna get you in
to see my friend
at Stanford
Medical Center.
I'm gonna clear
my book tomorrow.
Can you be here
around 10 A.M.?
I want you to use
the emergency line
if you need anything,
or you feel sick, all right?
And take notes.
Take notes, Aaron.
I want to know everything
that's going on.
And tell your folks.
I mean, that's
what parents are for.
Maybe I had a stroke
or something.
Or maybe it's genetic.
My father was a...
genius,
or my mother was part
of a medical experiment,
and died
while giving birth.
It's hard not knowing
who your parents are.
You're kind of an orphan
too, huh?
Aaron Gabriel's family.
What the--
Something's coming.
Ah.
Hello young Nephilim
Do you understand the
tongue of the message
The Messenger?
What you are is obvious.
You are in danger...
Nephilim.
Aaron?
Aaron! Wait for Gabriel!
Oh, this is not good.
This is not good.
Play now?
Oh. Oh, good, yeah.
No play.
Must work. No play.
All work, no play, makes
Aaron talk to himself.
How are you?
You speak Portuguese?
I didn't know.
No...no...I don't speak Portuguese.
Well, kind of.
Not really.
Just a little bit.
But your accent is perfect.
Yeah, I've-- I've been
studying it some.
It's a pretty language.
You weren't in class today.
No, no, I, uh--
Some say you didn't want
to go to wrestling,
that you're chicken.
Would that "some"
be Peter Lockhart?
Yeah. He's a loser.
I thought you were sick,
but here you are,
talking to yourself.
Oh, I was, uh,
I was talking to Gabe.
Oh, hi, poochie.
Not Poochie, Gabriel.
What a pretty dog.
Yeah, Gabriel very pretty.
Uh...
Oh, uh,
I'm doing research
for, uh, for school.
It's a book report.
I love angels.
Uh...
See?
Um, I have all kinds
of books on them.
Do you know
about, um, Nephilim?
Sure, yeah. There's all
kinds of angels.
There's the Cherubim,
the Seraphim,
the Nephilim,
who were the children
of an angel and a human.
You see, they had
the powers of angels,
but the souls of man.
Here, let me
show you a site.
"From the root 'nephel,'
"meaning 'unnaturally
begotten men,' or 'bastards.'
"They are the biblical
half-breeds:
half-human, half-angel."
Isn't this site great?
Yeah, yeah, this is--
This is really cool.
I think angels are here,
all around us.
What, you mean, like,
you can see 'em?
Well, not see 'em, but...
don't you ever feel
like you're in the presence
of something special?
Yeah.
I--I know
what you mean.
When's your
book report due?
Maybe I can help
with research.
Wow. Yeah.
That would be--
That would be fantastic,
yeah.
Um, I got to get the bus.
Uh, we both have study hall
second period tomorrow.
You want to meet
at the library?
Sure, I'd love to.
Yeah.
"Nephilim had the gift
of tongues,
"understanding all languages,
including that of the animals
and the plants."
We got to find that bum.
He's right over there.
Hey! Hey!
Ohh...
Hey, you, come here,
come here, come here.
Listen to me. Why did you
call me that name?
I don't want
to hurt you.
I'm not gonna let go of you
until you tell me
what's going on, okay?
Okay.
Go easy with the threads.
Huh?
It's my best outfit.
Why did you call me
Nephilim?
'Cause that's what you are.
You're half-angel,
half-human.
You some sort of cult
person, is that it?
I'm an angel.
Name is Ezekiel,
Zeke for short.
Okay, okay, I got it.
I'm talking
to a nut case.
Well, ha ha--
You're crazier than me.
Have it your way.
Come on, Gabe.
Well, Happy 18th Birthday
to you, nonetheless.
Yep.
How did you know
it was my birthday?
Nephilim come of age
when they're 18,
and you can smell 'em
a mile away
when they're turning.
Ahh...
And boy, you do
smell of angel.
This is a bunch of bull.
Well, you're taking it
a lot better than most.
What do you mean?
Well, angel nature
and human nature
don't live well
together.
Nephilim, when they
experience both,
they, hmmm,
they go wackadoodle,
and you, you're just
a little wonka-wonka.
Huh, wonka-wonka--hoo.
Wonka-wonka. Wonka.
I have done your bidding.
I have sought out
the abominations
and destroyed them.
But it has been a long time
since I have heard your words,
a sign that my work
is pleasing in your sight.
I know it is not
for me to ask,
but...a sign.
if you could just show me--
Your lordship.
What?
Your lordship, I thought
you might want these:
the remains of Samshial.
What would I want
with his ashes?
Do you think
I'm like these humans,
needing their remains
to make themselves feel better?
Huh!
Wait!
A sign.
Thank you.
You have done well.
For this, you may have
the next kill.
Thank you, my lord.
We must send Kolazonta
to Massachusetts
to find someone named Corbett.
If you're an angel,
show me your wings.
I'm a Grigori,
one of the highest
orders of angels.
I, uh, hate to break it
to you, bud,
but, uh, those
aren't wings.
Uh, yeah, I had 'em
clipped in the fall.
Oh, yeah?
So they'll grow back
in the spring?
Uh, that's fall,
not as in autumn,
uh, as in fallen.
I'm a fallen angel,
so they clipped my wings.
Those scars you got,
they could be from anything:
an accident, surgery.
Yeah, well,
believe it or not,
I am an angel.
Heh heh heh.
You are Nephilim,
which means that,
uh--ha ha--
I want to be
out of here
when they come
looking for you.
Who's "they"?
The Powers.
They, uh, their gig is
to get rid of creatures
they're not pleased with,
and, uh, usually,
they find 'em
within two days
after their 18th birthday.
Now, you've got,
maybe, a day,
something like that,
I think, yeah.
So you're telling me that
because I'm a Nephilim,
God has sent killer
angels after me.
Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
God, God
is such a limiting term.
The Creator
is so much more:
Allah, Shiva,
the Tao, Jehovah--
Can you please
stick to the point?
The point.
Oh, yes, well,
uh, humans and angels
are not supposed to, uh,
canoodle, uh, fraternize,
socialize, that sort of thing.
Well, anyway...
the result
of our dalliances...
are beings like you,
Nephilim.
That's it, here we go.
Aha! My prize, yes.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah, here we go.
Play ball!
Yes! Play ball!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is not to play with.
This is mine. I caught this
is straightaway center field
from Babe Ruth,
and it's signed by him.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You can hear my dog?
Oh, yes, I can hear
your dog, absolutely.
That's what talking
in tongues is.
It's an angel thing.
And we're really good
dancers too--woo-hoo!
Uh, the Powers think
that they are the Creator's
personal storm troopers,
and their whole goal
is to get rid of Nephilim,
and they absolutely
hate the Fallen.
Why? Why do they
hate the Fallen?
The important thing is that
Camael, leader of the Powers,
is here, and he's probably
looking for you.
What is that?
Wait a minute.
That's my name.
This is just a bruise.
That ain't no bruise.
That's a mark.
That's ancient writing.
This is getting weird!
I wanna get--
That--That's, uh--
That's ancient writing.
That's, uh--
I'm out of here.
Wait, wait!
Whoa-ho-ho!
Wait a minute!
So you tell me some Camel
guy's looking for me?
Whoa! Hold it!
Gabe! Ball!
Gabe! No!
Ball! Oh, yeah!
Play ball!
Gabe.
He came out of nowhere.
I didn't even--
Just get help, quick.
Gabe, you okay?
Gabriel hurt bad.
Gabe, no. Gabe,
no, no, no, no, no.
Please, please,
Gabe, Gabe, Gabe, Gabe.
Gabe.
Aaron?
All right, all right.
Move aside, move aside.
Let me show you
how a real angel heals.
Come on, move aside.
All right.
Easy, boy.
Easy, big fella.
I'm gonna take you
for a little ride.
There you are.
It...hurts.
What is that?
What's happening?
Did you see that?
That's his soul
leaving the body.
Whoo. That means
I lost my touch.
Sorry, kid. You know
what they say:
use it or lose it.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
There's got to be
something.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Please.
That's something you're not
supposed to be able to do,
unless--
Now, look here, now, if you
are what I think you are,
then we can--we can
still save this dog.
Please, you've done
enough damage.
Look, you either believe me,
and he lives,
or you don't,
and he dies.
Now, it's your choice.
You put your hands on him.
Animal Control's
on their way.
Now.
This is crazy.
You got to tap into
your angel nature.
It's like everything's
speeding up inside ya.
See it in the darkness.
Look hard.
You see it?
You see it.
I see something.
Hear it. Call to it.
Let it fill you.
What is it?
No, no, no.
You got to control it.
You got to--
If you're gonna
save this dog,
you've got to accept
your angel nature.
You've got to open
yourself to it.
You've got
to let it fill you.
You've got to accept it
as part of you,
and if you doubt it,
if you question it,
it'll destroy you,
or you will destroy it.
You understand?
Okay.
This is a part of me.
This is a part of who I am.
Aaron?
Where's the ball?
Gabe.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, I'm free at last.
Where's the ball?
Where'd the ball go?
I'm free at last!
This is impossible.
I'm not half an angel.
Oh, sorry to tell you, kid,
but you're probably
more than that.
Ah!
He bears the names
of the Fallen,
he has the touch
of the angels.
No more exile.
Gabe, stay away
from the birds.
Don't worry, Aaron.
Gabriel won't hurtrt.
Honing hunting skills.
Honing? Who uses words
like "honing"?
I don't even
words like "honing."
So, if you are
what I think you are,
we've got some business
to tend to.
No, we don't.
We have no business
to attend to, okay?
My dog almost died.
There you are.
And I just brought him
back to life.
Exact--
That's crazy.
That's insane.
I got to talk to Jonas.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Go easy with this.
You're quite a find.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Whatever just happened's
never gonna happen again.
Great! I can help you!
I can make it all go away.
Yes, I can. There's just
one little thing
you have to do for me:
Redeem me.
What?
You can restore me
to an angel
and send me home.
Then I can call off
the Powers,
and you can be
a normal boy again.
Okay, I'm--
I'm out of here.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Listen. Listen to me.
Just stay here.
Just listen to me, please.
Just listen for a moment.
Now, there is a chance
that you can redeem me,
and clear me
of my transgressions.
How can I redeem you?
I don't know
what that means.
if you're real.
You know I'm real.
Come over here.
Let me give you
something here.
Babe Ruth signed this.
It's yours. Here.
It's not about the payment.
Do you understand?
This is just--This is--
This is too weird.
All right, all right,
all right.
The prophesy
said you would come,
and here you are,
so all I'm asking you to do
is to redeem me.
Just, uh, touch me,
to wave your hands over me,
have redeeming thoughts.
I don't even know
Please, just do it,
do it,
and I won't ask you
anything more.
Just--I promise.
All right, fine.
You're--You're saved.
You're redeemed. Whatever.
That's it?
No. See? You got
the wrong guy.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please, try again.
Try like you did
with the dog.
Look what you did with the dog.
Huh?
Come on.
Are you satisfied?
All right, go on,
go on, damn it.
Just go on.
Don't redeem me.
Let me give you
a little advice, Mister!
You better get
your butt out of here
because if the Powers
find you,
your ass is grass,
you understand that?
I'm getting out of here.
I've had enough of you.
Super sauce comin' at ya.
Hey! Happy Birthday!
Hey, Happy
Belated Birthday!
Ready for some of that
special spaghetti sauce?
Aaron?
It's okay.
Hey, is everything okay?
What's wrong?
Aaron?
You can tell us.
Um, I just, um...
Thank you.
Thank you for--
for everything.
I just want you guys
to know
that I can never repay you.
Repay us?
Buddy, we're family.
We don't repay.
Hey,
we love you.
I love you too,
Mom and Dad.
Please don't
forget that.
Um, don't worry.
We won't.
Come on, let's eat.
Oh, my God.
Look what he's doing.
Stevie, did you
do that, sweetie?
Angel.
Oh, my God,
you're speaking!
Stevie,
you're talking!
Hey!
Hey, hi, Stevie!
Hi, sweetheart.
Where's
the video camera?
Uh...
We got to get this
on tape.
Go, go, go, go.
Baby, it's me, Mommy.
Hey, can you say "Mommy"?
Aaron.
He's--
Stevie's speaking.
Hey, can you say
something for me?
Aaron.
Angels.
Angels come.
He knows who
you are, Aaron.
This is amazing.
He knows who you are.
I think I'll call in
sick tomorrow
and come with you
and Stevie to the clinic.
What if he's
getting better?
What if this
is all a mistake?
Take it easy.
One step at a time.
Yeah.
You missed weigh-in
this morning.
Hmm?
Coach Chaney called.
Tell her what
Dr. Jonas said.
I, uh, was doing
a report for school.
Dr. Jonas said that you
should tell Tom and--
Oh, cake!
That's good. Can't make it
on brawn alone.
I got to get
this one to bed.
I'm gonna, uh, go
get some fresh air.
Oh, there we go.
You're a big boy.
The Studebaker parts
finally came.
Water's stuck
in the pit again.
Oh, yeah. We're gonna
have to get that fixed
one of these days.
Here you go.
Quite a day, huh?
I mean, with, uh, Stevie,
and plus it being
your birthday.
Yeah.
You know, Stevie talking...
We've been hoping
for something like that
for...years.
Yeah, I know.
Well, Lori and I, uh--
your mom and I--
Look, I remember
turning 18.
I was still in foster care,
and I waited my whole life
for that birthday
so I could get out
on my own
and stop bouncing
from place to place.
Look, just because
you've turned 18,
and legally
you're an adult,
that doesn't mean
we're not family.
Tom--
Uh, Dad,
there's stuff going on.
I'm really scared.
I think there's
something wrong with me.
I mean, um...
I'm afraid my parents
weren't normal.
Aaron, you and I have talked
about how I was at your age.
You know,
I stole, and I lied,
and I got kicked out
of every foster home
within a few months.
I know, but--
Wait, wait.
It's because I thought
my biological parents
were bad people.
And I thought I was bad,
you know, like I didn't
have a choice.
I was--I was a victim
of my own fear.
You understand
what I'm saying?
Yeah, but--
But then I started to see
that I was taking
the easy way:
you know, blaming others
for how my life was going.
But the only person
in charge of my life was me,
and I had a choice.
You know, I could be
angry and resentful,
or I could work,
and create a life
that I could be proud of.
But I think there's
something wrong with me.
Aaron, there's nothing
wrong with you.
You're human,
like all of us.
You're a good kid.
I mean,
you're a good man.
You have refused to let
what happened to you
define who you are.
I'm proud to have you
as my son.
Come here.
Hello.
I was wondering
if you could help me.
I'm looking
for someone.
Well,
I'm the only one here.
How did you get in here?
A boy. Just turned 18.
An orphan.
He has...abilities.
I think you'd better leave.
There's no one here.
It's the damnedest thing.
I haven't seen
anything like it,
not in my entire life.
You know,
I never believed
in spontaneous human
combustion before,
but there's
no other explanation.
The guy was completely
incinerated.
Just him and the phone.
Fire doesn't work that way.
It's the damnedest thing.
Excuse me.
The doctor who works here,
is he okay?
You family?
He's my friend.
I'm sorry, kid. I can't
say anything officially.
We see Dr. Jonas?
No.
We don't.
This is so screwed up.
Who's gonna
believe me, huh?
All right, I'll be
right back, okay?
Brady, have you seen
Vilma Rodriguez?
You mean the girl you've
been pining over all year?
If you see her, tell her
I can't make study hall.
Here, let me.
Geez, Corbett, you ripped
the whole door off.
What's with you?
Hey, Corbett-hole, surprised
to see you at school.
You been hiding or what?
Not now, Lockhart.
Find Vilma,
and tell her I'll
talk to her later.
Don't turn
your back on me.
I'm just gonna get
the vice-principal.
No. Brady, you intervene,
and you're next.
Peter, don't do this,
okay?
You're dead.
You're a freak, Corbett.
How did you do that?
Honestly, I--
I have no clue, man.
Things
are really screwed up.
I can't even...
begin to explain.
Aaron.
There you are.
Hi.
Um, listen, I got to cancel
our study date.
I know. I figured you were
already in there.
What? In where?
In the counselor's office.
They were looking for you.
There's a guy here
from Cornell.
Oh, no, no, no.
Now is not a good time.
Don't be silly.
You'll be fine.
Just be yourself.
New York, can you imagine?
That is so cool.
I want to hear what happens
with the interview.
I'm gonna be by the cafe
around 4 P.M.
You can tell me
all about it.
Tree.
Bird.
"Significant improvement."
That's what he said.
I'll get out of work
and go with you.
I'd like to check out
this new doctor.
Aaron! Help Aaron!
Oh! Hey, Stevie,
you're okay.
If you're gonna
kill me...
just do it.
What are you waiting for?
Just do it.
Kill me.
Kill you?
I've been looking for you
for centuries.
I'm here to protect you.
There was a great battle.
A mighty angel
convinced many followers
to rebel against the teachings
of the Creator.
Although these rebels
were strong,
they did not win their fight.
They were banished
to the Earth.
Their wings were clipped.
The Fallen.
You killed them.
In the past.
I thought it was
my holy mission
to eradicate the Fallen
and their offspring.
You've eradicated
others like me?
Yes, I have.
Then why are you
so set on saving me?
I mean, aren't I one
of your abominations?
A prophet once said
that a Nephilim would be born
who could forgive the Fallen
of their sins
so that they may
return to the Source.
I saw that the Creator
had a plan
much greater
than I could comprehend.
After that, I could no longer
be a part of the killing,
and I realized
that I had to save those
the Powers
wished to destroy.
This is ridiculous.
What are you,
like, part
of the Angelic Witness
Protection Agency or something?
I don't understand.
So basically,
I'm screwed.
I either go into hiding,
or I'm killed
by fanatic angels.
That's--That's great.
There is another thing.
I don't want to hear it.
We have studied the signs
foretold by the prophet.
A child would be born
when the Sun was in Virgo.
The footprint of the father
would mark his birthplace
and he would be called
as a Messenger.
Get toto the point.
These signs
have led us to you.
It is possible
that you are the one that
I have been searching for.
Okay, well, I hate
to break your bubble,
but I'm not, okay?
Zeke fed me that whole
redeeming line too, and--
You've met Ezekiel?
Yeah. I tried the whole
redeeming thing on him,
and it didn't work.
I'm not your guy.
So why don't you
leave me alone, okay?
Ezekiel is not
to be trusted.
According to Zeke,
neither are you.
If Ezekiel knows
that you're here,
he will tell the Powers.
Whether you are
the Redeemer or not,
your life
is in grave danger.
I can protect you.
I can hide you.
There's no way.
They've killed
your friend Dr. Jonas.
Stop it.
They have killed
my friend Samchial.
They will kill your family.
They will kill you.
Stop it.
Look, I've been
kicked around
since I was a baby,
one foster home
to another.
and all I ever wanted
was a normal life.
And now I'm graduating
high school,
and colleges
are interested in me,
and I have a family
that loves me,
and, you know, there's
this girl I just met--
And all this angel stuff,
I--I just--
I can't take it.
I don't want
any part of it.
You have no choice.
I have no choice?
Screw you.
I have a choice,
and I'm choosing
to be rid of you
and all this angel crap,
so why don't you go
back to Heaven
and leave me
the hell alone?
As you wish.
Ezekiel, my old friend,
and always as-- fragrant as ever.
I thought I'd
stop by and say "hi,"
talk over old times.
Oh, by the way,
have you seen any Nephilim
in these parts?
Oh-ho-ho...
They must have passed
right on by.
Sorry.
Come on, Ezekiel.
We have always had
such a good arrangement.
Mutually beneficial,
wouldn't you say?
You tell us
where the Nephilim are,
and we let you live.
Ohh...
I...know nothing.
Oh, that's funny,
because his scent
is all over the place.
And I find it
very interesting
that you gave up
your own child,
but this one
you protect.
I haven't seen him.
Hmm...
Hmm.
I...
Non, s'il vous plat!
Nephilim.
Papa! Papa!
Aaah!
It's him, or it's you.
Ohh...
I'll tell Tom and Lori.
They'll think I'm crazy,
but I have to.
Aaron, look out!
Oh-ho-ho. Whoa!
What's wrong with you?
Uh, look, I'm, uh--
Stupid idiot!
Yeah, well,
nevertheless,
uh, the Powers
are looking for you,
and I had to, uh, well,
tell 'em where you live, so--
You sent killer angels
to my house?
What about my family?
That's a good point,
That's a good point.
Now, if you're lucky,
Verchiel will spend time
questioning and...
killing 'em--
nicely, I'm sure--
and then you'll have time to escape.
What?
Yes. Well, they're
not your family anyway.
I love them.
Oh, that's sweet.
I'm sure they appreciate it,
but you better run right now.
I'm not gonna run.
I'm not a coward like you.
Courage
is vastly overrated.
Why are you doing this?
I am not
your precious Redeemer.
I'm doing this
to help you out.
Now just run.
You disgust me.
I'd rather love and die
than live and hate myself.
Oh, that's beautiful.
If it's me they want,
it's me they'll get.
I'm not gonna let them
hurt my family.
come on ?
Wait a minute. Wait!
Hey, hold on just a second.
Now, what about--
What about me?
Lori?
Tom?
Aaron, we get out of here.
Lori! Tom!
Aaron, what's going on?
What is this slamming?
What is going on?
Listen! Go back
into the basement!
Angels! Angels! Angels!
Lock the door!
Don't come out,
no matter what you hear.
But, Aaron--
Just do this for me,
please.
okay okay
Wait.
Just go.
Just go, please.
Okay.
Protect them.
Don't let them get hurt.
Come, Nephilim!
Gabriel protect.
Aaron's fine.
It's okay.
Come, Nephilim!
Meet your death!
Kid, go back!
Run for it!
Go now!
You want a piece of me?
You got it!
Grrr!
Aah!
Kushiel, kill Ezekiel!
Leave him alone.
It's me you want.
Yes, it is!
Look, I don't want
anything to do
with angels or prophesies.
So just leave me
and my family alone,
and we won't bother you.
I promise.
Oh, you promise!
Ha ha ha!
The abomination bargains!
How amusing!
He's yours.
Must save Aaron.
Raah!
Traitor!
You deserve to die!
He is the Redeemer.
The Redeemer?
You can't be serious!
Ha! Ha! Haah!
Aah!
Peniel!
Raah!
Aah! Aah! Aahr!
Go. Go get a weapon.
How?
See it in your mind.
Your turn.
Raah! Ha! Ha! Aah!
Aahhh...
Ooohh...
Aaarh!
Aarh! Aah! Aah!
Aargh!
Raah! Aah!
Aah!
Mama's gonna
touch you, baby.
There we go.
Ha ha! Ha ha!
Aah!
Stop! You can't
kill the Redeemer!
He's part of the Creator's
divine plan!
Him? You're not
just a traitor,
you're also a fool.
Look at him! Has anyone
ever fought back before?
Can't you feel
his presence?
Tell me this
isn't different.
You almost had me.
No!
Oh!
Oh, my God! Aaron!
Aaron! Angel!
Aaron!
Aaron! Aaron!
So much for your prophesy.
What have you done?
Aaron!
Angel! Aaron!
Aaron! Trapped!
Open up!
Aaron!
We're trapped!
Uh...
Thank you.
I misjudged you.
I was waiting for a sign.
I--I understand now.
Fine. You go ahead,
and you get rid of me,
but that is not gonna
solve your problem.
The Powers will never
let you roam this planet.
They will hunt you down.
And you will have to leave.
Your family will never
be safe with you here.
Aaron!
Aaron, look out!
Agrrr!
He stood you up.
Something
could have happened.
I'll give him
ten more minutes.
It's almost 5.
I'll wait for him
a little longer.
Zeke.
You came back.
You surprised me.
Yeah...
I surprised myself.
Oh, no. Don't touch me.
If you use your powers,
it's like a beacon.
They may send someone
back to look for you.
It is true.
But don't they
already know?
If you forsake your powers,
you can save the life
you have here.
If not, you will become
what you were born to be:
the Redeemer.
Zeke.
I want the truth.
Do you regret letting others
die so you could live?
Yes.
So would I.
Hey.
Open up! Aaron!
Come back!
I'm going away now.
No.
But I'll always
be with you, okay?
Aaron.
Aaron! Angel.
Aaron!
Here.
Aaron. Angel.
Aaron! The longer you stay,
the greater the danger.
I'll come back.
I promise.
Gabe? Gabe?
Can you hear me?
Come here, boy.
Tell Mom and Dad
that I love them, okay?
Lori!
Lori.
Hey, hey, it's Aaron.
There's something horrible
that's happening.
What is going on?
Where's Aaron?
I don't know--
Stevie! Stevie! Stevie!
Aaron!
Hey.
It has been said
they walk among us...
that they guide us.
It could be the banker...
the girl next door...
or the cop on the beat.
But I know now
that some tempt us.
They even destroy
what we believe in.
My future is not my own.