When God created man,
a jealous Lucifer mounted
a great rebellion in Heaven.
His army of angels
was defeated
and forever banished
from paradise.
These angels, the Fallen,
abandoned Lucifer,
choosing to live on Earth
among the pleasures of humans.
They took mortal wives
and fathered abominations,
children called Nephilim.
They have the powers
of angels
but the souls of men.
Angry, the Creator
flooded the Earth,
killing the Nephilim
and driving the Fallen
into hiding.
He sent the Powers,
fierce warrior angels,
to hunt those
that survived the flood.
But there was hope
for the Fallen in a prophecy.
A Nephilim would be born
who would redeem them
and return them to paradise.
So the Fallen watched...
and waited.
Sometimes I...
wonder what it would be like
if Lucifer had won
the war.
I mean, it's not like
he got us on his side
with promises of an evil empire
and
eternal suffering.
All that came later...
after the Fall.
I've tried my best
to make up
for what I've done.
To help the humans
defend themselves
against what I helped to create.
But...
I mean, there's just
as much hate in the world,
just as much suffering.
More, even.
So have I atoned
for what I have done?
I don't know.
I just know
I wanna go home.
Then that's where you'll go.
It's been one year since I found out
that I have the power
to send Fallen angels
back to Heaven.
But the Powers can sense
every redemption.
And we always risk
the possibility of an attack.
So we never stop running.
So many Fallen...
yet to be redeemed.
Be patient.
Stay here.
I'm fighting with you this time.
No, you're not.
I'm not gonna just sit here.
Aaron!
Most Nephilim
don't put up a fight.
Well, I'm not like
most Nephilim.
You'll die like them,
though.
I don't know what just happened to me.
I told you to stay in the car.
It's like I almost
wasn't even there.
I remember fighting, but it's
like remembering a dream.
I felt like I could take on
the Powers all by myself.
- I almost felt like I was invincible.
- You are far from it.
When you lose control like that,
you are losing the very thing
that gives you the advantage
over your opponent.
You are as powerful
as any angel there is,
Aaron.
But your humanity
makes you stronger.
In time, you will learn
to master this duality,
but until then you will focus
on returning the Fallen
to Heaven,
and you will leave
the fighting to me.
If I hadn't fought,
you'd be dead right now,
Camael.
Your journey...
has just begun.
You must be patient.
You all right?
I could heal you.
He did heal me,
Camael.
A wound...
caused by angelfire is much different.
You cannot heal it.
What are we
gonna do, then?
Find someone who can.
She's gone, Ariel.
Get the paddles, Clarence.
Get the paddles.
Nobody dies on my watch.
Welcome back.
Drop me off here.
This may take some time.
Camael.
Could we check out
the school?
Fine.
But stay close.
And that's the long history of division,
as nation after nation suffered the effects...
Aaron, this is bigger
than your old school.
Well, this is college.
It's different.
...and every freethinking
individual is a lost prophet.
And every poetic prophecy
is a conscious conspiracy
to emancipate ourselves
from mental slavery.
And we will get free or die.
Because the numbers
don't lie.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't even watching where I was going.
No, I wasn't watching where I was going.
Hi.
Paradise Lost.
I know, it, uh...
Yawn.
So, uh,
what's your major?
Oh, no, no, no,
I don't, uh...
I don't... I don't go
to school here.
Uh, just...
just visiting.
Yeah.
Right.
Looks pretty cool,
though.
Yeah, it's okay.
- I'm Chloe.
- Aaron.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Excuse me,
is there something
I can help you with?
Hey, you're not supposed
to be in here.
He's right...
you're notsupposed to be here.
- Ariel.
- Punisher.
Punisher?
Yeah, that's what we called
him in high school.
Linebacker.
Wow. This is great.
What's it like,
going to college?
I don't know.
It's pretty fun,
I guess.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I mean, it's true what they say,
you know.
Being away from your parents
in a different environment,
you really do learn
a lot about yourself.
What have you learned?
that I like partying
almost as much as I hate hangovers.
Uh, how come
you don't go?
I... I want to.
I do.
I guess I just...
I got a lot going on
in my...
in my life right now.
Well, if you're interested,
you can come to class with me.
Help me stay awake.
You can do that?
Well, they won't let any random
person come in off the street,
but if you're accompanied
by an actual student...
I suppose I could vouch
for you.
Thanks.
Well, I'd love to
i'd do something like that.
I would, um...
I just, uh...
I don't know
if I can.
Why not?
You need Gabe's permission or something?
I like her, Aaron.
Come on, 9:00 tomorrow
in that building right over there.
I'm gonna meet you
out front.
I'll see you there.
Hello?
Who's there?
Don't tell me it's judgment day already.
I was just getting comfortable.
No, Azazel.
Not yet.
But soon.
Before you know it,
Gabriel's horn
will sound,
and you will be cast
into the fires of Hell for all eternity.
I doubt you'll find that
environment any more hospitable.
Well, at least it will be
a change of scenery.
What...
is this language
we're speaking?
It's called English.
It's been very popular
on Earth
for quite some time.
How long have
I been here?
5,000 years.
Give or take a century.
I'm curious.
Did you think more time had passed,
or less?
What do you want?
To give you...
what you desire most.
You'd give me my freedom?
If you agree to help me.
It is the time
of the Redeemer, Azazel.
As the prophecy
has foretold,
a Nephilim has been born
with the power to return fallen angels to Heaven.
And I need you...
to help him fulfill his destiny.
So...
do we have an agreement?
We most certainly do.
How are you, Gadreel?
How did you get out?
Don't concern yourself
with such things.
You know, you got to learn
how to blend in.
That's how I stayed alive for so long.
Fine, but there's something
I should rather do first.
I'll bet there is.
But you waited 5,000 years.
You can wait
a few more hours.
Can you?
Thousands have taken to the streets
in protests of the arrests of
anti-Russian activists this morning.
Cars were set on fire
and storefronts smashed,
as an angry mob stormed the Russian embassy
in the capital of Rome.
So who is
this woman, anyway?
Over in the Middle East
oil fires were still burning...
Ariel took over
the underground
after the death
of Samchial last year.
She's the one who has been giving me
the locations of those you have redeemed.
She's in charge
of the Fallen?
Yes.
Aaron.
It is so good
to finally meet you.
God, I feel like I already know you.
Camael's told me so much about you.
He did not tell me how good-looking
you were, though.
You didn't tell me how cute he was.
I'm not exactly his type.
What?
It's just... Usually when I'm
around the Fallen, I get this...
weird feeling.
Um, it's how I know
they need redemption.
I don't feel that need
from you.
You're picking up
on their desire
for forgiveness,
their beliefs
that they're ready.
You know, and whether they're worthy
of redemption or not is a whole other story.
But you're not picking it up from me,
because it's not my time yet.
I'll be the last Fallen
you'll redeem, Aaron.
Comes with the gig.
Welcome.
There's a bedroom for you upstairs.
Come on, Gabe,
The Nephilim
has escaped us again.
You have disgraced us
with your incompetence.
You're the mightiest angels
on Heaven and Earth.
And you can't dispose
of one simple half-breed.
The Nephilim we could handle.
It's Camael that's the problem.
Mazarin, the energy signature
that drew us here,
there's something different
about it.
What if the traitor
is right?
What is this Nephilim he's been dragging
all over the country really is the Redeemer?
There is no Reedemer,
Sachael.
It is the Powers' mission
to eradicate all of the Nephilim.
This one is no different
from the rest.
Now, when we catch up
with the little bastard,
and we will,
the prophecy will become
a dead issue.
You've been killing a lot
of your old friends lately.
I take no pleasure in it.
Yeah, that's what you used to say
when you used to kill us Fallen.
It was true then, as well.
So how's he doing?
He's struggling.
His angelic and human desires
are at constant odds.
Yeah, well...
all Nephilim are like that the first few years.
It'll get better.
It's getting worse.
Maybe you're just
working him too hard.
You're new here,
ain'tcha?
Er... Yeah.
Then he went out back
with Gina for, like, 15 minutes.
Gina?
The barmaid.
He doesn't
even know her name.
Damn, man.
You're all right.
What's with the threads,
though?
Threads?
Oh, you mean my clothes.
I like the way you talk.
- The way I what?
So, you're
a gambling man, huh?
You up for a game?
So how does one
play this game?
Hold your horses, chief.
We only play for money.
I have neither money
nor horses.
- But I'll wager you a night with Gina...
- We could do that.
for your mode
of transportation.
My bike?
Okay, here.
I smell a fight.
You better come through
once you lose.
Teach him
some manners, buddy!
It's goin' down.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute now!
You don't mean
my bike, man!
We had a deal,
didn't we...
man?
You want my bike?
Come take it.
Bad dreams again?
You ever have nightmares?
Sometimes.
You know how to stop them?
All you have to do is wake up.
Morning.
Good morning.
I've never seen
him sleep before.
He's not sleeping.
He's healing.
Angelfire wounds
can be bad news.
In time,
even a little nick
would have killed him.
Don't worry.
By tonight,
he'll be good as new.
Mmm, I love waffles.
Thanks.
I haven't had a...
real breakfast
in what seems like forever.
You miss
your parents, huh?
I just haven't seen them
in a really long time.
I wish there was
a way I could...
get a hold of them
and just
tell them that
I'm okay, you know?
I know.
But it's safer
for them this way.
Do you know who
my real father
and mother are?
The Fallen don't
exactly advertise it
when one of them
becomes a daddy.
It's a good way
to get the Powers
all over your ass.
Yeah.
Camael pretty much
said the same thing.
Yeah.
Hey, um...
Do you think it would
be all right if I...
went by the, uh,
college
and, uh,
just checked out
a couple of the classes?
Well, you're a big boy.
You don't need
my permission.
It's just that Camael
never lets me
go anywhere
or do anything.
You're in Ariel's house now.
And I say you can do
whatever you want.
Just no angel stuff.
Angels.
Warring amongst themselves
because of mankind.
Lucifer's ambition
sprang from envy
that angels
were no longer God's
favorite creation.
At the beginning
of Milton's epic,
he has suffered
a crushing defeat.
Lucifer and his followers
had been banished
from Heaven forever.
We see him struggling
with self-doubt.
We see he has hopes
and fears,
just like us.
We identify with him.
Yes?
So, the devil...
he's a good guy?
Well...
he's certainly sympathetic.
Lucifer sees himself
as a victim.
And it's fair to question
whether the Rebellion
was his design,
or pre-ordained destiny.
Wait a second.
Are you saying that Lucifer was
created to rebel?
Is that so hard to believe?
What is good without evil?
Does doing the right thing
have any meaning
if there is
no alternative?
But that doesn't make
any sense.
Even if Lucifer
was destined to become
the epitome of evil,
he made the choice
to follow that path.
o/~ It's never gonna be o/~
o/~ Normal o/~
o/~ You and me o/~
o/~ What you're signing up for
is a storm at sea o/~
You have no idea
how much I miss you,
Azazel.
I'm so glad
you got back.
I know.
Well, gotta go.
What do you mean,
you gotta go?
- You just got here.
- Yep.
I've got something
I need to take care of.
What things?
The Redeemer's arrived.
Ariel contacted me
a few months ago.
Really?
Where is she?
She lives in this college town
200 miles from here.
Good, then that's
where I'm going.
You know,
your speech has improved,
but your clothes suck.
You need real ones.
Angelic robes aren't
as stylish
as they used to be.
I'm sure I'll find you
something that fits.
Whose are these?
I don't know.
An old boyfriend.
Or a husband, maybe.
You've been locked up
for 5,000 years.
I have my needs.
It's not like fidelity
was ever your strong suit.
Oh, wow, okay.
Thanks for letting me
sit in, though.
That was really cool.
It's not a problem.
- I don't know, I just kind of thought you might like
to sit in on it.
-
Hey, um...
I don't mean to be rude.
Can I just...
Can I catch up with you in,
like, one second?
- Of course.
- Sorry.
Excuse me.
I just wanted to apologize
for talking out of turn
back there.
Not at all.
I admire your passion
on the subject,
Mr. Corbett.
- Correct?
- Yes. Yes.
Um, and thank you
for letting me sit in
on your class, Dr. Grasic.
So...
are you a religious zealot,
or just a die-hard
Milton fan?
Uh, neither.
Um, I've actually
- never read Paradise Lost.
- Shame on you.
Anyway, I was thinking about
what you said about Lucifer
and his destiny,
and it goes against...
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I have
no time.
But I spend
most of my evenings
at the library.
If you'd like to come by,
I'd be happy to continue
our discussion.
Hi.
Come here.
- How was work?
- It was great.
I didn't even have
to use my healing magic
on anyone today.
You use your healing magic
on the job?
- Aren't you worried about the Powers?
- Oh, I'm always worried about the Powers.
But if I have a chance
at saving a life, to me it's worth it.
Besides,
I got a few tricks
up my sleeve.
It's a protective rune.
It's not strong enough
to mask a redemption
but
it's good for
a little interference.
You know, in a pinch.
Keep it.
I've got dozens of them.
Thanks.
Do you think I'm doing
the right thing?
What do you mean?
By redeeming the Fallen?
I don't know.
What do you think?
Camael's always drilled it
into my head
that it's my destiny.
But just because
I'm meant to do something,
does that
make it
the right thing to do?
What if the Earth...
I don't know,
needs angels?
And I'm just...
taking them away?
Aaron...
this is your mission.
Now, whether
it's right or wrong
is for you to decide.
And I think,
until you know,
you should keep your gift
to yourself.
Because what you're doing
is far too important.
You have to believe
in it.
That's my two cents.
See your I.D.?
- Can you hold these?
- Yeah.
There you go.
- You got that?
- Yeah.
- You're 21?
- No, but my sister is.
One for you. Yep.
There you go.
Okay.
You guys ready?
Yeah!
Okay, let's do this!
Woo!
Yep!
Cheers.
Yo, aren't you drinking?
I'm not really much
of a drinker.
He's the designated driver.
Didn't you guys
walk here?
Yeah.
Don't you guys
have classes
in the morning?
Does that make
any difference? Class?
Class?
You guys...
Take one drink!
It's right there!
Come on!
One shot won't hurt you.
Man up.
You can't waste
alcohol, man. Man up.
Drink it.
Do it! Woo!
Leave it.
Yeah!
Just one shot!
He's got it
right there.
One shot. One shot.
Ooh, you're not
gonna puke, are you?
Okay, we're gonna
grab some air.
Ten bucks says
we don't see
either one of them
again tonight.
So, how was
your first day
of college?
It was great.
Thanks.
- Chloe.
- What is it?
Just...
You don't want
to get involved with me.
Why not?
What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
- Then is something wrong with me?
'Cause I've been
practically throwing
myself at you all day.
Aaron!
No!
Wait, dude. Chill.
We were just
messing around.
Chloe.
o/~ Help o/~
o/~ I have done it o/~
o/~ Again o/~
o/~ I have been here o/~
o/~ Many times before o/~
o/~ Hurt myself again o/~
o/~ Today o/~
o/~ And the worst part is o/~
o/~ There's no one else
to blame o/
o/~ Be my friend o/~
o/~ Hold me o/~
o/~ Wrap me up o/~
o/~ Unfold me o/~
o/~ I am small o/~
o/~ And needy o/~
o/~ Warm me up o/~
Oh, Mr. Corbett.
- I wasn't sure
you'd still be here.
- The library doesn't close
until midnight.
The staff always
has to chase me out.
Yeah.
What can you tell me
about the Nephilim?
It's widely accepted
that the Nephilim
were killed
in the Great Flood.
They were powerful beings,
very often portrayed
as giants.
Monsters.
Have you ever...
heard of a Nephilim
called the Redeemer?
I have.
I'm surprised that
you know of him, though.
It's quite
an obscure prophecy.
Very controversial.
The Redeemer was a vehicle
for forgiveness.
He or she has the power
to pardon anyone
of any sin,
no matter how great.
But there are clues
to something else
in the prophecy,
hints that he may serve
another, darker purpose.
What purpose?
We don't know.
All we know is
that for every claim
that praises his arrival,
there is another
that speaks of it
in terror.
We are not even sure
if he is a force of good...
or evil.
Aaron.
Ariel.
How you feeling?
Much better. Thank you.
I'm glad you're up.
I got called in to work,
and somebody's
gotta walk Gabriel.
Oh, and I promised him
some ice cream.
Where's Aaron?
He's hanging with
his friends from college.
His friends?
Mm-hmm.
How long have I been out?
Don't worry.
He's fine.
You can't protect him
all the time, you know?
Yes, I can.
I must.
- He's an irresponsible child. And that temper will get someone...
- He's 19,
he's a good kid,
and he needs some normalcy
in his life.
You gotta remember,
he's human.
Half human.
That's more than you are.
Who are you to talk?
The Nephilim are monsters.
Why?
What did they do?
What is that?
It's nothing.
Where did you get it?
My friend gave it to me.
What are you doing?
I know what this is.
Protective rune
used to hide yourself.
To hide yourself?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You hide yourself
from angels.
Yes.
It all makes sense now.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
You never know
who might be listening.
But I know what you are.
And I'm just like you.
We are brothers, Aaron.
Brothers in the Order.
The Order?
Yeah.
I know why you're here.
You do?
Yes.
We both know that
the angels are real.
We know that
they walk among us.
Tell me...
would you like to see one?
Yes?
All this
on a teacher's salary?
My family
has a long history
of dealing
in ancient artifacts.
What I'm about
to show you,
you can never
breathe a word about,
for your own safety.
You have nothing
to fear from me.
But as I'm sure
you know,
some of our members
are overly cautious.
Do I have your word?
Come.
There she is.
Child?
We have a guest.
Show us your wings.
Your beautiful wings.
Breathtaking...isn't it?
Now turn around.
Show us your pretty face.
Isn't she beautiful?
Vilma!
How do you know her name?
That's impossible... what is she doing here?
She's quite comfortable here.
I've taken excellent care.
She's a prisoner.
She's the only living Nephilim.
Would you rather her
be strapped to a table in a laboratory somewhere?
I'm taking her out of here.
No.
You'll do no such thing
It's time for you to leave my house.
Right now.
Lukas...
God!
Those markings.
Wipe away those runes.
I don't want to.
Do it.
Do it now!
You are... the Redeemer.
Wipe away those runes.
Do it!
Vilma.
It's me.
Vilma, it's Aaron.
We're going to get out of here.
It's okay.
You're safe now.
I promise.
You all right?
Yeah.
Vilma, say something, please.
You're like me.
How is that possible?
I don't know.
I don't know what the hell's going on.
Aaron!
Camael. It's okay.
This is Camael.
He's my friend.
Hey! I rember you.
This girl is Nephilim.
Where did she come from?
It's a long story.
You lost control.
The Powers are coming.
You must leave now.
No. I'm going to stay,
and I'm going to fight.
If you don't leave now,
they will kill all of us.
And if I do, they'll kill you?
I have pledged to lay down my life for you.
That is what I intend to do.
What is going on?
Aaron, you must protect
this child, as you once
need my help.
Run!
Take care of the traitor.
I'm going after the Nephilim.
Well, I'll be damned.
Two for the price of one.
It must be my lucky day.
I got to admit, kid.
You gave us a run for our money.
But this is how it ends.
Leave the children alone, Nathaniel.
Azazel.
Don't you have some puppies to go kick or something?
This can't be you.
This isn't real.
Oh, it's real.
What could I possibly do to convince you?
Oh. Aren't I?
You guys all right?
What, are you scared of me?
I just saved your asses.
Who are you?
I'm Azazel.
Glad to meet you.
Are you one of the Fallen?
I'm Azazel.
You never heard of me?
Yeah, I'm one of the Fallen.
I'm the Fallen.
Your girl looks a little
freaked out, man.
Yeah, well,
it's been a rough night.
Yeah, well you know what?
It's only going to get worse.
We need to get off these streets,
go underground. Let's go.
Let's go! They can smell you.
They can feel you. Come on.
We got to go.
Aaron. He just killed that man.
Vilma, I know what you're
going through right now.
But he's one of the Fallen.
He's on our side.
On our side?
Whose side are we on?
Are we the good guys
or the bad guys?
If we survive this night, I promise you
I will tell you everything I know.
But right now,
we've got to go.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Hey, could I ask
you something?
How did you end up
in that nutjob's attic?
Well, it all started
on my 18th birthday.
Strange things started
happening to me.
I was getting these headaches,
and I was hearing voices.
And then...
And the angels came.
They're so majestic
at first, you know.
So beautiful.
Real angels from Heaven.
Then they attacked.
They killed my aunt.
Burned down the house.
Somehow, I got away.
The angels who did that
to you,
they're calledthe Powers.
They are the same angels
that are chasing us right now.
I just ran.
Hid in the woods.
I thought I was dead,
for sure.
I stopped this man in the woods
and asked him for help, but...
he pulled out a gun
and shot me with a tranquilizer.
Lukas didn't hurt me or
anything, though, he, uh...
He was kind.
You probably won't understand.
It's not like I had anywhere else to go.
Until you came.
So, thanks for coming
to my rescue.
Maybe you can tell me now why angels
are trying to kill us?
What did we do?
It's because we were
born Nephilim.
They're on a mission from
the Creator to cleanse
the Earth of...
our kind.
We're abominations.
Abominations.
Yeah, you're freaks. It sucks.
Can we all stop feeling sorry for ourselves now?
We're alive,
which is more than can
be said for Nathaniel.
Hey, listen. Um...
I want to thank you
for what you did back there.
If you hadn't shown up,
we might have been...
Hey.
You're the Redeemer.
What kind of Fallen would I be
if I didn't look out for you?
Hey, we got to find out
what happened to Camael.
Camael? Ah, I wouldn't
worry about him.
What do you mean?
Camael's dead.
I can't believe
What is the big deal?
So Camael's troops finally turned on him.
That's a good thing.
He wasn't with the Powers anymore.
He...
He's been protecting me,
ever since I turned.
He was my friend.
Your friend?
We are talking about
the same Camael, right?
Tall, bald,
no sense of humor?
This is all my fault.
No, Aaron,
you were trying
to help me.
That's what Camael
would've wanted.
I didn't have to
do it like that.
I lost control.
And I don't know
what we're going
to do now.
Look, I've got an idea.
Why don't we get
out of town?
Lay low for a while.
Somewhere where
the Powers won't find us.
Where is that?
Has anyone ever told you
about the Light Bringer?
It's about time
you met him.
Hey!
Don't move!
Stay right there!
Get back here!
Come back here and get down on your knees!
Give me your wallet.
Your wallet! All right.
Hurry up!
All right!
And your watch.
Your watch, too!
Hurry!
Come on!
It's not nice
to steal from people.
Hey.
What is wrong with you?
It's kinda harsh, isn't it?
I'm not a guardian angel.
I'm an avenging angel.
This is who I am.
The world needs both.
Got us a car.
Wanna drive?
We're not seriously going
off with this guy, are we?
He can protect us.
We need him.
We need somebody.
Any day now.
Just hold on.
What is the Light Bringer?
Not what. Who.
He's a fallen angel,
just like me.
And his name
is the Light Bringer?
Is your name the Redeemer?
Don't be an idiot.
He doesn't have a name
in a traditional sense.
We call him "the Light Bringer"
because that's what he does.
He brings us light.
He's an oracle. He's a seer.
Are you sure
that he can help us?
He can't help me,
but he can help you.
Remember that prophecY about you?
The one that foretold your coming?
He wrote it.
You'll find that
quite impossible, traitor.
Aaron?
I suspect we'll have him
or his remains within the hour.
He can't last long
without your protection.
Mazarin.
Aaron Corbett is the Redeemer.
The prophecy is real.
No, Camael.
It's a lie.
I do hope Nathaniel
brings the boy back alive.
I'd love to make you watch
while I slit his throat
so that when you die,
you'll know for certain
that your sacrifice was for nothing.
Mazarin.
This is not what
the Powers stand for.
You dare tell me
the Powers' mission?
Are you under the misconception
that you're still one of us?
You turned your back on us, Camael.
You turned your back on the Creator.
And you'll pay
for your sins, traitor.
What I want to know is...
what in the hell were you thinking
showing her to anyone?
But he was Nephilim.
You didn't know that
when you brought him
up here, did you?
I thought
he was one of us.
Oh, right.
Of course.
Because the Order is just teeming
with teenage members, isn't it?
Please, put that down.
It's 4th century.
Really?
It's exquisite.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Was that precious to you?
What about this?
Haven't I lost
enough tonight?
It's not about what you've lost,
Dr. Grasic.
You've lost nothing.
We let you keep her.
She was never yours.He's the Redeemer!
What?
Yes.
The boy who freed her...
he has the markings
of the Redeemer.
Start from the beginning.
Is that look in your eye
meant to intimidate me?
Now, I admit there was a time
when it might have,
but those days are over,
old friend.
Mazarin.
What is it, Sachael?
It's Nathaniel.
He's not coming back.
He's dead.
That half-breed
killed Nathaniel?
Somebody did.
Where is he now, Camael?
Tell me.
You know,
over the millennia
we served together,
many of the Fallen
said they would never
give up their children.
But they always did,
thanks to us.
No, thanks to you.
Where is the Nephilim?
So who is this
Jesus character anyway?
Seriously, I've been
seeing his name everywhere.
Well, um, a lot of people
think that he was the son of God.
What's so funny?
The Creator had a kid.
Well, do as I say,
not as I do, eh?
Did you seriously
not know that?
Been out of the picture
for a while.
How so?
Well, you probably heard
about what happened
in the old days.
About how the Creator
flooded the planet
because we contaminated
his precious Earth
with half-breeds like you.
A bit of an overreaction,
if you ask me.
But, hey, mysterious ways
and all that.
Wait. You mean,
like, Noah's Ark?
That flood?
Yeah, that's right.
Noah.
That guy could
really throw it down,
let me tell you.
Anyways.
Afterwards, your buddy Camael
and a few other half-wits
from the Powers
decided they were going
to come down and tell us
things had to change.
I guess to prove
a point,
they decided to make
an example of someone.
I fought.
Killed one of them.
Slashed this son of a bitch
Mazarin across the face.
It was beautiful.
But in the end,
they got me.
Took me deep underground,
chained me up,
and left me for 5,000 years.
So you've been a prisoner, too.
Like me.
Yeah.
Six months
in a luxury suite...
just like being chained
to a stone slab
for five millennia.
Just like it.
Don't talk to her
like that.
Or what?
I'm just messin'
with you, kid.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I'm sure it must've been
very difficult for you.
I smell food.
What about food?
Who wants to eat?
Want to stop for a bite?
Well, we're kind of
on the run right now.
You gotta eat.
I'm hungry. Who's hungry?
Let's vote.
Me! I'm hungry!
Me, too.
I'm starving.
Looks like you lose, chief.
All right, order up.
Oh... my... God.
What are these things
called again?
What?
French fries?
French fries.
I gotta remember that.
Here, try 'em with ketchup.
This is the best food
I've ever had
in the history of ever!
Hey, we get it.
You like French fries.
This is the first meal
I've had in a long time.
So if you don't mind,
I'm gonna enjoy it.
All right?
And lighten up...
Redeemer.
Why does he keep
calling you that?
Redeemer?
'Cause that's what he is.
He sends us Fallen
back to Heaven.
Show her your arms.
The names of the Redeemed.
These are all angels?
And you send them
back to Heaven?
How?
I don't know.
Um... When I'm around them,
I get this, um...
this weird feeling.
It's hard to explain, really.
Um...
I kinda...
open myself up to them.
And then I usually...
take their hand and, uh...
this weird energy
passes between us.
And then they're gone.
Wow. Um...
Do it to him.
What?
No, you keep that voodoo to yourself.
Don't you want
to go to Heaven?
Hell, no.
If I liked it,
I wouldn't have rebelled
in the first place,
would I?
Yeah, well, I'm not
really doing it anymore.
Not right now.
Why not?
There's just a lot I...
I still don't understand about it.
Plus, I'm not even sure
if I'm doing the right thing.
Aaron, how can sending angels
back to Heaven be wrong?
I don't know.
But I've been having these...
these weird dreams lately
about the end
of the world...
and I'm the cause of it.
Damn, kid, you're a mess,
ain't you?
Look at me.
When we get
to the Light Bringer,
I promise you'll understand
yourself and your destiny
a hell of a lot better.
More coffee?
Hello, sweetheart.
What's your name?
Suzie.
That's such a pretty name.
Saw you looking
at me earlier, Suzie.
No, no. Don't be embarrassed.
Sometimes I can't stop looking at me.
Let me ask you
a question, Suzie.
Is there anywhere near here
where you and I
could go, um...
talk?
I'm going on a break.
Yeah, all right.
Catch you losers later.
I've told you
everything I know.
Hawkins.
No. No teams.
I hunt alone.
What do you want me
to do about the girl?
Understood.
Are you going to get
my Vilma back?
Go on.
I don't care.
I don't want to live
without her anyway.
Do you believe
that things happen
for a reason?
You mean, like fate?
There's really
no other explanation
for all this, is there?
You and me?
I'm just...
happy to see you again.
Everything makes
so much sense now.
The day you left,
people said you'd gone crazy
- and burned your house down.
- People said that?
About me?
You ever think
about going home?
Yeah.
All the time.
It's been a year now
and I just...
I feel like I keep getting
further and further away.
You know?
At least you have a family to go back to.
Someday.
I wonder if this Light Bringer
knows anything about me.
You know, maybe...
maybe I have a prophecy, too.
Don't jinx yourself.
Still got it.
It's almost too easy,
isn't it?
Mortal wenches.
God bless 'em.
You know, you really
shouldn't say that stuff.
Why?
Because it's derogatory
towards women.
No, but I'm saying that
I like that they're easy.
Weird.
You kids ready to go?
Come on, Gabe.
I'm riding in back
with Azazel.
What is it?
Nothing to worry
your pretty little head over.
Let's go.
The aerospace manufacturer
pleaded guilty to two counts
of violating the Federal
Clean Water Act,
admitting dumping
industrial discharge
into the river.
In addition to being placed
on probation for five years,
the company agreed to pay
$1 million in fines
and to contribute
another $11 million
for environmental
improvement projects.
Good God,
what is happening
to this place?
Human beings used to care
about the Earth, you know?
They used to appreciate
just how good they had it.
Guess a lot has changed
in 5,000 years.
Will this Light Bringer
know who my father is?
You sure that's something
you want to find out?
Most Nephilim don't
want anything to do
with their fathers.
Human women can't
survive the births.
At first, we were like,
whoops, you know?
But it didn't take us long
to figure out that, you know,
getting one pregnant
was like handing down
a death sentence.
So they all die?
All our mothers?
Every one of 'em.
Your old man still sound
like someone you wanna
go fishing with?
Play catch?
I just want to know
who he is.
We're being followed.
What?
By who?
I don't know.
Pull over.
Let me deal with it.
It's time, traitor.
Time for you to say good-bye
to something you hold dear.
Perhaps your eyes.
No. There's a certain
nobility in blindness.
I could cut out your tongue,
but then once you're broken,
you wouldn't
be able to tell me
what I want to know.
Sachael.
I want to see his wings.
Mazarin, no.
You can't...
That wasn't a request.
Just do it.
Mazarin.
You are lost.
You do not serve
the Creator.
Mazarin.
You are the one who's lost.
And as for the Creator...
what I do now,
I do in his name.
And now, you take
your true place
amongst the Fallen.
Looking for something?
Anane.
I picked up your scent
just outside of town,
and I've been following you
ever since.
How did you escape?
I am so sick of everybody
asking me that question.
Maybe I didn't escape.
Maybe the Creator decided
I was such a perfect specimen
he'd set me free.
Did he?
That's not the point.
What do you want?
I want to know
if I'm worthy
of redemption.
I can tell that
you want it really bad.
But I'm sorry,
I'm not doing that right now.
I see.
It's nothing personal, okay?
I just...
I don't know
how much time
I have left.
Nathaniel did this to me.
He was looking for you.
It's too late for me
to be healed.
The wound is too old,
too deep.
It's killing me.
You know what happens
to angels when they die
without redemption?
We don't have souls.
Not like you do.
There's...
There's no Heaven for us.
No Hell.
Just...
Just nothingness.
Forever.
And that scares me
more than anything.
Yeah, well,
tough luck, Anane.
Welcome to the yawning
abyss of oblivion.
Aaron.
You have to help him.
Please?
I want to.
I really do.
It's just that...
Ariel told me not to
until I know
it's the right thing.
He wants to go back to Heaven
and you can do that for him.
How can you refuse?
Look in your heart.
You know it's right.
Wait a second.
You're not actually
considering this, are you?
With that amount of energy,
you're just going to call
the Powers right to us.
I know that.
But Vilma's right.
I can't just...
let him die.
Aaron, don't.
You ready?
Yeah.
Stay with the traitor.
Sachael.
You.
I need your help.
Fantastic!
You are a genius
of epic proportions,
my friend.
That was great. Yeah.
'Cause, uh...
we got away
and it was plain sailing
the whole time.
But now it's brilliant
because they know
exactly where we are.
I'm really proud of you.
Well done.
Look, just shut up,
all right?
Hey, I'm trying
to look out for you.
Trying to keep you alive.
The rest of the Fallen
will be plenty pissed with me
if you died on my watch.
I'm just saying...
I'm not afraid
of the Powers.
You?
I'm not afraid of anything.
Well, that's good.
Because here they come.
I'm gonna put
an end to this.
I'm not running
from them anymore.
1080p by VISTA