are the man
sam Harris on from Southern California
and
I was raised in a totally secular
homes I'm not not reacting in my
criticism of religion on
reacting against any kind a
fundamentalist upbringing in
I'm but nor was I told
that there was no got it was really not
a a
a subject to conversations on my my
rather strident criticism a religion
is really a product above very recent
events in my case its
September 11th 2001 so it's my my
upbringing isn't so
informative my views
at the moment
well it was two things one just
the and the rather obvious liability
religious certainty was was made
extraordinarily
clear on that day when we were having
people flying planes into our buildings
for explicitly religious reasons I'm
was was also made clear that we were
going to nah I
the religious rationale because of our
own attachment to our own religious
myths the only language we could find is
a culture to comfort ourselves
was to endorse our own cod talk so I i
suddenly saw faith plane both sides the
board
in a in a very dangerous game are we as
a nation
I E N prosecuting our war on terror
which was
obviously necessary thing to do though
calling it a war on terror think it's
rather silly
I'm but would we we were
Arkansas in ourselves with our own
religious certainties
you know he made a very much in the
language of Christian
fundamentalism I have that the president
you comes before congress
talks about God not being indifferent to
freedom in fear he
as an atheist I hear that exactly the
way I would hear someone say in
zoos is not a indifferent to freedom
unfair but it is a
on Canali strange an empty utterance
I'm and yet our culture is is
is now program not to notice how strange
an empty it is and it does really
significant work and so we see things
like stem cell research and
I'm other causes
that upon which the the lives and and
happiness have millions of people really
turn I
get subverted by religious thing can
explicitly religious thinking
Wes Malott I'm thinking about and
explore in
spiritual experience in our are
contemplative traditions mostly
in and eastern contacts in Buddhism and
Hinduism but
have also CuZn red much of the
contemplative literature
Christianity and Judaism and Islam I'm
so I've been interested in religion for
at least 20 years
and interested in spiritual experience
and and
have spent a lot of time practicing
meditation and study in with
various meditation masters and Indian
the pollen
spendin months and weeks on on retreat
just practicing meditation I'm very much
the way up
you know monastic wouldn't in in the
Buddhist tradition
I'm so I i'm the concerns over
religious people the ethical and the
and the spiritual concerns are religious
people are something that I
I think I understand I take very
seriously a member I take very seriously
the possibility I love experience in the
world the way Buddha and Jesus another
famous patriarchs a major arts seem to
have experience the world and I
I think we want to actualize that kind
of experience me if it's possible to
love your neighbor as yourself
I'm interested in learning how to do
that I'm
I just on the way to believe anything on
insufficient evidence in order to the
men
for what astonishes me when I read the
newspaper
are watching news is how many problems
are the direct result
what people believe about God me their
days while the New York Times Square
fully half of the stories are
he in a way that Sonic knowledge by the
the the paper
relate to people's religious convictions
I'm it's a mad
you know I mention the Virginia Tech
shooting this was that the role that
religion played in providing a context
for
the shooting was never really discussed
in the media but maybe we just hear that
the mother happened to be you know
devout Christian and
structure child from church to church in
search of exorcism
I'm I just try to see
continually our attention bound up
in these competing in
ideas about God I at best
this is this is often just a waste of
time but it worse
it is just it is manufacturing violence
and and
unnecessary conflict and misuses over
resources
and what's more it is it is very rare
that we acknowledge me now are beginning
to acknowledge the role that Islam is
plain
in in Muslim terrorism
but even that has been very slow
to come minutes but it has been obvious
for many many years long before
September 11th
that a certain style love I love
Muslim infatuation was leading into this
kinda
jihadi behavior I'm where we because a
the respect we accord religious faith
were very slow to
to acknowledge that sits causal role in
in conflict
why I think the biggest challenge as a
matter a discourse and debate
I'm concerning the most frustrating
challenge is
he is what comes from otherwise secular
and even
non believing people who are just
reluctant to admit how much mad work is
being done
because our religion in this world may
be either can't believe that people
really believe this stuff years when a
suicide bomber blows himself up in
in a crowd of children I'm this secular
type of person will imagine that was in
religion
and there was no I hadn't had nothing to
do with a belief in paradise and 72
virgins who believe that if this is
this is a some kind of psychological
aberration or it's a
is caused by economic desperation or our
policies in the region means not
matter love metaphysical believes I'm
I think the the jury is in on this I
mean we know
that that people really do believe these
things they are telling us ad nauseam
they believe these things
and I don't think there's any more
powerful rhetorical device
for emphasis then blow yourself up for
four or fly a plane into a building
these people are really willing to die
I for what they believe
and we know it's not a matter by going
to speak specifically about the Muslim
world from we know it's not a matter of
economics and
and education because you know in this
recent plot in in the UK these are all
doctors who are who are aspiring suicide
bombers me how you know
how much more education did these
doctors need one was a neurosurgeon
you know you if I mean neurosurgeon
suicide bomber and you tell me the
problem is education and economics its
it clearly isn't and I'm
the deeper problem and I think a far
more
sinister problem is that it is possible
to be well-educated so well educated
that you can be a neurosurgeon
and still believe that you can get 72
virgins in paradise and this is made
possible
by the fact that we have allowed a
certain
motive thought religion to thrive in
in a bit in a I'm a cocoon
love this is hereof protection from
criticism is just taboo to criticize
people's religious themes
well that this is a I'm a common
criticism the idea that the atheist is
guilty over up a literal it's really not
scripture
I no better than the reading a
fundamental essence very naive
way of approaching religion and there's
a far more sophisticated and nuanced
view
religion I on offer in the atheists
disregarding that
I'm few problems with his first is
anyone making that argument is is
failing to acknowledge
just how many people really do approach
these texts literally or functionally me
love whether their selective literalist
or literal
all the way down the line there is a the
there are certain passages in these in
Scripture that this cannot be read
figuratively I'm and
people really do live by the lights
above what is literally laid out in
these books so you know the Koran says
hate the infertile and Muslims hate the
infertile because the koran spells it
out
ad nauseam I'm now
it's true that you can
cherry-pick scripture and you can look
for all the good parts you can ignore
where it says in love the case that a
for
a woman is not a virgin on our wedding
night stoned to death on a father's
doorstep you can ignore that and now it
to my knowledge all Jews and Christians
do ignore that in fact that's not true
there some Christians who actually
doing a reconstruction is Christian
dominions Christians in the US who will
say and I think the
the pally for adultery should be death
into their their people who are
have the courage of their convictions
there I'm but most of us
most religious people ignore those
pastors which really can only be you
red literally I'm and say that all they
were only appropriate for the time and
they don't don't apply now and
likewise muslims tried to have the same
reading a passage is that advocate holy
war until these were appropriate to
those
battles that Muhammad was fine but now
we don't have to fight those battles
I'm this is all up a good thing
but which recognize what is what's that
what's happening here people are feeling
pressure from the host love
all too human concerns that have nothing
in principle to do with God
I mean secularism and human rights and
democracy and scientific progress
these have have made certain passages in
scripture
untenable okay so this is coming from
outside religion
and religion is now making a great show
up its sophistication in
kinda grappling with these with these
pressures
I'm but once again this is this is a
example if religion losing the argument
with maternity
example busy you to know the recent
shooting at Virginia Tech
the in the mother of this the shooter I
recognize that there was something wrong
with her son
you know he's suffering from some kind
of mental problem
in the context of her a rather
doctrinaire Christianity she did not
take him to a psychiatrist who took in
from church to church
in search of exorcism generally found a
church that performed an exorcism
maybe if they were there it just picture
this is some I know
it we have a I an atrocity
in the makin we have a date dangerously
mentally ill
college student we have a concerned
mother whose worldview about mental
health is trimmed down through the
the the keyhole
love a kind medieval Christianity
and with have a church willy nilly to
put for his expertise in the performance
an exorcism
I'm it would be a lot better if everyone
involved had a 20 percent review of
mental health
I'm no one is really a
moderate people moderate Christians and
Jews and Muslims
have to look at this situation and say
well there's something wrong here it be
better to go to a psychiatrist
I'm but the problem is you can't show
what's wrong
in terms of Scripture you can show
what's wrong in terms of
I've religion because in terms of
religion
the the mother was right to mean there
is there are demons
and you Jesus cast them out you know me
is it demonic possession is actually a
problem
I'm the only reason why we're we we
don't
take it seriously is because we have a
wider view
up the univers the University that view
the universe did not come to us from
religion came from science
let's just grant the possibility
that there there is a creator guy who's
omniscient who occasionally
authors books I and he's going to give
us a book
I the most useful bookies a loving God
is compassionate God
I'm he's going to give us a guide to
life I
he's got a scribe describes gonna write
it down what's going to be in that book
I just think how good a book
would be if it were authored by an
omniscient
deity me that there is not a single line
in the Bible the Koran
that could not have been authored by a a
first-century I person
I mean there's not there's not one one
reference to anything
held their older their pages and pages
about how to sacrifice animals
and keep slaves and who did kill and why
I'm there's nothing about I
electricity is nothing about DNA there's
nothing about how do infectious disease
the principles a
infectious disease I'm there there's
there's nothing particularly useful and
there's a lot of
Iron Age barbarism in there and
superstition I
this does not mean this is not a
candidate book and I can go into a
to any Barnes and Noble blindfolded
and pull a book off the shelf which is
going to have more
relevance more wisdom
I for the 21st century the Bible the
Koran
its Riz really not an exaggeration is is
he every one of our specific sciences
has superseded and surpassed the wisdom
a scripture from
from cosmology to psychology and
economics
we know more about ourselves than anyone
right in the Bible the Koran did and
that is a a distinctly inconvenient fact
for the the for anyone what who want him
to believe
that this book was was dictated by the
creator the man
well the there are many problems with
this idea that
me personal that that's unfolds the
viable
thesis minute then their infinite
numbers upon also viable
PC's that you're not tempted to believe
and we could believe that this is
were in the matrix and you know that
that
you go down that path and there's a lot
that could be asserted
by people who are sure we're in the
matrix and where you know some alien
civilizations simulating us on I'm
their hard drive I'm I
one problem is that we have many
holy books authored by the created
universe and they're in conflict you
know they're not yet
the New Testament makes it perfectly
clear that Jesus is the Son of God
really the Son of God and you have to
believe this
otherwise your gonna spend eternity in
hell the koran
says twice the Jesus was not the Son of
God and anyone who believes he is the
son of God
will spend eternity how me this is this
offers as much room for compromise
as a coin toss so so let's say let's say
we just knew the one of those claims
were
was right you know we have a unit we now
it's we've we've
we've eliminated all the other
possibilities we're living in this
challenging universe where God has given
us the highly imperfect book
and me and asked us to grapple with it
but now have the biblical claim
the New Testament claim to divinity of
Jesus and and it did
necessity believe in unit and the
Khurana claim that belief into Jesus
divinity
leads to damnation which is more likely
that the one of those is right
and the other is wrong or that we have
these competing tribes who were
with toy lean in the context love just
abysmal ignorance about the the world
and
and the you know the the birth of the
cosmos and the and
the destiny of any individual soul after
death I
you know I would put my lot in with a
wider view the circumstance but even if
we
granted your premise that no no there's
a good reason to believe the one of his
books perfect
we're still with a cake or entire
situation we don't know whether to be a
Christian or Muslim
I'm and we're noticing the people are
are
choosing basically on that on the basis
that accidents have birth
you just accidentally born in
Afghanistan and yours you choose to be a
Muslim
I'm and likewise with Christianity
elsewhere
a it is a it's a very strange sorta
loving God who would have created the
circumstance that were by mere accident
of birth
you are raised to believe that a certain
book was
was and ran was the rightly raised to
believe that this book was
you know the perfect book but if you
happen to be born in China you know you
go for centuries without hearing
about this it's a it's a a stray a
for for an obvious reasons they totally
provincial and
and implausible scenario and yet
it's the scenario that most people
believe in the twenty-first themes
why do have existential worries and I'm
I like
I think everybody else's I am
concerned about death you know it's it's
you know death is
in some ways unacceptable it's just
astonishing fact
a Barbie here that we that we die but I
think worse than that is that if we if
we live long in a
we lose everyone we love in this world I
mean to people die and disappear
and we're we're left with this stark
mystery I
visions sheer not knowing love what
happened to them
and into this void religion comes
rushing with a very consoling story same
nothing happened to them they're in a
better place and you're gonna meet up
with them
after you die you can get everything you
want after you die death is an illusion
I'm there's no question and that if you
could believe it that would pay
emotional dividends min is not there's
no other story you can tell
somebody who's just lost her daughter to
cancer say
to make her feel good you know if you is
kit is consoling to believe that
the daughter was just taken up with
Jesus and everyone's gonna bring
be reunited in a few short years I'm
there's no
replacement for that doesn't need to be
replacement for that
I think we have to be we have to just
witnessed the cost of that
me that there are many obvious cost that
way of thinking I'm
one is we just don't teach people how to
grieve
you know that religion is it going to
the antithesis of teaching
your children how to grieve do you tell
your child that been your grandma's in
heaven
and there's nothing to be sad about I'm
that's religion it would be better to to
equip your child for the reality of this
life which is
you know we death is death is a fact
and we don't know what happens after
death and I'm not pretending to know
that you get a dial tone after death I
don't know what happens after
that the physical brain dies I don't
know what the relationship between
consciousness and the physical world
is I'm I don't think anyone does know
now I think they're there many reasons
to be doubtful
love naive conceptions about the soul
when about this idea that you could
just migrate to a a better place after
death
but I simply don't know
about what I don't know when I believe
about
death I'm and I don't think it's
necessary to know
in order to live I as sane leeanne
ethically and happily
as possible I don't think you get I'm
you don't get anything worth getting
by for tendon to know things you know
the names
hear what I think that there's this myth
that unless you think
one of your books was dictated by the
creator the universe and
and there he told you what could what
good and evil are
you'll just have no basis for morality
you you need
religion in some sense to have a a
generalizable
morality without religion is no way to
say the Nazis were really wrong
to to do what they do believe what they
believe I'm
I think that's clearly untrue I think we
have a some very serviceable intuitions
about
about what good and evil are and what is
I'm
what constitutes an ethical life and we
converge on those intuitions me with the
every culture I'm agrees that that
cruelty is wrong
is the taking pleasure in the suffering
of others is wrong within the context I
love you are in Group I mean that the
many cultures think it's good to take
pleasure in the in the suffering of
people
who are not part of your tribe I'm but
in terms of
you who you're going to I'm
it made into your moral sphere
we have some very serviceable intuitions
about how we treat the people we accept
inner sphere
and the challenge for maternity the
challenge civilization
is to it to extend the spear our moral
community to include the entire species
and
even other species so that we really we
really don't have these
these us and them boundaries that we
have an
r us and them boundaries are are really
propped up by
dogmatism their profit by nationalism
the trip propped up by racism in as many
ways to divide your world
dogmatically but the most insidious
us and them boundary for from my point
of view is religion I mean it really is
it religion
posits a transcendental object between
you
and this other person not only are you
different because her skin color are
your political persuasion or because you
speak a different language you were
different for all time
free what what you believe about God and
what he believes about God
are so opposed that
that energy it's going to require
eternity to
you know an eternity of punishment in
his case to work out that difference
I'm so I think it's a very I'm
I think are more a you to this question
rallies
is an important one to to focus on
because many people are attached to
religion
not because they're convinced that that
the metaphysics make sense but because
they
the to see no other alternative to I'm
teaching kids you know right and wrong I
think there's
you the few obvious things to point out
one is that you we will clearly don't
get on around the outer bar
holy books because we go into the holy
books they are bursting with cruelty
me the Old Testament the New Testament
the koran
these are I'm profoundly
cruel and morally ambiguous books at
best
me the you know the Ten Commandments I
the first four commanders have nothing
to do with morale that have to do with
with
theological offenses you know don't take
any other gods before me don't a guy's
name in vain or even images
excedrin or on the Sabbath what he's
supposed to do when people break those
commandments
it was a kill them and this is
unbelievably immoral and yet
when we're we're not doing that now not
because
the the book itself is so wise me to
take away
more relevant example slavery
miss labor is clearly endorsed in the
Bible's endorsing the Old Testament is
endorsed in the New Testament
we all agree that slavery is wrong we
we conquer that ground morally
for some very hard-fought conversations
and
also wars I'm religion was a very little
help
in that made their worries this true did
abolitionists were cherry-picking
scripture trying to find
ways to to justify their project
but their project wasn't coming from
Scripture because scripture is clear
it supports slavery there's there's no
the evil slavery is not recognized in
the Bible and it is
it is certainly not repudiated in the
Bible I'm
and so the this label to the south were
on the women's side at that theological
argument and
and it the religion was an impediment to
making that
that moral progress I'm again the back
even if it were not an impediment even
if it were extremely useful
that would not be a reason to believe
that any of our books were
dictated by a mission theme
I'm not make any strong claims about
where science is going I think it's is
certainly reasonable to expect that we
will understand our experience
much better than we do at the level of
the brain and there may there may be
some real impediments to that
but I'm it could also be true that the
sky's the limit I mean we could really
understand it in a very precise way
in such a way as to to allow us to to
alter our experience in in you this fine
grained ways we won
who knows what what awaits us there but
I know we're not gonna get there
if we I'm don't have an honest
conversation about the roots of human
experience
this whole idea secular fundamentalism
were atheists dogmatism this is really a
a play on words that there's nothing
that you have to accept
are as dogma there's nothing you have to
accept an insufficient evidence
in order to reject the biblical God or
in order to reject the idea that the
Koran on the bible's
is is the perfect word of God I'm
there's no dog by the UN I have accepted
on insufficient evidence in order to
reject Zeus and Poseidon the thousands
of dead guys that live
buried in that's in that mass grave way
home ology
me these are these are is God's were in
good standing
among generations of our ancestors and
for a variety of historical reasons here
most media center
%uh monotheism they put your now in
disrepute but
they have the same a piston logical
stature as the God of Abraham
missus not like it's not like there's so
much data for the God of Abraham in
there's no data for Poseidon they're
both without data
I'm and it's an accident of history that
we are not worshipping the side and then
when trying to constrain our
I'm in america time law
as you know in deference to the whims of
that mean I got off the ocean
there may be a there's a value in
storytelling there's a value in
and certainly in art and literature and
and I think there's a
specifically a value in in narrative
and I'm there may be a value in
taking on certain mythical propositions
as though they
as s kinda schema through which to look
at your life into
Tina take Joseph Campbell's story the
net you know the hero's journey and to
think if you're
self in those terms and to look at what
I'm
features up your your life in psychology
that
Springs interview I'm but
I think we have to be very careful up
about making claims to knowledge about
the world
me take something like you know tarot
card reading you some 10
puts the cars down in front view I and
they
they to turn up whatever it is the 30
rods whatever work tarot card is and
they say well this you know this
suggests to me that I'm
you're dealing with issues honesty and
he have you been dishonest with anyone
in your life
I'm now the two ways to approach the
situation I i
you know I think tarot card reading is
totally bogus as a metaphysical
instrument I don't think the
the card is is is doing anything
important there
except it is causing you to ask a
question about your life min someone is
just point-blank a moment ago you
weren't thinking about honesty
and now I just put this card from here
so what this tells me that you know you
might want to ask yourself this
question:
all of a sudden that may that changes
your
your experience in the present moment it
may in fact get you realize oh yeah
had some real work to do with my wife
for my father I'm
but the questions then what you let's
say you have that experience a really
valuable Tero card reading
you know what are you going to conclude
about tarot cards under that
on the basis of that I think you'd be
wrong to conclude
that this is magic you the right to
conclude that there's a certain value
in asking him questions I'm and
and that it's very easy we know this is
very easy to
to set up a system which has a very
psychological resonance
for most people most of the time is why
astrology seems to work for most people
most the time you can give
Charles Manson's astrological chart 200
people
and 99% of them will say at withers
you never think it's their chart and I
think you know this really does come get
me
I in some fundamental way because
there's no magic to this things are
written with
you know sufficient generality as to PO
Box Live
for everybody because we're very similar
theme
well I mates it's an allusive thing to
get a hold over there I think the
absence love neurosis the absence of
fear the absence of anxiety
when you recognize what consciousness is
like
when those states of mind her
subsided I it seems to be intrinsically
happy
intrinsically at ease is intrinsically
peaceful and I'm
I'm at times even blissful mistress its
the lack of complications just merely
being aware
I'll oneself I in the present moment and
not
I'm continually being in conversation
with with with oneself about the present
moment just thinkin thinkin thinkin
thinkin
you know incessantly when that can
subside either because you're meditating
or because you're
enjoying yourself so much in you know in
sport tourer you know you're havin sex I
mean any
peak experience has this feature love up
having your attention
really focused
Ian you in a very uncomplicated way I
on your experience in the present and
that that state of mind is
is what I would call happiness and
and all the obstacles
to been addressed in that in that state
of mind I I would
I think about as the obstacles to
happiness and those are things like
you know an erotic self-absorption with
how other people perceive you
or you know anxiety about the future or
regret about the thing you didn't say
you know yesterday in all those those
are the way those the modes of thought
that keep us from recognizing that is
possible to actually be
really at ease in the present and and
happy with with
happy before anything happens me they
are they have to have a happiness that's
not contention
upon the next good thing that's going to
happen but have just directly be
addressed with what is
happenin right now the men
certainty is is I think a false colour
or not
achieving what we achieve in functional
certainties
in science and in just in our in our
day-to-day lives mean is a functional
certainty that I'm sitting here talking
to you though it's possible I could be
dreamin or
near deceived by an evil demon I'm those
kind to fill a philosophical
epistemological worries don't really
relate too much to the ordinary practice
of science very useful practice of
science and our ordinary
I'm task to Pinterest negotiating
our lives and finding happiness in this
world we recognize there's a
a range as a continuum I love you know
I'm not sure
you know the coin toss 50/50 a
understand enough
a circumstance to being functionally
certain about what is so
and many people are pretending to be
functionally certain
or believe themselves to be fun to a
certain about things like
Jesus is going to come back in judge the
world in their lifetime
a 20 percent of the American population
claims to be functionally certain
that that is not gonna come to pass and
78 percent thank the Jesus gonna come
back sometime not necessarily
in their lifetime I and the certainties
do real work for us
me that the person who certain that the
soul enters the zygote at the moment
conception
is the person who wants to veto stem
cell research
despite the fact that ended millions of
people are suffering conditions
wait for which stem cell research is the
best line research to generate therapies
so these these are ideas that are not as
a academic interest for personal private
spiritual relevance in these are these
are shaping policy their shape in a
national conversation
and then when you look to the Muslim
world they are causing people to blow
themselves up on
street corners the net
oh I think we are misled by this this
very term religion we use this word
religion
as though it named a distinct thing is
is that in one
phenomenon in in human discourse and is
really a range
love infatuation zine practices
that go by the name of religion and the
therefore many points on this continuum
don't have much in common
with with others so if you take a
religion like Jane -ism
religion in India its core principle is
non-violence
this work on the got his conception of
non-violence I'm
into the chains are vegetarian a they
have no
doctor and holy war in fact they don't
even have a doctrine proper doctor in
self defense minister pacifists they
don't hurt
fly I'm and then you on the other end to
the continuing have something like Islam
where has he explicitly
a doctor in a holy war and a notion love
I'll sir your combat and
death in certain contexts his is
actually the highest obligation
a religious person can can fulfil so
these are both religions
you know says so religion as a word like
sport you know you have a sport like
badminton and you have a sport like
you know boxing they're not they're both
sports
you know they're one is much more
dangerous I'm
so I'm i'm concerned. I'm obviously more
concerned about religions like Islam
that wary and you have this marriage
have I'm
Friday spiritual and ethical concerns
but also
certain kinds of metaphysical
certainties
that inspire people to not only diaper
to kill others
in the process I'm and you don't have
that in other religions so I think that
we have it be clear about how
this term religion I'm can
can mislead us
religions as essentially failed science
is a minute the religious religion was
the discourse
I that we had when
all causes in the universe were opaque
we didn't know
we didn't know the basis of anything we
didn't know why we were here
we we didn't know how diseases spread or
what disease was we didn't know how
people
I why people died early and why others
flourished we don't know what what's
causing thunderstorms arco causing crops
to fail
and we very naturally as a as a
cognitive and behavioral imperative with
reform
job descriptions of the world and we try
to figure out what's going on
I'm we tell ourselves stories about our
origins and about where we're going on
about causes in the world and
those stories given given our is
pervasive ignorance
and our our disposition to see agency in
the world to see
you know to feel ourselves in
relationship to the world the stories
entail
be in relation to invisible friends
you know and enemies and we so we have
you know that this parent figure in this
guy who's gonna
take care of things if you live rightly
and and we have other
demonic presence is that we should be
really worried about and
gradually what what
you see happening is that religion as as
as rationality and and dozens of
specific sciences
were birthed in the human conversation
you see religion on a hundred franz
losing the argument with signs and we
see that you know on the front tooth
love human health and disease religion
there used to be that you could get a
diagnosis have demonic possession
community that was a Reno reasonable
thing to believe you had if you were
having seizures say you know but now we
have a science and neurology and we know
about epilepsy and so when your kid has
seizures
you know you don't go to the church to
get get him diagnosed and treated people
would buy exorcism
and so that's a good thing i'm saying
that religion is losin
the argument on every other front is
losing the argument
ethically is he is gonna it will lose
the argument spiritually and we will
understand spiritual experience
so well at some point at the level of
the brain and the level love
now the way in which she using attention
in certain ways can change in my
experience well understand in a way that
makes a mockery
love this kinda dot denominational
religion talk about
cheeses and grace or about Buddha and
magic powers and and and
that will break down in the same way
that has broken down on medicine on
medicine thats that's a process I think
we just have to be honest about it and
let on the move
why I can say that I'm an optimist you
know it's
I see that this are emotional attachment
to these myths is so well subscribed and
so deep
and i believe even people who are not
religious belief that everyone else
needs to be religious
it's like you know I don't need it but
even so the ultimate condescending
attitude but
everyone else does I mean this is a a
myth that that is also widely described
even among atheists
I'm so the the inertia
in the system around around really just
have an honest conversation about what
it's reasonable to believe in what
religion is doing in the world I is
profound as I like I'm certainly not
optimistic
I'm I don't know what else to do and I
see how's
how tissue thin these
these believes actually are many really
it would be so easy
to just on burden ourselves
evolve this mythology I'm an idiot would
be accomplished in a single generation
if we just talk
our children reasonably about the
Bible's place in literature
you know the Bible's not science I it's
not particularly good philosophy
but it is literature let's let's let's
read the Bible and then it was read all
these other
books about dead gods like that you know
of its metamorphosis
on if we talk the Bible in and the koran
in that way
in a single generation really good I did
Abraham would take his place alongside
Zeus and Poseidon Apollo and the other
day cards and none of this would be a
problem
I'm but that the is not likely to happen
I think
know the name