I'm calling for the widower's wife.
Are you the person in charge of...
you're not?
Who is?
In charge of casting extras.
It's all over?
May I speak to someone
about kitty-crunch?
"Excuse me, but this kitty-crunch ad.,"
...is aimed at what audience?
Mostly men or women?
Cats? That's very interesting.
May I ask...
what kind of cats exactly?
"I'm wondering because statistically,"
most cats have brown eyes.
Green-brown eyes
which happens to fit my profile well.
"My front-view profile, that is."
Are you producing poppy's return?
Do you still need a Swiss terrorist?
I can come whenever you like.
Now?
That's a pity.
I've an urgent appointment.
Some other time.
"Is that you, Augustin?"
"Hello, Mrs. Haton."
Come a bit closer.
I can't see you very well.
When can you come read to me?
Soon
can you remember where we were?
I marked the page
but the paper fell out.
"Well, Jackie..."
met that ugly guy with a boat
on a Greek island.
Onassis right
she doesn't like him much at first.
But he's very wealthy
...and so is she.
- Will she marry him?
- We don't know yet
of course she will!
But does it really matter?
Maybe not.
"Faster, tang!"
That's better.
Sauerkraut a la Strasbourg?
Why didn't you call me?
"Strasbourg, a la sauerkraut."
Cut!
It's the other way around.
Sauerkraut a la Strasbourg. Of course
"twice in a lifetime, 24-7, take 18."
Action!
"I tried to call, then I forgot."
"As they say,"you haven't changed.""
You don't have to say it.
Isn't it hot in here?
So why didn't you phone?
- I don't know -two sauerkrauts
a la...
was it Salzburg?
What town was it?
A city in eastern France
with a big cathedral.
With two spires?
Exactly.
"24-7, take 31."
Sauerkraut a la Strasbourg.
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing?
You're a waiter
present the food and put it down!
I only had a week to rehearse my part.
I've broken it down into three phases.
Motion phase: I appear.
Static phase: Present the sauerkraut.
Last phase: Touchdown. I lower the food.
Let's do it. Go ahead.
We're not rolling.
We weren't rolling.
May I have some tea?
"The crew seem tired, don't they?"
We all have off days.
At times you can stumble over
the easiest lines
the results can be surprising.
I agree. The lines aren't
that important.
- They're not? - no
it's body language.
"The neck, for instance.
It supports the face."
A neckless face...
hasn't a leg to stand on.
"Then you have feet, for balance."
Balance is inherently unstable.
So you have your feet to thank
for your balance.
I agree. The body's vital.
I only do physical roles now.
Like what? Stunts? Song-and-dance?
"No, only kung fu."
You know kung fu?
Not really.
"Pity. It's like boxing,
only it's Chinese."
"I'm not Chinese, but I'm good at it."
Are many kung fu movies made in France?
"I know, it seems a bit impossible..."
but impossible things aren't
always impossible.
True.
Fanny? Five minutes.
Coming.
You should get going.
Can you cope with all your lines?
I'm used to it.
"Well, goodbye."
Sorry. I have a problem shaking hands.
I understand. What's your name?
Dos Santos. It was Portuguese.
"Bye, then."
Good luck.
"Faster, tang!
You're as stiff as your stick!"
Big oaf!
You'll never beat Wang Chu.
You stand no chance against him
...unless you learn from me.
Bring me a bowl of tea and sit down.
"You have fire and youth on your side,"
but you know nothing yet. Nothing!
You must continue working here.
Leave your family and friends.
It is the only way.
Are you listening?
"Yes, you!"
"You're a man of good will,
Mr. Dos Santos,"
but you still have far to go.
Hard work lies ahead.
"To do it, you must create a void
inside you."
Seek out new horizons.
Renounce your surroundings.
"Go far,"
far away.
"Back to the roots,"
"the birthplace of kung fu,"
the land of the warrior monks.
It may be nearer than you think.
I'm going to miss you.
Who will read to me?
I don't know.
I'll be going.
How about a hug?
Actually... I'd rather not.
"Goodbye, Mrs. Haton."
'Evening.
Is this hotel Chinese?
"I'm afraid so, yes."
Great! You have a room?
How much?
"150 francs. Shower, no breakfast.
One night?"
"No! Much more. I can't say how long,
but long."
Your name? Dos Santos
"two "osses". One with a d,
one with a sant."
Does the room face east?
"Rise to the east, sleep to the west.
Ideally."
Arms back. Tiger stance!
Loosen up.
Can I help you?
Are you master Wang?
I saw the sign with all your diplomas.
You trained in china?
You're sure? Your french is good.
- I've been here 20 years.
- I got here yesterday.
"I think, to study kung fu,"
a Chinese environment is best.
As Chinese as possible.
Return to the roots.
Renounce my surroundings
beginner? Far from it.
I'm highly trained.
I need to work on details.
"For instance, if I may say so,"
"when you showed the tiger stance,"
your tiger's claws looked
more like goat's feet.
They did? Explain.
I'll demonstrate. It's easier.
Stand by!
See my claws?
Where did you learn that?
Hi. I'd like to open a bank account.
"Certainly, sir."
How much do you have?
"6,250 francs. French francs."
I didn't bring the coins.
How much is that in Yuan?
Hold on.
"That makes about 8,872 Yuan."
Not bad.
"Waterfalls. Niagara-style,
but in Mongolia."
Mongolia? Genghis khan?
Guts and carnage?
"No! Gushing cascades,
constantly glimmering."
Only a power cut stops it.
Then all goes black.
"Look at these colors.
Mauve, gray, yellow, pink..."
...the lot!
Forever flowing for family fun.
For young and old alike.
Where would it go?
Good question. You can put it anywhere!
"Hall, bedroom, living room."
Not the toilet. Although...
it's soothing. Relaxing.
"Rousing, too. It's energizing!"
It's sensual! This cascade is
like a silken caress.
Never goes out of style.
And guaranteed never to dry up.
You can't beat the price.
It's so low it's painful.
You know our name! Cheap'n... - china.
Right! Take a wild guess.
"No, much less! 1,299 francs."
It's as low as I can go.
That's 14 francs 50.
Are you looking for help?
Is that man the boss?
Is the boss here?
Why hesitate? Pay for it over two years!
Sorry. No problem.
"If you need anything, just knock room 21"
today we make contact.
Could you make a little less noise?
What's the problem?
He's too loud. He doesn't understand.
Should he really be clutching my arm?
"In combat sports, contact is necessary."
Contact? How awful. Can't it be avoided?
No. Try marbles or monopoly. Go on.
"I'm dizzy. Sorry, I don't feel well."
Dr. Ling's office?
Could you repeat that?
Come in.
Good afternoon.
I'm here to see Dr. Ling.
I am Dr. Ling.
Pardon me. I expected a man.
Follow me.
Now? Yes.
I have one quick question.
I'm free. This way...
just for a moment.
I'm in good health. Great health.
Please excuse my bad french.
"I'm taking lessons.
I'll be better soon, I hope."
I'll be taking lessons too.
In Chinese. Lots of people
speak it fluently.
What brings you here?
What's the problem?
I don't really have one.
"By the way, how much do you charge?"
100 francs. Okay?
Yes.
Go ahead.
I'm a top-notch athlete.
I'm learning Chinese boxing.
To act in kung fu films.
It's fine. The training's
going normally.
"I have one handicap.
Trivial, but annoying."
What is the problem?
The problem is... touching.
Making contact.
We fight with one another and have to...
it's most unpleasant.
Contact? Shaking hands? Being touched?
"Yes. It starts where I'm touched,
then moves up."
"Up to my elbows is bearable,"
but sometimes it reaches
my shoulders and head.
Then I get dizzy and hot.
Hotter and hotter.
"Then suddenly, I'm cold. Ice-cold."
Then I'm totally paralyzed.
Maybe it's no big deal.
Do you dream a lot?
I don't think so.
Are you a good eater?
I eat cereals and vegetables.
Mostly broccoli.
Are you color sensitive?
What colors do you like?
Why is that important?
"It helps locate your inner peace,"
but you don't have to answer now.
Show me your tongue.
Really?
Stick it out.
More.
It's very white.
Very white?
Your energy isn't circulating well.
Is that bad?
Everything is curable.
Can you undress?
Do I have to?
The top?
Everything. You can keep
your underpants on.
That's lucky.
Please lie down.
That looks sharp.
Relax.
Close your eyes.
Both of them?
Of course.
Are you okay? Not hurting?
Will it leave holes?
Did you find it?
Is it listed in the book?
I don't think it's a skin-problem
the surface is only a symptom.
"The book says,"water lilies
can grow on dry land."
"...but when they do,"
"there must be a hidden spring nearby.""
We have to dig.
Dig?
Dig where?
Good reaction.
Am I cured?
We've just begun. Step by step
for best results.
Interesting case. You're my
first french patient.
- Can I see the boss?
- He's in his office
can I help you?
I live nearby. I'm a customer here.
Let me say first how much
I like your goods.
I love the wicker basket I bought.
It's excellent. For broccoli.
Thank you.
It's expertly woven
...and barely smells.
"From now on, you can count on me."
I won't shop elsewhere.
Your clientele is fascinating.
Do you work alone?
You sell such a variety
and quantity of goods.
Where's the flowered teapot folder?
Down there.
I'm pretty free these days.
I like this place.
"If you're overworked, I can help."
Don't bother. We're not hiring.
"Right, Mr. Li?"
"Sorry to insist, but here"
...I'll meet Chinese people. I need to.
The streets are full of them.
Train me.
The answer's no.
I'm not asking for money.
I have enough for now.
I'll work for free.
For free?
For free...
at first.
Did you leave china long ago?
A year and a half ago.
But you live with family here.
Cousins. Not very close.
Until I find someplace else.
"Try to relax, please! D"
is acupuncture an old art?
As old as kung fu?
"Older, 2000 years."
2000 years? It must take
forever to learn.
I was taught by my uncle in canton.
"A very good doctor,
but more conventional."
He taught me basics. Good and solid.
I use it for foundation.
Sometimes I invent.
Has this been tested?
Is it scientific?
Of course.
But it's hard to explain to you.
My french is not yet good enough.
Try in Chinese
I'll leave you now. Empty your mind.
I'm glad you slept a little.
It's progress.
Same time tomorrow?
"Better to wait a few days.
Too fast, not good."
You may feel some side-effects.
Don't worry. We'll see this through.
I'm on the right track.
"Dos Santos, what are you doing?
Come and listen."
Kitchen appliances...
lemon squeezer - easy.
Blender - no comment.
Very important! What is this?
"Carpet sweeper?
No, d387 crumber."
"Study it well. A banal, everyday object.
But!"
Crumbs collect in this special cavity.
Beware of eggshell! It jams the works.
Made in Macao.
You're Portuguese. Macao? Gambling dens?
Not your thing.
Are you listening?
Come see our chinaware.
"You're crazy, working here for free!"
"If you get hurt,
don't expect compensation."
Let me tell you about the Chinese mind.
"They're smart cookies, not easy to con."
Make them laugh.
Don't underestimate them.
They're no country bumpkins.
Repeat after me:
The customer arrives. We speak first.
"Confidently, masterfully,"
"with a twinkle, an old pal
doing her a favor."
Listen hard. Picture the scene.
"Chinese housewife arrives.
Shopping bag full,"
"purse almost empty. She walks around,"
unaware of the lurking danger.
"You pounce, smiling. She's yours,"
a captive customer at your command.
"Sell her a dream! A wok,
a flowerpot holder,"
"a singing doll, a toilet seat!"
She's glowing. And grateful.
She can pay for it over ten years.
What next? Give her a bonus.
A trinket?
"Any old crap. Incense, matches..."
anything cheap and cheerful.
Dos Santos! Wake up!
I'm undergoing intensive therapy.
"I don't give a damn, kiddo."
Useless! Doesn't have it in him.
I give him my best and he nods off.
"Hello, Mrs. Pei."
How's missy?
What cute pigtails.
Dr. Ling. It's urgent.
Acupuncture.
I don't understand french.
Try the living Buddha club.
Thanks.
Sir?
Is miss ling here?
She's downstairs.
What's this?
The sacre coeur!
And this?
The pantheon!
What's written on the front of it?
"To the nation's great men,
with thanks"
yes. Many great Frenchmen
are buried there.
"Remember,"thanks"has an"s"at the end"
"think of a snake."hisss""
who is this famous woman?
The mona lisa!
With her enigmatic smile.
"Enigmatic, from "enigma".
A synonym, please?"
"Ling?"mysterious""
"very good. Now,"
everyday words.
Bottle.
Cauliflower.
Broccoli!
"Like you said, I'm getting side-effects."
- Strong ones. - it's normal.
I need emergency treatment.
You do first aid?
Excuse me. Talismans date
from the qing dynasty?
- That's right. - thanks. Goodbye.
Mr. Boutinot knows china like an expert.
What kind of side-effects?
Won't your family mind?
Don't worry about them.
I pay rent. I can do as I like.
Is much of Paris like this?
Not really.
I only know Chinatown.
"You're a foreigner here, like me!"
Will you stay here?
I don't know. It's too early to say.
What's that?
A first world war memorial.
Were many battles fought in France?
Lots. At least until 1939.
Your teacher speaks good Chinese.
What will you do tonight?
"Your shoulders, chest and
around your heart."
No! What are you doing?
Jumping and shouting.
"May I suggest a simple,
yet popular gift?"
"These small bowls, or cuplets."
For rice liquor. If you like alcohol.
I don't.
"Remarkably, the enamel is
baked into the paste."
See? A traditional technique.
There's another very special... feature
which may appeal to you-or not.
Let's test it with this fluid.
"Not rice liquor, but kerosene."
Now.
What appears at the bottom?
Correct! A woman.
She's totally undressed.
Quite shameless.
She took the part. Why?
For money? I wouldn't.
Whatever. Let's not judge her.
"Nudity is not my taste,
but it may be yours,"
...is it?
What's that?
That? It's sort of... a clock.
Forget it. It's not too ugly
but it's very expensive.
"We're called cheap "n" china,
but cheap it's not!"
I'll buy it.
You will?
"It's a gift, so remove the tag."
"You'll need paper, ribbons,
and lot of tape!"
Thank you very much indeed.
"3,500 francs."
"Nice work, son. Hats off to you!"
I tried to sell that thing
for god knows how long.
"It's hideous, too!"
It was a hardware store.
I owned it for 15 years
"then came the invasion.
Nice people, though."
"I sold it well,"
for a very good price.
"Now I'm a manager,"
"it's a cinch! No loans,
no nit-picking inspectors."
"Still, it takes work. Stay in harness,
that's my motto."
Are you alone at the hotel?
No girlfriend?
Not now? Or never?
Not now.
"Right, who needs them?"
So you're out of luck with girls?
I'm the opposite; they're
out of luck with me.
That's the way it goes.
That's your lunch?
"You eat like a jockey. Of course,
you're an athlete."
"For a future kung fu star,
you're not beefy."
"You're no Rambo. But clothes
are misleading. Me,"
I'm lean for my age. Not a
pinch of fat. Feel it
I think I hit a bone.
Bones are harder to build up!
Li should put you on a commission.
It's only fair.
I blabber on. You're so quiet...
modesty's nice.
Sorry to pester you but
you're my savior.
My novel's full of details
I must get right.
"Mr. Boutinot, Augustin."
We met before.
"Mr. Ren,"
see you Friday.
Who's she? A friend?
In a way.
Where is it now? Page...
eigth-eight
here's what I write:
"As night fell, the firelight
by the river flickered"
"on the grinning old man's
betel-stained teeth""
my question is: Would a
Yangtze river-dweller
...be chewing betel in 1885?
What's betel?
Pepper and tobacco mixed with lime.
Leng-yip?
It's possible.
"It is? Good, so"betel"can stay."
"Great. If it's published,
I'll owe you a lot."
I'm happy to help.
I didn't take the easy way out...
did you find a title?
How's this? I thought of it yesterday:
Rice of the ricefields.
"Because of"rice"and"ricefields"."
It's enigmatic.
You have a certain charm.
It's not written all over you.
"Deep down, you have that
Portuguese mystique."
May I say something?
You sell yourself short.
You should try...
try slicking your hair back.
"Or else, grow it longer."
Are you listening?
Who is that girl?
My therapist.
That's better.
Hello. How are you?
I need some information.
"Not bad. Now, something harder;"
it was fine this morning but
it'll rain tonight
excellent! I'm impressed.
You're talented.
I've studied for years and
been to china twice.
All right. Enough torture for today.
Can I pay you now?
End of the month.
Here. Thanks.
"How do you say,"your treatment
does me good"?"
Thanks.
You want to say it to ling?
Do you see her often?
In class. Sometimes outside.
My best student.
She'll go far. She has guts.
She was forced to marry in china
and left it all.
I admire her a lot.
You know her very well.
"Hold it. I'm married,
faithful, monogamous."
It's almost a religion for me.
She's been a big inspiration
for my book.
For what it's worth...
"dear sir, rice of the ricefields"
"...is admirably well researched...""
the usual empty flattery...
"loaded with images and
tangled metaphors,"
leads the reader into
an inescapable maze.
Your manuscript is not for us.
"With our regrets and best wishes
for the future...""
may I see it?
Maybe I went wrong.
Maybe it lost its flow.
I think it's quite encouraging.
Encouraging? Yes.
Regrets means that they liked it.
But regret they can't say so.
"And then..."best wishes."
"Best" is a strong word."
"Wishes, too. They're not common."
That's one way of looking at it.
What are you doing?
"I'm searching for the vital point,"
the center of hidden feelings.
"Today, we must go deeper."
I've thought about you.
The answer isn't in books
not in the books?
Human matter is more complicated.
You have to reach inside
to touch the root.
There. I think I have it.
That's not the usual one.
Isn't it too long?
It's a very old Chinese needle.
"I've never used it before,"
I'm sure it's necessary now.
Won't it burn?
It will hurt a little.
Do you feel the heat?
It's very hot. Very hot.
It'll spread all over your body.
All over?
We must awake what has been
too long asleep.
Stop thinking. Isolate yourself.
It's moving down.
And up.
Just lie here. Relax.
You're leaving?
Wait!
It's not finished!
Augustin!
He's always here.
You trying to marry him?
Butt out! You're not my mother.
How are you?
Find it okay?
Put your bike there.
"If you get sick of the hotel,
sleep here."
"It's small, but we'll make do."
Stay seated.
- Coffee? - I'd rather not.
You're on the payroll!
Li's signing you on at a decent rate.
Thanks.
Me and my pompom!
"You, in the navy?
- For years! Tough customers."
We had good times.
We traveled the world over.
"Here, a drop of bunyuls."
What is it?
A liqueur made from wine.
Let your hair down. Try it!
Not bad. Reminds me of cough syrup.
You need to learn how to enjoy life.
Let's play some music.
I loved dancing.
I had rhythm in my bones!
I'd dance to anything. I was a natural.
Have you seen Mirza?
Where did that dog go?
I've looked everywhere.
He's gonna drive me mad.
Where did that dog go?
"There he is! Come here, boy."
I won't say it again.
"Come here, boy!"
"Then beat it, mutt!"
It's the last one. It's unique.
I've put it on to model it for you.
"It's warm in the winter,
and cool in the summer."
Top-grade silk.
Embroidered with flowers.
Japanese garden varieties.
"Imported from Xian. The silk route,
you know?"
How do you wash it?
"With water, either hard or soft."
Hand wash or dry clean?
That's up to you. It's your call.
You've missed a week. I was worried.
"We stayed open late.
Night sales, until 11 PM."
And the fish got food poisoning.
We had to treat them one by one.
Are you coming to the party tomorrow?
"It's tomorrow? No, I can't."
Or maybe. Monday's kung fu.
Shame to stop the treatment
now at the last step.
You abandoned your customer?
"No, she... you lost the sale."
Are you here to shop?
Just passing through.
Make yourself at home.
The seven seas keep us apart
...with tears in our heart
"karukera, caledonia"
"ouessant, virgin of the seas"
"alone, always..."
the seven seas keep us apart
...with tears in our heart
good evening to all.
Thank you all from the
bottom of my heart.
"For 10 years, you've made
this place wonderful."
The nicest place in the area. Thank you.
"We're like one big, extended family:"
"...elders, parents, children, cousins..."
"...including me, I'm proud to say."
"I won't take long. I'll introduce
my wife, Chantal."
"Hi, honey."
"My daughter, Marion."
Enough. Back to the party.
Here's to fun and china the eternal!
How are you? Meet my wife.
- This is ling -hi!
Are you settling in?
Parisians aren't too rude?
I don't know many.
They're like everyone.
They grumble a bit.
Thanks for helping with his book.
Excuse me.
It's a success.
Yes! It's weird. No one seems bored.
You look different.
"The lipstick, maybe."
Big difference!
Everyday not workday. Forget needles
dance?
I can't.
Try.
I've never danced.
It's a party. Come on.
"Good! We can see if contact problem
is cured,"
...in everyday life.
Are you okay?
Fine.
How is he? Still sedated.
Sedated...
careful. Chemical treatment is
dangerous for him
they know their jobs. Let them work.
You turn people into voodoo dolls.
No wonder they're bewitched.
"It's low blood pressure, that's all."
He was out for 10 minutes!
It's not serious. Tachycardia.
- Did he have a trauma?
- We were drinking.
Can you see him? One by one.
"When I got there, I was my normal self."
As normal as usual.
Maybe the music was too loud.
"Don't worry, son. I'm here."
Coffee? No thanks.
Are you still treating him?
The treatment isn't over yet.
He may react to it unpredictably.
You don't know your power.
I'm out of line.
"He is very sensitive, but too hidden."
He's endearing. Not your average guy.
I didn't want to wake you.
"I think he's better, so I'll come home."
He needs sleep. I'll stay.
Can we say goodnight?
It's best if you don't.
Tell him meet me tomorrow
in the cafe after work.
See you around.
Cold? A little.
You want my jacket?
I'll walk you home.
"1,850 francs."
Thanks for your hospitality.
We hope to have you back.
Was I a pain? Not at all.
"You were discreet, but very energetic."
"Is he your friend? Yes, a friend."
Let's go.
Are you okay?
- Not too uncomfortable? - it's fine.
"-What's that smell?
- "Bad boy" by Molyneux."
"Heady, but it scored me a few hits."
...in the dim and distant past.
It's ages since I slept with someone.
Were you ever married?
Yes.
With a woman? You bet.
A good woman. A dutiful wife.
We weren't madly in love.
We married late.
Dead? Guess again.
She grows carrots down south.
She hated Paris.
You never see her?
Once a year. At most.
"If it's nice this weekend,
...we'll go for spin."
I know a nice place.
The Rabette inn.
I meant to tell you...
what?
Nothing. Sleep.
Sleep well?
- No tachycardia? - I'm fine.
Croissant?
Tell me what you'd like for tomorrow.
Sit down!
A load of chinaware came in from Taiwan.
We have to sort it all out.
There's damage. Put price tags
on the cracks.
Help yourself. No thanks.
You're not hungry?
Biscuits?
I don't like them.
You're not an easy kid.
I should change my cabinets.
They're grim.
I want them bright and peppy.
What do you think?
Say something!
It's not all you should change.
Thanks a lot!
- Wait. - I'm taking a ride.
There's no time.
I need to think.
Where are you going?
You can't fool me!
No ceramic teapots?
"Sorry, we're sold out."
We can't order any more!
Discontinued!
It's hideous! Why litter
your living room?
Mr. Rene...
I only have two arms! I'm all alone!
Have you seen Augustin?
He missed tonight's lesson.
Am I bothering you?
May I?
Here's your book on the tang dynasty.
Are you okay? You look...
I'm fine.
Your weapons...
I should give it a try.
Maybe not with you.
No. Not when we're friends.
Obviously.
You must need a lot of intuition.
A special touch.
Yes. It's difficult here.
"Different culture, different,"
"mixed-up, sometimes aggressive."
You don't know many french people.
Yes. Two.
"Discovering a new world,
when you're all alone..."
I'm sorry I bothered you.
"No, stay."
I'll get going.
Are you really okay?
Got your passport?
Here's your ticket.
I'll pay you back.
Don't annoy me. It's my idea.
It's a present.
It'll do you good.
You need a change of scenery.
I'll let you cope on your own.
I'll be at the bar.
How many bags? One.
My bike stays with me.
I'm afraid not.
But the tyres are fragile.
They're patched all over.
What's the pressure in the hold?
You must check it in.
I could go with it!
"Okay, I'll undo the wheels."
Hurry! You'll be late!
The ticket's non-refundable. Hurry up!
"Send me a postcard. Anything!
The great wall,"
"Mao's tomb, the yellow river
under ice..."
go easy on the opium!
"Hurry, or you'll miss the plane."
Maybe they'll cast you
in a kung fu film.
"China, here I come."
Yes. See how you like it.
"Sir! Your backpack, please."
A few years later
...interviewing Jean-Louis Boutinot
how's business?
"...rice of the ricefields,
out this week."
"Mr. Boutinot,"
how much historical research
...went into the book?
"A great deal of research, of course."
"But in my view... primarily,
it's a novel."
I'm so fulfilled. A baby and a book!
Mrs. Wang! Hi.
"Hi, Mr. Rene. How's retirement?"
"I dreaded it, but not bad with a
little imagination."
Excuse me.
See you later.
Hi. Thanks for coming.
At long last.
Your name?
See you later.
Don't disappear. I'll sign you a copy.
Your name?
You're very elegant.
Where do you live now?
"The 9th, near Clichy. I consult there."
Still wielding the needles?
They can't do much harm.
Are you married? Children?
I'm married.
Good. So you're happy?
I like living in France.
I often think about...
have you heard from him?
"-Hi there! - Hi, dad."
Did you buy me chocolate? I did.
Done your homework?
I'll do it later.
...not a crumb left on the table.
The wise man came and said.
Never mind. I'll eat the leftovers.
In case you didn't notice.
"...as you all eat so fast,"
today we're eating soybeans
from Guangxi.
They're good for the memory.
Your mother won't like it.
Not until you finish.
Not hungry. I want to go out.
He's eaten a lot.
Finish your homework first.
I already did it.