1
00:00:18,627 --> 00:00:21,128
Hey, you got a permit
for those guns?

2
00:00:22,195 --> 00:00:24,095
I got your permit right here.

3
00:00:35,195 --> 00:00:36,628
Catchy tune.

4
00:00:43,962 --> 00:00:46,460
Fuck this game.

5
00:00:46,560 --> 00:00:48,494
FUCK YOU!

6
00:01:23,128 --> 00:01:26,661
We need backup, we need Kung Fury.

7
00:01:42,427 --> 00:01:44,661
Yeah, that's my bicep.

8
00:01:46,094 --> 00:01:47,295
One second babe.

9
00:01:48,095 --> 00:01:49,961
Hello?

10
00:01:50,062 --> 00:01:52,194
We got an arcade machine
down here going crazy,

11
00:01:52,295 --> 00:01:53,394
it is killing everybody,
it's destruction,
chaos, terror-

12
00:01:55,328 --> 00:01:56,428
What are you gonna do?

13
00:01:56,528 --> 00:01:57,628
My job.

14
00:03:04,895 --> 00:03:06,561
Game over.

15
00:03:12,427 --> 00:03:16,228
I'm a cop and damn good at my job.

16
00:03:16,327 --> 00:03:18,428
It all began years ago.

17
00:03:18,528 --> 00:03:19,894
In the line of duty,

18
00:03:19,994 --> 00:03:21,261
me and my partner were
chasing  down

19
00:03:21,360 --> 00:03:24,694
a mysterious Kung Fu-master.

20
00:03:24,794 --> 00:03:26,294
You're under arrest, punk.

21
00:03:26,394 --> 00:03:27,661
Show us your hands.

22
00:03:29,627 --> 00:03:31,094
Good work, Dragon.

23
00:03:31,195 --> 00:03:33,228
That crazy stunt could've
killed us both.

24
00:03:33,327 --> 00:03:35,761
But goddammit, you're the
best partner I've ever had.

25
00:03:35,861 --> 00:03:39,228
Thanks, I learned from the best.

26
00:03:39,327 --> 00:03:41,361
You're like a father to me.

27
00:03:41,461 --> 00:03:44,195
With one fatal blow, he hit my partner.

28
00:03:46,195 --> 00:03:48,394
I could tell he was dead straight off.

29
00:03:54,628 --> 00:03:57,494
Before I could pull the trigger

30
00:03:57,595 --> 00:04:01,094
I was hit by lightning
and bitten by a cobra.

31
00:04:01,194 --> 00:04:03,360
I blacked out.

32
00:04:05,928 --> 00:04:09,128
And saw images of ancient
Shaolin temples and monks,

33
00:04:09,229 --> 00:04:11,427
mastering the art of Kung Fu.

34
00:04:11,527 --> 00:04:12,961
There was an ancient prophecy,

35
00:04:13,061 --> 00:04:15,460
about a new form
of Kung Fu so powerful,

36
00:04:15,561 --> 00:04:17,628
only one man could master it.

37
00:04:17,728 --> 00:04:18,962
The chosen one.

38
00:04:20,962 --> 00:04:22,527
When I woke up,

39
00:04:22,627 --> 00:04:24,861
I saw the Kung Fu master
running towards me.

40
00:04:24,961 --> 00:04:26,928
I could feel my body mutate

41
00:04:27,028 --> 00:04:29,995
into some sort of
Kung Fu freak of nature.

42
00:04:41,394 --> 00:04:42,628
You!

43
00:04:43,527 --> 00:04:44,928
You are the chosen one!

44
00:04:46,794 --> 00:04:48,995
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?

45
00:04:50,028 --> 00:04:51,628
Knuckles.

46
00:05:12,228 --> 00:05:13,994
As a memento,

47
00:05:14,094 --> 00:05:16,861
I put on a strip of cloth
from the dead Kung Fu master.

48
00:05:16,961 --> 00:05:19,561
I decided I would use
my new super Kung Fu powers

49
00:05:19,661 --> 00:05:21,128
to fight crime.

50
00:05:21,227 --> 00:05:22,995
So, I became
the best cop in the world.

51
00:05:23,095 --> 00:05:25,661
I became, Kung Fury.

52
00:06:17,127 --> 00:06:18,961
I don't wanna hear it Kung Fury.

53
00:06:19,061 --> 00:06:22,661
I just got back from city hall,
$50 million worth of damages,

54
00:06:22,761 --> 00:06:26,061
and I got the mayor up
my ass like a fag on Viagra.

55
00:06:26,160 --> 00:06:29,894
How am I going to explain
this to the press, hm?

56
00:06:29,994 --> 00:06:33,627
You just destroyed an entire
city block for Christ's sake.

57
00:06:33,727 --> 00:06:35,527
Didn't you tell me
to block it out?

58
00:06:35,627 --> 00:06:37,194
I told you do it by the book.

59
00:06:37,294 --> 00:06:38,594
Cut the bullshit.

60
00:06:38,694 --> 00:06:39,995
Nobody else could have stopped

61
00:06:40,095 --> 00:06:42,062
that arcade machine
and you know it.

62
00:06:44,094 --> 00:06:47,160
Oh man, listen to me Kung Fury.

63
00:06:47,260 --> 00:06:50,761
You need to start following
the rules like the rest of us,

64
00:06:50,861 --> 00:06:52,861
so I'm assigning you
a new partner.

65
00:06:52,962 --> 00:06:54,995
What?
Hell no, I work alone.

66
00:06:55,094 --> 00:06:56,561
Not anymore you don't.

67
00:06:56,661 --> 00:07:00,260
Say hi to your new partner,
Triceracop.

68
00:07:00,360 --> 00:07:02,327
Very nice meeting you Kung Fury,

69
00:07:02,427 --> 00:07:04,794
looking forward to
working with you.

70
00:07:04,895 --> 00:07:06,895
You're like a father to me.

71
00:07:09,460 --> 00:07:11,227
I work alone.

72
00:07:11,327 --> 00:07:13,561
Either you team up
with Triceracop,

73
00:07:13,661 --> 00:07:15,394
or you're off the case.

74
00:07:15,494 --> 00:07:17,028
I'm not off the case,

75
00:07:17,127 --> 00:07:18,161
I quit.

76
00:07:29,294 --> 00:07:32,394
Yeah Yeah, I did the blood test.

77
00:07:32,494 --> 00:07:34,194
It was positive, yeah?

78
00:07:34,294 --> 00:07:35,294
What the hell are you talking about?

79
00:07:35,394 --> 00:07:37,094
Yeah no problem.

80
00:07:37,194 --> 00:07:38,327
Give me the phone.

81
00:07:44,761 --> 00:07:47,060
What the hell is this?

82
00:07:49,060 --> 00:07:52,761
- Chief McNickles speaking.
- Is this the police?

83
00:07:52,861 --> 00:07:55,294
- Yeah, this is the police.
- Fuck you!

84
00:08:11,027 --> 00:08:12,695
MALFUNCTIONING?

85
00:08:13,928 --> 00:08:16,428
I need someone
to trace that call!

86
00:08:16,528 --> 00:08:18,394
But that's impossible!

87
00:08:18,494 --> 00:08:19,895
Not for me it isn't.

88
00:08:27,194 --> 00:08:30,061
Hackerman, he's the most
powerful hacker of all time.

89
00:08:33,895 --> 00:08:34,962
Follow me.

90
00:08:38,227 --> 00:08:40,461
I was able to triangulate
the cell phone signal

91
00:08:40,561 --> 00:08:41,828
and trace the caller.

92
00:08:43,260 --> 00:08:45,427
His name is Adolf Hitler.

93
00:08:45,528 --> 00:08:48,695
Hitler, he's the worst
criminal of all time.

94
00:08:48,795 --> 00:08:50,227
Do you know him, sir?

95
00:08:50,327 --> 00:08:51,761
I guess you could say that.

96
00:08:51,862 --> 00:08:55,561
In the 1940's,
Hitler was a Kung Fu champion.

97
00:08:55,661 --> 00:08:57,427
He was so good at Kung Fu,

98
00:08:57,527 --> 00:09:01,094
that he decided to change
his name to Kung Fuhrer.

99
00:09:02,194 --> 00:09:03,661
But he didn't stop there.

100
00:09:03,761 --> 00:09:05,727
He knew of
the Kung Fury prophecy,

101
00:09:05,828 --> 00:09:07,560
and wanted to claim the throne.

102
00:09:07,660 --> 00:09:09,794
He and his posse of
Nazi soldiers

103
00:09:09,894 --> 00:09:11,695
conducted experiments
for years.

104
00:09:22,895 --> 00:09:24,494
But they weren't able
to figure out

105
00:09:24,594 --> 00:09:27,094
how to master the art
of Kung Fury.

106
00:09:28,193 --> 00:09:29,660
And one day,

107
00:09:29,761 --> 00:09:31,927
he disappeared
from the face of the earth.

108
00:09:32,026 --> 00:09:34,260
And no-one has seen him
ever since.

109
00:09:34,361 --> 00:09:36,060
Until now.

110
00:09:36,160 --> 00:09:38,993
I guess he figured if he could
find and kill the chosen one,

111
00:09:39,093 --> 00:09:41,060
he would become
Kung Fury himself.

112
00:09:41,160 --> 00:09:43,628
He must have traveled in time
in order to get here,

113
00:09:43,728 --> 00:09:46,427
that's probably why
he disappeared.

114
00:09:46,527 --> 00:09:47,895
So, what're you gonna do?

115
00:09:48,427 --> 00:09:49,795
My job.

116
00:09:49,895 --> 00:09:52,260
I'm gonna go back in time
to Nazi Germany,

117
00:09:52,360 --> 00:09:54,160
and kill Hitler,
once and for all.

118
00:09:54,260 --> 00:09:56,360
So, how are you gonna do that?

119
00:09:56,460 --> 00:09:58,294
I'm not sure.

120
00:09:58,394 --> 00:10:00,194
I need some sort of
time machine.

121
00:10:04,193 --> 00:10:05,694
Wait a minute,

122
00:10:05,794 --> 00:10:07,761
using an RX modulator,
I might be able to conduct

123
00:10:07,861 --> 00:10:10,527
a mainframe cell direct and
hack the uplink to the download.

124
00:10:10,627 --> 00:10:12,227
What does that mean?

125
00:10:12,327 --> 00:10:15,161
With the right algorithms,
I can hack you back in time.

126
00:10:16,160 --> 00:10:18,194
Just like a time machine.

127
00:10:18,294 --> 00:10:20,694
Well then, it's hacking time.

128
00:11:37,161 --> 00:11:38,228
Oh, no!

129
00:12:39,260 --> 00:12:41,161
Fuck!

130
00:12:41,261 --> 00:12:42,893
That's a Laser-Raptor.

131
00:12:42,993 --> 00:12:45,227
I thought they went
extinct thousands of years ago.

132
00:13:09,527 --> 00:13:10,927
Who are you?

133
00:13:11,027 --> 00:13:12,127
My name,

134
00:13:13,494 --> 00:13:14,727
is Barbarianna.

135
00:13:21,260 --> 00:13:22,960
What year is this?

136
00:13:23,060 --> 00:13:24,628
It's the Viking age.

137
00:13:24,727 --> 00:13:27,260
That explains the Laser-Raptor.
Fuck!

138
00:13:27,360 --> 00:13:29,361
I went too far back in time.

139
00:13:29,461 --> 00:13:31,427
You need to get out
of this valley.

140
00:13:31,527 --> 00:13:33,827
This place is swarming
with Laser-Raptors.

141
00:13:33,927 --> 00:13:37,260
I'll meet you at the God's drop.
Katana can help you get there.

142
00:13:37,360 --> 00:13:39,027
Who's Katana?

143
00:13:39,127 --> 00:13:40,261
I'm Katana.

144
00:13:43,860 --> 00:13:46,194
I can give you a ride to Asgard.

145
00:13:46,294 --> 00:13:48,061
A ride on what?

146
00:14:10,127 --> 00:14:12,394
So, who are you?

147
00:14:12,494 --> 00:14:15,294
I'm a cop from the future.

148
00:14:15,394 --> 00:14:17,494
I was sent back in time
to kill Hitler,

149
00:14:17,594 --> 00:14:22,061
but I accidently went
too far back in time

150
00:14:22,161 --> 00:14:23,495
and ended up in this place.

151
00:14:26,027 --> 00:14:28,894
I know someone
who might be able to help you.

152
00:14:32,860 --> 00:14:37,094
Thor!

153
00:14:51,827 --> 00:14:54,626
Behold! It is me, Thor!

154
00:14:54,726 --> 00:14:57,660
Son of Odin
and protector of mankind.

155
00:14:57,760 --> 00:14:59,693
Check out my pecs.

156
00:14:59,793 --> 00:15:01,194
Your pecs are epic.

157
00:15:01,294 --> 00:15:02,660
Thanks bro!

158
00:15:07,127 --> 00:15:09,495
So, anyway.

159
00:15:09,594 --> 00:15:13,060
Thor, this is Kung Fury,
he's a cop from the future.

160
00:15:13,160 --> 00:15:16,693
Yeah, I need to get to
Nazi Germany and kill Hitler...

161
00:15:16,793 --> 00:15:19,261
- so if you could help me with--
- Stop!

162
00:15:21,261 --> 00:15:22,660
Hammer time.

163
00:15:26,494 --> 00:15:31,261
Walk through this portal and
you'll end up in Nazi Germany.

164
00:15:31,361 --> 00:15:33,894
Good luck to you Kung Fury!

165
00:15:33,994 --> 00:15:35,061
Thanks Thor!

166
00:15:41,694 --> 00:15:44,528
Well,
looks like this is my ride.

167
00:15:44,627 --> 00:15:48,161
Hey, future cop,
where are you going?

168
00:15:52,560 --> 00:15:55,627
You know what.
Here, take my number.

169
00:15:56,527 --> 00:15:58,760
And use this phone to call me.

170
00:15:58,860 --> 00:16:01,860
It's a personal, transportable,
cellular telephone.

171
00:16:01,960 --> 00:16:05,227
It features 645 channel
capacity,

172
00:16:05,327 --> 00:16:09,560
10 number speed dial,
and an electronic security lock.

173
00:16:09,660 --> 00:16:12,927
This revolution in communication
could make it possible

174
00:16:13,027 --> 00:16:16,127
for more and more people
to have a phone in their car!

175
00:17:34,894 --> 00:17:36,593
Tank you.

176
00:17:44,593 --> 00:17:49,493
I'm the greatest Kung Fu master
of all time,

177
00:17:49,593 --> 00:17:50,894
right guys?

178
00:17:58,127 --> 00:18:00,560
Thank you!

179
00:18:13,660 --> 00:18:15,493
I'm disarming you.

180
00:18:15,593 --> 00:18:17,660
My arm! My arm!

181
00:18:31,427 --> 00:18:32,627
Kill him!

182
00:20:04,893 --> 00:20:06,560
You don't need that spine,

183
00:20:08,693 --> 00:20:10,094
it's holding your back!

184
00:20:40,094 --> 00:20:41,227
A-ha!

185
00:20:41,326 --> 00:20:42,726
Fuck you Kung Fury.

186
00:20:42,827 --> 00:20:46,793
Now nothing can stop me
and my army of death.

187
00:20:58,993 --> 00:21:00,228
Thank you guys!

188
00:21:07,393 --> 00:21:08,827
What the fuck?

189
00:21:52,493 --> 00:21:53,793
Kill them!

190
00:22:48,961 --> 00:22:54,260
Alright Hitler, the gig is up,
show me your hands.

191
00:23:12,093 --> 00:23:15,160
Hackerman,
have you seen Kung Fury?

192
00:23:17,426 --> 00:23:19,927
Oh, no! We were too late.

193
00:23:57,427 --> 00:23:59,027
Who the hell are you?

194
00:23:59,126 --> 00:24:02,226
My name is Cobra.

195
00:24:02,326 --> 00:24:05,961
I've been expecting you
Kung Fury.

196
00:24:06,060 --> 00:24:08,293
I'm your spirit animal.

197
00:24:08,393 --> 00:24:10,260
What the hell is this place?

198
00:24:10,360 --> 00:24:14,760
This is heaven,
I'm afraid you're dead.

199
00:24:15,460 --> 00:24:16,961
What?

200
00:24:17,060 --> 00:24:19,360
But it looks so real.

201
00:24:19,460 --> 00:24:23,593
Yeah, no it's totally real.

202
00:24:23,693 --> 00:24:25,826
Mr. Cobra, I'm a police officer.

203
00:24:25,927 --> 00:24:29,293
I need you to send me
back to earth, pronto.

204
00:24:29,393 --> 00:24:31,593
I'm sorry,
I can't help you with that.

205
00:24:31,693 --> 00:24:34,392
You see, you're dead.

206
00:24:34,493 --> 00:24:36,727
- You're under arrest!
- What?

207
00:24:36,827 --> 00:24:41,493
For obstruction of justice,
you're breaking the law!

208
00:24:55,226 --> 00:24:56,760
What the hell happened?

209
00:24:56,860 --> 00:24:59,493
I hacked away all of
your bullet wounds Kung Fury.

210
00:24:59,593 --> 00:25:00,827
Thanks!

211
00:25:22,060 --> 00:25:26,026
I want to welcome you
and your friends to Germany.

212
00:25:28,760 --> 00:25:31,427
We are not so different,
you and I.

213
00:25:31,527 --> 00:25:34,927
I mean we both got
good style, you know?

214
00:25:35,026 --> 00:25:36,694
Red, you know?

215
00:25:37,393 --> 00:25:38,660
So, that's cool!

216
00:25:40,927 --> 00:25:44,260
We both like doing moves,
check it out!

217
00:25:46,360 --> 00:25:50,594
And killing people, I love it,
you clearly do, too!

218
00:25:51,493 --> 00:25:52,927
And that's cool!

219
00:25:54,126 --> 00:25:55,560
Join me,

220
00:25:55,660 --> 00:25:59,026
we could be brothers,
we are so alike.

221
00:25:59,126 --> 00:26:01,927
It's almost like
we finish each other's...

222
00:26:02,026 --> 00:26:03,560
- Balls.
- What?

223
00:26:25,959 --> 00:26:28,327
Oh, my,
not much left of him is there?

224
00:26:28,427 --> 00:26:30,293
The important thing is that
he is gone.

225
00:26:31,693 --> 00:26:33,726
Sorry I doubted you Triceracop.

226
00:26:33,827 --> 00:26:35,760
You're the best damn partner
I've ever had.

227
00:26:35,860 --> 00:26:38,926
I came back in time
for you Kung Fury,

228
00:26:39,026 --> 00:26:41,326
because, damn it,
I love you.

229
00:26:45,360 --> 00:26:48,660
Team work is very important.

230
00:26:49,992 --> 00:26:53,026
So, what happens now Kung Fury?

231
00:26:55,892 --> 00:26:58,160
Well, I need to
head back to the office.

232
00:27:00,026 --> 00:27:02,660
Looks like it's gonna be
hell of a lot of paperwork.

233
00:27:25,260 --> 00:27:26,693
Open the doors, Hoff.

234
00:27:26,793 --> 00:27:29,527
I'm sorry Fury,
I can't let you do that.

235
00:27:29,627 --> 00:27:31,327
Open the doors, Hoff!

236
00:27:31,427 --> 00:27:34,626
I'm sorry, I can't let you
open the doors Kung Fury.

237
00:27:34,726 --> 00:27:36,359
Goddammit, open the doors!

238
00:27:36,459 --> 00:27:40,060
- Sorry I can't--
- Open the doors!

239
00:27:40,160 --> 00:27:45,660
Did anyone ever tell you
not to hassle the Hoff 9000?

240
00:27:45,760 --> 00:27:48,794
Oh, Hoff 9000,
you son of a bitch.

241
00:28:03,326 --> 00:28:05,359
Piece of shit.

242
00:28:21,193 --> 00:28:23,426
Oh, my, not much left of him is there?

243
00:28:23,526 --> 00:28:26,892
The important thing is that
he is gone.

244
00:28:38,627 --> 00:28:40,093
Game over.

245
00:28:41,726 --> 00:28:43,160
Wait a minute,

246
00:28:44,760 --> 00:28:47,093
I've seen that symbol before...

247
00:28:49,260 --> 00:28:50,627
somewhere.

248
00:29:00,026 --> 00:29:01,226
Hitler!

