Hi.
My name's Jimmy Livingston.
My mom says when I was born...
I came gift-wrapped
from Heaven.
Aaah!
Whoa! Whoa!
Well,
I guess this is growing up
My first memories
are kind of hazy.
All I remember is
a place with white walls...
bright lights,
and a gigantic bird.
I was there because I was born
with no immunities.
A single germ could kill me.
But when I was four,
my mom took me home...
to beautiful
Palmdale, California.
Mom helped me
make friends right away.
Let's go.
Get him in!
Our house was enormous
like a castle...
and for the first time,
I felt completely free.
There.
Now you're safe from
that evil, filthy world.
You're home, Jimmy!
And you'll never, ever, ever
have to go out there again.
Look at that.
Look what Mommy made for Jimmy.
I had a big room
with my own bed...
Lots of toys...
and two pairs
of retractable arms.
"And the prince climbed to
the top of the tower and said...
'Come with me...
and we'll live
happily ever after.'
"And Rapunzel left
her plastic bubble and died."
The End.
Those evil doctors.
Nobody's gonna get any germs
on my little boy now.
You'll always stay pure.
Won't you, Jimmy?
Jimmy! Breakfie!
I had my reading.
I wish they had more than
one magazine in the world, Mom.
So do l, dear.
My favorite TV show,
"Land of the Lost. "
I wish TVs had more
than one channel, Mom.
So do l, dear.
And I had
the best teacher...
in the whole, wide world.
And then the Indians...
decided to move
to the reservations...
where they
could open casinos...
and sell
tax-free cigarettes...
and stay out of
the white man's way.
Another A-plus.
The neighborhood kids always
wanted to hang at my house.
Lives in a bubble,
smells like poop
Bubble boy, bubble boy
Get out of here,
you little buggers! Go on!
But I liked
to hang with my dad.
Holy mother of shit, Morton!
Are you trying to kill
him with that thing?
Jimmy, lunchie.
Suppertime was the best.
Nothing could beat Mom's
homemade, vitamin-rich...
soy-based, germ-free,
fat-free fiber cookies.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
I grew up
like any other kid.
At 16,
I didn't get a car...
but I did get an electrical
rock-music guitar!
I can't
believe the things I found
I need to find my way
I'm lost, I'm lost
I do believe I'm living
In the Land
Of the Lost
I'm living in the Land
Living in the Land
Of the Lost
I was so happy.
I had everything
a boy could ever want.
Until...
Chloe.
"And then Pinocchio came out
of his plastic bubble...
"touched the filthy little
whore next door and died."
The End.
Ooh, baby
Ahh
Oh, yeah
Over the next few years...
I washed my window a lot.
Oh, my
Something
was happening to me.
But I didn't know what.
Mom!
-Jimmy! What's the matter?
-Mom!
Are you all right?
-What is it?
-Oh! Oh, my God!
Ow!
Don't touch it! Hands off!
Now, just relax,
don't get upset.
It hurts!
Just do what
I tell your father--
just say the pledge
of allegiance...
until it goes away.
Come on!
I pledge allegiance
to the flag...
of the United States
of America...
and to the republic
for which it stands...
one nation under God,
indivisible...
with liberty and justice
for all.
I pledge allegiance
to the flag...
of the United States
of America...
and to the republic
for which it stands...
one nation under God...
Thanks, Mom.
Can't touch this
Can't touch this...
Dude!
You live next door
to the bubble boy.
Know what I heard?
The only thing he can drink
is his own urine.
True story. Swear to God.
I heard the same thing, man.
It's gross.
Then what did he drink
to make the urine?
Well, it would...
Tell her.
Shotgun!
He's not a monster, you guys.
He's just a boy in a bubble.
I am not a monster.
I'm a human being.
-Bye, Lisa.
-Bye, Chloe.
I wish I was the boy
in her bubble.
Oh, yeah!
Let's hit the arcade.
Hi, Mr. Livingston?
I'm Chloe.
I live...next door.
Hyah!
Oh, my gosh!
-What?
-Are you OK?
What?
Wait, no, no, no.
I was just playing.
Mayday! You know, that.
Oh.
Ahem.
Was that Pakuni
you were speaking?
From "Land of the Lost"?
I love "Land of the Lost."
I love you, too.
It! It, too.
I love it, too.
-I'm Jimmy.
-I'm--
Chloe, the whore next door.
What?
Where did you hear that?
My mom.
She teaches me everything.
Well, really she got it wrong.
I'm actually more of a bitch
than a whore.
A bitch. Oh, yeah.
A bitch.
Absolutely, a bitch.
Yeah.
You play guitar?
Oh, yeah!
Do you wanna try it?
Oh, no, I don't know how.
I could teach you.
Right now.
I can't right now.
I should go.
How about tomorrow?
Oh, jeez, I don't know.
I don't know, bitch.
I got a lot to do.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
She's certainly proud of
those boobies, isn't she?
Something tells me she's not...
the kind of friend
Jesus would pick, Jimmy.
When I look
All a--round
Oh, I suck.
No, no. Come here.
You have to press harder.
-OK.
-Harder. Here.
-Like...
-Now go. Harder.
When I look
All around
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the republic
for which it stands...
one nation under God...
Everything OK?
Yeah. Let's go.
Wouldn't it be nice
If we were older
And we wouldn't have
to wait so long
And wouldn't it be nice
to live together
In the kind of world
where we belong
I know it's gonna make it
that much better
When we can say good night...
Trick or treat!
Smell my feet!
Oh, hey!
Aah!
In the morning
when the day is new...
It's Bubble Guinea.
Oh, my God!
Hi, Bubble Guinea.
Jimmy!
Ow! Ah!
Stupid gutter.
Jimmy! Ah! Ouch.
Jimmy. Ahh. Hello.
Chloe?
Yeah. Bubble Boy!
What about your party?
Jimmy, you have to wish me
happy birthday.
What about your party?
Uhh, the party.
I'll show you a party.
Come here.
-Don't be shy.
-Huh?
Come here.
My mom's asleep.
Don't you wanna give me
a birthday kiss?
Chloe. Heh heh. Shh.
Shh.
Whoa! Oh, Chloe!
I hate this stupid bubble.
I got everything
I wanted for my birthday...
except you, Jimmy.
That's why I'm coming in.
Chloe, wait! Whoa, whoa.
Don't worry.
You can decontaminate me.
-Hee hee hee.
-What?
Relax. Have a beer.
Wait, um, wait. Chloe?
I'm not so sure
that's such a good idea.
Jimmy.
Jimmy. Please let me in.
Oh, baby
Please?
Ahh
Chloe?
I...
Maybe
I should have let her in...
but I was scared.
So who could really blame her
for what happened next?
Hold on.
You look beautif--
Oh, hi.
Ooh, corsage.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mark, Jimmy. Jimmy, Mark.
'Sup, Jimbo?
'Sup, Marko?
You ready?
Yeah. Just let me
use the bathroom.
All right.
Pinch it quick.
-She loves that one.
-Hmm.
-Cigarette?
-What?
So Chloe tells me
you're a musician.
Well, I rock,
if that's what you mean.
Ahh
You know?
So, what are you guys
gonna do tonight?
You know,
a little bit of this.
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's it, ahh.
Oh, oh!
That's it. Ohh!
Sounds like fun.
All right. All ready.
That's how I do it on stage.
Did I tell you
how beautiful you look?
Come here.
I'm gonna be
the luckiest guy at the prom.
One thing was for sure.
Mark was cool.
Bye, Jimmy.
Who could compete
with a guy like that?
-Hands.
-I'm sorry.
Come on, Chloe.
We've been going out
for two years...
I want a little action.
Mark, I told you--
I want to wait
till I get married.
Hands.
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen.
All women
will leave you someday.
That girl didn't love you.
She just felt sorry for you.
You think she'd marry a boy
who couldn't even touch her?
Hey.
Hi.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah. You know Mark?
We've sorta been going out
off and on for a while now...
and, um...
Well, he kind of asked me to...
-To go fishing?
-No!
-To go to the movies?
-To get married?
-Yes!
The wedding's this Saturday
in Niagara Falls.
I didn't know how to tell you,
Jimmy, because...
The thing is, um...
I really wanted to know...
if you think
he's the right one...
because it's such a big step,
you know? And...
Jimmy?
I made you something.
Take Bubble Guinea Pig.
I don't want him anymore.
So that's it?
That's all
you're going to say?
Bye, Jimmy.
Good-bye.
Can you still remember
How it seemed
That we could live forever
In a lovers' dream?
The falling
was the best part
But now you know
The things you cling to
Your heart can start to grow
You, you're walking away
I've been there
Now I know what to say
I'm the king of yesterday
Why don't,
why don't you stay
Chloe!
God...bless America!
That nasty little slut...
Left just in
the nick of time, Morton.
I had no idea
what I was up against.
Chloe hadn't told me much.
All I knew was that
she was in New York...
which may as well been on
the other side of the galaxy...
and I only had
three days to get there.
Three days.
I just needed the bubble suit
to last that long.
Flying high now
I'm so high now
Ooh!
Ooh! Oh, oh, oh!
Getting strong now
Moving on now
Uhh!
Aah!
Grass.
Street lamp.
Oh.
Ooh.
Dog poop!
This is awesome!
I'm running!
Well, I guess
this is growing up
Hello? Hello?
Hi. It's my first day
out in the world.
I'd like to go
to Niagara Falls.
That'll be $260.
Plus I gotta charge you
for an additional seat...
for that...stupid thing
you're wearing.
Oh, money. Oh. Money.
How far will this get me?
Take a step back.
That far.
Um...
the girl I love
is getting married...
and I have
to stop the wedding.
That's fantastic.
Next!
Next in line, please.
OK. Have a nice day.
The white zone's
for loading and unloading only.
Hey, are you all right?
-Are you all right?
-What is it?
Oh, he's alive!
I need to get
to Niagara Falls...
by Saturday to stop Chloe
from getting married.
-I'm Todd.
-And I'm Lorraine.
And we can get you
to Niagara Falls.
Yeah!
Bright and shiny!
Stick him in the rear!
Bright
And shiny
People all across the land
Come and join our happy band
Always happy, never gay
Living clean is A-OK
Bright
And shiny...
Excuse me, Todd.
And shiny
If you save yourself
for God
You will get the golden rod
Give up on society
We will be your family
Bright
And shiny
Jimmy! Breakfie!
Jimmy!
The Kloobda.
The Kloobda is
the holy guide to living pure...
dictated to Gil
by a talking salamander.
But more on that later.
This will help explain.
Put it
in the decontamination bay.
Right there.
First,
we prepare our souls...
by stripping ourselves
of all material possessions...
and sexual desires.
Ha ha ha ha!
-Kool-aid, Lorraine?
-Thanks, Lorraine.
-Lorraine?
-Ooh!
Her name's Lorraine, too?
We're all Lorraine.
And you will be Todd...
a name chosen
especially for you by Gil.
What does Bill
do with all your stuff?
He's holding it for us
at the compound.
Where's the compound?
I'm not really sure.
In Texas?
Oh. You're not
a singing group...
you're a cult!
Ha ha ha!
Why'd we stop?
This isn't Niagara Falls!
This is a desert!
Yes--yes, I realize
that in typical cases...
you have to wait 48 hours.
But this is not a typical case.
My son is a bubble boy.
He'll die out there!
Well, you'll certainly be
in my prayers tonight.
And I'll be praying
you get nut cancer!
All right, Plan B.
Did you finish the note?
Come on.
"Mr. and Mrs. Livingston,
we have kidnapped your son.
"Pay $1 00,000 or he dies.
Signed, the Jews."
Are you kidding?
Are you kidding me?
Who in their right mind
is gonna believe this note?
It's the Jews, Morton!
They're gonna want
more than $1 00,000!
Think, man, think!
I'm havin' a bad day
Havin' a bad day
So get out of my way
'Cause I'm havin' a bad day
Uhh!
Havin' a bad day
Get out of my way
'Cause I'm havin' a bad day
Havin' a bad day
Get off!
Get out of my way...
Uhh! Aah!
Have you seen my son?
Hello?
I think he's deaf.
Have you seen my boy?
Your weird-ass son
got on a bus...
full of happy people skipping
around all over the place...
and they headed towards Vegas.
You know, Satan's anus.
Thank you.
You filthy, fat,
filthy deaf man!
I heard that.
Mort, let's move it!
I'll have you know
that I've lost two pounds.
I have my ankle weights
on right now...
and it's very hot in here
and I'm losing weight.
I've lost four pounds
in the last two months.
Havin' a bad day
Get out of my way
'Cause I'm havin' a bad day
I'm havin' a bad day
Get out of my way
Hey!
-Hey, hey!
-Whoa!
What are you...
some kind of astronaut?
No, I'm some kind
of bubble boy.
How do you take a dump
in that thing?
I think I could help you
with your situation here.
How's some bubble vato
gonna help me?
I got patches.
Patches?
I could use
some stinkin' patches.
-Gil!
-Gil, we love you!
Welcome, my children.
Welcome.
Today will truly be a time
of spiritual illumination.
Now, can anyone guess
why we're all here?
-Ooh!
-Ooh, me!
Yes, Todd.
No, the other Todd.
To find out the final
incarnation of the Chosen One?
Exactly.
I can see you've been
reading your Kloobda.
The Chosen One is among us!
He walks the earth.
His final incarnation
will be...
A round one!
Yes, the round one.
The holy messenger
trapped in a living globe.
We must find him
and release him...
so that he may carry us...
only true believers,
to the kingdom of Heaven.
And those who reject him
will mutate...
and burn eternally
on Planet PX-41 .
Or PX-42,
if they run out of room.
If there are
no further questions...
Let's move on to the buffet.
So they kicked you
out of the bus...
in the middle of the desert
to die like some perro?
Yep.
Where you headed?
Niagara Falls. I gotta
get there by Saturday...
to stop Chloe from marrying
the wrong man.
Ha ha ha!
Let's cut the vato, ese!
I wasn't planning on
cutting the vato, no.
Somebody run off
with your old lady...
Legally
you're allowed to cut him.
She wasn't
technically my old lady.
I just never...
I just never told her
how I felt.
When I was your age,
I was in love with a woman.
-Debbie?
-No.
-Danielle.
-No. Wildfire!
Oh, Wildfire!
She looks really nice.
Yeah, but she left me
for some other vato.
You know,
real buttoned-down...
"I gotta get a job"
kind of vato, you know?
To this day, ese,
I regret not finding him...
and cutting his heart out
in a really violent way.
Don't be like me, ese.
Don't live in regret.
We'll be riding wildfire
We'll be riding
Ohh!
Wildfire
I'm OK.
Look at the lights!
Now this is
Las Vegas, Jimmy!
Wow!
Paris!
That's beautiful, ain't it?
And New York!
That's big New York.
This is amazing, Slim.
Ha ha ha ha!
Go faster! Go faster!
You like the wind
in your hair?
-Yeah.
-Ha ha ha!
"We have the loosest sluts."
That's "slots"!
I'll show you how to play
the slot machines.
We can win some gas money
to get to Niagara Falls!
All right, chicas!
-Chicas!
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ow! Ha ha ha!
This is amazing!
This town
never goes to sleep.
We'll do some partying!
Whoa! Oh, no!
Wow! Oh ho!
Ha ha ha ha! Whoo!
Jimmy!
Where are you, baby?
My baby Jimmy?
Here we go. Oh, yeah.
Coming through.
Excuse us.
Come on,
talk to me, babies.
Lookin' good!
Yes, all right.
-Slim?
-Yeah.
What's it like?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I could tell you what it was
like with me and Wildfire.
1,200 CCs of American steel
vibrating between your legs.
Oh, man.
I'm talking fourth gear.
4,000 RPMs! Ay!
Ha ha ha ha!
That sounds amazing!
Ha ha!
-Hors d'oeuvres?
-Oh, no, thanks.
I got my own.
OK. Last one.
You go for it!
Oh, no. I couldn't.
Go on.
You want to win the money
for our trip, don't you?
But what if I lose again?
You didn't get out of that
bubble room to play it safe.
You're right.
Go for it.
Oh! I'm tapped out.
I'm gonna steal some quarters
from that blind lady.
Slim, I don't think--
I gotta go.
I only have two days--
No, Slim! I gotta go!
I only have two days left!
-It'll be awesome!
-I only have two days left!
Bow-wow
ba-ba-ba bow-wow
Ba-ba-ba-ba
Bow-wow
ba-ba-ba bow-wow
Ba-ba-ba-ba
Bow-wow ba-ba-ba bow
Rrrow-wow
ba-ba-ba bow-wow
I didn't like leaving Slim
without saying good-bye...
but I knew the vato
would understand.
The wedding
was two days away...
and I only had 12 CCs of
American steel to get me there.
Don't think I can't see you
gawking at those neon boobies.
Just keep your eye
on the road, mister.
Hey, have you seen
my little buddy?
He's got frizzy hair,
and he's in a bubble.
Hey, what's up?
Uhh!
Have you seen
this little bubble guy, ma'am?
I didn't mean it.
Excuse. Hola.
We're a bit lost.
Could you tell us the way to--
Niagara Falls?
I beg your pardon?
'Cause that's where
my little buddy was headed...
when you left him
in the desert to die!
Come back!
You Bright and Shinies--
come back and get shiny
on my knife!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Aah!
This looks like Area 51 .
Holy mother of shit, Morton!
What is that?
A space creature? An alien?
Oh, my God! Jimmy!
Bow-wow
ba-ba-ba bow-wow
Ba-ba-ba-ba
Jimmy!
Stop the car!
Aah!
Uhh! Aah!
I wasn't quite sure
just how I'd gotten on board...
but I'd always dreamed
of riding a train.
Thank goodness
the worst was behind me...
or so I thought.
RUBBER WO
Look, he's awake.
What are we going to do?
Aah!
-Aah!
Shh!
Dr. Phreak is gonna hear you!
-What?
-He'll hear you. Hide!
What did you say?
He said be quiet or
the doctor will hear you. Shh!
Who are you?
They call me
the Human Sasquatch.
What's your real name?
Um...Clark?
So what's your deal?
Why are you in a bubble?
To protect me from germs.
I was born
without any immunities...
so even a single one
could kill me.
But your doctor
would know all about that.
Be quiet!
He's gonna come!
He's not your average doctor.
He's Dr. Phreak.
We're all part of
his traveling Phreak Show.
He owns us.
-Owns you?!
-Shh!
Be quiet!
Here comes Dr. Phreak!
He's an ex-con.
If he finds you in this train,
he'll own you, too.
Now you did it, bubble butt.
Here he comes!
Run for your life!
He's a vicious brute.
You're Dr. Phreak?
Ha ha ha ha!
You're so mini! Ha ha ha!
-Mini? Oh, no!
-No!
Me, mini?! I'm not mini!
I'm not mini!
Not! Not! Not!
Who the hell are you?
He's the bubble boy.
Shut your beak!
What are you doing
out of your coop?
I shut up.
I could use
some fresh meat in my show.
Why don't you hop
your little bubble butt...
back on that train?
Thanks, but, um...
I gotta get to
Niagara Falls by Saturday...
to stop Chloe
from getting married.
That's so, so beautiful.
I, too, once loved another.
-You did?
-For 1 0 minutes.
Then I kicked her ass
out of the car.
Well, I gotta get going.
Going?!
-Oh!
What are you gonna do?
You're a freak,
and I should know.
That's my business.
No decent girl wants
to marry a bubble freak.
Once you get that through
your thick, freaky skull...
then give me a call.
What's wrong with being a freak?
Aah!
-Oh!
-Oh! That hurt!
Doctor?
Is he OK?
I didn't mean to...
He looks so sweet
when he's not yelling.
You've killed him.
-What are we going to do?
-Whoa!
Good luck! Bye!
Uhh! Heads up, Bubble!
OK. Bye!
Get your own bags!
What do you think I am--bellhop?
Hey, where are you guys going?
We're going with you,
Dr. Bubble.
We're going with you.
Dr. Bubble? No, no!
You guys are free.
You can do whatever
you want now.
Oh, we're free!
Free as a bird!
On to Niagara Falls!
All the way!
Oh, I love it!
Look, you guys...
I gotta do this alone.
Oh, yeah.
Bye!
It sure was nice...
of the train man
to loan me his vehicle...
but if l was gonna make it
to the wedding on time...
I had to find something
with a motor.
Oh, my God!
He ain't eating meat!
Can you all believe it?
It's tofu!
Tofu!
Could anybody
give me a ride?
Tofu gives me such gas!
Bloody red meat!
Rare American meat!
That's the stupidest-looking hat
I've ever seen.
It's adorable!
Hey! Hey!
Stop picking on him.
-Oh!
I don't want any trouble.
I'm just--
Really?
Sissy beach ball!
Why are you
in that bubble, boy?
Huh?
Because I was born
without any immunities--
Immunities?!
What the hell are immunities?
Well, I ain't sticking
around to find out!
Me, neither.
Everybody out!
He's got immunities!
-No, no, no!
-He's contagious!
I don't have any immunities!
Don't try to change
your story now, boy!
I don't have germs!
I'm not contagious!
I just need a ride!
I need a ride!
I hereby declare
this place quarantined!
I don't have germs!
Oh! Ohh!
What's going on, Sheriff?
Oh!
Guys, I think
your building's on fire.
Carl Peterson's
best pig just died!
It's spreading!
Burn, baby, burn
Disco inferno
Burn that mother down,
y'all
Burn, baby, burn
Disco inferno
Whoo! Just like Calcutta
in the summer!
Come! Follow me!
Come on!
Whoa!
I don't think I'm in!
Stop messing about!
This whole town
is going to blow!
Ha ha ha ha! Boy, howdy!
Now, that's a good fire!
Heh heh heh!
Uh-oh.
Disco inferno, yeah
Burn the mother down
Burn, baby, burn
Ice cream! ice cream!
Curry!
Let's go. Come on.
Watch out for the feet.
I told you before.
Look out!
Coming through!
I'm on the run!
Morton, that's the one!
Jimmy! Jimmy! We're here!
Morton, get this thing open.
Jimmy?!
Jimmy--Ooh!
Look at this cute
little boy, Morton!
Can you tell me,
have you seen my son?
He's wearing
a large plastic bubble suit.
I know what you want.
I'll give you some candy.
He stole my freaks,
that son of a bitch!
Oh! What a potty mouth
you have!
Where was he going?
Screw you, lady!
Aah!
Thanks.
Thanks for
saving me back there.
You're welcome.
Those were some crazy vatos.
For some unknown reason,
Shiva has brought you...
into my life
like a hot flash.
You came to my defense...
and the law of karma
requires me to return the favor.
This ice cream truck
is merely a catalyst...
a way to teach
the wisdom of the Sacred Cow.
For who can resist
ice cream, eh?
I know I can't.
So, how may I be
of service to you...
my Zip-locked friend?
I need to get to
Niagara Falls by Saturday...
to stop Chloe
from getting married.
Oh. I was thinking...
more along the lines
of a free snow cone...
but, OK,
Niagara Falls it is.
Livin' in
the Land of the Lost
Livin' in the Land...
No way is this better
than "Jurassic Park."
I can't believe you and
bubble geek like this show.
The effects look totally fake.
That's the whole point.
What?
It's supposed to look fake?
I'm not here.
Hello?
What have you done
with my son?
Mrs. Livingston?
Is he with you?
How could he be here?
Well, apparently
he's on his way...
to your wedding
in a bubble suit...
exposing himself to
all the wickedness and filth...
this world has to offer!
And you're responsible!
Come on! Over here! Come on!
-Come on!
-Over here!
-Come on! This way!
-Come on!
Let's go, Morton.
Correction. You two
aren't going anywhere...
until I get my freaks back.
Don't you take that tone
of voice with me, young man!
Morton, are you gonna let him
talk to me like that?
Yeah, Mort. Are ya?
-My car!
-My freaks!
Help! Jimmy!
Aah! Jimmy!
Help!
Hang on! Hang on!
Aah!
Screw you, Grumpy!
Hop on, babe.
Thanks for saving me, Mark.
How do you do it?
Immunities, baby.
Immunities.
-Aah!
Oh, dear.
Oh! Oh!
Look at that.
It's an elk.
Or is it a caribou?
Or an American bison?
l, uh...
I think that it's a cow.
Oh, really?! A cow?!
I didn't know.
What have I done?
It's just a cow, Pushpop.
Just a cow?
Just a cow?!
In my religion,
the cow is the womb...
from which all life springs!
Heh heh heh!
I have transgressed
against Shiva!
Shiva?
The six-armed goddess.
Have you ever been
karmically bitch-slapped...
by a six-armed goddess?
I'll take that as a no!
Oh! Um...
It's OK, Pushpop.
Your religion's all lies.
Pardon?
That's what my mom says.
I mean...
Bollocks.
I must atone.
His mother taught him.
What nonsense.
May Shiva
shine upon your journey!
Well, can't we...
can't we drive and atone?
No! One for the road.
What? No, no, no.
There are germs in here!
Frozen! No germs!
No germs?
When did this happen?
Thanks for the lift!
So long!
Ice cream
It was one thing
that my mom...
had never heard of
the bitch-slapping goddess...
but it seemed like everybody
should have heard...
offrozen,
germ-free ice cream.
Ohh!
Everybody loves ice cream.
Stripper.
Dykes.
Dear Lord,
if Thou findest...
the stealing of this truck
offensive in any way...
please direct Thy wrath
upon that midget...
and not upon us,
Thy humble servants. Amen.
All right.
Let's haul ass.
One of you drive.
I can't reach the pedals.
Upsy-daisy. Whoo!
I am coming back
as a cockroach.
Definitely a cockroach.
Aah!
Oh ho ho! Oh ho ho!
Aah! Aah!
Now, we don't know where
those hands have been, do we?
Rub them together.
Kill those germs!
That's right.
Good boy.
No! Stop!
Show some respect!
Hey! Yo, hippie!
You seen a big, yellow bus
with a lot of bright...
and shiny cabrones
pass through here?
No, sir.
I don't believe I have.
You got any bomb pops
on that truck?
Oh, yes. Please,
take the whole damn truck.
All right!
Who wants a blue one?
Everything is A-OK
Bright and shiny
Uhh! Uhh!
What have I done?
You OK?
Yeah.
It's just--
Jimmy's my best friend.
We basically spent every day
together in high school.
Yeah? Did you ever...
you know,
get in his bubble?
No.
Not that I didn't
think about it, though.
I know what you mean.
I used to play
"Spin the bottle"...
with the kid from
Special Ed. Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Well.
It would've never worked out
between the two of us.
Yeah. Rubber comes in handy
every once in a while...
but let's not go overboard.
You're way better off
with my brother.
Yeah. Way better off.
Take a little time
Throw it on the line
Let me believe
That you believe in me
Baby, turn around
Look at what I found
You're the one that I want
Take a little time
Throw it on the line
Let me believe
That you believe in me
Stand and turn around
Look at what I found
You were the one that I wanted
Take a little time
Throw it on the line
Let me believe
That you believe in me
Baby, turn around
Look at what I found
You were the one that I wanted
Taxi! Taxi!
Hi! I need to get
to Niagara Falls by tomorrow.
Can you take me there?
-Depends.
-On what?
Goin' that far I'll have
to get me some Depends.
And 500 smackers!
$500?!
Where am I gonna get $500?
Who wants to be next?
Who wants the $500?
Now, we need
some fresh blood here!
Whoa! Spotlight
on the dance floor!
Whoa, I like the look of this!
Mr. Alien, is it?
What are you doing here, dummy?
I saw the sign outside...
and it said that you
have $500, and so...
You want $500?
Yes. I would like $500.
Yes. Please, I would like $500.
You want $500?
Yes, I want $500!
-$500!
All right!
Our next contestant,
Mr. Alien!
Red Hot, Working Girl,
bring him on over!
A big cheer for Mr. Alien!
Mud! Mud! Mud! Mud!
Mud! Mud! Mud!
-$500!
Aah! Hey!
Whoa! Oh, whoa!
-Unh!
$500!
Bubble Boy! Bubble Boy!
Goddess Shiva,
I really need that money!
I pledge allegiance
to the flag...
of the United States
of America...
and to the republic
for which it stands!
Ha ha ha!
We have winner!
Winner! Winner! Winner!
Bitch-slap me, Jesus
I've lost my way
Strayed from your path
Yet I pray
Who let the dogs out
Woof woof woof
Morton!
I was listening to that!
Yeah, Mort.
A girl can't get five minutes
of quality time with Jesus.
Man, this is some good curry!
Ha ha! Yeah!
I got the money!
Look! There he is!
I've got the money!
Ha ha!
We found you, Todd.
We know who you are.
We've come to set you free!
Ow!
You are the Chosen One!
I don't need you
to set me free!
I don't--Oh!
Wait! Wait!
Look!
Those people have Jimmy!
-Stealth!
-What the hell is that?
We've gotta get him away
from those freaks.
-What can we do?
-We need a plan.
We blend.
I got a plan.
What size shirt you wear?
And now, to avoid mutating
and burning on planet PX-41...
we release the Chosen One
using the ceremonial tweezers.
With this tiny prick,
I release thee!
No! Don't! I'll die!
It must be a test!
Where's my Kloobda?
Right there, Lorraine!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wait a minute!
You're not a Shiny!
Who are you?
Uh...Todd?
-Oh!
-Hi, Todd.
Wait a minute!
What's the matter
with your arms?
What are you talking about?
There's nothing wrong
with my arms!
We're too late!
We're mutating!
We'll get you out
through the front of the bus.
Oh, God!
Why won't you help me?
Ha ha ha ha!
He's got a bubbly face
And a bubbly nose
Mr. Bubble
Bubble, Bubblicious
The ultimate bubble.
Tiny bubbles
In the wine
I know. I miss him, too.
Come on, Bubble Boy!
Hurry up!
Come on!
This way, guys! Hurry!
This way!
Ow! Guys! Oh!
Hey! Come on! Todd!
Hey, Shinies!
We have some
unfinished business, huh?
No, no, Slim.
They're my friends.
They got him brainwashed!
No! No! No!
Wait!
Bubble, we'll help you out!
Don't worry!
I'll take you on with
one flipper behind my back!
You want
a mouthful of tuna?
Free Willy! Free Willy!
I'm gonna whup that ass!
Yeah!
Aah! Oh, my God!
Get it off of me!
Ha ha ha ha!
Niagara Falls,
and step on it!
It's the cops!
-Wait a minute!
-Don't touch me there!
Where's Bubble Boy?
You ask me if l love you
And I choke on my reply
I'd rather hurt you honestly
-Poon !
-Huh?
Chasing a dame, ain't you?
Who am I to judge you
Last time I was
in a commotion like that...
it was all on account
of Poon .
Oh, what the astronauts drink.
No, no. My wife.
My little China doll.
Yeah, till that damn
brother of mine...
took her off to Waxahachie.
Snatched my Poon
right out from under me.
86 years ago.
I ain't spoke
to that bastard since.
Don't live in regret, ese.
He's your family.
Family. Heh.
I really gotta go!
I told you, once we're on
the road we're not stopping!
Than mislead you with a lie
And after all that...
they still didn't get you
a new puppy?
No.
Ohh.
Poor little thing.
No wonder you turned out
the way you did.
Ohh.
And sometimes when we touch
The honesty's too much
Morning, Pappy.
You must be tired.
You get any sleep?
Ha ha ha!
I said, you get any sleep?
Pappy!
Pappy?
Pappy? Pappy! Stop!
Aah!
Oh! Ow!
Yow! Yeah, I'm fine.
You have a phone?
Yello.
Hello?
Hi. Is Chloe there?
Who can I say is calling?
It's Jimmy.
Oh. Hello, Jimmy.
Where the hell are you?
I'm really close.
In New York, I think.
I don't mean to burst
your bubble, Jimbo...
but if you got a thing for
Chloe, it's not gonna happen.
We're getting married
in one hour.
What are you
expecting to happen?
You can't even touch her.
How are you
gonna have children?
Do you even have sperm?
Fact it, dude,
you're a charity case.
Chloe felt sorry for you
because you lived in a bubble.
Do us all a favor.
Go on back to Palmdale
where you belong.
I wasn't quite sure what
Mark meant about the sperm...
but he was right
about one thing.
Even if l did get there...
I couldn't ever really
hold Chloe in my arms...
or kiss her for real.
I really was a freak.
Hello.
Hi, Dr. Phreak.
It's Jimmy.
Jimmy who?
The bubble boy.
Jimmy?! Give me that!
That's my phone!
Hello? Jimmy?
-Mom?
-Jimmy!
What are you doing
with Dr. Phreak?
-Where are you?
-Where are my freaks?
OK, sweetheart,
we'll be right there.
Don't move!
Morton, we've got our boy back!
Gimme that.
Aah! Ow! Ooh!
Ow! Eek! Ohh!
Son of a bitch.
Mama.
Ohh! Aah!
I never stole anything before...
and I just fell off
a dead man's car...
and my parents are about
to come pick me up...
and this is the girl
I love's favorite beer...
and I was just wondering,
could I borrow it?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Now open the safe!
Do it! Chop chop!
Ohh...
Aah!
My baby!
The sweet Lord
has delivered you from evil.
Ohh!
I must say, you put us
through heck, young man!
But I think you learned
a valuable lesson.
There's no place like home.
Morton, load him in the car.
The Spirit's burning
so strong in my bosom...
I think I have to wee-wee.
How--ahem--
how was it out here?
Was it fun?
You can see the moon today.
You know, it kind of
makes you wonder...
what would have happened
if Neil Armstrong...
had gone all the way
to the moon...
and then never
stepped on the surface.
Jimmy!
Morton, where's Jimmy?!
What happened?
Jimmy! Jimmy!
Jimmy! Come to Mommy!
No, Mom! I'm sorry!
I gotta do this!
I'm not coming home!
Jimmy!
Todd!
Todd, we love you!
We've come to set you free!
Who the hell are you?
Back off, bitch!
He's the messiah!
We love you, Todd!
Jimmy, no!
Pedal to the metal, Flippy!
Look!
I guess
this is growing up
-Hey!
-Whoa!
Oh!
Jimmy! Ha ha ha!
Vaya con dios, Bubble Boy.
Hang on, kid.
Pappy?
Aah! Shit!
Watch out!
Slim?
Wildfire?
Wildfire
What happened to you, Pappy?
I thought you were dead.
I ain't Pappy. I'm Pippy.
Ain't talked to that sumbitch
brother of mine in 86 years.
-That's on account of--
-Poon!
-Poonani!
-Poonani?
Sister to Poon.
Pappy talked about Poon...
but he never mentioned
any Poonani, Pippy.
Oh! Ha ha!
Oh, my gosh!
I made it! I made it!
Ha ha ha!
Niagara Falls!
Oh, there's the church!
There's the church!
Chloe! Ha ha ha!
Take me down, Pippy!
Take me down!
Oh, we're goin' down.
Very fast.
Pippy!
Aah!
Chloe!
You didn't break out
of that bubble room...
to play it safe.
Don't live in regret, ese.
No regrets. No regrets.
No regrets! No regrets!
No regrets!
I made it! Ha ha ha!
-Score, dude.
-Mmm. Mmm.
I'm late! I'm late!
Do you, Mark, take Chloe...
to be
your lawfully wedded wife?
To honor and cherish,
in sickness and in health...
as long as
you both shall live?
Oh, yeah.
I'm almost there!
I'm almost...
And do you, Chloe...
take Mark to be
your lawfully wedded husband...
to honor and cherish,
in sickness and in health...
as long as
you both shall live?
Come on, babe.
Easy question.
Chloe!
Don't!
Jimmy!
Hey, dude, what the hell
are you doing here?
I thought I told you
to head on home.
Just hold on a second, vato.
Vato?
Shut up!
Am I out of line here?
Chloe, l...
What?
Jimmy, what are you doing?
Jimmy?
I'd rather spend
one minute holding you...
than the rest of my life
knowing I never could.
So if you don't mind...
may I kiss the bride?
Is it me?
I love you.
-I love you, Chloe.
-Jimmy?
Forever.
OK?
Jimmy?! No!
Jimmy!
Jimmy?
I love you, Jimmy.
I've always loved you.
He's dead!
You killed him! Oh!
Ohh!
Oh, Jimmy!
My little sweet Jimmy.
Ohh.
Oh, my angel.
My precious little one.
My angel.
Tell him.
What are you talking about?
Tell him what?
You're not dead, Jimmy.
-He's lying.
-Tell him.
Tell him everything.
Ohh...
you're not dead, Jimmy.
I'm not?
Ohh!
You developed immunities
when you were four.
I couldn't let the world
ruin you with its filth!
There are so many
awful things out there.
There's so many horrible...
I love you, Mom.
Oh!
Ain't that sweet.
So...
since I'm not dead...
Wouldn't it be nice
If we were older
Then we wouldn't
have to wait so long
And wouldn't it be nice
to live together
In the kind of world
where we belong
May Shiva bless your union.
Thanks for
the ice cream cake, Pushpop.
Well said, Master.
You don't have
to follow me this closely.
Everyone!
The buffet is open!
Winner! Winner! Winner!
Here. For your honeymoon.
What is it?
$500!
-$500?
-$500!
-$500.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's a long story.
I'll tell you on the honeymoon.
Thank you.
To family.
That's right.
And my 40.
-Have fun, you two!
-You, too, Mom.
Don't worry. We will.
Hit it, Slim.
Hit it, Ace.
-To friendship.
Now we're gonna party!
Jimmy!
Congratulations, kids.
Ready to take off?
Pippy?
You're right about family, kid.
Pappy?
Poon!
Poonani! Poonani!
Wouldn't it be nice
Wouldn't it be nice,
oh, baby
Sleep tight, my baby
Good night, my baby
Sleep tight
Bright
And shiny
People all across the land
Come and join our happy band
Always happy, never gay
Livin' clean is A-OK
Bright
And shiny
If you save yourself for God
You will get the golden rod
Give up on society
We will be your family
Bright
And shiny
People all across the land
Come and join our happy band
Always happy, never gay
Livin' clean is A-OK
Bright
And shiny
If you save yourself for God
You will get the golden rod
Give up on society
We will be your family
Bright
And shiny
Oh, I love Cadillacs!
-Shotgun!
-Shut up, Chicken!