One Year Ago.
And now give it up for Sonny Munroe!
Thank you so much, West appleton high.
I can't believe one week from today
I will be leaving Wisconsin
to go to Hollywood!
And it's a good thing too, because
I didn't finish my book report.
Boo!
Sorry, Mr. Henderson.
But I promise exactly one year from today
I will be back for homecoming to
accept West appleton's highest honor,
The firing of the cheese cannon...
And to deliver my book report.
And even though I'll be leaving Wisconsin,
I will always have cheese in my heart.
♪ gouda, havarti, cheddar and Jack ♪
♪ Wisconsin cheese
is an awesome snack! ♪.
All right, now in honor of Sonny's
first year on "So Random!"
I'd like to take a moment to
say a few heartfelt words:
Here comes cake.
Guys, I feel so loved.
Oh.
"Sonny Munroe is a phony."
Marshall, is this some kind of joke?
I'd never put that on a cake.
They charge by the letter.
Mine said, "yay!"
Who would do something like this?
Who cares? Cake is cake.
Scrape off the top. Let's eat.
A phony?
♪ off to the races, I'm going places ♪
♪ might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it ♪
♪ this is the big break
and it's calling my name ♪
♪ yeah! ♪
♪ so far, so great, get with it ♪
♪ at least that's how I see it ♪
♪ having a dream is just the beginning ♪
♪ so far, so great, believe it ♪
♪ can't take away this feeling ♪
♪ taking a ride with chance on my side ♪
♪ yeah, I can't wait ♪
♪ so far, so great ♪
♪ so far, so great... ♪
♪ yaooww! ♪.
How can you guys eat that cake?
It's full of hatred and lies.
Whoever doesn't like you, Sonny,
was trying to make a statement...
A delicious, Fluffy statement.
I mean, come on, Sonny,
it's not a big deal.
I mean, we've all gotten hate cakes before.
- Really?
- No.
No. But, you know,
if they're anything like this,
I'm gonna start ticking people off.
Yeah, Sonny, what did you do?
Can you do it again for my birthday?
Look at this: Sonny's hate cake is
the lead story on "tween weekly."
- What? - I know, not a
single mention of me.
I hate and I hate and I hate.
Where's the love?
"Sonny Munroe and
her costars..."
See? I'm not even a star
anymore, I'm a costar.
"... Were shocked when
during a celebration.
Of her first year
at 'So Random!'..."
No mention of my five years here.
"... An anonymous hate cake
was delivered."
Saying, 'Sonny Munroe
is a phony. '.
Sources on the scene describe
the cake as creamy.
"And buttery, but filled
with hate."
I remember when they used to
describe me that way.
Okay, good news and bad news.
The good news is, the bakery has no idea.
Who changed the message on the cake.
How is that good news?
When you compare it to this.
Sorry, that was mine.
I mean when you compare it to this.
I'm Ryan loughlin.
And this is "Tween Weekly TV."
Apparently cakes aren't the only way.
To send a nasty message
to So Random!'s Sonny Munroe.
I received this
mysterious letter this morning...
Mysterious because it seems.
To be using letters from an
outdated form of communication.
Called a magazine.
"Sonny Munroe is not.
The girl
she says she is."
So if she is not, who is she?
And what is she hiding?
Looks like things aren't so "sunny"
At "So Random!."
Who is doing this to me?
Well, let's think about this.
Have you made any enemies lately?
Well, I didn't take that flyer
from the guy in the hot-dog suit.
And I guess he was just doing his job.
That lady who said "good morning"...
I didn't say good morning back.
I thought it but I just didn't say it.
Ryan's right.
Who am I?
Sonny, this is crazy.
You're a nice kid.
Nice kid! There was a nice kid
selling chocolate for his school.
And I didn't buy any.
But it had nuts. I don't like nuts.
And for that I deserve a hate cake?
No you don't.
Come on, I'm gonna get you a new cake.
What would you like it to say?
And I'm willing to go as high
as six letters.
Without my bottles, your water is useless.
And without my water,
your bottles are just...
Empty like your heart.
Oh, cut, milady's on the set!
Come on now.
- We're in the middle of a scene here.
- Uh, he called me.
Cut her some slack, Penelope.
You saw the "tween weekly" story.
Someone's got it out for milady.
So you okay?
No, not really. I mean,
I'm totally stressed out.
With that cake and the hate and the letter.
I mean, it's just hard for me to be
excited about going back to Wisconsin.
Well, not to mention the book report.
Ah, the book report.
Relax relax.
I can help you.
- With the book report?
- Ha! Sonny, no. Please.
There's only three things that I read...
My scripts, my reviews and my checks.
And my check report
says that I'm rich enough.
To fly you to Wisconsin
on my private jet, air Chad.
You would do that?
I don't know.
Let's find out.
"let your heart take wing."
Well, that settles it.
We're going.
Wait a minute. You just made that
decision based on a fortune cookie?
It helps that I have
a private jet. But yes.
Now you can't tell anyone about this,
But this is how I make every
major decision in my life.
- Since when? - Since I had chinese
food with my psychic last week.
She said,
"you're destined for failure."
My cookie said, "you're
destined for greatness."
So I went with the cookie.
And now I'm flying air Chad.
You are one smart cookie.
Ha! Speaking of
smart cookies,
I got a great idea that's
gonna cheer you up.
- Penelope!
- Ready to get back to work?
I'm thinking we can finish our scene later.
My leading lady and my leading milady.
Do a little shopping together, huh?
What?
We don't even know each other.
That's where the shopping comes in.
Come on, girls, shop it up!
So you think that all
it takes for girls to bond.
Is to go shopping?
- It doesn't?
- No.
It helps to have something
in common to talk about.
Yeah, like the fact that
you think all it takes.
For girls to bond is to go shopping.
Well, I think we've found our topic.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
Dude? Dude, what
are you doing?
Oh oh, I'm testing out
my new app... treasure tracker.
It turns any phone into
a portable metal detector.
Yeah, who knows what
valuable stuff we'll find?
Maybe you can find the 99¢
you lost on that worthless app.
Booya! Sunglasses.
Worthless.
Retainer.
- Rare gold coin.
- Worth lots. What...
We're rich.
Do you know what this means?
We can finally get those matching tug
boats we've been dreaming about.
I certainly hope that noise
is coming out of your mouths.
Where's Sonny?
I've got a more important question.
- Is that lasagna?
- Not just any lasagna.
Somebody sent me hate lasagna.
"dear Tawni, you are the second
prettiest girl on the planet."
Oh, that is some saucy hate.
Yeah. I want to rub it in Sonny's face
before I show it to "tween weekly."
You spelled "prettiest" wrong.
- No I didn't.
- Aha!
I knew you baked your own hate.
Well, it's not fair that
Sonny gets all the hate food.
Where is she?
She's at the mall with Penelope.
Of course she is!
She's out shopping.
With another celebrity
to get more publicity.
Well, she's about to be
shopping with two celebrities.
Baby, if you want to shop with two
celebrities, just come with us.
- Yeah, we're heading out to the
tugboat factory outlet. - Whoo-whoo!
There's not one word or sound in
that sentence that's appealing.
Hey!
My retainer!
I have been looking for this.
Oh, I almost forgot my lasagna.
Okay, how about this one?
How about this one?
- C. D. C.!
- Wha-doo-doo!
"peace out, suckers!"
Oh, okay, what do you think about this top?
It looks really great on you.
Thanks. Oh, and how good
does this necklace look with it?
Yeah. Oh wow,
that's expensive.
Oh, I know. Right?
I don't want to take it off.
It's too pretty.
This is fun, right?
Yeah. We can't
tell Chad though.
No.
Excuse me one sec.
Hello.
Hi, it's Tawni.
Who?
- Tawni.
- Tawni?
That's what I said...
Tawni.
So are you having a good time?
Actually I am. Penelope just
picked out an awesome top for me.
Let me be the judge of that.
Curses!
What are you doing here and why
are you tatking like that?
Oh, I'm wearing my retainer.
Although it doesn't seem to fit so good,
So I'm just gonna...
Much better.
So where are we celebrities shopping next?
Oh, I get it, Tawni.
You're feeling a little left out.
Only of having my picture taken.
I may not have been seen
coming in with you two,
But I'm gonna be seen walking out.
- Sonny, Penelope!
- Tawni. What? I'm right here.
Sonny, care to make a comment
about the letter?
- Leave her alone.
- That's right.
And pay attention to me.
Wanna see what I bought?
- So what are you two girls...
- Three girls.
... Up to today?
Honestly, Ryan, there's no story here.
We're just going shopping.
That's what celebrities do.
Duh.
Excuse me, miss.
I'm gonna need to look in that bag.
- Why?
- Oh, you did buy that necklace?
No, ma'am, she didn't.
- You're gonna need to come with us.
- What?
No, there must be some sort of mistake.
Or has there?
Sonny Munroe, shoplifter.
Looks like that necklace just got.
Some matching bracelets.
I'm Ryan laughlin for
"Tween Weekly TV."
Cut.
I promise you, Mr. Condor, this
whole Sonny-shoplifting thing.
Is gonna blow over.
Yes, you know the press.
They'll lose interest in
the story in five minutes.
Ah!
What? Oh. No no, sir,
nothing's wrong.
I just won tickets for Justin bieber.
Ah! Ha ha ha.
Yes, of course you can come along, sir.
Yes, pick you up at 8:00.
Great.
Now I gotta win Justin bieber tickets.
I'm innocent. I promise
I didn't steal the necklace.
Get back.
All you people care about.
Is dragging people through the mud.
Speaking of mud, we're getting down
and dirty on "MacKenZie Falls"
Wednesdays at 8:00,
7:00 central.
Get back!
Chad, thank you so much
for bailing me out of jail.
Well, can't have milady
rotting away in the big house.
And, Marshall, thank you
for having my back.
Well, I can't have one of
my stars treated like this.
Pizza delivery for Sonny Munroe.
Aha.
I'll handle this.
Sonny, how did you break out of prison?
I can't believe you tried the old
paparazzi-disguised- as-a-delivery-guy trick!
We'll find out the truth about you, Sonny!
Get out of here, you hack!
Aha ha ha ha ha!
This is why I got into this business.
Can either one of you
get me Justin bieber tickets?
Oh, it's perfect.
Thank you so much.
I was gonna put something in,
not take something out.
That's it.
Everybody hide your wallets.
Sonny Munroe coming through.
If she doesn't get you,
her cheese ball will.
Don't worry about them, Sonny.
We know you're innocent.
But we're not too sure about your sanity.
What is this?
And why does it smell like Grady's feet?
Oh, sorry, that...
that is my feet.
Ew!
Yeah, I was changing into
my lunch socks, so...
Okay, this cheese ball right
here happens to represent
175 years of West appleton
High School tradition.
Not a lot going on
in West appleton, is there?
Wait, I didn't tell you the exciting part.
As the person who gets to
fire the cheese cannon,
I get to bring a cheese ball
that best represents me.
So I had the cafeteria make one...
Half californian/ half Wisconsin cheddar.
You think your cheese ball is cool?
Check out what me and Grady found
while you were in the pokey.
Our first treasure.
Oh, so that explains the hats.
You guys are finally
getting your tug boats.
I guess some Hollywood dreams
really do come true.
- Let me look at that.
- No!
Man, if I'd had a couple of these,
I would have bought the necklace.
Ha. I'll be taking that
back now.
And putting it somewhere were
no one else would think to go.
Oh, your "facechum" page?
Oh look, it's Penelope.
- Hey, you're gonna strike out.
- No I'm not.
Hey! You know,
my friend and I.
Are treasure hunters.
And your x just marked my spot.
That line just might work...
Oh really?
... If your goal is
to die alone.
I don't want to die alone.
Sonny, how are you doing?
This is Sonny watch!
Not so good anymore.
Coming up tonight on "tween wkly tv, "
Another Sonny Munroe shocker.
The voice behind the letter speaks.
That necklace wasn't.
The first thing Sonny Munroe stole.
If you're keeping track,
That makes it at least the second thing.
That Sonny Munroe has stolen.
Where will this crime spree end?
At three? At four?
At five?
Tune in tonight at 6:00.
As we continue "tween weekly
tv"'s Sonny watch.
When will this end?
For you...
I mean for you.
Do you have any idea who that person is?
No.
Oh, think about it, Sonny.
Who do you know.
Who talks...
like this?
- Nobody.
- But I just did.
Don't worry, Sonny.
If you need me, call me.
If you need me, call me!
I am gonna die alone.
I'm dying a little right now.
Ryan will stop at nothing
to get his story...
Unless we stop him first.
You guys are there for me, right?
Yeah!
Will there be cameras?
I mean...
Oh, come on, who am I kidding?
Will there be cameras?
All right, Sonny's dating Chad.
And I will stop at nothing to dig
something else up on her in here.
- Ha!
- Ah!
Looking for something?
Whah!
Well, if it ain't the trash
looking through the trash.
That was good.
I've been working on that all afternoon.
I could tell.
Why are you in a dumpster?
We're in a dumpster because that's
where the trash is thrown out.
I've been working on that
since I heard your line.
I can tell.
Look, every single thing you've
said about me, Ryan, is not true.
But you wouldn't know that because you haven't
even asked me my side of the story yet.
Ah!
Or mine!
Uh, dude, get this...
Out coin is somewhere in the trash.
You know what?
I am not gonna laugh at your stuff.
If you don't laugh at mine.
It's not a joke.
It's gone.
Not as long as I have my treasure tracker.
You just hurt people with
false accusations.
There's no proof that I did
any of that stuff, okay?
It's just people saying that I did.
You know what?
You're right.
You deserve to be heard.
Roll it.
I'm Ryan laughlin for "Tween Weekly TV"
With Sonny Munroe's side of the story.
Hi, I'm Sonny Munroe and I'm...
- A thief!
- You stole our rare coin?
- No! - And that's her
side of the story.
- No I didn't!
- Cut.
Please, you guys have to listen me.
I have no idea how that coin
got into my pocket.
- We believed in you.
- We defended you.
You couldn't allow me one shining
moment in the garbage, could you?
I can explain this.
We're waiting.
Guys, I can't explain this.
I sure hope you can explain this.
Ha.
That's mine.
I mean, I sure hope you can explain this.
Everybody knows sicky Vicky,
Sonny Munroe's first breakout
character on "So Random!, "
The one that landed Sonny
her big Hollywood dream.
Today I've got pink-eye.
I got it from Alice mazarsky
because she came to school.
With pink-eye... not cool.
So how would a girl.
Who's stolen a necklace...
Not cool!
-... A coin...
- Not cool!
... And heaven knows
what else...
Not cool!
... Come up with an original
character like sicky Vicky?
By stealing it.
Not cool!
What? I didn't steal
sicky Vicky.
I made that character up.
Meet the real sicky Vicky, Vicky sicowitz.
I couldn't keep quiet anymore, Ryan.
How many lies has she told?
How many more people will she hurt?
Not cool.
Not cool at all.
Not cool, Sonny.
Marshall, look, I know
this looks really bad,
- But you've got to believe me.
- I want to believe you.
But it's all too much.
And now it's affecting the show.
So until this is cleared up,
I'm sorry, Sonny,
But you're off "So Random!."
Guys?
I'm Ryan laughlin for "Tween Weekly TV, "
Reporting live outside
Sonny Munroe's apartment.
Go away!
Never.
This is Sonny watch!
And tonight...
I said no interviews!
Delivery for Sonny Munroe.
Oh, my food's here.
Chad?
- You recognize me?
- There are people who didn't?
Yeah, Ryan and the other reporters.
It's a zoo down there.
This is the only way I could sneak up.
Oh, I'm so glad to see you...
Even looking like that.
Let's go eat. You won't believe
how many fake delivery guys.
Have shown up at my door.
You're the first one I haven't beaten up.
Sonny Munroe!
Did you steal sicky Vicky
from Vicky sicowitz?
There is no Vicky sicowitz!
I made sicky Vicky up!
Yeah, now leave milady alone!
Shut up, chinese-food guy!
Oh my gosh, it's Chad Dylan Cooper.
Yeah, and he's telling you to
leave his lady alone.
Oh really?
Did your fortune cookie
tell you to say that?
Ha ha ha!
- You told?
- No I didn't.
How'd they all find out, Sonny?
You were the only one who knew.
Chad, I didn't tell anybody
about your fortune cookies.
Oh my gosh, you don't believe me.
Well...
Are you thinking about checking a cookie?
Would that be bad?
I don't know.
Let's see.
"he who checks cookie.
Checks into hospital."
Come on, Sonny. I told you a secret.
Now everybody knows about it.
- What am I supposed to think?
- You're not supposed to think.
I'm your girlfriend.
You're supposed to trust me.
You know what? Just take
your stupid fortune cookies.
And your private plane and just go.
- You're gonna lose all
your Chad miles. - Out.
I said go away, Chad.
- Tawni?
- You're living my dream.
What?
I'm stuck inside my apartment
trapped by paparazzi.
Stop rubbing it in!
You want my life?
Take it.
Everyone either thinks that
I'm a thief or a liar.
I have to find my way back to Wisconsin.
Without paparazzi following me.
And I still haven't done my book
report on "the grapes of wrath."
You think you have it bad?
Nobody even notices me anymore.
Try being me and see how that feels.
What are you doing?
Wow!
You weren't kidding.
Looking like you is the perfect
way to sneak out of my apartment.
Nobody... and I mean nobody...
paid any attention to me.
Ha ha!
Yeah, I was there.
You know what?
I thought with at least two Tawnis,
It would draw some attention
just for the curiosity factor.
But no!
We were doubly ignored.
Oh, too funny.
Ah.
So where do you want to drop me off?
They're probably looking
for me at the airport,
So bus station, train?
It'd probably be easier for me
to drive you to Wisconsin.
How is that easier?
Uh, I don't want to go
anywhere near a bus station.
That's where the carless go.
I see what's happening here.
You're being nice to me.
Only because you look like somebody I like.
- Now get that thing off your head.
- Ow!
No.
You sound like the only
person left who believes in me.
How do you know I'm not just doing this.
For the publicity I'll get
once we prove you're innocent?
You think I'm innocent?
You do believe in me.
Well, since there are no cameras here,
Sadly,
Yes, I believe in you.
But don't make a big deal out of it.
Oh!
I'm trying to drive!
- Read your book!
- Okay.
You believe in me, Tawni.
Those better be the first
words of that book.
So let me see if I've
deduced this properly.
I go away for three days
to a Sherlock Holmes convention;
Sonny's accused of being a liar,
Stealing a necklace and your valuable coin;
Has a fight with her
fortune-cookie-eating boyfriend.
And then hits the road with
her new best friend Tawni?
Which leads me to.
Did you know your valuable
coin was chocolate?
Say what now?
I'm giving you one last chance, MacKenZie.
If you don't give me your water,
I'll fill my bottles from the tap.
Chad, this is where you turn and face me.
This is milady at the zoo...
Milady at the pancake house
eating a short stack.
This is milady screaming at me to stop
taking pictures of her short stack.
Chad, what are you doing?
That's what she said
when I took the picture.
Oh, why did I let her go?
Don't look at me.
We ran over something.
Well, ladies,
Looks like the reason you're
stuck here in jawbone junction.
Is what we in the tow-truck
vernacular call a flat tire.
Yeah, I know it's a flat tire.
And I would have changed it myself.
If someone hadn't removed
the spare to make room.
For her spare velour designer sweatsuit.
Sir, can you just fix our tire?
Don't I know you from somewhere?
No no, just a stranger passing through.
What about me?
Do you know me from somewhere?
Now that you mention it, there is
something about you that's familiar.
Finally!
You remind me of something
I found under your wheel well.
This dead critter looks just like
the one on top of your head.
What?
Anyway, to fix the tire and
to decritterize your vehicle,
It'll be $527.
Okay, you know what?
How much without the decritterizing?
Oh, that's on the house.
Provided I get to keep it.
So let's get a move on, 'cause I'm due up.
At the jawbone junction
joke-off tonight.
Just give him the credit card.
Credit card?
Ha ha!
I don't take no credit card.
Just cash money.
We don't have any cash money.
You know what? It's okay.
We'll challenge you to the joke-off.
Yeah. You fix our car
and if we win tonight,
We'll just call it even.
I've got to warn you:
I've won that thing five years in a row.
Well, we're just two girls from California.
- That don't know anything
about being funny. - Mmm-nhh.
What choice do we have?
Fine. If you win,
you don't owe me nothing.
- But if I win, I get...
- The car?
- My velour pants?
- That cheese ball.
- No! - No, you said
it yourself, girlie...
What other choice to you have?
It's winner takes ball.
Okay, let's go through this one more time.
The coin is chocolate.
See, this is where you keep losing us.
Look, for the sake of argument, okay,
Let's just say that the coin was chocolate.
It was chocolate!
It doesn't matter what
the coin was made of.
Sonny still stole it.
Well, I'm not convinced.
Did you actually see her take the coin?
- No.
- But we know it was her.
- Yeah.
Not enough.
If I learned anything at
that Sherlock Holmes convention,
Besides not to inhale this bubble pipe,
It's that you can't solve
a case without cold hard facts.
Fact: The missing coin
was in her pocket.
Fact: The stolen necklace
was in her bag.
Fact: It's hard to take you
seriously wearing those dumb hats.
Fact: You're wearing
a dumb hat too.
Fact: Mine matches
my coat.
- Fact: Ours matches our boats.
- Fact: Mine's waterproof!
Fact: So is ours!
Fine, we all agree... we all
have cool waterproof hats.
So that proves it!
- Sonny's guilty.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay okay, folks.
Welcome to the jawbone junction joke-off.
You know how it's done.
The first one without.
A clever retort loses.
Ladies first.
City before pretty.
No no, after you.
Hicks before chicks.
Whoa!
Now we got ourselves
a joke-off.
You might be from the city if your heels.
Are higher than
my I. Q.
Well, you might be from jawbone.
If you're missing teeth and
you're not looking for them.
All right, all right.
You might be city folk.
If you've changed out of your sweatpants
so you ain't sweatin' in 'em.
You might be from jawbone.
If you call the food in your beard dessert.
Well, you might be from the city if...
If...
Shoot, I can't top that.
It's funny and true.
Mmm!
Looks like we've got
ourselves a new champion.
Not bad for a couple of amateurs.
Thank you.
Oh oh, thank you.
You guys have been a great audience.
And you know what? You can watch
us weekly on our hit comedy show,
- "So Random!."
- What?
I've been bamboozled by
a couple of "con-medians."
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Get back here.
You get back here!
Boo!
Well, you must be from the city.
If you left without
your fancy cellular phone.
Hello?
I miss you, short stack!
All right, boys, you think Sonny's guilty?
Prove it.
Show me some evidence.
- Ah, we'll show you something.
- Yeah yeah, we will.
- Come on, you take the left, I'll take the right.
- All right, I got it.
Aha!
Look at these terrified hairy
children and the fear in their eyes.
Who knows what she did to them?
Those are baby seals.
Sonny rescued them from an oil spill,
Then bathed them by hand
and nursed them back to health.
Face it, she's as innocent
as you are wrong.
There's got to be a clue
around here somewhere.
- What are you eating?
- Mmm, Sonny's cheese ball.
Wait, what's Sonny's cheese ball
doing on Tawni's makeup table?
Next to a receipt for a cake?
Oh, and a magazine with all
the letters cut out.
Like the letter Sonny got.
Okay, clearly Sonny has moved
all her evidence.
Over to Tawni's makeup table.
It's elementary, my dear half wit.
If you had spent $2, 000 on
a deductive-reasoning seminar,
As I did, you would know, as I do,
That the guilty party is Tawni!
Whoa whoa.
Okay, this changes everything.
If Sonny isn't guilty,
Then logic follows that
the coin isn't chocolate!
Ha ha ha! Stick that in
your pipe and blow it.
No.
What it means is.
We owe Sonny an apology.
Yeah, we do.
I just hope we get the chance.
"how to build
a cheese-ball bomb."
"how to build a cheese-
ball bomb."
- You're saying Tawni's behind this?
- Think about it.
Who's had it out for Sonny since
she first came to the show?
- Tawni.
- Okay.
And who just happened to show up just
before Sonny got caught for shoplifting?
- Tawni.
- Right.
Right. And who was in
the dumpster when Sonny.
Allegedly stole Nico and Grady's coin?
Tawni! Tawni! Tawni!
This is all my fault.
Sonny should be flying safely
to Wisconsin with me.
Instead who is she driving with?
This is where you would
all yell "Tawni."
Oh, Tawni!
- Tawni.
- Why didn't I see it?
Yeah.
Dude, for something that could
possibly blow my face off,
- This is good eatin'.
- I told you.
Wisconsin cheddar, California cheddar.
You know what I'm not tasting?
The blowing-your-face-off part.
There's no gunpowder.
Wait a minute. If we've got
the real cheese ball,
- That means Sonny's got the...
- Bomb!
This book is the bomb!
And from where I'm sitting, it
looks like you're almost finished.
Whyyyy!
And that concludes
our in-flight entertainment.
Thank you.
Good thing this plane comes with barf bags.
Man over p. A.
This is your Captain speaking.
We're about 20 minutes
out of appleton, Wisconsin.
Please keep your seat belts buckled,
and thank you for choosing air Chad.
Chad, I have to say,
I've always hated you
for having your own plane.
But?
That's it.
Sonny's still not answering.
I'm getting worried.
It's gonna be okay.
We're almost there.
Oh, what's up, cappy?
Thought I'd give you folks a heads up:
You're in for a bumpy ride.
- Hello, my love.
- What?
Excuse me?
I think cappy loves you.
- Whoa!
Penelope! First of all,
thanks for taking the mask off.
And making this only slightly less awkward.
- Secondly, what?!
- Chad,
This plan isn't going to
make it to Wisconsin.
What?
Ahh! I see
what's going on here.
This is part of
the in-flight entertainment.
Bravo.
Shut it!
There are only two parachutes...
One for me and one for
the man I've always loved.
I knew this day would come.
Hey, lover boy, she's not into
you; she's trying to kill you.
Jump with me, Chad, out of this plane.
And into the rest of our lives.
Penelope, I'm both flattered
and a little creeped out.
- But I have a girlfriend.
- Not for long.
As soon as she lowers my cheese-ball
bomb into that cannon of hers.
And blows herself into cheese spread,
You'll be free to date.
Your cheese-ball bomb?
Of course it was mine, you dimwits.
I did everything!
I switched out the cheese ball.
With the cheese bomb, sent the hate cake,
Mailed the letters, framed Tawni.
I was wrong?
Nice Detective work, Sherlock.
I do not deserve this pipe.
What about our coin?
- That line just might work.
- Oh really?
If your goal is to die alone.
If you need me, call me.
What about the necklace?
- So what do you think?
- Wow.
Even you can make this top look good.
- Really?
- No.
And how did you find out
about my fortune-cookie secret?
Your microphone was on.
We also heard...
Ah, you are one pretty man.
I only said that 'cause my fortune
cookie told me I was pretty.
- So...
- Ah.
Okay.
With Sonny gone and Tawni going to jail,
It'll just be you and me.
I have got to get myself a plane.
Whoa!
- Who's flying this plane?
- Nobody!
What? Ah!
What's it gonna be, Chad?
I can't think!
I don't need a cookie
to make this decision.
I choose Sonny.
Yeah! Let's go!
Wrong choice.
'cause if I can't have you, nobody will.
And with you gone,
"MacKenZie Falls" will become.
"Penelope falls!"
Speaking of which,
Ah!
Peace out, suckers!
She left the other parachute!
- Oh no!
- Relax.
It's not like I can't fly my own plane.
I can't fly my own plane.
Will you relax? We're gonna get to
your High School in plenty of time.
You just had to stop and get your face
carved out of butter, didn't you?
Hey, at least that old butter carver
was paying attention to my face.
I'll take what I can get.
I'm Ryan laughlin and
this is Sonny watch...
On the radio!
We are live in West appleton, Wisconsin.
Are you kidding me?
He's there?
I'm here...
Waiting for the arrival
of known liar and thief
Sonny Munroe.
And it looks like letting down Hollywood.
Wasn't enough.
With only 20 minutes left until
the firing of the cheese cannon,
My forecast is...
Very little chance.
Of Sonny...
And winds out of the southwest.
Oh yeah?
Well, here's my forecast:
- I'm firing that cannon.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Nothing's gonna stop us now.
No way.
Oh my gosh,
"just the facts."
Just let the butter face
do all the talking.
Three things my mom told me.
My traveling socks, a ham sandwich.
And a clean parachute.
The strap! The strap...
it's starting to rip.
- We're too heavy.
- Get rid of the ham sandwich!
All right.
- No, get rid of it!
- All right.
I can't believe we're not gonna make it.
We traveled all this way for nothing.
That's not true. Here's
a little something for you.
Why are you giving me the ticket?
She was the one driving.
Huh. I didn't
even notice you.
The icing on the hate cake.
I've lost my good name, my job,
my boyfriend, everything!
- Nico?
- Sonny!
We know you're innocent.
Marshall said you can have your job back.
That's great!
- Zora?
- Penelope framed you.
- She's behind everything.
- That's horrible.
- Grady?
- Has anyone seen a ham sandwich?
Ah! Stop!
- Oh!
- Chad?
Sonny, I'm so sorry.
I should have trusted you.
- Please forgive me.
- Oh my gosh!
You flew all the way to Wisconsin.
And fell out of the sky just
so you could apologize.
Nobody's ever done that for me.
How could I not forgive you?
I missed you, short stack.
Ew!
I missed you too, egg whites
with tomatoes on the side...
But don't let them touch.
Otherwise it's going back.
You're Chad Dylan Cooper!
Yes, officer, I am.
Before we get a picture of us on your bike,
I'm gonna need a favor.
I'm gonna make it.
Thank you, guys!
Thanks for the picture, Chad.
- Goodbye, Sonny!
- Follow your dreams!
- Bye!
- Get 'em!
Wait a minute. I forgot to
give her the real cheese ball.
That means Sonny's still got the bomb!
- Oh oh oh!
- Sonny! You've got the bomb!
- Wait!
- Hold this.
- Oh okay.
- I don't deserve this hat!
Just get in the car!
Oh oh, all right!
Students, are you ready
to kick off homecoming.
With the West appleton high cheese cannon?
- Well, Sonny Munroe isn't.
- Boo!
But that doesn't mean we can't
have a good time, right?
♪ gouda, havarti, cheddar and Jack ♪
♪ we don't care if
Sonny ever comes back. ♪.
Yeah!
And apparently you can turn anything.
Into a cheer in West appleton.
But this cheese cannon.
Will not go unfired.
Please welcome America's favorite victim,
Vicky sicowitz!
Out from the shadows,
Riddled with disease,
Comes one very brave young girl.
Hello.
I am Vicky sicowitz...
- Bless you.
- Thank you.
... And it is an honor
to fire your cheese cannon.
Hold your fire!
What's this?
West appleton.
Seems to be rife with intrigue.
Hello, everybody.
Boo!
Sonny Munroe will apparently.
Stop at nothing.
To steal the spotlight.
From this courageous...
And contagious young woman.
Look, I know there's been a lot
of things said about me lately.
That may have you questioning who I am.
But I'm here to tell you
that I'm still the same honest.
Truthful girl that stood here a year ago.
And promised to come back.
And you know, here's
another promise that I kept:
Mr. Henderson,
here is your book report.
"the grapes of wrath"?
But I assigned you
"a raisin in the sun."
Vicky sicowitz,
Are you gonna stand for this?
Yes, Ryan, I am.
Because I have a confession to make.
Sonny Munroe didn't steal
this character from me.
I just made that up to get attention.
I tried to tell you.
She's the one who should be
firing the cheese cannon.
Really?
Yes.
That would be cool.
10, nine,
Eight, seven,
Six, five,
Four, three,
Two, one!
Going somewhere, Penelope?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, your face may say Vicky,
But your ugly pilot shoes say Penelope.
Penelope?
This is like a bad episode
of "MacKenZie Falls."
Or a good one.
Tawni figured it out?
$2, 000 and three days of my life for nothing!
I don't deserve this coat.
I would have gotten away with it too.
If it weren't for these comfortable shoes.
Come on, let's go.
I'll wait for you.
Please don't.
Well, everybody, I think
we all owe Sonny Munroe.
A big West appleton apology.
Yeah!
Welcome home, Sonny.
Well, as I've been saying all along,
Sonny Munroe is the girl.
She said she was.
What?
Unbelievable.
Guys like this just lie and lie.
And nothing ever happens to them.
Don't let him spoil your moment.
Here you go, milady...
What's left of your real cheese ball.
Fire away.
Wherever there's injustice or betrayal,
I'll be there.
Reporting the full story
for "Tween Weekly TV, "
- I'm...
- Whoa!
... Coated with cheese!
I can't believe this!
That's a good look on you.
And a good taste.
Cut. Would you cut?
Turn it off.
Keep it rolling.
From coated in sleaze to coated in cheese,
Looks like Ryan's done lying!
For "Tween Weekly TV, " I'm Tawni Hart.
Oh! Come on!
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Addic7ed.com