Sunscreen for my cruise to cancun!
Whoopee cushion for my week at camp comedy.
Bikini.
Slide whistle.
Funny nose
and glasses... hmm?
- Flip-flops.
- These aren't mine, no.
Aw, look at you randoms going
away for your week off,
Which in a way is like
giving me a week off too.
- You I'll miss.
- Aw, I'll miss you too.
Oh, I haven't even left for my cruise yet.
And I already feel seasick.
Oh hey, speaking of things
that make you sick,
I don't know if you heard, but
my life as I know it is over.
What? Oh, chad, I'm only going to
be gone to camp comedy for a week.
Oh, not 'cause of you, milady.
Condor studios are so cheap.
They give me nothing.
Zac efron's studio?
Bought him a car.
Then they bought him a house.
To put that car in.
Then they put that house on an island.
And named it after him.
Look! It's called zac island.
Oh, okay, you know what, chad?
Look, you've got everything that you need.
You've got a great parking spot.
You have room rvice in your dressing room.
What else do you want?
Someone to cut your meat for you?
Oh my gosh, you get that too?!
- Well, it's just for the filet.
- You get filet?
- Efron gets kobe.
- Kobe beef?
No, bryant. He comes in and
cuts his steak for him.
You know what?
I'm going to mr. Condor.
And I'm giving him a list of my demands.
You just need to be grateful
for what you have.
Think about it... you have
a wonderful girlfriend.
Who lets you carry her luggage...
And puts up with your baggage.
You're right.
Come on, I'll drive you to the airport.
You know, efron has
a full-time chauffeur so...
- Oh well, maybe I should date efron then.
- Do not even joke about that!
♪ off to the races,
I'm going places ♪
♪ might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it ♪
♪ this is the big break
and it's calling my name ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ so far, so great,
get with it ♪
♪ at least
that's how I see it ♪
♪ having a dream
is just the beginning ♪
♪ so far, so great,
believe it ♪
♪ can't take away
is feeling ♪
♪ taking a ride
with chance on my side ♪
♪ yeah, I can't wait ♪
♪ so far, so great ♪
♪ ba ba da da-da,
ba da da da-da ♪
♪ yow! ♪
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.ORG
www.Addic7ed.com
finally.
Everyone's away so grady gets to play!
Well, what should I do first?
Ah, first thing is
to stop talking to myself.
And the second thing is...
oh look.
I just broke the first thing.
You know what?
No rules, just video games.
Game on.
Stupid hurricane.
Game off.
Can you believe they canceled a
cruise because of a 14omph wind?
You know what I did?
I went right up to that captain,
I looked him in the eye and I said, "man up!
" next thing I know,
That man was up and blowing
across the deck.
Let me guess, you're going
to spend your vacation.
At home like nico and zora.
Wrong!
My house is getting bedazzled.
So I will be spending
my vacation right here.
Whoo!
Hey, I'm gonna go get some
spray tan and guacamole.
Hey, frankenstein just called.
He wants his bride back.
Oh and, grady, your really
annoying loud brother is here.
Hey hey, gravy!
What up, pup?
Hey, grant.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I just finished my first
semester of college, brah.
I don't want to brag,
but I got straight "c"s!
In two of my classes.
So where are you planning on staying?
Oh, with my fraternity brothers, bro,
- At the local delta nu house.
- All right!
Scooter, tubbs, where you at?
♪ delta nu, delta nu ♪
♪ party down with my crew ♪
- ♪ we're so much better
than all of ♪ - ♪ You! ♪
- ♪ what's our name? ♪
- ♪ Delta nu. ♪.
Oh yeah!
All right.
So let me guess...
you're gonna hit three.
Me, the beach and dad up for money.
I'm here to work, grots.
Get me a summer job.
Wow, look at you being
mr. Responsible.
So what are you gonna do?
Get a job washing cars.
Or bagging groceries?
I'm gonna do what you do...
work in showbiz;
Be a director;
Star in a movie;
Find some old rich lady to take
care of me for a couple of months.
Hey, you leave grandma alone!
Oh, you didn't hear?
What what what?!
Psych!
You're so gullible, bro.
You can't just waltz
into hollywood and be a star.
And then scare me about grandma.
I'm sorry I freaked
you out about grandbones.
But I'm still very serious
about getting a job.
It's not as easy as you think, grant.
You have to start at the bottom.
Oh, you mean
like "so random!"
Booyah! See,
I can do comedy.
Oh yeah, the bottom,
"so random!" yeah.
- But there's nothing funny about
grandbones being dead. - What?
See, I can do drama too.
I'm totally kidding.
- She's fine, she's just fine.
- All right, okay.
Delta nu, bam!
Oh hey, mind if I join you?
I don't know what you're saying.
Why don't you join me?
Oh, are you eating for two
since nico's not here?
Oh oh, it's not for me.
It's a little welcome present
for my brother grant.
Whoop, oh no.
Yeah, I got him his first hollywood
job as a cafeteria busboy.
Oh, I even got him this apron.
He thinks working on
"so random!" is the bottom.
I'll show him the bottom, baby.
Nice. Nice.
Nice try.
Ooh, a coconut drink with an umbrella...
Tropical.
Hey, you know what would make this better?
Bigger!
Scooter, tubbs, go find me a coconut.
Big enough to fit that umbrella.
Oh yeah, huh!
Oh, so what was that job
you called me about?
Well, you're looking at it.
Congratulations, you are
now a hollywood busboy.
Whoa.  Whoa.
I didn't attend one third of my
classes in college to be a busboy.
Oh, by the way, is that a sarong?
Because on you it looks so right!
Only a jerk like you would say out loud.
What everyone else
in this room is thinking.
You know what else they're thinking?
This guy shouldn't be cleaning up
tables, he should be dancing on them!
♪ nu nu ♪
♪ nu nu. ♪.
Wow, that is one arrogant guy.
Yeah, that attitude's
gonna get him nowhere.
Oh, f.Y.I., mr. Condor,
Here's my list of demands.
It accordions out.
You... reaccordion this.
And clean up that table!
We don't want the dancer to slip.
Everything always goes grant's way.
Oh come on.
You're exaggerating.
- ♪ coconut! ♪
- ♪ Coco-what? ♪
- ♪ Coco-what? ♪.
Am I exaggerating, tawni?
Am I?
Okay, great first day at camp, kids.
Now remember, pies are for
eating, not throwing.
I know what cabin you sleep in, brian!
Hello?
- Hello?
Sonny? Sonny, I can't hear you.
Hold on.
I'm gonna try and move around,
find a good spot.
Chad? Hey,
I can't hear you either.
The reception's horrible.
Thank you, you're adorable too.
I gave my list
to mr. Condor.
No no, I didn't see a condor,
But I think I saw an eagle.
No!
No no no no.
Everything I'm asking for is legal.
Okay, I'm not sure what you're asking,
But my advice is don't be greedy.
That is great advice.
I will be greedy!
No no, why would you beat grady?
Wait.
Oh, brian, put down that pie.
I gotta go.
What?
Hello?
This is a nightmare.
Chad, I've looked over your entire list.
And the answer is yes to all of it.
- Really? The indoor spa?
- Yes.
- The bumper cars?
My weight in chocolate?
Agreed.
I believe that covers the entire list.
Should we put
this baby to bed? Deal?
Not quite.
A wise woman once told me
I should be greedy,
- So I want a pony.
- A pony?!
Yes, a pony... the one thing zac
efron did not get from his list.
So I want a pony.
And I want his name to be frank.
You're pushing it, cooper.
And I want a puppy to ride
on the pony's back,
'cause it is really cute when they do that.
Now do we have a deal?
Here's what we have.
- You can take frank...
- Oh, I got a pony!
- ...And the puppy on his back...
- Aww.
...And ride them off together
to the land of you-are-fired.
Because, as the name of the
land indicates, you are fired!
Where is this coming from?
Hello? No, chad, I still
can't hear anything.
How did everything go
with mr. Condor?
Oh, I got fired from "mackenzie
falls" and I lost everything.
Oh, you got everything?
Good for you!
- Oh, hello?
- Hello?
- Hello.
We're sorry.
Your service has
been disconnected.
What?
No, you know what?
You can take my phone,
You can take my job.
You cannot take my dressing room!
I am mackenzie, do you hear me!
You will never get me out.
Okay, you got me out,
But you still can't do the show without me.
I am mackenzie!
Hey, brah, I didn't need to
start at the bottom at all.
I totally just landed a job on my ownski.
You'll never replace me!
- I'm the new mackenzie.
- You're the new mackenzie?
I'm the new mackenzie.
- I am the new mackenzie.
- ♪ delta nu! ♪
- No-ooo!
Nu-uuuuuu!
Grady's losing it.
Grady's losing it!
Grady's losing it fast.
I can't believe grant!
He comes into hollywood.
With his ♪ nus ♪
and his "nice!"
And his stupid giant coconut.
And then he thinks he can play in
my sandbox... my sandbox!
Oh, oh no, oh no.
Oh... whoa-aaaa.
I think you might have used
a wee bit too much spray tan.
According to this bottle,
I should be a "golden goddess."
According to these eyes
you are "oompa loompa."
What?
I look like a carrot stick.
Not nice!
Check it out, brah.
Bam!
"there's a new mackenzie in town"?
Totes.
I want you to check out
my new crew from my new show.
- Hold this.
- Oh okay.
Mack nu!
- What happened to the delta nus?
- Oh, I've been busy.
Doing the hollywood thing
with my "mack falls" crew.
This dude is my laugh guy.
That's not funny.
Good work!
And this is my flosser.
Oh yeah!
And this is my biographer.
Are you gettg all this?
Good! Then get it over there.
And make me sound smart.
The only thing I'm missing
is my human sack man.
- What?
- A human to carry the sack, man,
With all my new cool hollywood stuff in it.
Hey, that could be your job!
I have a job.
Right. I keep
forgetting about that.
Look at us!
A couple of guys that came
to hollywood with a dream.
- My dream.
- We worked hard.
You got here yesterday!
Man, I remember when I was bussing tables.
I bussed the table!
Eh, you know, the bottom line is.
Now that I've made it,
At least one of the mitchell
brothers made it, right?
Mom can finally be proud.
Excuse me for one second.
Grady's lost it!
Who needs a job?
I've got my pony and I've got my puppy.
Ooh yes.
Ma! I said I'd make
my bed in a minute.
Hi, chad.
Can I come in?
- Oh hey, buddy.
- Buddy?
Wow, he's worse off than I thought.
Oh man!
I've dreamt of a room like this.
No way, a racecar bed!
How could you have ever
wanted to move out of here?
Ah, don't worry.
We are not making that mistake again.
Are we, frank?
No no.
Chad, I can understand
the allure of this...
Modern-day eden,
But we've got to get you back
on the "falls" where you belong.
I don't belong there.
- I'm not mackenzie anymore.
- Not mackenzie?!
You're kidding me.
You are the only mackenzie.
Without you there'd
be no "falls."
It'd just be water falling off
a rock. You gave it purpose.
You gave it a name!
What happened to that chad dylan cooper, huh?
The one who was arrogant, full of himself,
Who made all our lives miserable?
The chad dylan cooper we all know and hate?
You put that horsie down!
Get out of the coolest bed I've ever seen,
March right back down to that studio.
And reclaim what's rightfully yours!
So come on, man. Let's go!
We're gonna go. Ha ha ha!
Dude, did you not hear
that gigantic speech?
Have you seen the "falls" since you left?
Have you seen what grant
has done to mackenzie?
I don't care about mackenzie anymore.
Really, chad?
Really?
I know my face is different
since the accident.
But my heart's the same, brah!
Oh, he did not just
call her "brah."
Mm-hmm.
I can't believe grandbones
mackenzie is dead.
Bam!
That's for thinking
grandbones mackenzie is dead.
♪ delta nu! ♪.
What did he do to mackenzie?!
He nu'd him up, chad.
He nu'd him up good!
- What do you got to say to that?
- I don't like it!
- And neither does frank.
- Oh well, maybe you should listen to frank.
And what would frank have you do?
He'd want me to go take the "falls" back.
Well, what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna go take the "falls" back.
- All right!
- Ha ha ha! To the studio.
- To the studio.
What up, pup?
Why are there delta nu letters
all over that dorky vest?
Oh, 'cause I'm a delta nu now.
Nu-nu!
Not funny, what is going on?
You haven't been around the delta nu house.
So you don't know about
all the exciting changes.
You're letting in chicks?
Orange ones?
Yep, and we have a new delta nu president.
That'd be me.
Scooter, tubbs, what did they do to you?
You've been busy as mackenzie.
I had some free time,
And scott and melvin tubberson here,
Needed a new leader.
So I took over and made a few changes.
♪ delta nu, delta nu ♪
♪ study hard, obey curfew ♪
♪ return library books when they are due ♪
- ♪ or renew ♪
- ♪ At delta nu. ♪.
It burns! Oh.
Grant, what's going on?
You're late.
Everyone is waiting
for you down on the set.
They're gonna have to
keep on waiting, condude,
Because I quit!
I can't let delta nu take
a back seat to my summer job.
Summer job?
You're gonna give up.
A hollywood career to go
back to some fraternity?
You obviously don't know the deep respect.
Fraternity brothers have for one another.
Scooter, tubbs, grab my giant
coconut and let's bounce.
What?
I...
What am I gonna do now?
I need a mackenzie.
You know, you've got one right there.
The orange chick?
No, the pasty dude.
I don't know,
The old mackenzie was pretty
greedy... a pony and a puppy.
Well, sir, the new mackenzie
has been humbled.
I'll settle for either a puppy or a pony.
- You'll get neither!
- I'll take it.
Grady, I couldn't have gotten
my job back without you.
You know, I learned a valuable lesson.
About being happy with what you have,
And about how whether
you're chad dylan cooper.
Or zac efron.
Studios just don't want
to give you live animals.
No problem, buddy.
Yeah, about the whole buddy thing...
Oh oh, yeah, I get it.
Everything's back to normal now, huh?
So this is where you call security.
And kick me out of your
dressing room, right?
You know what?
As my way of saying thank you,
Why don't you kick yourself out?
- Oh, you mean it?
- You've earned it.
Okay, uh...
Security! Oh no, I just can't.
My friend.
He's my buddy.
Oh no, oh oh oh!
Game on.
- What up, pup?
- Game off.
I'm outie.
Just wanted to say bye-onara.
Hey, grant, before you leave
I have to confess something.
What? That chad didn't
really take over delta nu.
And it was a big scam
so he could get his job back?
Oh, not the face!
Not the face!
Relax, I'm not mad.
All right.
You know, I figured if me being here.
Drove you to team up
with a dude you can't stand,
I must have really been
cramping your styles.
I mean, this whole hollywood
thing is your thing, not mine.
You know? And I should have
never crashed your party.
- Thanks, bro. - 'Cause there's a million
other parties in this town to crash!
Whoo!
Well, are you coming?
Oh yeah. Yeah!
Oh hey, willy wonka called.
He needs you back at the chocolate factory.
Oh, are you leaving already?
Ni-iiiiiice!
Nice.
Have you always wanted to be the class clown?
Well, now you can,
Thanks to camp comedy.
Where you'll learn classic comedy
skills like the double take...
The spit take...
The double spit take.
You'll also learn advanced
physical comedy bits.
Like the banana-peel slip...
Whoops.
...And the fine art
of stepping on a rake.
We'll also teach you how to be
funny without using words at all.
Woo-woo-woo.
Ah-oooo!
That's camp comedy.
Call now.
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.ORG
www.Addic7ed.com