I can't believe this.
I've never seen a game seven.
- Go into double overtime.
- Get it to lebron! Get it to lebron!
Five, four, three...
To channel 2.
What are you doing?!
They're announcing the
tween choice nominations.
Finally, the nominees
for best tween show are...
"skateboarding boyz,"
"so you're thinkin'
you're Lincoln?"
"mackenzie falls,"
And last but not least...
Come on, come on, come on.
..."so random!"
no way, yes!
Why are you guys groaning?
We just got nominated for best tween show.
This is huge.
No, this is just another opportunity
for us to lose to "mackenzie falls."
Mm-hmm,
that's right, Sonny.
This'll be our sixth year in
a row losing to "mac falls."
Well, you know what?
This is my first time.
Being nominated, so I'd like to enjoy it.
I'm going to enjoy it
tawni-style,
With a special outfit that says,
"even though I lost,
Look at me, look at me,
not kristen Stewart!"
And I'm working on a special.
Congratulatory prank for "mac falls"
That involves eggs, three types of dung.
And an industrial vacuum cleaner.
Three types of dung?!
Okay, you know what?
Stop right there!
Are we really the kind
of people that would resort.
- To petty pranks out of jealousy?
- Three types of dung!
Okay, we are, but look,
this year win or lose...
- Lose! -... We're gonna
be gracious about it.
Why should we? "Mackenzie falls"
is never gracious about it.
Chad is a totally changed person
since we started dating.
- This year, win or lose...
- Lose!
- Or win!
- Or lose!
... It's gonna be totally different
with "mackenzie falls."
If a boyfriend and a girlfriend can compete
civilly, then so can our two shows.
And just to be sure, I'm gonna go
talk to him about it right now.
No pranks!
What am I supposed to do
with 4,000 poached eggs?
Oooh, dibbs on eight of them.
♪ off to the races,
I'm going places ♪
♪ might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it ♪
♪ this is the big break
and it's calling my name ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ so far, so great,
get with it ♪
♪ at least
that's how I see it ♪
♪ having a dream
is just the beginning ♪
♪ so far, so great,
believe it ♪
♪ can't take away
this feeling ♪
♪ taking a ride
with chance on my side ♪
♪ yeah, I can't wait ♪
♪ so far, so great ♪
♪ ba ba da da-da,
ba da da da-da ♪
♪ yow! ♪.
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.ORG
www.Addic7ed.com
And this sixth straight win
for "mackenzie falls"...
No no no, huh-uh.
You know what?
Let me rehearse that
one more time. Sorry.
And this sixth straight win
for "mackenzie falls"
Would not have been possible without my...
My passion, my dedication,
My creativity.
Am I leaving anything out?
I'm sorry, are you on our show?
Oh hey, "mac falls."
So "so random!" wanted me to
bring over a little something.
To congratulate you guys
on your nomination.
- It's gonna blow!
- Everyone duck!
Oh my gosh, come on, guys, really?
This is a real muffin basket, not a prank.
"so random!" has decided
to take the high road.
Well, of course I trust you.
But these guys and what's-her-face
are gonna need some proof.
- Eat it.
- What?
Eat it.
Come on, Sonny.
You are not shoving this in my face.
Chad, you are ridiculous.
So what if we're up for the same award?
We should be thrilled.
Why does it have to be about
winning or losing?
- Because we like winning.
- And more importantly we like you losing...
To us.
No no no no.
Guys, you know, maybe there's.
Something to this high-road thing
milady's yammering on about.
You know what?
New year, new attitude.
Everyone grab a muffin.
Except you.
I don't know who you are.
To "mac falls"
and "so random!"
No matter who wins best show, we
promise not to rub it in your face.
- That's your high road?
- Pretty good, huh?
No, give me my muffins back.
Give them back.
- Fine.
- I'm taking them back.
Except maybe I'll just leave this one.
Really?
Awesome.
We'd be thrilled
to do it. Thanks.
- Dude.
- Hmm?
We get to present the tween choice
award for best sound effect.
- This is big.
- Oh yeah, huge!
So... so it's an award
for sound effects, right?
- Yeah yeah.
- How about
I do my impression of the sound.
Of a small bird laying a big egg?
Bok-kkk!
Come on, dude, that's not funny.
- We're presenters...
- Yeah?
...At "the tween
choice awards."
- Yeah.
- We have to be witty.
Like you say, "we're presenting.
The award for best
sound effects."
And I say,
"I like the sound of that."
And then you say,
"I hear ya."
Yeah, and then we'll both hear silence,
because that is not funny at all!
Okay okay, how do we settle this?
This may be the most important
decision of our careers.
We have to figure this out like adults.
Boom!
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war!
Hello, I'm Ryan loughlin, this year's
host of "the tween choice awards,"
Coming to you live from the red carpet.
It is a veritable "who's who"
Of who can't stay out
past 10:00.
Oh look,
it's "so random!"'s
Nico Harris and Grady Mitchell...
Standing in front of two people you
would much rather see me interview.
Sonny, Chad, quick word!
We of course are joined now.
By tonight's hottest Hollywood couple.
And, Sonny, this is your
very first red carpet.
Sixth consecutive battle between "so random!
" and "mackenzie falls,"
But our first one between
boyfriend and girlfriend.
- Your thoughts? - Actually, you
know, we don't see it as a battle.
It's just an honor to be nominated.
Which is something the loser always says.
- Am I right, Chad?
- Ryan, there are no losers.
Aww, that's right, Chad.
Tonight we're taking the high road, okay?
- Isn't that right, sweetie?
- Absolutely... high road.
High road.
We're gonna win.
What?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. You look great, wow.
...Meal or no meal dancers.
I still think we should do my "bok" joke.
Dude, I won the thumb-war
contest fair and square.
And now presenting the award
for best sound effects,
Give it up for Grady Mitchell
and Nico Harris.
- Ahh.
- Mmm.
- Sound effects...
I like the sound...
Of that.
Oh...
I hear ya, buddy.
You hear that?
Nothing. Nothing!
You know another sound I like?
- What?
- The sound a small bird makes.
When it's laying a big egg.
Bok!
Bok bok!
And the nominees are...
One more time for the best
adult cast playing tweens:
"glee."
I can't believe you stole my joke.
But we were dying out there.
Oh, you're lucky you're
not dying right here!
Am I right, lincolns, huh?
Coming up after this commercial break,
It's the one you've been waiting for...
Best tween show.
It's so exciting.
I'm so nervous.
Aw, you first timers are so cute.
- Hey, good luck.
- Good luck.
Welcome back.
Well, I think we all know.
Who's going to win tonight's
final award for best tween show,
So let's get right to it.
And the choicey goes to
Mac... Aroni and cheese,
It's "so random!"
What?
Well well well.
Oh gosh, you know, I have something
that I have been waiting to say.
For five years.
To my friends at "mackenzie falls"...
- Ahem... high road.
- Ahem.
To my friends at "mackenzie falls"...
In your face, "mackenzie falls"!
Yeah! Oh yeah,
in your face!
We won and you thought
we'd lose, but guess what?
We won, Whoo!
Uh, what I meant to say.
Was...
Thank you.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Be sure to get the good side of my beak.
Guys, guys, quick word with the winner.
Um, could you...
could you hold this?
- I gotta go talk to Chad.
- Yes I can.
Hey look,
I'm really sorry about my stupid speech.
I was just excited and I got
caught up in the moment.
- Are you okay?
- Never better.
I can't wait for "the tween
choice awards" to begin.
Hey, you look great. The night's young,
nothing horrible's happened yet,
Whoo!
Um, Chad, the show's over.
- "so random!" won.
- That's crazy talk.
And my watch says it's 5:00.
You look great,
The night's young and nothing
horrible's happened yet.
Okay, he's in shock.
We are all in shock, Sonny.
You have just pulled off the biggest upset.
In tween choice history.
Hey, Ryan, buddy,
Hate to cut this short, but, uh,
According to my watch, we're
gonna be late for the show.
- What show? - He's talking
about the after-show party.
Where I'll thank him again
for not being mad at me.
Over my stupid little speech.
Speech? Why would you do a speech
before the show even begins?
Crazy talk, right?
Okay, you know what?
Let's get you home for a little hot cocoa.
I like cocoa.
More like cuckoo.
For "the tween choice awards,"
I'm Ryan loughlin.
Heading home.
How did I come up with "bok"?
How do you explain comedy?
Who knows where this stuff comes from?
I do, but apparently I'm the only one!
Grady!
Grady, wait!
Grady, Grady!
I made a mistake.
Oh no no no no,
See, a mistake is, "oh, I'm sorry, sir.
I charged you twice
for that action figure."
A mistake is, "oh, we're the Titanic.
That iceberg will move for us."
But what you did was much much worse.
And I know the Titanic was a tragedy,
But I was just exaggerating
to make a point.
But still!
What you did.
Was much much worse.
Much worse!
And just like the Captain of the Titanic,
I did not see that coming.
Look at us!
Sitting at the fancy table,
Eating fancy food.
Yeah, and look at "mackenzie
falls" eating loser food.
Losers!
You sure you don't want to sit with
your friends at the winners' table?
Oh sure.
Come on, join us.
Sonny, the table is for a winner like you,
- Not a...
- Loser!
Hilarious...
talking lobsters.
Chad, look, I can't not sit with my boyfriend.
That would be weird.
I can't sit at the winner's
table... that would be weird.
Sonny, I know you're new at this, but...
- This is your moment, enjoy it.
- I am, Chad.
I just don't want to
flaunt it in front of you.
Oh wow,
it's Mr. Condor.
Heh heh, head of the studio
calling to congratulate you,
Not me.
Oh, Chad, I can't answer
this in front of you.
- I just... I feel bad.
- Answer it! Go!
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Hi, yes, sir.
It's Mr. Condor, sir.
How's it going?
Oh, thank you so much.
Yes, I am thrilled.
You wanna hear me say it?
Right now?
In your face,
"mackenzie falls."
You know, Chad is standing right here
and I'm sure you want to say hi.
H-hello?
Hello?
You know, I think he was going
through a tunnel or something.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Look, Chad, are you okay?
I'm fine! Okay?
I'm... I'm fine.
Why wouldn't I be fine when they're
covering up my picture with yours?
Hey, Chad,
Don't look directly
into the "sonny."
Look, Chad, clearly you're having trouble.
Dealing with the fact
that "so random!" won.
I know. I'm just...
I'm not used to this.
Losing, my picture being covered
up, condor being in a tunnel...
Who am I kidding?
He wasn't in a tunnel, I'm in a tunnel.
It's dark in here, Sonny!
Well, you better climb on out of there,
Because if we're gonna be
together you have to get used.
To me being in the spotlight sometimes.
- I hope to win a lot of awards.
- Exactly how many?
Well, I don't know!
A lot, I hope.
You know what?
We're gonna get back to normal.
Wait, we're...
we're not normal?
- I'm gonna fix this.
- Fix what?
You and me, we're gonna be good.
You will see.
- All right.
- I'm good,
We're good,
it's all good. Yeah!
He's good.
We're good. I'm good.
- How's the lobster?
- It's good.
This is so cool.
Look at all this stuff people
sent to congratulate me.
"dear tawni"... oh.
"congratulations from the entire
male cast of 'twilight.'"
- Ah.
- What? Let me see that.
"dear 'so random!'
congratulations.
From the condor studios
custodial staff."
Okay, if that's how you want to read it...
Hey, Grady, this one's for you.
Oh really?
"Grady Mitchell wrote the bird joke."
Dude, you rock and 'bok.'.
"Your friend Nico."
Wow, hey.
You took out this big ad to apologize?
Your joke, man, you deserve the credit.
Hey, you do realize
you spelled "bok" wrong?
But I spelled "friend" right.
Actually you did not.
But, um, you know,
It's the thought that counts
and not the spelling.
But I spelled "grady" right.
Come here, buddy!
Hey, what's up, randoms?
How are we enjoying this fine day?
- Oh hey there, Chad Dylan chipper.
- Oh, that I am, that I am.
- I figured out how to solve our
little problem. - Oh, great.
- Hey guys, could you give us
like five minutes? - Sure.
Who wants to take a taxi ride to see
where they make Chad park his car now?
It's funny 'cause it's true.
Wow, you're being an awfully good sport.
Well, there's no reason not to be.
See, I've been thinking
about what you said about how
I was letting "so random!"'s
win get between us.
And I wanted to fix that.
See, I knew you'd get past this.
Well, I had to...
for us.
Gosh, it just feels so good
to hear that coming from you.
You know, some silly award
shouldn't get between us.
I totally agree.
So I ordered.
A recount of the votes for best tween show.
You did what now?
I ordered a recount.
Oh, great news... "so random!" lost.
- I can't believe this.
- What, that you lost?
Oh, don't worry about it.
You'll get used to it.
I did.
No, you didn't.
You ordered a recount, Chad.
Why would you even think about doing that?
You felt weird about winning,
I felt weird about losing.
And now, thanks to me, we don't
have to feel weird anymore.
But you do have a very weird
look on your face.
It's called disappointment, Chad.
You were so miserable that you weren't
the center of attention for one day.
That you went out and ordered a recount?
Whoa, okay. I just wanted
things to go back to normal.
- Like I promised.
- Normal?!
Oh, you mean the normal where you
always win and I always lose?
I don't like that normal!
Boyfriends and girlfriends are
supposed to support each other.
Root for each other.
I can't be in a relationship with someone.
- Who always puts himself first.
- Whoa, I did this for us, okay?
No, Chad.
The only us there is now is
between you and this award.
I hope you two will be very happy together.
I'm sorry, are you breaking up with me?
'cause I thought I was helping.
That's the worst part about it.
Goodbye, Chad.
- Sonny, don't do this...
- No, just go.
- But I... - Chad, there are
no second chances this time.
I'm sorry.
You won the recount, but you lost me.
I know you guys are up there.
I'm sorry we lost.
- I don't care about that right now.
- Yeah, none of us do.
Tomorrow we will. Tomorrow I'll be
perfecting my "chad is dead to me" glare.
And we'll be painting
mustaches on Chad's posters.
Yes, and a certain someone
Dylan Cooper will be hairless.
But right now.
What we care about is you.
Thanks, guys.
You know, we could turn back the clock.
And pretend like nothing
horrible has happened yet.
And we're still winners!
I appreciate that, but...
Actually I'd rather not
turn back the clock.
I'm fine right here.
Awwww.
And the nominees for best impression of my impression are.
- Nico Harris...
- Bok-kk!
- ...Tawni Hart...
- Brawk!
- ...Sonny Munroe...
- Bawkkkk.
- ... And Zora Lancaster.
- Bwok.
And the winner is...
- Chad Dylan Cooper?
- Yeah Whoo.
No. This is such a...
Bok, suckers.
- Bok-kkk.
- Bo-oook!
- I want a recount.
- Oh!
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.ORG
www.Addic7ed.com