Mom, you home?
A little help here!
Sonny, someone
at the door needs help.
Yeah, me.
Well, tell her
I said hi--
Look out, mackenzie!
He's in the pool!
Mom, you're
watching "mackenzie falls"?
- How could you?
- How can't I?
There's just so much drama.
But it's "mackenzie falls."
it's a betrayal.
And as long as I live under
your roof, I forbid this.
- You really should give it a chance.
- Oh, I've seen it before.
The falls have been in my
family for generations, Chloe.
- He said "falls"!
- Falls!
Lemme-- no--
Give... Me...
That... Remote!
Yes! Yes!
- Don't do it!
- No! No!
Maybe it's you,
maybe it's me.
Maybe it's the horse.
Maybe it's...
The falls.
Falls!
Seriously?
Sorry.
Bad habit.
I'm really sorry.
You know, I think you need
To give this show a chance.
- At first I really didn't care
much for your show-- - Shh!
Oh, mack, how much longer
Can we keep denying our
feelings for each other?
Until I can be sure that one
of us isn't going to get hurt.
Oh, mackenzie.
Isn't it great?
Sweetie, you don't
have homework, do you?
I do.
Three seasons worth.
There's just so much drama.
* off to the races,
I'm going places *
* might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it *
* this is the big break
and it's calling my name *
* yeah *
* so far, so great,
get with it *
* at least
that's how I see it *
* having a dream
is just the beginning *
* so far, so great,
believe it *
* can't take away
this feeling *
* taking a ride,
chance on my side *
* yeah, I can't wait *
* so far, so great,
so far, so great *
Synced By YesCool
WwW.Addic7ed.com
And there's the sea
of tranquility.
And there's the second coat.
And... Done!
Hey, fellas, how's your solar
system project coming?
- Right on schedule.
- Haven't done a thing.
So it's your usual plan?
Wait for Sonny
to finish her project,
She sees how little
you've done on yours,
You "freak out,"
and she feels sorry for you.
And then she does it for us.
We put a lot of effort
into this plan.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wanna go bowling?
Ooh, I'll grab neptune
and kick your butt.
Oh.
Uranus is mine!
They should be
ashamed of themselves.
For relying on Sonny
to do all their work?
No, just in general.
Morning.
Wow!
If how bad you look
is any indication
Of how hard you've been
working on our project,
Well, may I say "hello a+"?
Because you look horrible.
Well, I didn't
get much done last night.
There was a lot
of drama at my house.
You know how this town is.
If people see us on the same
horse together, Chloe,
They will talk.
But I'm tired of riding alone.
Get on that horse, mackenzie!
I don't know what went on
at your house last night,
But I am very disappointed in you.
I did my part. See?
What does a manicure have
to do with the universe?
Because my nails
are out of this world.
Man, I had no idea you
were such a good bowler.
I am a man of many layers.
Peel one back, I am a bowler.
Peel back another,
I'm a krumper.
That might be a layer
you wanna keep covered.
- Let's get something to eat.
- Yeah.
Oh, hey, there's Sonny.
I wonder how she's doing on her project?
You know, she can't start on
ours until she finishes her own.
Wait wait wait.
Relax, g.
Your worry layer is showing.
She's probably over
there, studying away.
It's weird, Chloe.
I've never experienced
this feeling before.
It's called love!
Worried now?
This could be worse
than your krumping.
Hey, Sonny.
Oh, hey guys, what's up?
Oh, sorry.
Hey, so how's your
solar system coming?
Oh, good good.
And yours?
- Good.
- Great.
- Okay, that was a little weird
What you yelled out
a minute ago.
- What?
- Something about "love."
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
- No no no no no.
- Yeah.
That was just me, you know,
Practicing to be a...
Tennis judge.
- 40-love!
- A tennis judge?
Yeah, you know, it's always
been a dream of mine.
Fault!
Match point!
Ball boy!
See how annoying that is?
You know what?
I'm just gonna
go practice somewhere
Where I won't bother anyone.
- I'll see you guys later?
- Yup.
- Deuce!
- Whoa!
A tennis judge?
I wonder what else
she's keeping from us.
Maybe...
She's a krumper.
You have hurt me
for the last time.
It's over!
Oh no, what have I done?
That was the best
relationship I ever had.
Hi, it's Sonny.
Leave a message.
It's me again...
Partner.
Listen, that last message
was just my fear talking.
And I don't know
why my fear is talking
When your guilt should be,
Because you should be working on our project!
We're through!
Oh no, what have I done?
- Hey, have you seen Sonny?
- No, and I'm very worried.
- Me too. - You realize if she
doesn't do her project--
Then this was all for nothing!
I bought rings to match saturn.
Don't you guys see
what's happening here?
We've become just like
the solar system itself--
A perfectly balanced,
inter-connected group of bodies
Bound by gravity to the sun.
Or in this case, the Sonny.
See, I kind of felt
my metaphor was clear
Without having
to hit it on the nose.
- I don't think so.
- Well, I know so!
Stop it. Stop it!
This is horrible.
If Sonny becomes the
center of my universe,
Where does that leave me?
You?
What about us?
The fate of our scale-model
universe hangs in the balance.
People, this is bigger
than the solar system,
Or 10% of your grade.
What are you talking about?
- Well--
- Oh!
Sometimes a girl sees things,
Things she wishes she hadn't while
she's slithering around in the vents
And hiding in places
she probably shouldn't.
- What kinds of things?
- Horrible things.
The kind of things that can get you
an "f" on your science project.
Oh, I'm talking about betrayal,
The kind of betrayal that has
to be seen to be believed.
Can't we just hear about it?
Are you really this lazy?
Yes.
It's one of my layers.
You gotta see it!
Normally I control
my own destiny, Chloe,
But I'm just so confused.
Oh, mackenzie!
Sonny's a secret
"falls" watcher?
If my nails weren't so perfect,
I'd scratch her eyes out.
We can break
her of her despicable obsession
With that cheesy melodrama
and help our friend...
- Or?
- Or we can shame her.
I see no reason
we can't do both.
If I don't ask Chloe out
after they unveil my statue,
I may never get the chance
Or the courage again.
How much longer can you
expect a girl to wait?
Just ask her out, mackenzie.
Ask. Ask!
Ooh! Hey, guys.
How's it going? What's up?
- The jig, sister!
- We know your dirty little secret.
- You've been cheating on us.
- With the "falls"!
That is ridiculous, okay?
You know I hate the "falls"
just as much as you do.
Oh, do you?
Then I guess you won't mind
If we just take a look
at your phone?
- Yeah, get it!
- No no!
Hey!
The first step is admitting
you have a problem.
You're right.
I do have a problem.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go talk to a
professional immediately.
I need to talk
to you immediately.
I'm glad you're here.
I need a favor.
I don't have time to help you
with your science project.
Please, I have actual
scientists for that.
I need a tennis judge.
- Word on the street is you can help.
- What?
- I'm not a tennis judge.
- So you just made up that up?
- Yes, but listen-- - Who
makes up something like that?
Who needs a freelance
tennis judge?
Actually, I'm hosting my
annual charity tournament
- And I don't want to lose again.
- Oh, I see.
Well, as much as I'd
love to help you cheat
For a good cause,
I can't. Why?
Oh, yeah.
Because I'm not a tennis judge.
- Uh-huh. So what did you want?
- Some answers.
- To what?
- To how it all ends.
To how long it's going to be
before you ask the girl
- You're destined to be with.
- I'm not sure I can answer that.
Aren't you in charge
of your own destiny?
I guess.
Well then it's time
to say, "enough!"
I mean, when two people are this right for
each other, there's only one thing to do.
How long have you
felt this way?
Just since yesterday.
It hasn't been long,
But it hit me
like a ton of bricks.
I mean, I guess
I feel the same way.
Well, then do something
about it.
- Okay, I will.
- Great!
Sonny, will you go out with me?
I'm sorry,
did you just ask me out?
I'm sorry, didn't you
just beg me to?
Wait, did you think
I was talking about--
Oh, dear, this is awkward.
It sure is.
It sure is awkward.
I mean, I know
why it's awkward,
I just want to know
if you know...
Why it's awkward.
I was talking about
mackenzie and Chloe,
But you seemed
to be talking--
Yup yup, me too.
Same page.
- Whew!
- Whoo-hoo.
See, I just thought
you thought I thought
It was awkward because you
thought I was asking you out.
Rather than mackenzie
asking Chloe out.
Which I was.
Yeah, but you
said Sonny--
Yup yup, that's awkward.
- So.
- You're a "mackenzie falls" fan now?
- Yeah.
Cool. Cool.
So I suppose I should probably tell
you I'm a "so random!" fan now.
- Really?
- Yeah, but I'd be lying.
You know, it's funny.
Like I learned
with "mackenzie falls,"
Sometimes if you
look at something
With an open mind,
you can surprise yourself.
So... Yeah.
What?
Yeah, I'll go out with you.
- Good.
- So we're doing this.
- I guess so.
Wait. So I still don't know.
Does mackenzie ever ask--
Bah bah bah bah.
If we're gonna make this thing work,
I'm going to have to insist you
never ask me about my business.
Ugh, fine. I guess
I'm gonna have to
Check the blogs
like everybody else.
Solar system's done.
Pretty good huh?
Uh-huh.
It's a little busy.
It's a little loud.
I'll have to re-think my scarf,
but I can make it work.
Sonny, have you noticed
how little progress
Nico and I have made
on our project?
My parents are going to
be so disappointed in me.
Well, I think my glue gun is still
warmed up, so let me help you.
See? All the planets
have re-aligned
- Around the Sonny again.
- Mm-hmm.
By the way, you guys, I just
really want to say thank you
For helping me kick that
"mackenzie falls" habit.
I am so glad that's behind us.
Behind us? Ha.
I'm not over the betrayal.
- We are, we are.
- We're cool with the betrayal.
We don't mind a little
betrayal every now and again.
No, you know what?
You're right.
It was betrayal.
I kept something from you, something
that I knew would upset you.
Which is why, in the spirit
of full disclosure--
I mean, the only thing
you could possibly do
That would be a bigger betrayal
Would be if you were
dating Chad or something.
Dating Chad?
- Whoo-hoo!
- Don't even like his highlights.
That's too funny, guys.
So what did you want
to disclosure to us?
Oh... That.
That, um...
I just need to disclose
that I'm torn...
As to...
Whether or not I should
include pluto as a planet.
Uh, pluto's not a planet.
Says you.
Says NASA.
You know what?
I'm not just gonna
take NASA's word for it.
I'm going to go talk
to a professional.
Immediately.
Again.
I just need to run my lines once
before we shoot this thing.
Let's take it from where I say,
"I need to talk
to you right away."
I need to talk
to you right away.
That is my line!
Do I need to fire some-- oh, hey Sonny.
Hey, um, can I talk
to you for a sec?
Sorry to interrupt.
- Huge fan since yesterday.
- That's a five, everybody.
- Apparently I need to talk to my lady.
- Joking!
He's just kidding.
I'm not his lady.
Okay, look,
I gotta talk to you
about something.
Is this about our date?
Yes, I just...
I think we need to call it off.
Is this about
me not telling you
How things play out
between mack and Chloe?
No no no.
I seriously don't care about them
Or the "falls" right now.
I just... I think
I rushed into something
- That I didn't fully think through.
- That hurts me, Sonny.
I'm sorry.
How could you say you don't
care about the "falls"?
Whoa whoa, wait!
What are you more upset about,
The fact that I'm
calling off our date
- Or that I'm over the "falls"?
- That's a toughie.
- That's a toughie?
- It's just that, you know,
If you date me,
you date the "falls."
So if you hurt one of us,
you hurt us both.
Oh my gosh.
I can't believe I was so close
To going on a date with you.
I mean, what was I thinking?
Obviously I wasn't thinking.
Yeah, and ironically
this is a drama-free zone,
- So security!
- Let me tell you something.
24 hours ago I fell in love with a guy
named mackenzie. And you, Chad, are no--
- Don't say mackenzie!
Do not say mackenzie! - Mackenzie!
She said it! That's it!
Where's my security?
You are no longer
welcome at the "falls."
You said "falls"!
You know another layer I have?
Origami.
It's like a paper petting zoo.
You know, I'm not really a fan
Of your whole "layer"
thing, all right?
Are you okay?
Dude, why are our
planets on the ground?
And why are
they leading to--
"mackenzie falls"?
Because Sonny's not just
watching it anymore,
She's living it!
Oh! Oh!
They chased me and they chased
me until finally I shook them
When I transferred
to the cross-town bus
And grady didn't have change.
That is an unbelievable story.
It's very dramatic.
Very dramatic.
- You know what else is dramatic?
- Mom!
Oh, please let me
watch the "falls"!
Can't we just talk?
Tell me about your day.
Come on.
Oh, good.
Something to do.
- Mackenzie!
- Mom!
Sorry, I didn't know
how strict your ban was.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
Can I come in?
A little.
I thought about
what you asked me, and--
Excuse me.
Mom, you may go
watch the "falls."
I'm good.
Go watch the "falls."
- In your room.
- Awww.
Go on.
Anyways, you asked
which hurt more,
Being over the "falls" or you
canceling our date, and...
It was definitely
you canceling our date.
It's not a toughie at all.
Thanks, that's very
mackenzie of you.
Thanks.
So you never did give me a reason
why you called off our date.
It's kind of like you said.
When you date me,
you date "so random!"
And you know them,
they can be a--
What are you guys doing here?
I found change.
It's worse than we thought.
Flowers, a "mack falls" box set
And a photo of Chad
holding flowers,
And a "mack falls" box set?
- Chad?!
Well, it's pretty obvious
what's going on here.
Well, you're all wrong
Because Chad is here to see me.
What?
- Mom?
- It's okay, Sonny.
I am not ashamed
to tell them the truth.
- No, but I might be.
What are you doing? - Trust me.
Chad came here tonight bearing
gifts for me because--
Sonny's mother is also...
My mother.
So that means...
That's right.
- Chad is--
- Yes.
Your long lost brother.
You lie!
Don't believe them, Sonny!
This is the plot line
of the season finale
How would you know that, grady?
't know.
Grady? How would you
know that, grady?
Because...
Cause I used to secretly watch the "falls."
That, grady?
Ahh, who are we kidding?
We've all been hooked
at one point or another.
I hit bottom three years ago.
I've been "falls" free
for two seasons.
Six episodes.
This is awesome.
So, wait, why have you guys
been getting all over me?
- Because we thought you were different.
- We wanted to keep you pure.
And we were all very concerned
about our science projects.
But mostly to keep you pure.
But you've been
soiled by the "falls,"
Like the rest of us.
And that means that makes
you no better than me.
Ha ha! You guys can start
revolving around me again.
Wait a minute,
If Chad is not really here
because he's Sonny's brother,
Then what is he doing here?
Good one, nico.
You want me to tell them?
No! No no no,
um, I'll tell them.
Because I am not ashamed
and I have nothing to hide.
That's my girl.
I am...
Judging Chad's celebrity
tennis tournament! Duh!
- Oh!
- I know!
- I thought you were gonna
say "dating." - No.
- I'll see you guys later.
- We'll get out of here.
All right.
- Bye, Sonny!
- Later, Sonny!
So, uh...
When's the tournament?
I'll give you the details
tomorrow night.
What's tomorrow night?
I'll give you the details
tomorrow night.
Oh, our first date.
See ya.
Ooh, the plot thickens.
- Room.
- Can't we just talk?
- Room. - Aww.
Can't we just talk? - Room.
On the next
"Mackenzie falls"...
An innocent dance turns
into a date
With danger.
Chloe, we're going to polka.
Nobody can find out.
And you won't believe who's
got it out for mackenzie.
No! No spoilers--
no spoilers!
See you there.
And wear your polka pants.
I'm already wearing them.
What are u doing, J?
Sync By YesCool
WwW.Addic7ed.com