Are you ready to get
"so random!"?
Hello! I'm sicky vicky.
And welcome to "how to have
fun when you're sick."
Today I've got pinkeye.
I got it from alice mazarski.
Because she came to school with pinkeye.
Not cool.
And she also rubbed it with my pink eraser.
And then I chewed on my eraser.
And now I've got pinkeye.
I've also got pink eraser
stuck in my teeth.
But you can still have fun with pinkeye.
You can make it a whole pink day.
You can have a pink pillow.
You can drink pink lemonade.
And you can make.
Pinky puppets!
Ben feldman made a foot puppet at camp,
But that's 'cause he has
a really giant big toe.
That kinda looks more
like a finger than a toe.
I like to call it
a finger-toe.
Not cool.
But I still have a crush on him.
You can also make neat eye patches.
To cover your pinkeye
'cause it can look
really really really gross.
You can make pretty ones.
Or you can make ones
that look like a pirate.
Arrrrgh!
Dominique rombado
went as a pirate for Halloween.
And he had a real parrot on his shoulder,
But it pooped.
Not cool.
And he had
to trick-or-treat all night.
With bird poop down his back.
Well, that's it for today.
I'm sicky vicky.
Uh-oh.
This looks like an itchy red dot.
Looks like next week I'll be showing you.
How to have fun with
the chickenpox! Bye.
♪ off to the races,
I'm going places ♪
♪ might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it ♪
♪ this is the big break
and it's calling my name ♪
♪ yeah! ♪
♪ at least that's
how I see it ♪
♪ having a dream
is just the beginning ♪
♪ so far, so great,
believe it ♪
♪ can't take away
this feeling ♪
♪ taking a ride
with chance on my side ♪
♪ yeah, I can't wait ♪
♪ so far, so great ♪
♪ so far, so great... ♪
♪ yaooww! ♪.
Shut it!
Thank you.
Sonny's mine!
All right!
Everybody! Everybody!
Hey hey!
Calm down!
Okay, sonny's got just
so many hours in a day.
So be patient.
She's gonna help us all.
- He's trying to go first!
- Hey!
No, I'm not!
No, I'm not, okay?
Now let's figure this schedule
out one person at a time.
- Zora?
- Thank you.
Sonny promised to help me
prepare for my karate test.
- Hai!
- Oh!
But I just found out that I have
a conflicting kickboxing test.
Huh!
So I'm gonna need to switch my
1:00 slot with grady's 10:00.
- Oh, hey hey!
Get your hands off... - Hai!
Hey hey hey hey!
Don't touch my 12:00!
I have a lunchtime appointment with
sonny that I can't reschedule.
You know what else can't be rescheduled?
My emotions.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not giving up my special
talk time with sonny.
Know what, guys?
I'm very good at scheduling, okay?
Let me just see if I can help, okay?
- All right.
- Okay, but just don't move my 12:00.
There, everybody happy?
Hey! Awww.
Is there trouble in the funny hut?
What do you want, chad?
I'm looking for sonny.
She's supposed to be.
Helping me hang my new "mac falls" posters.
Really? Because I don't
see your name.
- On the sonny scheduling board.
- Yeah.
Well, you wouldn't 'cause now
that sonny and I are dating...
Every time!
Still so gross!
...She has a very special
chad scheduling board.
And it's, uh...
it's right there.
- Oh.
- No you didn't.
- So disgusting.
- Oh my god.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
That bugs you, doesn't it, randoms?
You know what?
Get used to it!
'cause now that sonny and I are dating,
It's time for you to start
calling chaddy daddy.
As in who's yo chaddy?
Who's yo chaddy?
Oh. Hey, babe.
Oh, don't you babe her.
She's our babe.
Yeah! Hey, babe.
Okay, all right.
Stop arguing.
I'm gonna settle this right now.
Nobody gets to call me babe.
In your face, chaddy.
Mmm! Hey!
Okay, you know what?
You guys arguing.
Is really starting to get old.
You know what else is getting old?
The sicky vicky voice.
Rehearsal's over.
I'm not doing a voice.
I'm sick.
- Oh, really?
- Aww.
Then get away from me.
Oh, but not too far.
Because I still need you to help me.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Can't you people see
my lady's not feeling well?
You people disgust me.
Almost as much as the snot rocket.
That just came out of my lady's nose.
It's okay. Come on.
Let's go get you some tea
'cause you're sick.
Lovesick.
Stop it!
You know, I'm really disappointed.
I thought once we started dating you guys
would figure out a way to get along.
And I thought once we started
dating you'd stop talking to them.
I am just as disappointed as you are.
Oh, you really are sick.
You should go home and get some rest.
I can't. I have a whole
list of things I've gotta do.
I know. The demands the randoms
put on you... they are horrible.
I'd never pressure you like that.
So I'm thinking I only need you
to hang 50 of these babies.
- You're so good to me.
- Oh, I know.
- You're not good to me!
- Hey! Careful!
If you were good to me, you wouldn't
be asking me to hang your posters.
You'd be offering to help me with my list.
What, you mean the list of things.
That help the randoms?
Wow.
How sick are you?
You know what?
You're right.
It must be the fever talking.
'cause if I wasn't sick,
Clearly I'd know that you
could never handle this list.
Really?
- Really. - 'Cause I'm pretty
sure I can handle a day.
Of babysitting your little fun hut buddies.
- Yeah, I don't think so.
- I know so.
- Really? Good.
- Really. Good..
- Fine. Going home.
- Fine. Feel better.
- Thanks.
- Miss you.
Miss you too.
My name is chad dylan cooper.
Substitute sonny.
Now I'm sick.
So, uh, how sick does this make you?
Now listen, you clowns.
I took over the list of things.
That sonny was supposed to do for you.
So if you need any help with one
of your stupid little problems,
There is a new sonny in town.
So you think you can just.
Waltz on in here
and put your name on the board.
And that's all it takes
to replace sonny, huh?
Pretty much.
I'll get you first.
It was hard to choose who goes first,
But you were very persuasive.
- It's all there.
- Ya-bop-bop-bop-bop-bop.
99, 100... okay.
So how may I be of sonny to you?
This is a list of guys I've dated.
Broken down into two categories...
The absolutelys and the absolutely nots.
And I'm here because?
Sonny always breaks up
with the rejects for me.
She's got a more gentle touch.
When it comes to dumping.
You'll see.
When sonny breaks up with you, you'll say,
"huh, that was gentle."
And when she doesn't you'll say,
"huh, I was wrong.
Sonny digs chad."
Chad's awesome.
Chad's the best.
"Everybody loves
some chaddy."
Okay, just put an x by anyone who cries.
Yeah, right.
Like I'm gonna deal with that.
I knew you could never handle this list.
- Fine.
- Good.
See?
I'm doing it.
You happy now?
Who am I talking to?
Hello, is this isaac?
How do you think that date
with tawni hart went?
Really? Wow.
Now divide that by three, subtract two...
Uh-huh.
Good. And as long as we're
talking about numbers,
Lose tawni's!
Oh, this is fun.
I know it's hard to hear,
But tawni's breaking up with you.
Oh. Well, when your
big brother gets home,
Pass this message along, okay?
Thanks, sport.
Hey, is this bennett?
Nah, chad dylan cooper here.
I'm good, I'm good.
- Chad?
- Hold on, buddy.
Is it my special talk time
with substitute sonny yet?
It's not your time.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
It's not your time either, bennett.
Yeah, tawni hart's cutting you loose,
Kicking you to the curb,
giving you the old heave-ho.
She's breaking up with you.
Still not getting it, huh?
I have broken up with a lot of guys today,
But you by far are the dumbest.
Oh!
Bennett's a crier!
All right, you got me for 20 minutes.
- What do you need?
- Her.
Sonny was gonna help me
break the ice today.
Dude, she's here for massage Monday.
You want to meet the girl,
go get your back cracked.
Oh no.
Nobody's cracking anything on me.
Okay? That's what you're
here for, substitute sonny.
You take the pain, I get the gain.
It's true.
I take the pain, he gets the gain.
Get! Get!
Fine.
You are here for your massage, ja?
Uh, ja.
You bet he is.
Uh, so tell me,
What is your specialty?
We take his unhappy spine.
And we make it happy like this.
That sounds great.
That sounds crippling.
- I don't want to do that.
- Sonny would.
Ja, I would.
Fine.
Sorry, I'm late.
I had a personal matter to deal with.
You know, I think I'd prefer that ja girl.
- Relax.
- Oh!
I spent the last two hours.
Consoling my heartbroken son.
Who was brutally dumped over the phone.
And she didn't even have
the courage to call herself.
He was dumped by some jerk.
Named chad...
Dylan cooper!
You go now?
Ja, I go now.
I can't...
I can't feel my arm.
My little boy can't feel his heart.
Oh, bennett, how are you?
I still can't feel my heart, mama.
Oh.
Wait, you're bennett the crier?
You're chad the dumper?
- You know what I'm gonna do to you?
- What?
I'm gonna cut you loose,
kick you to the curb,
- Give you the old heave-ho.
- Okay, I see what you're doing there.
You're using all those words
I wish I hadn't said.
Pretty smart for a dumb guy.
Another thing I wish I hadn't said.
Oh, excuse me.
One little call.
Just take like one sec.
I'll be right with you.
- Hello, sonny!
- Hey, chad.
How's it going with the randoms?
Just swell.
That's my girlfriend.
I gotta take this.
You know how girlfriends
are, right? Am I right?
- Yeah.
- I wouldn't know.
Oh, that reminds me.
Oh, what?
Why am I running?
I just can't wait to get
to the next thing on my list.
Whoo.
Safe and sound.
Well, my arm's feeling better.
Things are looking up for chaddy.
- Hai!
- Ow!
Where did you come from?
Look at the board.
2:00, martial arts with zora.
- Hai!
- Ow! What...
- Ow! - I'm in a match with
someone three times my size.
To qualify for my black belt.
So sonny was going to spar with me.
While wearing a fat suit.
Put this on.
- I'm not putting that on.
- Hai!
- Ah! - Come on, man,
defend yourself.
It's the only way I'm gonna
get ready for my test.
Ah, crane!
Would you quit it?!
- I got a phone timeout.
- Paralyzing death blow.
Cut it out.
- Hi.
Is everything okay?
All of a sudden I heard screams
and then the phone went dead.
- ( zora grunts )
- ( Chad screams )
- ( dial tone blares )
- Kind of like that.
You broke my phone!
Are you ready for my special talk time?
I was hoping there might be a cancelation.
Hai!
What did you do?
I wrote on the wall with crayons, mommy.
- Chad, it's me.
Get up. - Huh?
Did you break up with
this side of the list?
Yes. Yes.
The absolutely nots.
That was absolutely not as in you should.
Absolutely not break up with them!
- Absolutely.
- Who speaks like this?
Sonny would've understood this.
Absolutely.
Now you've broken me up
with the smartest guy.
- I've ever gone out with!
- Wow.
Worst day ever.
I mean, I feel like
I'm an interesting person.
And I contribute to society,
But sometimes it feels like
I'm talking and talking.
And nobody's listening.
- You know what I mean?
- Oh, I do. I do.
Lies!
You are seven minutes late!
I'm sorry.
But in my defense,
I was unconscious for five of them.
What usually happens during
your special talk time?
I'm not going to get bruised
or broken in any way?
No no no.
It's a time for me to reflect.
The people I work with,
the friendly atmosphere.
It's kind of like thanksgiving every week.
Whoo, what a relief.
I was worried.
You were gonna unload
a bunch of issues on me.
Like what?
Well, like, um...
Oh! The way nico's
always ready to ditch you.
For some pretty girl.
- Doesn't that bug you?
- I don't know. Should it?
Well, it would bug me.
- Oh, you know what else would bug me?
- What?
The way zora acts all smarter than you.
Why... why would
that bug you?
What bugs me is that it
doesn't bug you. Come on!
You don't have to yell at me.
It bugs me a little.
What else bugs you that doesn't bug me?
Mmm, well... and maybe
it's just me...
- Yeah? - What about
the way tawni treats you?
Should it bug me?
Only if you don't care.
That you're less important
to her than her shoes.
And her handbags and that yappy little dog!
Yeah, that dog!
- Oh, man, I hate that dog.
- Right?
And... and her shoes.
And the shoes she makes that dog wear.
Oh, man, that bugs me.
Whoa, calm down, mr.
Angry pants. What happened?
I thought this was supposed to
be "thanksgiving every week."
Well, it's time to take
the turkey out of the oven.
- ( timer dings )
- Yeah, grady!
Take that turkey out of the oven.
You show 'em who's boss, yeah!
Oh, there's an actual turkey.
Now that that's done,
I'm gonna have a word with my friends.
- Get 'em, grady. Yeah!
- Is chad in there?
- Do you have an appointment?
- No.
Well, we finished early, so we
can probably squeeze you in.
- That's very generous of you.
- After you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
No!
Turkey's done, and so are we.
What are you talking about?
Oh, you people with your girlfriends.
And your smarts and your little dog.
Your shoes.
You think that doesn't bug me?
Well, it does.
It bugs me bad.
And I'm bugging out, people!
What's going on with you, man?
You... you just came
from special talk time.
You always come from there with
a turkey and a happy face.
Yeah, since when you do you come out angry?
Since chad told me all the things.
That bug me about you.
- And you believed him?
- Yeah, well...
Don't you see what's going on here, g?
He ruined special talk time.
He broke me up with the
smartest guy in hollywood.
Thanks to him, I...
I cried in front of that hot girl I like.
Yeah, and I blew my karate test.
Because chad didn't train me correctly.
- Now look at this. Ya!
- Ooh.
Nothing.
- All because of...
- Chad...
- Dylan...
- Cooper.
Hey, y'all, have you seen a very tall,
Very wide, angry man looking for me?
- Oh, you've got smaller...
- Skinnier...
- Angrier...
- Prettier...
Problems to deal with.
Guys, whoa whoa whoa.
Sonny would not approve.
We-e-e-ell,
- Sonny's not here now, is she?
- Mm-mmm.
No, she's not.
You know why?
'cause she's sick.
Any of you think to call her today, huh?
See how she was doing?
Did you?
No!
You were too worried about
your own petty problems.
You know what, guys?
Chad's right.
- I'm gonna go call sonny.
- No no, I'm gonna call her.
Why should you two call her?
- I care way more about sonny.
- What?
Whoa! Time out!
As adorable as it is,
I'm gonna get her on the phone.
- On your phone...
- Oh!
'cause I am her sweet sweet sugar chaddy.
Quiet, I'm on the phone!
Hello. Oh, hey,
miss munroe.
Yeah, it's chaddy...
Uh, chad, ma'am.
I'm just calling to check
on my l... your daughter.
What?!
You... you're kidding me.
Well, okay.
Thanks.
- What is it?
- Is she all right?
We need to go see her...
Right away.
Uh, excuse me, you're blocking my...
sun... hey.
Look at all you guys
going to the beach together.
- Shut it.
- Okay, how did you find me?
- We followed the trail of lies.
- Lies!
Why did you fake being sick, sonny?
I hate to say it, sonny,
but I am on the same page.
- As the randoms on this one.
- Thank you. Yeah.
- We're a super team right now.
- Yeah, chad agrees with us.
Then I guess that means my plan worked.
What plan?
Well, ever since chad and
I started going out,
You guys have been fighting more than ever.
I just thought that if I could get.
My work family and my boyfriend...
We were just on the same page, come on.
If I could get the most
important people in my life.
To spend some quality time together,
Then maybe they could get along.
Well, that's a very noble,
Beautiful dream, sonny.
But wake up, girlfriend.
This is reality.
Nice try, sonny.
But we're out of here, okay?
There's nothing this guy can do for us.
Randoms.
Well, it's just a day
full of surprises, sonny.
And you were right.
I couldn't handle the list.
I can't believe what you do for those guys.
You're... you're
a pretty amazing friend.
Thanks. And that
was really sweet.
- What you did for me.
- Well...
- Even though I had to
trick you into it. - Whoa.
You didn't trick me into it.
Aww, it's cute that you think that.
But seriously, you have
a lot in common with them.
Really, like what?
Well, you're both easy to trick.
You both have no idea when
you're being tricked.
And you both need a lot of work.
But you're worth it.
Thanks.
You should really put some sunscreen on.
I want your face to stay perfect.
- That's disgusting!
- ( All shouting )
Get used to it, randoms!
Here. Call him and end it.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
I am so over him.
Okay.
Hi, yes.I'm calling for tawni hart.
This isn't going to be easy.
But on a scale of one to 10, how do you think it went with tawni?
I know where this is going.
Look, chad, she just doesn't want you doing a break up anymore
no no, but I can change.
Chad, it's over.
You said she'd be gentle.
Ooh. Crier
Sync by Hana.Bean
www.Itfriend.ORG
www.Addic7ed.com