Sync By YesCool
When are they gonna finish
filming this vampire movie?
I'm so sick of finding
fangs in my soup.
Oh my gosh, those could be
blake radisson's fangs.
I loved him
in the "tridark" movies.
Well, I hope you love him
eating fish sticks because...
He's eating fish sticks.
Oh my gosh, hide me.
Talk to him.
I can't.
It's blake radisson.
Hey, blake!
You're welcome.
Hot.
I mean, hi.
I mean,
how's it going?
This--
I love you as frederick,
by the way.
- See you, frederick.
- Thanks, I--
And by the way,
I love vampires
way more than werewolves.
I mean, what's with
the ah-ooh!
Less howl,
more flirty.
Right.
So did you know
That when bats
fly out of a cave,
they always turn left?
I hadn't heard.
Oh, it's true.
Just check "tridarkipedia."
Have you ever
flirted before?
Not with a vampire.
Your fish sticks
look a little dry.
Blargh!
Oh my gosh, blake,
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean--
But it looks good
on you.
Okay, bat leaving
the cave.  Bye.
Go left.
( phone ringing )
♪ off to the races,
I'm going places ♪
♪ might be a long shot,
not gonna waste it ♪
♪ this is the big break
and it's calling my name ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ so far, so great,
get with it ♪
♪ at least
that's how I see it ♪
♪ having a dream
is just the beginning ♪
♪ so far, so great,
believe it ♪
♪ can't take away
this feeling ♪
♪ taking a ride,
chance on my side ♪
♪ yeah, I can't wait ♪
♪ so far, so great,
so far, so great ♪
♪ ba ba da da-da,
ba da da da-da ♪
♪ yow! ♪
- Anxious?
- Yeah.
Me too.
What are you pacing about?
Well, I'm expecting a call
from my brother grant.
- Oh.
- Yeah.  You?
I put ketchup
on a vampire.
- Ooh.
- A totally hot vampire.
Oh.
- ( computer bleeping )
- ohh!
Don't let grant get to you
like he always does, okay?
You know what?
You're right.
Not this time.
I'm feeling good.
I'm feeling strong.
Ha ha!
Hello.
He-hey, gravy!
I'm not interrupting
anything, am I?
- Well, I mean--
- of course not,
Because that would mean
you had a life.
Grady, don't just take that.
Give it back to him.
No life, huh?
So true.
How can you
not have a life?
You're on
a t.V. Show, man.
- Have you seen it yet?
- No.  I have a life,
Filled with girls
and more girls, bro.
But you wouldn't know
about that.
I've had girlfriends.
Hermione doesn't count.
Grady's got no lady.
Oh, yeah?
Grady's got a lady,
- And you're looking at her.
- What?
You mean, you didn't tell
your brother about us?
Uh, well, it's just
it's all so new.
Speaking of new,
the shirt I bought you
looks great on you.
I thought mommy
got you that shirt.
Mm-hmm, mommy did.
Bye.
Am I a good friend
or what?  Or what?
A little love up top
right there,
right there.
What did you do?
Grant is flying out
to visit tomorrow.
This is not good.
- Oh.
- Yeah, "oh."
'cause when he finds out
you're not really
my girlfriend,
I will never hear
the end of this.
Don't worry, grady.
You know what?
I'm officially
your girlfriend--
Officially
your fake girlfriend.
Oh, really?
Well then,
make me a sandwich.
I'm just messing around.
I'll go make you
a sandwich.
So look at us
Having breakfast together
without grady and sonny.
Yeah, look at us.
For a moment there
I thought we'd have
nothing to talk about.
But here we are,
Talking about
How we thought we'd have
nothing to talk about.
That's something
to talk about.
Yeah.
No, it's not.
Yeah, we got nothing.
Oh, this could be
something.
Oh, hello hello.
Are you on the hunt
for a nutritious breakfast?
Huh?  Yeah.
Maybe there's one hiding
behind your dignity.
Enough.
Mock all you want,
But allow me
to introduce you to
The chad dylan cooper
safari bar.
It brings out
the beast in you.
Rarr!
You have your own
energy bar?
Yes, and more
importantly,
You don't.
Oh, and it's good too.
Oh.  Ohh!
A little granola,
nougat--
What's that I'm tasting
in the middle?
Success.
Chew on that, suckas!
Ow!
Pompous jerk.
If grady were here,
we'd be planning
A simple but easily-botched
prank on him.
Well, guess what.
Tawni is here.
So we're gonna
lose the botch
And kick it up a notch.
Oh, I like working
with you already.
Grady never made
our plans rhyme.
Oh, I do it all the time.
See what I did there?
I like it--
the "time-rhyme" thing.
Who is this superhero?
Oh, I know this one.
It's-- it's--
Waterguy?
No, aquaman.
Aquaman, waterguy--
what's the difference?
I don't hate waterguy.
Come on, sonny.
If my brother's gonna believe
you're my girlfriend,
You've got to know
this stuff.
Just write it on your hand
if you have to.
Well, why don't you
just hit me with some
family questions first?
Whoa, family?
We're not moving on
to family
Until you know
about my loved ones.
Sorry, but this is just like
too much pressure.
I think
I need a break.
No.
- What?
- Are you dumping me?
No, I just need
a little fresh air.
Okay.
This is how it starts.
All right, aquaman-- bad.
Iron man-- good.
Narnia-- real.
What does your hand say
about vampires?
( laughs )
Let's see...
It says "sweaty."
I mean, no, "sweet."
That was bad.
I mean--
What do you think about
having lunch with me today?
Um, let me check the hand
you're not holding.
Ready?
Oh, look at that.
It says yes.
Great.
I'll text you the details.
I'll see you later.
- Later.
- ( hisses )
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, girlfriend.
My brother just landed
and he wants to haveunch
with me and my lady.
Lunch today?
Thanks, sonny.
This might be
The coolest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
( whistling a tune )
( dramatic music playing )
Tawni:
Hey!  Seriously!
( music stops )
Just a thought--
maybe your pranks
are easily botched
Because of loud music,
bad choreography
And the throwing
of stuff.
That's my style.
Now put the bar
with the fake label
on there.
( chad singing )
♪ chad dylan cooper
safari bar ♪
♪ if you're feeling bad--
jerky chad. ♪
Huh?
That's weird.
This all fit before.
Dude, we can't
eat this.
Did you even read
the warning label?
No, all I read was
my name on the bar
And my name on the check
for the commercial
I'm gonna shoot later.
Well, you might want
to take a look.
"warning: Side effects
may include
The swelling
and/or shrinkage
of the head and--
And/or body."
Get off my vest.
"as well as intermittent
hearing loss."
You... Shouldn't...
And if you're...
Longer than four hours....
Hospital.
( hums a tune )
Where is my brother
already?
Grady, calm down.
It's gonna be okay.
Is it, sonny?
Is it?
He's gonna see
right through us.
Not if we stick
to the plan, okay?
You're gonna break up with me
in front of your brother
So you'll look strong
And so I can make my date
with blake.
You know what?
I'm gonna break up with you
Because I don't like
your singing.
Gravy!
What's up, bro?
Hey.
Don't hit me.
- I'm not gonna hit you.
- All right.
That's for thinking
I was gonna hit you.
Sorry I'm late.
I was consoling some girl
who was just dumped,
So of course,
got her number!
But I'm not gonna
call her,
Because I don't want
to deal with that baggage.
Grant, you're even more
charming in person.
Wow, and you're
even cuter.
So did you win a date-somebody-
out-of-your-league contest?
Yeah.
Are you kidding me?
He is so in my league.
In fact,
I'm out of his league.
Wow, way to go, bro.
Delta nu rules!
Did I mention
he's president
of his fraternity?
Delta nu rules!
- ( phone mooing )
- oh, excuse me.
It's blake.
He's wondering
where I am,
- So dump me
when I get back.
- Okay.
I'll miss you.
I really will.
I don't want to go.
You'd better be fast.
I'm getting flustered.
Wow.
Mad props, little bro.
Sonny's awesome.
I'm crazy
proud of you.
You're proud of me?
Totes.
And when you two break up--
and trust me,
At some point
you will lose this girl--
Guess who's gonna get
the rebound.
You?
As in ulysses s. Grant!
Okay, grady, I'm back
From rudely taking
a phone call
In the middle
of our lunch.
I'm sure you have
something to say about that.
Uh-huh, I do.
Mm-hmm.
I think it's adorable.
And it makes me
Never ever want
to break up with you.
Never?
Ever.
And you can never
ever have her.
What did you do?
We had a plan.
You were supposed to dump me.
Sorry.  I was gonna
break up with you,
But then grant said
that if we ever broke up,
He was gonna go after you.
And I couldn't let
that happen.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
But what am I supposed
to do about blake now?
Maybe he can do
dinner instead.
Great idea.
I'll text him.
Ha ha ha!
Good news--
I've got a date
with jennifer.
I mean, jessica.
She's really special
to me.
Oh, blake can
do dinner.
Don't make
any dinner plans.
The mitchell brothers are
going on a double date.
Delta nu!
Thanks, cousin.
What the delta
am I supposed to do now?
You know, I'll just
tell grant
That you're pretending
to be my girlfriend.
And then I'll
put my mouth guard in and
take what's coming to me.
Oh, no no.
Just keep it in the case.
We've got to figure out
a reason for you to break up
with me before dinner.
Yeah, but what could
anybody do
That would make a person
want to break up with them?
Oh, jackpot.
Oh, yeah.
Jackpot.
What do you think
of this?
That is disgusting.
Oh, yeah.  Oh, yeah,
that's the stuff.
( belches )
Oh.
- Seconds.
- Oh.
What happened to you?
Yeah, sonny,
you are disgusting.
I'm gonna have to rethink
our entire relationship.
Yeah, you are...
- Thinking about
marrying her.
- What?
You hit the jackpot, bro.
You've got a girlfriend
Who can never
get on your case
about being disgusting
'cause she's even
more disgusting.
Sonny is gross
and a hottie.
She's a grottie.
So I guess this means
I'll be seeing you
at dinner.
He's harder to kill
than a vampire.
You scored!
She's disgusting.
Gravy!
- Blake.
- Sonny?
I bet you're wondering
why I'm dressed like this.
You're not wearing this
on our date, are you?
'cause buca di fester's
has a dress code.
Yeah, I've heard
about that.
It's actually
for a character
On "so random!"
called "gross-out girl."
Pretty convincing, huh?
Nailed it.
Don't worry
about tonight.
I'll be cleaned up
in time for our date.
Speaking of tonight,
I was just wondering
if maybe we--
If you're going to push
our date again,
Then maybe we should
just cancel it.
No no no,
tonight's perfect.
Tonight's great.
- Cool.
( hisses )
Bye.
I delta nu it.
Grody, change of plans.
Bros' night out, bro.
So call your girlfriend
and tell her
She's free to do
whatever she wants
to do tonight,
'cause you and me are
going to buca di fester's.
B-b-b-b-b-bouncing!
Delta nu!
All right, everyone.
We got a safar bar
commercial to shoot.
Let's go.
Settle in.
Places places.
( bell rings )
"in extreme cases
Head swelling
may be followed
By funhouse vision."
Funhouse vision?
What the heck is that?
Oh!
Chad dylan cooper
for the safari bar,
take one.
And action!
Being the greatest
actor of a generation
takes a lot out of you.
So when life bites you,
bite back.
Chad, this is where
you bite the bar.
I can't do it, I can't.
I can't do it.
It's poison,
you hear me?
Celebrity.
Funhouse vision?
Awesome.
When did you have time
to change the mirror?
What are you talking about?
I didn't change the mirror.
Wha--?
( screaming )
Oh, you're good.
Wow, sonny, I have to say,
you clean up well.
Thanks.
To soap and water.
So tell me about
the "tridark" series.
Oh, this is great--
You and me at a restaurant
together
And you're not
whaling on me
Or pointing out
my shortcomings
Or telling me stuff
that makes me feel
like a loser.
Your girlfriend's
cheating on you.
Yeah, stuff like that.
No, your girlfriend
is cheating on you.
That's why I brought
you here.  Look.
Oh my gosh.
It's my girlfriend
And blake radisson,
Clearly having
a business dinner.
- Get over there.
- No no.
- Hey, sonny.
- Grady.
What are you
doing here?
waiting for, bro?
She's your girlfriend.
Mess him up good.
Wait, girlfriend?
Is that true?
- It's complicated.
- Labels-- friend, girlfriend
All right!
Once again you punk out
And I've got to step in
to protect the mitchell name.
No no, stop stop.
Enough.
Sonny is not
my girlfriend.
So you were
lying to me?
Yes, we were pretending
to be a couple
So you'd stop
giving me grief
About not having
a girlfriend.
Sonny, go get yourself
a vampire.
Thanks, grady.
Okey-dokey, since
everything's cleared up,
I am single
and totally available.
Of course you are.
A girl like you
Would never date
a dork like that.
Excuse me?
I'm just saying
we're good here.
And I'm just saying
we're done here.
Excuse me?
Yeah, if being sweet,
kind and sensitive
Makes you a dork,
then yes,
Grady is the dorkiest
dork there is.
But I'd rather date a dork
over a jerk any day.
Thanks, sonny.
( clears throat )
Now I believe the lady
Just gave you
your flying papers.
( hisses )
It works better when
I've got the makeup on
And the script says
that you're scared.
( hisses )
So, grant, I don't
really have a girlfriend.
Let the humiliation begin.
- You're a lucky man.
- Oh, come on!
Wait, what?
I've had a million
girlfriends...
Eww.
But I've never had
a friend who's a girl.
Actually, I've never had
a friend like sonny
at all--
Someone who always
has your back.
You mean, kind of
like a brother?
Yeah.
Yeah, like a brother.
You know,
all these years
I thought you should be
more like me,
But maybe I should be
a little more like you.
Starting right now
I will always be here
for you.
Nice!
Delta nu!
I like the new grant.
I like the new grady.
Hey, while we're here,
want to get a bite to eat?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- So...
- No.
To friendship!
- Hey.
How was your weekend?
Oh, good.
Yeah, it was good.
- How was yours?
- Good.
I heard
you dated sonny.
Oh, sorta.
Heard you pranked
with tawni.
Yeah, a little.
- Was she better than me?
Wait, don't answer that.
| Sync By YesCool |
| WwW.Addic7ed.com |