1
00:00:21,000 --> 00:00:25,999
<font color="#ff0000" face="Stencil"><b>Sync and Corrected by coolsuren.
Thank you for downloading!</b></font>

2
00:03:02,265 --> 00:03:03,473
Move! Move it!

3
00:03:03,474 --> 00:03:04,515
Move!

4
00:03:05,935 --> 00:03:07,310
Move!

5
00:03:07,311 --> 00:03:08,395
Now!

6
00:03:38,217 --> 00:03:39,342
It's me home.

7
00:03:39,343 --> 00:03:41,135
Bye, Bruno!
Bye, Bruno!

8
00:04:07,038 --> 00:04:10,039
Hello, sweetheart.
Mum, what's going on?

9
00:04:10,666 --> 00:04:13,043
We're celebrating.
Celebrating?

10
00:04:13,044 --> 00:04:15,045
Your father's been given a promotion.

11
00:04:15,046 --> 00:04:17,546
- That means a better job.
- I know what promotion is.

12
00:04:18,090 --> 00:04:20,050
So we're having a little
party to celebrate.

13
00:04:20,051 --> 00:04:22,510
He's still going to be a soldier
though, isn't he?

14
00:04:22,511 --> 00:04:26,347
Yes, my love.
Yes, just a more important one now.

15
00:04:27,350 --> 00:04:29,351
There's some even more exciting news,

16
00:04:29,352 --> 00:04:32,811
but I think Dad wanted
to tell you about that himself.

17
00:04:34,106 --> 00:04:38,109
- Moving? Where to?
- To the countryside.

18
00:04:38,110 --> 00:04:42,906
That's miles away. What about
Karl and Leon and Martin?

19
00:04:42,907 --> 00:04:44,407
Sweetheart, I know it's hard,

20
00:04:44,408 --> 00:04:48,078
but we're all having to say good-bye
to our friends for the time being.

21
00:04:48,079 --> 00:04:50,747
Anyway, we'll make new ones
where we're going. Won't we?

22
00:04:50,748 --> 00:04:52,915
Of course you are.
You'll make lots of new friends.

23
00:04:55,252 --> 00:04:59,005
Bruno, you can have your friends
around in the morning before we go.

24
00:04:59,006 --> 00:05:02,424
Think of it as an adventure,
like in one of your books.

25
00:05:03,386 --> 00:05:05,260
But this is the best house ever.

26
00:05:06,389 --> 00:05:10,100
Well, you never know. The house
we're going to might be even better.

27
00:05:10,101 --> 00:05:12,267
Dad says it's got a garden.
Mm-hmm.

28
00:05:14,230 --> 00:05:18,274
Look, the thing is, Bruno,
the thing about being a soldier,

29
00:05:18,275 --> 00:05:21,569
is that life is not so much about choice,
it's more about duty,

30
00:05:21,570 --> 00:05:24,572
so if your country needs you
to go somewhere, you'll go.

31
00:05:24,573 --> 00:05:28,118
Now, of course, going somewhere else
is much easier...

32
00:05:28,119 --> 00:05:32,037
when you know that your family
are so delighted to go with you.

33
00:06:14,081 --> 00:06:18,293
Bruno! You're getting bigger
every time I see you.

34
00:06:18,294 --> 00:06:20,587
It's only been a week, Nathalie.

35
00:06:20,588 --> 00:06:23,505
Well, perhaps it's me
that's getting smaller.

36
00:06:25,342 --> 00:06:27,010
So, you two,

37
00:06:27,011 --> 00:06:30,263
well, what do you think of all this?
Moving out of Berlin?

38
00:06:30,264 --> 00:06:33,099
Well, Mummy and Daddy say
it's a good thing, so I suppose it must be.

39
00:06:33,100 --> 00:06:35,059
Mmm.

40
00:06:36,854 --> 00:06:40,814
Children, be angels, will you?
Pass some food around.

41
00:06:47,031 --> 00:06:49,156
Heil Hitler!
Heil Hitler!

42
00:07:24,235 --> 00:07:25,692
Congratulations.

43
00:07:27,154 --> 00:07:30,572
Doesn't he look wonderful?
Absolutely.

44
00:07:31,408 --> 00:07:33,742
I'm so proud of you, my boy.

45
00:07:34,495 --> 00:07:38,748
Oh, dear. I sometimes wonder
if this is all down to me,

46
00:07:38,749 --> 00:07:42,710
making you those costumes
for your little plays when you were tiny.

47
00:07:42,711 --> 00:07:46,923
- You used to adore all that dressing up.
- Nathalie.

48
00:07:46,924 --> 00:07:49,883
Does it still make you
feel special, Ralf dear?

49
00:07:50,761 --> 00:07:53,930
The uniform and what it stands for?

50
00:07:53,931 --> 00:07:57,517
Mother, it's a party.
Let's not spoil things.

51
00:07:57,518 --> 00:08:00,102
Me, spoil things?

52
00:08:01,772 --> 00:08:03,690
You should be careful.

53
00:08:03,691 --> 00:08:07,735
Airing your views so publicly could
land you in trouble. You know that.

54
00:08:10,531 --> 00:08:13,950
So, how long are we losing you for, my boy?

55
00:08:13,951 --> 00:08:18,996
Until the war is won, I would think.
Well, not so long then.

56
00:08:20,791 --> 00:08:27,213
♪ You've got to smile when 
you say good-bye ♪

57
00:08:27,214 --> 00:08:32,677
♪ You've got to smile as the days go by ♪

58
00:08:32,678 --> 00:08:38,892
♪ And all the time that you're away
I'm thinking of you ♪

59
00:08:38,893 --> 00:08:43,813
♪ I'll write and say from day to day
how much I love you ♪

60
00:08:43,814 --> 00:08:50,153
♪ You've got to
smile when you say good-bye ♪

61
00:08:50,154 --> 00:08:56,034
♪ You've got to smile
till the clouds roll by ♪

62
00:08:56,035 --> 00:09:01,664
♪ So till we meet again
Say cheerio and then ♪

63
00:09:01,665 --> 00:09:07,169
♪ Give me a smile
when you say good-bye ♪

64
00:09:27,775 --> 00:09:29,024
Bruno!

65
00:09:34,448 --> 00:09:37,783
All right, Bruno.
Time to say good-bye.

66
00:10:05,396 --> 00:10:07,312
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye!

67
00:10:42,349 --> 00:10:46,269
"Time has come for me to sleep
Lord, I thank Thee for Thy keep.

68
00:10:46,270 --> 00:10:49,772
Watch this night well over me
And teach me, Lord, to trust in Thee.

69
00:10:49,773 --> 00:10:53,276
Care for children, sick and poor
Grant them, Lord, Thy blessing more.

70
00:10:53,277 --> 00:10:56,863
And this I pray in Jesus' name
Care for my family just the same...

71
00:10:56,864 --> 00:10:57,904
Amen.

72
00:11:42,576 --> 00:11:46,745
Children, look.
Look! Our new home.

73
00:12:35,796 --> 00:12:39,464
I have some business to take care of.
I'll see you shortly.

74
00:12:56,316 --> 00:12:58,316
Well, what do we think?

75
00:13:01,238 --> 00:13:03,406
Oh, come on. It's lovely.

76
00:13:03,407 --> 00:13:06,867
You two choose your rooms.
I'll have Maria come...

77
00:13:08,495 --> 00:13:10,412
and help you unpack.

78
00:13:24,595 --> 00:13:28,096
What do you think of it, Maria?
The new house.

79
00:13:29,183 --> 00:13:33,185
Well, it's not for me to say.

80
00:13:35,189 --> 00:13:38,399
But it won't feel like home
until we make it feel like home, will it?

81
00:13:45,908 --> 00:13:47,782
Is he already up?

82
00:13:52,789 --> 00:13:54,373
Who was that?

83
00:13:54,374 --> 00:13:57,084
One of your
father's soldiers, I suppose.

84
00:13:57,085 --> 00:14:01,463
- He looked very serious.
- Well, they are, aren't they?

85
00:14:05,302 --> 00:14:10,263
- Why are we whispering?
- I don't know.

86
00:14:44,841 --> 00:14:48,761
- And play with who?
- The children over on the farm.

87
00:14:48,762 --> 00:14:51,847
Farm? I didn't see a farm.
And that one, too.

88
00:14:51,848 --> 00:14:54,267
You can only see it from my room.

89
00:14:54,268 --> 00:14:56,686
Hmm.
And are some children there?

90
00:14:56,687 --> 00:14:59,564
Yes, quite a few.
That's good.

91
00:14:59,565 --> 00:15:03,401
So, I'll be able to play with them.
I don't see why not.

92
00:15:03,402 --> 00:15:07,780
I'll wait a little bit,
just to see what they're like,

93
00:15:07,781 --> 00:15:11,032
because they look a bit strange.
The children do?

94
00:15:11,785 --> 00:15:14,537
Well, and the farmers.
What sort of strange?

95
00:15:19,626 --> 00:15:21,209
I'm sorry.

96
00:15:22,045 --> 00:15:23,045
Vegetables.

97
00:15:24,840 --> 00:15:26,047
There.

98
00:15:30,512 --> 00:15:31,929
Bruno, have you unpacked everything?

99
00:15:31,930 --> 00:15:34,931
Because I think you should
go back upstairs and finish off.

100
00:15:38,020 --> 00:15:39,686
Thank you, ma'am.

101
00:15:43,692 --> 00:15:45,066
Bruno.

102
00:15:45,694 --> 00:15:48,029
- I told you they were strange.
- Who?

103
00:15:48,030 --> 00:15:50,697
The farmers. They wear pajamas.

104
00:16:08,342 --> 00:16:10,884
Bruno, I was just coming to look for you.

105
00:16:11,511 --> 00:16:13,596
Well, thank you for that.
That was extremely useful.

106
00:16:13,597 --> 00:16:15,878
I'll be over to see you later.
Of course, Herr Kommandant.

107
00:16:17,351 --> 00:16:18,725
Come in.

108
00:16:23,190 --> 00:16:24,939
Sit down, sit down.

109
00:16:26,109 --> 00:16:28,109
Well, what do you think?

110
00:16:30,197 --> 00:16:31,446
Oh, dear.

111
00:16:32,115 --> 00:16:33,782
I want to go home.

112
00:16:35,619 --> 00:16:39,622
You are home, Bruno.
Home is where the family is.

113
00:16:39,623 --> 00:16:41,289
Isn't that right?

114
00:16:43,377 --> 00:16:47,588
Bruno, you have to at least
give the place a chance.

115
00:16:47,589 --> 00:16:49,298
I promise you,
it won't be long before you-

116
00:16:49,299 --> 00:16:54,344
Why do the farmers wear pajamas?
I can see them from my window.

117
00:17:02,896 --> 00:17:07,315
The thing is, Bruno, those people-

118
00:17:08,110 --> 00:17:11,277
Well, you see, they're not
really people at all.

119
00:17:16,410 --> 00:17:18,244
Bruno, who told you it was a farm?

120
00:17:18,245 --> 00:17:19,994
Was it Maria?
No.

121
00:17:20,664 --> 00:17:22,288
It is a farm, isn't it?

122
00:17:24,251 --> 00:17:25,251
Yes.

123
00:17:27,587 --> 00:17:30,131
Is it to do with your new job?

124
00:17:30,132 --> 00:17:32,967
All you need to know about
my work here, Bruno,

125
00:17:32,968 --> 00:17:36,720
is that it's very important
to our country and to you.

126
00:17:37,597 --> 00:17:40,015
We're working very hard
to make this world a better place...

127
00:17:40,016 --> 00:17:41,100
for you to grow up in.

128
00:17:41,101 --> 00:17:43,852
But you're not a farmer.
You're a soldier.

129
00:17:44,521 --> 00:17:47,648
Bruno, can you come and help me
finish sorting out in the kitchen?

130
00:17:47,649 --> 00:17:51,526
I can still play with them, though?
The children.

131
00:17:52,446 --> 00:17:54,864
I don't think so,
Bruno. No.

132
00:17:54,865 --> 00:17:58,492
Like you say, they're a bit strange.
A bit-

133
00:17:58,493 --> 00:18:00,452
Well, they're different.

134
00:18:01,037 --> 00:18:03,789
Don't worry, my darling.
We'll find you some new friends,

135
00:18:03,790 --> 00:18:06,499
but they won't be the ones from the farm.

136
00:18:07,002 --> 00:18:10,421
Ralf, you promised. You said
it was miles away. It is.

137
00:18:10,422 --> 00:18:13,048
How was I to know he could see it
from the bedroom window?

138
00:18:13,049 --> 00:18:14,549
There was one of them in our kitchen.

139
00:18:57,093 --> 00:18:59,886
Master Bruno, how
are you today? Fed up.

140
00:19:01,348 --> 00:19:04,350
You said the same thing
every day for two whole weeks.

141
00:19:04,351 --> 00:19:07,436
- It's true.
- Well, you should be out playing.

142
00:19:07,437 --> 00:19:09,979
- Playing with who?
- I don't know. Gretel?

143
00:19:11,942 --> 00:19:16,904
- Well, you can make your own fun.
- That's what I'm trying to do.

144
00:19:16,905 --> 00:19:18,197
One thing's for sure,

145
00:19:18,198 --> 00:19:21,950
sitting around being miserable
won't make things any happier.

146
00:20:14,254 --> 00:20:17,172
- Bruno, what are you doing?
- Exploring!

147
00:20:17,173 --> 00:20:20,467
No! No, not in the back.
I told you, it's out of bounds.

148
00:20:20,468 --> 00:20:23,095
- Explore at the front.
- But I've explored it all.

149
00:20:23,096 --> 00:20:26,306
- Well, find something else to do.
- Like what?

150
00:20:27,309 --> 00:20:30,435
Come back in now, and
we'll think of something.

151
00:20:58,882 --> 00:21:00,674
So, children, what are you doing today?

152
00:21:00,675 --> 00:21:03,052
Same as yesterday.
And what was that?

153
00:21:03,053 --> 00:21:06,512
- Same as the day before.
- Except you went exploring.

154
00:21:07,891 --> 00:21:10,517
- I like exploring.
- Where did you go?

155
00:21:10,518 --> 00:21:14,438
I wanted to look in the back garden,
but Mum wouldn't let me.

156
00:21:14,439 --> 00:21:15,772
The back garden?

157
00:21:16,858 --> 00:21:18,484
Well, God forbid.

158
00:21:18,485 --> 00:21:20,819
I expect you'll be missing
those friends of yours.

159
00:21:20,820 --> 00:21:23,237
I even miss school.

160
00:21:24,157 --> 00:21:27,201
Well, I never thought
I'd hear you say that.

161
00:21:27,202 --> 00:21:29,203
Anyway, you won't be missing
it for long. Really?

162
00:21:29,204 --> 00:21:32,288
I've arranged a tutor for you both.

163
00:21:33,083 --> 00:21:35,917
A Herr Liszt will be visiting twice a week.

164
00:21:36,753 --> 00:21:39,504
So we're not going to school?

165
00:21:41,716 --> 00:21:43,591
School's coming here?
Mm-hmm.

166
00:21:44,427 --> 00:21:46,886
On an old bicycle, I gather.

167
00:22:05,115 --> 00:22:07,365
It's a bird without the-

168
00:22:32,642 --> 00:22:35,893
Good morning, little man.
And how are you this morning?

169
00:22:36,646 --> 00:22:39,731
Can I ask you a favor?
Well, you can ask.

170
00:22:41,151 --> 00:22:43,819
Are there any spare tires around?

171
00:22:43,820 --> 00:22:46,363
An old one from one of
the trucks or something?

172
00:22:46,364 --> 00:22:49,283
Well, the only spare tire
I've seen around here...

173
00:22:49,284 --> 00:22:50,909
belongs to Lieutenant Meinberg.

174
00:22:57,417 --> 00:23:00,835
Well, is he using it?
Yes, he's very attached to it.

175
00:23:01,629 --> 00:23:04,673
Stop it. He doesn't understand.
He's only eight.

176
00:23:04,674 --> 00:23:08,176
You're only 12,
so stop pretending you're any older.

177
00:23:10,346 --> 00:23:12,306
What do you want a tire for, anyway?

178
00:23:12,307 --> 00:23:15,350
- I want to make a swing.
- A swing?

179
00:23:15,351 --> 00:23:17,351
That does sound exciting.

180
00:23:23,902 --> 00:23:24,902
You!

181
00:23:26,321 --> 00:23:27,528
Here, now.

182
00:23:30,241 --> 00:23:31,574
Move!

183
00:23:34,162 --> 00:23:36,662
Take this boy to the outhouse
in the back garden.

184
00:23:37,665 --> 00:23:39,792
There are some tires in there.
He will select one.

185
00:23:39,793 --> 00:23:42,043
You will carry it where he asks.
Do you understand?

186
00:23:47,217 --> 00:23:49,383
Well, little man, what are you waiting for?

187
00:24:33,805 --> 00:24:35,638
How about this one?

188
00:25:22,687 --> 00:25:24,729
Where's my mum?

189
00:25:26,608 --> 00:25:27,815
She's out.

190
00:25:28,735 --> 00:25:31,235
When is she back?
Soon, I expect.

191
00:25:32,530 --> 00:25:34,155
But don't worry.

192
00:25:36,034 --> 00:25:39,452
But I might bleed to death.
No, you won't.

193
00:25:46,502 --> 00:25:51,505
Will I need to go to hospital?
No. It's only a small cut.

194
00:25:54,510 --> 00:25:56,677
Oh, come on. It's not that bad.

195
00:25:57,555 --> 00:26:00,890
There, all better.

196
00:26:13,154 --> 00:26:16,572
- What's your name?
- Pavel.

197
00:26:18,576 --> 00:26:22,162
Now, you better sit still
for a few minutes...

198
00:26:22,163 --> 00:26:24,915
before you start walking
around on that again.

199
00:26:24,916 --> 00:26:26,999
Will you tell my mum what happened?

200
00:26:28,544 --> 00:26:31,379
I think she's going to see it for herself.

201
00:26:32,423 --> 00:26:34,924
She'll probably want to
take me to a doctor.

202
00:26:36,302 --> 00:26:38,136
I don't think so.

203
00:26:38,137 --> 00:26:41,305
It could be worse than it looks.
It isn't.

204
00:26:42,433 --> 00:26:45,268
How would you know?
You're not a doctor.

205
00:26:49,732 --> 00:26:52,818
- Yes, I am.
- No, you're not.

206
00:26:52,819 --> 00:26:54,110
You peel potatoes.

207
00:26:55,989 --> 00:26:58,072
I practiced as a doctor.

208
00:26:59,242 --> 00:27:00,993
Before I-

209
00:27:00,994 --> 00:27:03,077
Before I came here.

210
00:27:04,163 --> 00:27:08,040
You couldn't have been much good
then, if you had to practice.

211
00:27:16,592 --> 00:27:21,220
Now, what are you going
to be when you grow up?

212
00:27:22,265 --> 00:27:25,433
I know. An explorer.

213
00:27:26,102 --> 00:27:27,393
How do you know that?

214
00:27:31,232 --> 00:27:32,440
Is it nice on the farm?

215
00:27:42,035 --> 00:27:44,745
Bruno. Bruno,
what happened to you?

216
00:27:44,746 --> 00:27:48,582
I made a swing,
but I fell off it and cut my knee.

217
00:27:48,583 --> 00:27:52,209
But Pavel here, he carried me in
and put a bandage on it.

218
00:27:59,427 --> 00:28:01,511
Go to your room.
But Pavel says I-

219
00:28:01,512 --> 00:28:03,679
Don't argue. Go to your room.

220
00:28:31,834 --> 00:28:33,167
Thank you.

221
00:28:57,610 --> 00:29:00,320
It's not fair, you having this view.

222
00:29:00,321 --> 00:29:02,239
Well, I'm not swapping.

223
00:29:07,328 --> 00:29:09,245
I think school's here.

224
00:29:10,998 --> 00:29:13,333
No, I mean more recent history.

225
00:29:13,334 --> 00:29:17,170
Are you interested in current affairs?
Yes, very.

226
00:29:17,171 --> 00:29:21,007
So, you'll be aware of the situation...

227
00:29:21,008 --> 00:29:22,928
in which our great nation
presently finds itself.

228
00:29:23,469 --> 00:29:27,889
Yes. I read newspapers whenever I can
and one of Father's men...

229
00:29:27,890 --> 00:29:29,975
keeps me up to date
on everything that's happening.

230
00:29:29,976 --> 00:29:34,562
Good. And you, Bruno.
Have you been reading newspapers?

231
00:29:36,357 --> 00:29:40,025
- Have you been reading anything?
- Books.

232
00:29:40,778 --> 00:29:43,112
Good. What sort of books?

233
00:29:44,240 --> 00:29:46,199
Adventure books, mainly.

234
00:29:46,200 --> 00:29:51,371
You know, knights in shining armor,
exploring strange lands and stuff,

235
00:29:51,372 --> 00:29:54,124
and silly princesses
always getting in the way.

236
00:29:54,125 --> 00:29:58,544
Well, this is why I'm here to help.
You're how old now, Bruno? Eight?

237
00:29:59,755 --> 00:30:01,715
Time to get your head
out of those fiction books...

238
00:30:01,716 --> 00:30:03,884
and start learning about fact.

239
00:30:03,885 --> 00:30:07,929
Time, I think,
to turn your mind to the real world,

240
00:30:07,930 --> 00:30:10,598
and I believe this would
be the perfect start.

241
00:31:46,654 --> 00:31:48,070
Die, die!

242
00:31:59,125 --> 00:32:01,292
Die, die.

243
00:32:54,930 --> 00:32:56,096
Hello.

244
00:33:02,146 --> 00:33:03,687
I'm exploring.

245
00:33:09,403 --> 00:33:12,988
- What are you doing?
- We're-We're building a new hut.

246
00:33:19,121 --> 00:33:21,914
Have you got lots
of friends over there?

247
00:33:22,792 --> 00:33:26,002
A few. But we fight a lot.

248
00:33:26,003 --> 00:33:30,631
That's why I like being out here.
I can be on my own.

249
00:33:33,135 --> 00:33:35,844
- I'm Bruno.
- Shmuel.

250
00:33:36,430 --> 00:33:38,472
Sorry?
I'm Shmuel.

251
00:33:40,101 --> 00:33:44,020
That's your name? Never heard
of anyone called that before.

252
00:33:44,021 --> 00:33:46,314
I've never heard of anyone called Bruno.

253
00:33:46,315 --> 00:33:50,693
But Shmuel.
No one's called Shmuel.

254
00:33:56,158 --> 00:33:58,492
I live in the house, back there.

255
00:34:01,664 --> 00:34:04,498
Have you got any food on you?
No.

256
00:34:05,918 --> 00:34:07,459
- Are you hungry?
- Mmm.

257
00:34:16,679 --> 00:34:18,303
How old are you?

258
00:34:19,056 --> 00:34:21,390
- Eight.
- Me, too!

259
00:34:27,690 --> 00:34:31,443
It's not fair,
me being stuck over here on my own,

260
00:34:31,444 --> 00:34:34,028
while you're over there,
playing with friends all day.

261
00:34:34,029 --> 00:34:37,574
- Playing?
- Well, that number.

262
00:34:37,575 --> 00:34:41,077
Isn't it a part of a game or something?
It's just my number.

263
00:34:41,078 --> 00:34:43,538
Everyone gets given a different number.

264
00:34:43,539 --> 00:34:45,582
Right. Then what happens?

265
00:34:49,003 --> 00:34:51,546
- I have to go back now!
- Really?

266
00:34:51,547 --> 00:34:52,588
Yeah.

267
00:34:53,215 --> 00:34:56,217
It was nice to meet you, Shmuel.

268
00:34:56,218 --> 00:34:58,510
And you, Bruno.

269
00:35:00,514 --> 00:35:01,722
Come back!

270
00:35:09,273 --> 00:35:10,397
Bye.

271
00:35:22,119 --> 00:35:24,496
Mum, I can't find my football.

272
00:35:24,497 --> 00:35:26,377
Well, it'll be in one of
your cupboards, sweet.

273
00:35:26,791 --> 00:35:28,081
It isn't. I've looked.

274
00:35:29,126 --> 00:35:30,959
Can I have a piece of chocolate?

275
00:35:31,754 --> 00:35:33,253
Mmm. A piece. Yes.

276
00:35:40,763 --> 00:35:42,388
Bruno?

277
00:35:42,389 --> 00:35:46,476
- Have you looked in the cellar?
- The cellar?

278
00:35:46,477 --> 00:35:49,812
- For your football.
- Oh.

279
00:36:27,810 --> 00:36:28,934
Damn.

280
00:36:55,045 --> 00:36:58,505
- Gretel, I've just seen all your-
- All my what?

281
00:36:59,633 --> 00:37:02,801
All your dolls, down in the cellar.

282
00:37:03,679 --> 00:37:06,890
Dolls are for little girls.

283
00:37:06,891 --> 00:37:09,642
It's not right to be
playing with silly toys...

284
00:37:09,643 --> 00:37:12,895
while people are away
risking their lives for the Fatherland.

285
00:37:54,188 --> 00:37:58,440
"My people's density is my density."
Destiny.

286
00:38:00,986 --> 00:38:04,781
"Its struggles and its sorrows,
its joys and its miseries are mine.

287
00:38:04,782 --> 00:38:08,493
"I must work and create
for the resurrection of my Fatherland."

288
00:38:08,494 --> 00:38:11,162
"The history of my people
is great and glorious."

289
00:38:11,163 --> 00:38:12,663
And it's 12:00.

290
00:38:15,751 --> 00:38:19,044
- I'm sorry?
- Isn't that when we finish?

291
00:38:19,964 --> 00:38:23,216
The termination of the lesson
is for the tutor to decide, Bruno,

292
00:38:23,217 --> 00:38:26,134
not the pupil.
Now, will you please continue?

293
00:38:41,360 --> 00:38:43,193
Bruno, there you are.

294
00:38:44,154 --> 00:38:47,531
I'm just going into town for an hour.
Do you want to come?

295
00:38:49,827 --> 00:38:51,118
You be careful on that thing.

296
00:38:52,371 --> 00:38:54,413
Thank you.

297
00:39:11,849 --> 00:39:14,142
Can I ask you something?

298
00:39:14,143 --> 00:39:16,852
Why do you people wear pajamas all day?

299
00:39:17,521 --> 00:39:21,189
- They're not pajamas.
- Well, those.

300
00:39:21,734 --> 00:39:24,861
We have to. They took
all our other clothes away.

301
00:39:24,862 --> 00:39:26,779
Who did?
The soldiers.

302
00:39:26,780 --> 00:39:28,447
The soldiers? Why?

303
00:39:31,452 --> 00:39:34,453
I don't like soldiers. Do you?

304
00:39:35,122 --> 00:39:38,248
I do, quite.
My dad's a soldier,

305
00:39:38,917 --> 00:39:41,501
but not the sort that takes
people's clothes away for no reason.

306
00:39:42,296 --> 00:39:43,879
What sort, then?

307
00:39:45,716 --> 00:39:48,509
Well, he's the important sort.

308
00:39:48,510 --> 00:39:51,970
He's in charge of making
everything better for everyone.

309
00:39:54,016 --> 00:39:57,934
- So is your dad a farmer?
- No, he's a watchmaker.

310
00:39:59,521 --> 00:40:03,774
Or was. Most of the time now,
he just mends boots.

311
00:40:06,695 --> 00:40:08,946
It's funny how grown-ups
can't make their minds up...

312
00:40:08,947 --> 00:40:12,116
about what they want to do.
It's like Pavel.

313
00:40:12,117 --> 00:40:14,576
Do you know him?
Lives over there.

314
00:40:16,038 --> 00:40:20,749
He used to be a doctor,
but gave it all up to peel potatoes.

315
00:40:30,385 --> 00:40:32,011
Can I ask you another question?

316
00:40:32,012 --> 00:40:34,680
What do you burn in those chimneys?

317
00:40:34,681 --> 00:40:38,434
I saw them going the other day.
Is it just lots of hay and stuff?

318
00:40:38,435 --> 00:40:41,562
I don't know.
We're not allowed over there.

319
00:40:41,563 --> 00:40:43,230
Mama says it's old clothes.

320
00:40:43,857 --> 00:40:46,442
Well, whatever it is, it smells horrid.

321
00:40:49,905 --> 00:40:52,156
I wish you'd remembered the chocolate.

322
00:40:52,157 --> 00:40:53,866
Yes, I'm sorry.

323
00:40:53,867 --> 00:40:56,702
I know! Perhaps you can come
and have supper with us sometime.

324
00:40:56,703 --> 00:40:59,496
I can't, can I? Because of this.

325
00:41:00,249 --> 00:41:02,834
But that's to stop
the animals getting out, isn't it?

326
00:41:02,835 --> 00:41:06,420
Animals?
No, it's to stop people getting out.

327
00:41:06,421 --> 00:41:08,588
Are you not allowed out?

328
00:41:09,550 --> 00:41:13,635
- Why? What have you done?
- I'm a Jew.

329
00:41:26,275 --> 00:41:27,941
I think I should go now.

330
00:41:33,240 --> 00:41:35,825
Will you be here tomorrow?
I'll try.

331
00:41:35,826 --> 00:41:38,493
Good-bye, then!
Bye.

332
00:41:42,958 --> 00:41:45,041
Little present, sweetheart.

333
00:41:48,630 --> 00:41:50,297
Thank you, Mummy.

334
00:41:58,223 --> 00:42:01,141
- Have you seen Bruno?
- Outside on his swing, I think.

335
00:42:15,240 --> 00:42:18,993
Yes, Thursday's perfect.
I'll have a car come to collect you both.

336
00:42:18,994 --> 00:42:20,452
Are Grandma and Grandpa coming?

337
00:42:22,331 --> 00:42:25,958
Hey, did you smell that
horrible smell the other day?

338
00:42:25,959 --> 00:42:28,877
- Coming from the chimneys.
- What sort of ill?

339
00:42:30,672 --> 00:42:32,839
The day I fell off the swing.

340
00:42:33,550 --> 00:42:36,385
Did you smell it, Mum?
Father.

341
00:42:36,386 --> 00:42:37,761
Mum.

342
00:42:39,556 --> 00:42:41,349
Let me speak to her.

343
00:42:41,350 --> 00:42:43,266
Yes, she is. I can hear her.

344
00:42:46,688 --> 00:42:49,022
Yes. We look forward to it.
Good-bye.

345
00:42:54,821 --> 00:42:57,197
Is Grandma not coming?
No.

346
00:42:57,699 --> 00:43:01,201
She's poorly, apparently,
but Grandpa's coming.

347
00:43:03,372 --> 00:43:05,581
- Did you smell it, Dad?
- What?

348
00:43:05,582 --> 00:43:09,084
That horrid smell from the chimneys.
What is it?

349
00:43:12,839 --> 00:43:15,216
I think they just burn
rubbish there sometimes.

350
00:43:15,217 --> 00:43:16,925
Look.
What?

351
00:43:20,138 --> 00:43:21,513
Hey!
Gretel.

352
00:43:23,101 --> 00:43:24,767
Hey, that's not fair!

353
00:43:24,768 --> 00:43:26,226
- Gretel.
- What?

354
00:43:27,145 --> 00:43:28,770
It's only a game.

355
00:43:34,152 --> 00:43:36,737
Ralf, this tutor you brought in,

356
00:43:36,738 --> 00:43:40,490
does he usually teach children
as young as Gretel and Bruno?

357
00:43:41,118 --> 00:43:42,827
I believe so. Why?

358
00:43:42,828 --> 00:43:44,829
Well, do we know what he's teaching them?

359
00:43:44,830 --> 00:43:46,747
Gretel seems to have
become so-

360
00:43:46,748 --> 00:43:49,375
They're being taught what all children
are being taught at the moment.

361
00:43:49,376 --> 00:43:51,126
They mustn't get left behind.

362
00:43:52,546 --> 00:43:54,587
Come on.

363
00:43:55,424 --> 00:43:56,464
Let's get to bed.

364
00:44:08,103 --> 00:44:10,896
"The Jew slandered us and
incited our enemies."

365
00:44:10,897 --> 00:44:13,357
The Jew corrupted us through bad books.

366
00:44:13,358 --> 00:44:15,443
He mocked our literature and our music.

367
00:44:15,444 --> 00:44:17,945
Everywhere, his influence was destructive,

368
00:44:17,946 --> 00:44:21,198
the eventual result of which
was our nation's collapse,

369
00:44:21,199 --> 00:44:22,782
and then-"
Yes, Bruno?

370
00:44:23,535 --> 00:44:25,870
I don't understand.

371
00:44:25,871 --> 00:44:28,413
A nation's collapse is all
down to this one man?

372
00:44:28,957 --> 00:44:32,543
The Jew here means the entire Jewish race.

373
00:44:32,544 --> 00:44:34,587
If it had been just one man,

374
00:44:34,588 --> 00:44:37,255
I'm sure something would've
been done about him.

375
00:44:39,301 --> 00:44:42,553
There is such a thing as a nice Jew,
though, isn't there?

376
00:44:42,554 --> 00:44:46,306
I think, Bruno, if you
ever found a nice Jew,

377
00:44:47,476 --> 00:44:50,518
you would be the best
explorer in the world.

378
00:44:54,733 --> 00:44:56,358
Continue, Gretel.

379
00:44:58,320 --> 00:45:01,489
"The aim of the Jew
is to become the ruler of humanity."

380
00:45:01,490 --> 00:45:04,241
The Jew is not creative, but destructive.

381
00:45:04,242 --> 00:45:06,744
He is the enemy of culture.

382
00:45:06,745 --> 00:45:10,080
"Thousands of Germans
have been made poor by the Jew."

383
00:45:23,428 --> 00:45:24,928
Master Bruno.

384
00:45:25,889 --> 00:45:29,600
What are you doing? You've just
had your lunch, haven't you?

385
00:45:29,601 --> 00:45:33,521
I was going for a walk,
and I thought I might get peckish.

386
00:45:33,522 --> 00:45:36,607
But don't make a mess of
your satchel. Bring it here.

387
00:45:36,608 --> 00:45:40,986
- I'll wrap it properly for you.
- No. It's none of your business.

388
00:45:40,987 --> 00:45:42,695
Bruno, what is it?

389
00:45:43,573 --> 00:45:46,075
What are you doing with your satchel?

390
00:45:46,076 --> 00:45:50,703
Herr Liszt gave us some books.
I'm going out on the swing to read.

391
00:45:52,207 --> 00:45:54,375
- Let me see.
- What?

392
00:45:54,376 --> 00:45:57,169
The books.
No.

393
00:45:57,170 --> 00:46:00,380
Bruno, I just want to see
what books Herr Liszt has given you.

394
00:46:02,300 --> 00:46:04,175
I told a lie.
What?

395
00:46:05,554 --> 00:46:07,053
I've just got...

396
00:46:09,683 --> 00:46:11,266
adventure books.

397
00:46:19,609 --> 00:46:21,860
Go on. Off you go, then.

398
00:46:25,532 --> 00:46:27,908
Now, Maria, there's
two extra for supper tonight.

399
00:46:27,909 --> 00:46:29,160
The Kommandant's father will be here,

400
00:46:29,161 --> 00:46:31,494
and I believe Lieutenant
Kotler is joining us.

401
00:46:54,352 --> 00:46:55,477
Here.

402
00:47:06,948 --> 00:47:08,615
What's the matter?

403
00:47:11,161 --> 00:47:13,828
- Don't throw it back.
- What? Why not?

404
00:47:15,582 --> 00:47:17,750
- It's dangerous.
- Dangerous?

405
00:47:17,751 --> 00:47:19,334
It's just a ball. Come on.

406
00:47:23,423 --> 00:47:24,631
Do you not like playing?

407
00:47:28,887 --> 00:47:31,638
- Just not ball games?
- Not here.

408
00:47:36,853 --> 00:47:38,687
Tell me how the number game works.

409
00:47:38,688 --> 00:47:41,440
I told you, it's not a game.
We just all have numbers.

410
00:47:49,366 --> 00:47:50,823
Shmuel!

411
00:48:04,631 --> 00:48:06,673
Bruno! What are you doing?

412
00:48:08,426 --> 00:48:11,553
My ball went over.
I was just getting it back.

413
00:48:21,398 --> 00:48:24,316
They smell even worse
when they burn, don't they?

414
00:48:24,317 --> 00:48:25,400
What?

415
00:48:42,335 --> 00:48:44,043
But, surely you-

416
00:48:59,853 --> 00:49:02,354
Elsa, I was sworn to secrecy.

417
00:49:02,355 --> 00:49:04,564
From your own wife.
Yes.

418
00:49:08,737 --> 00:49:13,031
I took an oath upon my life.
Do you understand?

419
00:49:14,659 --> 00:49:18,495
Elsa, you believe in this, too.

420
00:49:18,496 --> 00:49:23,416
- You want this country to be strong-
- No, Ralf, no! No, not that!

421
00:49:28,131 --> 00:49:29,673
How can you-

422
00:49:29,674 --> 00:49:31,383
Because I'm a soldier.
How can you-

423
00:49:31,384 --> 00:49:34,219
- Soldiers fight wars.
- That isn't war!

424
00:49:34,220 --> 00:49:36,929
It's a part of it! It's a vital part of it!

425
00:49:38,433 --> 00:49:42,519
The Fatherland we all desire,
all of us, you included,

426
00:49:42,520 --> 00:49:45,439
cannot be achieved without
work such as this!

427
00:49:48,151 --> 00:49:53,488
Elsa. Elsa.
Get away from me! Get away from me!

428
00:49:57,702 --> 00:49:58,952
Grandpa's here.

429
00:49:58,953 --> 00:50:00,953
I don't believe this.
Grandpa's here.

430
00:50:05,251 --> 00:50:06,501
We'll be through in a moment.

431
00:50:17,347 --> 00:50:18,471
Who told you about this?

432
00:50:51,214 --> 00:50:53,298
How's Grandma?

433
00:50:53,299 --> 00:50:55,843
She's a bit under the weather, I'm afraid.

434
00:50:55,844 --> 00:51:00,431
It's a shame, she was so much
looking forward to seeing you.

435
00:51:00,432 --> 00:51:03,474
Perhaps next time, if she feels up to it.
Oh, absolutely.

436
00:51:10,358 --> 00:51:14,944
You know, Ralf, your mother really is sick.

437
00:51:15,947 --> 00:51:18,699
She's been talking about
this visit for weeks.

438
00:51:18,700 --> 00:51:20,867
Maybe that's what's made her sick.

439
00:51:27,834 --> 00:51:30,877
So, your father tells
me that you've got a tutor.

440
00:51:31,671 --> 00:51:34,006
Yes. He's nice.

441
00:51:34,007 --> 00:51:36,674
But he won't let
us read any adventure books.

442
00:51:37,552 --> 00:51:39,970
All we do is boring, old history.

443
00:51:39,971 --> 00:51:42,514
Let me tell you something, young man.

444
00:51:42,515 --> 00:51:46,350
If it wasn't for history, we wouldn't
all be sitting around this table.

445
00:51:47,103 --> 00:51:49,729
The work your father is doing here,

446
00:51:50,774 --> 00:51:52,940
history in the making.

447
00:52:03,244 --> 00:52:06,872
When I was your age, history was
my favorite subject by miles,

448
00:52:06,873 --> 00:52:09,041
which obviously didn't please my father.

449
00:52:09,042 --> 00:52:11,001
Why not?

450
00:52:11,002 --> 00:52:14,046
Well, he was a professor of literature
at the university.

451
00:52:14,047 --> 00:52:17,924
Really, does he still teach?

452
00:52:20,386 --> 00:52:23,888
- I don't really know.
- You don't know?

453
00:52:26,851 --> 00:52:31,521
We're not in touch, my father and I.
He left the country some time ago.

454
00:52:34,108 --> 00:52:35,775
Really, when?

455
00:52:37,946 --> 00:52:41,239
About four years ago, Herr Kommandant.

456
00:52:44,786 --> 00:52:49,247
But surely he can't be very old.
What is he, still in his 40s, late 40s?

457
00:52:50,083 --> 00:52:51,165
Where did he go?

458
00:52:59,717 --> 00:53:01,425
Lieutenant Kotler,

459
00:53:02,762 --> 00:53:06,305
your father, the professor of literature,
where did he go?

460
00:53:12,146 --> 00:53:15,189
I believe it was Switzerland,
Herr Kommandant.

461
00:53:16,526 --> 00:53:18,986
How strange that he should choose
to leave the Fatherland...

462
00:53:18,987 --> 00:53:20,988
at the very moment it needed him most.

463
00:53:20,989 --> 00:53:23,448
Just when we're all required
to play our part in the national revival.

464
00:53:23,449 --> 00:53:24,824
More wine!

465
00:53:27,245 --> 00:53:30,080
What reason did he give?
Was he tubercular?

466
00:53:30,081 --> 00:53:31,081
Herr Kommandant?

467
00:53:32,959 --> 00:53:34,542
Did he go there to take the air?

468
00:53:37,171 --> 00:53:39,047
I'm afraid I really don't
know, Herr Kommandant.

469
00:53:39,048 --> 00:53:41,091
You'd have to ask him.

470
00:53:41,092 --> 00:53:43,886
Well, that would be rather difficult,
wouldn't it?

471
00:53:43,887 --> 00:53:46,012
With him being in Switzerland.

472
00:53:46,848 --> 00:53:47,889
Come on!

473
00:53:49,309 --> 00:53:51,851
What's the matter with you tonight?

474
00:54:00,028 --> 00:54:05,031
Yes, perhaps that was it.
Perhaps he was ill.

475
00:54:07,035 --> 00:54:09,368
Unless, of course, he had disagreements.

476
00:54:11,664 --> 00:54:15,584
- I mean, with government policy.
- One hears of such men.

477
00:54:15,585 --> 00:54:19,963
Disturbed, most of them,
or just plain cowards.

478
00:54:19,964 --> 00:54:23,717
Even so, all of them traitors.
Absolutely right.

479
00:54:23,718 --> 00:54:28,055
Presumably,
if that was the case with your father,

480
00:54:28,056 --> 00:54:31,766
you will have informed your superiors,
as is your duty.

481
00:54:33,895 --> 00:54:35,102
Lieutenant Kotler!

482
00:54:36,522 --> 00:54:39,565
You cretin Jew! Filth!

483
00:54:49,369 --> 00:54:51,328
Pig!

484
00:54:51,329 --> 00:54:52,578
Ralf!

485
00:54:57,752 --> 00:54:59,001
Jew!

486
00:55:00,171 --> 00:55:04,091
- But Dad just sat there.
- What did you expect him to do?

487
00:55:04,092 --> 00:55:05,257
The Jew deserved it.

488
00:55:14,936 --> 00:55:18,855
Can I ask you something about the farm?

489
00:55:18,856 --> 00:55:21,774
Bruno, you don't still think it's a farm,
do you?

490
00:55:40,628 --> 00:55:44,589
It's a camp.
What's called a work camp.

491
00:55:44,590 --> 00:55:47,091
For Jews, obviously.

492
00:55:48,636 --> 00:55:50,428
Just Jews?

493
00:55:51,305 --> 00:55:54,224
Because they're the best workers?

494
00:55:54,225 --> 00:55:55,976
They're not in there
because they're good, silly.

495
00:55:55,977 --> 00:55:58,228
They're no good at anything.

496
00:55:58,229 --> 00:55:59,896
They're in there because they're evil.

497
00:55:59,897 --> 00:56:02,315
They're the enemy.
The enemy?

498
00:56:02,316 --> 00:56:04,276
But I thought we were fighting-
They're evil, Bruno.

499
00:56:04,277 --> 00:56:06,652
Evil, dangerous vermin.

500
00:56:07,321 --> 00:56:09,030
They're the reason we lost the Great War.

501
00:56:10,158 --> 00:56:14,202
Haven't you been listening to anything
Herr Liszt has been telling us?

502
00:56:14,203 --> 00:56:15,619
No. Not really.

503
00:56:18,499 --> 00:56:21,793
Dad's not horrible, is he?
He's a good man.

504
00:56:21,794 --> 00:56:26,465
Of course, he is.
But he's in charge of a horrible place.

505
00:56:26,466 --> 00:56:29,176
It's only horrible for them, Bruno.

506
00:56:29,177 --> 00:56:31,762
We should be proud of Dad,
now more than ever before.

507
00:56:31,763 --> 00:56:34,388
He's making the country great again.

508
00:57:26,567 --> 00:57:29,861
Like you say, they're
a bit strange. A bit-

509
00:57:29,862 --> 00:57:30,987
Well, they're different.

510
00:57:30,988 --> 00:57:33,073
They're the enemy, Bruno.

511
00:57:33,074 --> 00:57:34,866
Evil, dangerous vermin.

512
00:57:34,867 --> 00:57:38,077
Well, you see, they're
not really people at all.

513
00:58:02,103 --> 00:58:04,604
What are you doing here?

514
00:58:04,605 --> 00:58:08,774
They wanted someone with tiny fingers
to clean all these.

515
00:58:21,664 --> 00:58:24,791
We're not supposed to
be friends, you and me.

516
00:58:24,792 --> 00:58:27,751
We're meant to be enemies.
Did you know that?

517
00:58:34,802 --> 00:58:36,468
Do you want some?

518
00:58:46,981 --> 00:58:49,607
What's your dad like?
What's he like?

519
00:58:50,109 --> 00:58:51,734
Is he a good man?

520
00:58:54,655 --> 00:58:56,447
You've never thought he wasn't?

521
00:58:59,619 --> 00:59:01,660
And you're proud of him?

522
00:59:02,997 --> 00:59:05,039
Aren't you proud of yours?

523
00:59:09,420 --> 00:59:11,128
Is it really horrible in the camp?

524
00:59:12,548 --> 00:59:14,591
How dare you talk to people in the house.

525
00:59:14,592 --> 00:59:16,842
How dare you!

526
00:59:19,347 --> 00:59:20,888
Are you eating?

527
00:59:23,476 --> 00:59:25,643
Have you been stealing food?

528
00:59:29,482 --> 00:59:33,776
Answer me!
No, sir. He gave it to me.

529
00:59:34,445 --> 00:59:35,569
He's my friend.

530
00:59:38,324 --> 00:59:39,698
What?

531
00:59:42,328 --> 00:59:43,328
Little man,

532
00:59:45,539 --> 00:59:47,791
do you know this Jew?

533
00:59:47,792 --> 00:59:49,501
Do you know this Jew?

534
00:59:49,502 --> 00:59:52,837
No, I just walked in,
and he was helping himself.

535
00:59:52,838 --> 00:59:55,839
I've never seen him before in my life.

536
01:00:04,517 --> 01:00:07,017
You, finish cleaning the glasses.

537
01:00:08,396 --> 01:00:10,105
When I come back, we'll
have a little chat...

538
01:00:10,106 --> 01:00:13,941
about what happens to rats who steal.
Come away.

539
01:01:55,586 --> 01:01:58,171
New arrivals here are
happy to discover that life in the camp...

540
01:01:58,172 --> 01:01:59,381
is not all work.

541
01:01:59,382 --> 01:02:02,759
And that there's
ample opportunity for leisure also.

542
01:02:02,760 --> 01:02:05,220
At the end of their day
at the ironmongery...

543
01:02:05,221 --> 01:02:07,847
or the build or boot factory,
the workers can enjoy...

544
01:02:07,848 --> 01:02:11,183
the many forms of pastime
that the camp has to offer.

545
01:02:12,103 --> 01:02:14,896
Organized sport is very popular.

546
01:02:14,897 --> 01:02:17,981
Those that don't play
certainly enjoy watching.

547
01:02:20,069 --> 01:02:21,569
At the end of the working day,

548
01:02:21,570 --> 01:02:24,030
the centrally located café
is the ideal place...

549
01:02:24,031 --> 01:02:28,617
for friends and families to join together
for a hearty and nutritious meal.

550
01:02:29,328 --> 01:02:33,497
The children, in particular,
enjoy the pastries and cakes on offer.

551
01:02:39,004 --> 01:02:41,631
In the evenings, the
occasional music concerts,

552
01:02:41,632 --> 01:02:44,717
either by visiting orchestras
or, indeed, by talented musicians...

553
01:02:44,718 --> 01:02:47,553
from within the camp itself,
are always well attended.

554
01:02:49,849 --> 01:02:52,392
Other recreations include
reading in the library,

555
01:02:52,393 --> 01:02:58,356
pottery, cookery, art and horticulture
for adult and child alike.

556
01:02:58,357 --> 01:03:02,526
Almost any activity one could wish for
is available within the camp.

557
01:03:08,534 --> 01:03:09,534
Splendid.

558
01:03:19,920 --> 01:03:21,920
- Bravo. Excellent.
- Thank you.

559
01:04:08,636 --> 01:04:09,801
Good-bye, little man.

560
01:04:57,184 --> 01:04:59,017
Shmuel! Shmuel!

561
01:05:16,203 --> 01:05:18,371
I don't understand.

562
01:05:18,372 --> 01:05:20,872
I saw a film about the camp,

563
01:05:22,209 --> 01:05:24,126
and it looked so nice.

564
01:05:31,552 --> 01:05:33,970
I don't know why I did it.

565
01:05:33,971 --> 01:05:36,806
Gretel and everyone
were saying all these things,

566
01:05:36,807 --> 01:05:38,974
and that soldier's so scary.

567
01:05:44,273 --> 01:05:47,984
Been coming here for days,
but you were never here.

568
01:05:47,985 --> 01:05:52,821
I thought maybe we weren't friends anymore.

569
01:06:01,248 --> 01:06:05,626
Shmuel, I'm really sorry for what I did.
We are still friends, aren't we?

570
01:06:37,201 --> 01:06:40,661
Where's Kurt these days?
I haven't seen him for ages.

571
01:06:42,164 --> 01:06:45,957
- Who's Kurt?
- Lieutenant Kotler.

572
01:06:47,628 --> 01:06:50,046
He's been moved to the front.

573
01:06:50,047 --> 01:06:52,006
It was felt that his
youth and enthusiasm...

574
01:06:52,007 --> 01:06:53,841
would be put to better use there.

575
01:06:53,842 --> 01:06:55,967
Herr Kommandant, telephone.

576
01:06:56,887 --> 01:06:59,472
In actual fact, Gretel,
he was sent there...

577
01:06:59,473 --> 01:07:01,307
because he failed to
inform the authorities...

578
01:07:01,308 --> 01:07:03,643
of his father's lack of
loyalty to the Party.

579
01:07:03,644 --> 01:07:05,687
Which was his duty, I might add.

580
01:07:05,688 --> 01:07:07,855
Which was his bad luck.
Bad luck?

581
01:07:07,856 --> 01:07:12,026
Well, bad luck that it was his father
who was disloyal, and not his mother.

582
01:07:12,027 --> 01:07:14,861
One presumably
doesn't have to report one's mother.

583
01:07:20,327 --> 01:07:22,869
What?
When will Pavel be back?

584
01:07:25,082 --> 01:07:28,125
- Mum?
- Never, stupid.

585
01:07:32,840 --> 01:07:34,715
It's Father. They've been bombed.

586
01:07:40,556 --> 01:07:41,556
Grandmother's dead.

587
01:08:27,686 --> 01:08:30,438
"The victory
which You have obtained for us..."

588
01:08:30,439 --> 01:08:32,815
and for all who sleep in Him,

589
01:08:32,816 --> 01:08:36,486
keep us who are still in the body
in everlasting fellowship...

590
01:08:36,487 --> 01:08:38,571
with all that wait for Thee on earth,

591
01:08:38,572 --> 01:08:41,407
and with all that are
around Thee in heaven,

592
01:08:41,408 --> 01:08:43,785
in union with Him who
is the resurrection...

593
01:08:43,786 --> 01:08:47,580
and the life, who liveth and reigneth
with Thee and the Holy Ghost,

594
01:08:47,581 --> 01:08:50,750
"ever one God, world without end.
Amen."

595
01:08:50,751 --> 01:08:53,210
He can't have that on there.
She wouldn't have wanted it.

596
01:08:55,506 --> 01:08:57,255
He does.

597
01:09:24,576 --> 01:09:26,369
"Almighty God, who by the death of-"

598
01:09:26,370 --> 01:09:28,010
Have you ever been to a funeral?

599
01:09:29,665 --> 01:09:33,167
My grandma and grandpa both died
just after we got here,

600
01:09:33,168 --> 01:09:35,460
but there weren't any funerals.

601
01:09:37,881 --> 01:09:40,048
That one there to there.

602
01:09:43,303 --> 01:09:45,095
They both died at the same time?

603
01:09:46,139 --> 01:09:47,347
What of?

604
01:09:48,851 --> 01:09:50,017
I don't know.

605
01:09:50,018 --> 01:09:52,978
Papa said they must have caught
something on the way here.

606
01:09:53,981 --> 01:09:56,356
They had to go to a hospital
as soon as we arrived.

607
01:09:57,192 --> 01:09:59,234
We didn't see them again.

608
01:10:02,990 --> 01:10:04,823
This is fun.

609
01:10:05,868 --> 01:10:09,369
Wish we could do something
a bit more exciting, though.

610
01:10:13,375 --> 01:10:16,835
- That one there to there.
- This one?

611
01:10:18,922 --> 01:10:20,630
- This one?
- No, that one.

612
01:10:21,717 --> 01:10:24,510
- This one to here?
- No, there!

613
01:10:24,511 --> 01:10:26,721
- To here?
- No.

614
01:10:26,722 --> 01:10:28,014
- Here?
- No.

615
01:10:36,189 --> 01:10:41,526
- I don't want you to go away again.
- No. Neither do I.

616
01:11:09,806 --> 01:11:11,890
You can't behave like this!

617
01:11:12,601 --> 01:11:16,103
You're questioning my behavior?
It can't continue!

618
01:11:16,104 --> 01:11:18,981
I know.
I can't stand this anymore, Ralf.

619
01:11:18,982 --> 01:11:21,066
I can't stay here and be a part of this.

620
01:11:22,402 --> 01:11:24,278
Don't you think there will be questions?

621
01:11:24,279 --> 01:11:25,780
Questions?
Well, now, what does it say...

622
01:11:25,781 --> 01:11:30,576
about my ability to carry out my work
if I cannot control my own family?

623
01:11:30,577 --> 01:11:33,579
Work? Is that what you call it?
Pull yourself together, woman.

624
01:11:33,580 --> 01:11:35,414
Right. Just ignore it. Ignore it.

625
01:11:35,415 --> 01:11:39,460
Ignore the fact that
the man I married is a monster!

626
01:11:39,461 --> 01:11:41,753
Even your own mother couldn't love you.

627
01:11:51,848 --> 01:11:53,598
Are you happy here?

628
01:11:55,018 --> 01:11:56,768
Yes. Very.

629
01:11:59,982 --> 01:12:01,606
And you, Gretel?

630
01:12:03,443 --> 01:12:09,114
Well, I was, but I do miss home.
I miss my friends.

631
01:12:09,616 --> 01:12:14,452
Yes, I'm sure. And you, too, Bruno.
You must miss those friends of yours.

632
01:12:15,622 --> 01:12:18,289
No. Not anymore, really.

633
01:12:30,053 --> 01:12:35,557
I suppose the real question is,
if the opportunity arose,

634
01:12:36,977 --> 01:12:39,353
would you prefer to live somewhere else?

635
01:12:39,354 --> 01:12:43,231
Back home?
No. Not Berlin. Not yet.

636
01:12:43,817 --> 01:12:49,362
Somewhere safe, say Aunt Lottie's
in Heidelberg, for example.

637
01:12:50,157 --> 01:12:52,282
All of us? You as well?

638
01:12:53,493 --> 01:12:56,829
No. That won't be possible just yet,
I'm afraid.

639
01:12:56,830 --> 01:12:59,414
I must stay and complete my work here.

640
01:13:01,835 --> 01:13:05,503
See, at the moment,
your mother is finding it-

641
01:13:07,716 --> 01:13:12,011
She just feels right now you need
to spend some time elsewhere.

642
01:13:12,012 --> 01:13:13,845
Would you like that?

643
01:13:23,857 --> 01:13:29,403
I'm afraid, Bruno, in life, we often
have to do things we don't want to do.

644
01:13:29,404 --> 01:13:32,198
The important thing is
your mother does not feel...

645
01:13:32,199 --> 01:13:35,117
that this is an appropriate place for you
to be spending your childhood,

646
01:13:35,118 --> 01:13:38,871
and the more I think about it, the more
I realize she's very probably right.

647
01:13:38,872 --> 01:13:40,580
- But, Dad-
- No!

648
01:13:47,422 --> 01:13:49,714
It's time for you to move away.

649
01:14:14,908 --> 01:14:16,866
Is everything all right?

650
01:14:19,830 --> 01:14:21,789
We can't find Papa.

651
01:14:21,790 --> 01:14:24,500
He went on a different work duty
with some of the men,

652
01:14:24,501 --> 01:14:26,543
and they haven't come back.

653
01:14:35,762 --> 01:14:39,430
I've got some bad news, too.
I'm going away.

654
01:14:41,184 --> 01:14:43,101
How long for this time?

655
01:14:43,603 --> 01:14:47,105
That's why it's bad.
It's forever, I think.

656
01:14:48,191 --> 01:14:52,527
Mum says this is no place for children,
which is just stupid.

657
01:14:53,029 --> 01:14:56,197
When do you go?
Tomorrow. After lunch.

658
01:14:57,325 --> 01:15:02,120
So, I won't ever see you again?

659
01:15:03,999 --> 01:15:08,169
Yes, you will. You can come on holiday
to Berlin if you like,

660
01:15:08,170 --> 01:15:11,588
when everybody's getting on
with each other again.

661
01:15:16,219 --> 01:15:18,678
I wish I could've helped you find your dad.

662
01:15:19,723 --> 01:15:23,309
I really want to make up
for letting you down like I did.

663
01:15:23,310 --> 01:15:26,353
That would have done it, wouldn't it?
Helping you find your dad?

664
01:15:26,354 --> 01:15:29,189
Would've been great.
Like a secret mission.

665
01:15:34,070 --> 01:15:37,489
I could dig under.
What? With that?

666
01:15:37,490 --> 01:15:41,159
No, but I could bring something.
You don't want to come over here.

667
01:15:45,248 --> 01:15:46,331
Look.

668
01:15:52,923 --> 01:15:56,342
I could come through to your side.
What's the point in that?

669
01:15:56,343 --> 01:15:59,177
Your dad's not going to
be over here, is he?

670
01:15:59,763 --> 01:16:03,849
But I'd stick out though, wouldn't I,
if I came through?

671
01:16:03,850 --> 01:16:05,809
I don't look like you.

672
01:16:09,439 --> 01:16:11,607
You could look like me, though.

673
01:16:11,608 --> 01:16:14,026
If you dressed like me and
shaved your hair off.

674
01:16:14,027 --> 01:16:16,195
I'm not shaving my hair off.

675
01:16:16,196 --> 01:16:20,699
You could cover it with a cap.
My pajamas are a different color.

676
01:16:20,700 --> 01:16:24,328
I could bring some.
There's a hut full of them,

677
01:16:24,329 --> 01:16:27,164
thousands of them.
Would you do it, though?

678
01:16:27,165 --> 01:16:29,667
- I want to do it.
- Would you dare do it, though?

679
01:16:29,668 --> 01:16:32,211
- I want to help you find your dad.
- I've got to go.

680
01:16:32,212 --> 01:16:35,714
Tomorrow, then?
I'll bring an extra-big sandwich.

681
01:16:35,715 --> 01:16:37,882
And don't forget the pajamas!

682
01:17:40,905 --> 01:17:42,071
Bruno?

683
01:17:42,782 --> 01:17:46,617
Mum, can I go and play on the swing?

684
01:17:47,996 --> 01:17:50,747
- Bruno-
- It's my last chance.

685
01:17:52,375 --> 01:17:54,792
All right. Go on then.

686
01:18:26,117 --> 01:18:30,454
I thought you weren't coming!
I'm sorry. It wasn't easy to get away.

687
01:18:30,455 --> 01:18:34,123
I'm not meant to be out here today.
You forgot the pajamas!

688
01:18:35,960 --> 01:18:39,128
- Did you bring the sandwich?
- Would I let you down?

689
01:18:41,174 --> 01:18:42,673
Oh.

690
01:19:04,030 --> 01:19:05,238
Shmuel.

691
01:19:14,040 --> 01:19:15,164
Here.

692
01:19:30,723 --> 01:19:31,723
How do I look?

693
01:19:39,774 --> 01:19:41,732
Right. Let's get going.

694
01:19:58,042 --> 01:19:59,208
Bruno?

695
01:20:00,587 --> 01:20:02,086
That's enough.

696
01:20:32,327 --> 01:20:34,118
Let's go and find your dad.

697
01:20:39,834 --> 01:20:41,083
Come on!

698
01:20:41,586 --> 01:20:43,169
Master Bruno?

699
01:21:27,966 --> 01:21:29,173
Shmuel.

700
01:21:29,968 --> 01:21:32,843
Can we go to the café or something?
Café?

701
01:21:36,474 --> 01:21:39,642
- Maybe I should go home.
- What about Papa?

702
01:21:49,195 --> 01:21:50,319
Yeah.

703
01:21:53,825 --> 01:21:56,033
We'll check our hut first.

704
01:21:59,706 --> 01:22:01,247
Bruno?

705
01:22:08,673 --> 01:22:10,172
Come on.

706
01:22:23,021 --> 01:22:24,021
Papa?

707
01:22:26,733 --> 01:22:28,942
Up! Up! Get up!

708
01:22:28,943 --> 01:22:31,069
What's happening?
I don't know.

709
01:22:31,070 --> 01:22:32,904
We go on marches sometimes.

710
01:22:32,905 --> 01:22:34,905
Move! Up, up!

711
01:22:37,076 --> 01:22:38,868
Move, move!

712
01:22:49,589 --> 01:22:51,255
Bruno!

713
01:22:52,216 --> 01:22:54,383
He must still be
outside somewhere, ma'am.

714
01:23:09,150 --> 01:23:10,775
Bruno!

715
01:23:13,529 --> 01:23:14,779
Bruno?

716
01:23:26,334 --> 01:23:28,460
Move!
Quickly!

717
01:23:31,422 --> 01:23:32,797
Get up!

718
01:23:35,343 --> 01:23:37,134
Get up. You must!

719
01:23:38,304 --> 01:23:39,762
Move them out!

720
01:23:51,442 --> 01:23:53,777
...which means that
our weekly capabilities...

721
01:23:53,778 --> 01:23:55,362
would be almost tripled,

722
01:23:55,363 --> 01:23:57,698
so, therefore,
by the end of the summer-

723
01:23:57,699 --> 01:24:00,825
- Ralf.
- Elsa, I'm in a meeting.

724
01:24:01,452 --> 01:24:02,493
Bruno's missing.

725
01:24:08,793 --> 01:24:10,126
Come on!

726
01:24:16,801 --> 01:24:18,467
Wait here!

727
01:24:29,313 --> 01:24:30,646
Come on!

728
01:24:33,526 --> 01:24:34,859
Move! Move!

729
01:24:42,869 --> 01:24:44,493
Join the queue!

730
01:24:52,670 --> 01:24:54,129
Come on, you!

731
01:25:03,222 --> 01:25:04,764
Bruno!

732
01:25:05,433 --> 01:25:07,057
Move it!

733
01:25:09,729 --> 01:25:11,228
Go on.

734
01:25:12,815 --> 01:25:14,399
Bruno!

735
01:25:23,951 --> 01:25:28,914
It's all right. I think we're just waiting
in here until the rain stops.

736
01:25:28,915 --> 01:25:30,373
Clothes off!

737
01:25:38,466 --> 01:25:40,466
Where are we going?

738
01:25:45,056 --> 01:25:46,639
No, it's just a shower.

739
01:25:48,434 --> 01:25:50,309
A shower?

740
01:25:59,028 --> 01:26:01,111
Herr Kommandant!

741
01:26:38,985 --> 01:26:41,652
Open the gates! Open the gates!

742
01:26:45,324 --> 01:26:46,448
Move!

743
01:27:28,701 --> 01:27:30,034
Move!

744
01:28:04,654 --> 01:28:06,404
Bruno!

745
01:28:39,585 --> 01:28:42,085
<font color="#ff0000" face="Stencil"><b>Sync and Corrected by coolsuren.
Hopeyou enjoyed!</b></font>

