[ Wind Blowing Softly ]
♪♪ [ 1 950's Rock On Radio ]
Mrs. Peterson!
Ramon, hey!
How's it goin'?
Howyou doin'?
There it is,
right there on the desk.
- Where's she headed?
- She's snowbound, Ramon.
- See you went with the pink.
- Yeah, yeah.
It's kind of
a pink day today.
I'm gonna have another pickup
foryou on Thursday.
- All right. We'll see you then.
- All right. Thanks, Ramon.
♪♪ [ Man Singing ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
♪♪ [ Humming ]
[ Speaking Russian ]
♪♪ [ Singing In Russian ]
[ Man Shouting
In Russian ]
♪♪ [ Singing Continues ]
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- Peterson! Peterson!
- Peterson.
- [ Russian ]
- Mr. Cowboy, da?
- Da.
- ♪♪ [ Humming ]
- [ Russian ]
Mmm, it's pretty.
[ Russian ]
Mmm.
It's from my wife.
[ Horn Honking ]
♪♪ [ Singing In Russian ]
- [ Russian ]
[ Russian ]
[ Whistle Blows ]
[ Man ]
Time...
- rules over us without mercy...
- [ Man Translating From English To Russian ]
not caring ifwe're healthy or ill,
hungry or drunk...
Russian, American,
beings from Mars.
It's like a fire. It could either destroy us
or keep us warm.
That's why every FedEx office
has a clock.
Because we live orwe die
by the clock.
We never turn our back
on it.
And we never, ever
allow ourselves...
the sin of losing track
oftime!
Locally, it's 1 :56.
That means we've got
three hours and four minutes...
before the end-of-the-day's
package sort.
- That's how long we have.
That's how much time we have...
- [ Translating ]
before this pulsating, accursed,
relentless taskmaster...
tries to put us
out of business.
Hey, Nicolai. Hey.
Nicolai, good to see you.
How are you, kid?
Look what you did.
You just delivered
your very first FedEx package.
That deserves something special,
like a Snickers bar...
and a C.D. player.
And something to listen to—
a C.D. There.
Elvis Presley. Fifty million fans
can't be wrong.
You all recognize this,
don't you?
I took the liberty
ofsending this to myself.
I FedEx'd it
before I left Memphis.
You're probably wondering
what could be in here.
What could it possibly be?
Is it architectural plans?
Maybe technical drawings?
Is this the new wallpaper
for the- for the bathroom?
[ Translator Continues ]
It is... a clock...
which I started
at absolute zero...
and is now at 87 hours,
22 minutes and 1 7 seconds.
From Memphis, America
to Nicolai in Russia, 87 hours.
Eighty-seven hours
is a shameful outrage.
This isjust an egg timer!
What if it had been something else?
Like your paycheck?
- Or fresh boysenberries?
Or adoption papers?
- [ Translating ]
Eighty-seven hours
is an eternity.
The cosmos was created
in less time!
Wars have been fought and
nations toppled in 87 hours!
Fortunes made and squandered.
[ Translating ]
What?
What are you saying
about me?
I tell them,
what do they expect?
This man, when his truck broke down,
he stole a boy's bicycle to do his delivery.
I borrowed it!
I borrowed a kid's bike.
And I got my packages delivered, and that is
what you people are gonna have to start doing.
You have to start doing whatever it takes,
because in three hours and two minutes...
every one ofthese packages
has to be on the big truck...
and on its way
to the airport.
- [ Bell Rings ]
- Fifteen minutes!
- Crunch time! Crunch time!
- Crunch time!
Let's go! Every package
on the airport truck.
Go!
Crunch, crunch, crunch!
- We have a big problem.
- What?
- The truck in Red Square is stuck.
- What do you mean?
- It's stuck.
- Stuck how? In snow? In ice?
It's stuck! The most important truck-
the Kremlin truck! Many packages.
All right, all right, all right.
Let's put the table right here.
We'll just do the sort.
Ah, yeah, a clamp.
That would make us stuck.
Let's go. Unload—
Get him out ofthere.
Right here.
Two lines, two lines.
One to the airport truck,
one to the Moscow truck.
Got it?
C.D.G., F.E., M.E, Memphis on the airport
truck. Everything else right there.
Nicolai! Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Four minutes.
[ Ringing ]
[ Answering Machine ] Hi, this is Kelly.
Ifyou're calling for Chuck, press one.
Otherwise leave a message
after the tone. Thanks.
- [ Beeps ]
- [ Chuck ] Hello, Kelly. Are you there?
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
pick up. You're not there.
You're not gonna believe this. I'm doin'
the sorts in the middle of Red Square...
in the shadow
of Lenin's tomb.
♪♪ [ Singing ]
♪♪ [ Continues ]
I'm outta here in two minutes
and I'm pickin' up the sweep through Paris...
so I should be back in Memphis
about 1 8 hours or so.
That's the good news.
The bad news is...
I gotta go to
the dentist this week.
I got something in there
that's hurtin'.
I love you and I'm gonna see you soon,
and you know what that means.
Bye-bye. Nicolai! Tick-tock, tick-tock,
tick-tock, tick-tock!
[ Speaking French ]
- [ Knocking ]
- I absolutely, positively
have to get to Memphis tonight.
Can't help you.
Try U.P.S.
With this extra head wind, are we gonna
be able to push it and make the sort?
- We'll do our best.
- "Our best," huh?
Gwen, is there something wrong with our
doctors thatJack keeps getting certified to fly?
- Aren't you concerned?
- I'm terrified.
But a girl's gotta do
what a girl's gotta do.
That's the spirit.
Relentless is our goal. Relentless!
What do you expect from the guy
who stole a crippled kid's bicycle...
- when his truck broke down?
- I borrowed it.
But I love that
the kid's now crippled.
So you missed the last truck
by two minutes?
Two minutes.
Actually, it was less than that.
The plane wasn't that heavy.
You could've added some fuel...
picked up the speed
and made up the time.
It's about the trucks.
Today's truck was two minutes late.
Tomorrow's will be four minutes late,
and then six minutes and eight minutes late.
- Next thing you know, we're the U.S. Mail.
- Yeah, well—
All I'm sayin' is, ifyou'd gotten
all those trucks on the plane...
those Russkies would be
walking on water right now.
Hey, don't—
Don't gimme that look.
- It'sjust grapejuice. Right, Chuck?
- Yeah.
It's like a 1 992
full-bodied grapejuice.
I see no evil, hear no evil,
speak no evil.
We'd offeryou some but, you know,
somebody's got to fly the plane.
Yeah, well,
I "just say no," right?
Listen, Stan,
I've been meaning to askyou.
How's Mary?
Oh. Uh, well...
- we really don't know anything yet.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, she went to the doctoryesterday,
and, uh...
it hasn't meta—
metastasized...
as far as they
can tell right now.
It'sjust kind of
wait and see.
I'm so sorry.
Tell her I'm gonna come by
and see her on my next layover.
I want you to know, Stan, we are
all thinking about her and you.
- And just blessings.
- Thankyou, Gwen.
[ Answering Machine ] Hi, this is Kelly.
Ifyou're calling for Chuck, press one.
Otherwise, leave a message
after the tone. Thanks.
Stan.
Listen.
Uh, I heard about this—
I heard about this doctor
down in Emory, in Atlanta.
Uh, he's supposed to be
the absolute best.
He worked on
Frank Toretta's wife.
Frank Toretta is
a systems analyst.
He played center field for us.
You know him.
In the softball tournament
last Labor Day.
Anyway, beside the point.
Uh, what I was thinking is,
is that I could get his number-
the doctor-
and, uh...
you know,
put you all together and—
You know, you could
get this thing fixed.
You could beat it.
Thanks, Chuck.
[ Sighs ]
So, I'll get his number.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
[ Knocking ]
- Is Kelly Frears around?
- She's copying her dissertation.
[ Laughs ]
- You're home.
- Home indeed.
I love that you're home.
[ Laughs ]
[ TV, Female Newscaster] Just
days before Santa departs on his
annual gift-giving venture...
he's been declared
physically fit to fly.
Santa got checked out by doctors
at the V.A. Hospital in Augusta, Georgia.
After they declared
thejolly old elf in tiptop shape...
Santa Claus took off into the wild
blue yonder for an early start.
In Sarajevo,
he spent the day with children...
handing out presents and
even helping them decorate...
the special Christmas tree.
[ Bell Clanging ]
Santa and a sea ofelves
took over the floor...
at the Hong Kong
Futures Exchange.
Market traders
bought Santa hats, donating—
[ TV Shuts Off]
The turkey's a little dry,
isn't it?
- [ All ] No.
- The turkey is perfect.
[ Indistinct Chattering ]
- How many did you do last night?
- Last night? 2.9 million.
Nowyou've got to be in the market
for more ofthese candied yams.
Here you go.
2.9 has got to be
the record.
Look at those marshmallows.
When I was there,
we did two million.
- We thought that was a big deal.
- The glory days.
- What'd they do the first night?
- The very first night?
- [ Man #1 ] Twelve.
- [ Man #2 ] Twelve thousand?
- Hell, no. Twelve.
- [ Chuck ] That's right.
And they did the sort
right there on a card table.
And Fred Smith had
that card table bronzed.
I've been hearing that
for five years.
- It's in his office today.
- They go from that to
the new hub up in Anchorage.
It's state ofthe art—
a perfect marriage...
between technology
and systems management.
Speaking of marriage, Chuck, when are you
gonna make an honest woman out of Kelly?
[ Excited Chattering ]
- How long?
- Fourteen minutes into the meal.
- You won. I owe you $5.
- So I win.
- Way before the pie.
- I told him on the way up.
Right about the time the pie
came out, the marriage—
Kelly is still recovering from her failed
relationship with that parolee.
He was a lawyer.
I knew it had something to do
with raising your right hand...
and swearing
to tell the truth.
Rememberwhen he fell on the
sidewalk and broke his shoulder
at the wedding reception?
He tripped on a curb
holding a door open for me.
- Aunt Kelly was married before?
- [ Kelly ] It's not even worth remembering.
So since her failed marriage
to the parolee-
- Oh, my God.
- Kelly can't see being with
a man who wears a pager to bed.
What're you gonna
attach it to, Hoss?
When you wear it to bed, I hope
you got one ofthose things...
that go vibratin'.
Watch it.
I'm not touching that.
Oh, did you
hit an olive pit?
- I thought I took all ofthem out.
- No, no, it's not that.
[ Guests Chattering ]
- Okay, I'll cancel Saturday.
- No, don't.
If I'm not here, I'm not.
But if I am, well...
- then I am.
- It's cancelled.
But you gotta be here
New Year's Eve.
Malaysia can't be that bad.
I'll be here New Year's Eve.
- When are you defending your dissertation?
-January 1 2.
[ Sighs ] I'm gonna have to switch
over the South America thing.
If I do that
on the third or fourth...
I'm gonna have to head
back out on the 1 3th.
So long as you're here
New Year's Eve.
I will be here New Year's Eve.
I promise.
- What?
- What about our Christmas?
I got a gift foryou.
We have to do it
in the car.
♪♪ [ 1 950's Rock On Radio ]
I'd just like a minute
over here, all right? Thanks.
Two minutes, okay?
Two more minutes.
Thanks. Hey!
- Merry Christmas.
- I thought you were gonna stiff me.
- No.
- What is the ribbon? Is it a thousand-pound...
- test fishing line or something?
- Here's your fancy thing.
Thanks.
I love the wrapping.
- And I love the box.
- Good.
Oh. Oh, my.
Oh, that is terrific.
My grandaddy used it
on the Southern Pacific.
Hey, I took this. This is
my favorite picture ofyou.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm always gonna keep this...
on Memphis time.
Kelly time.
Hmm.
You haven't said anything about
your presents. Is there a problem?
I'm sorry, no!
I love 'em.
Look at myjournal.
Ah!
- What about the pager?
- Real leather. The pages have gold on 'em.
- Did you like the pager or not?
- Yes.
I love it. Look at him in
his little blue Russian house.
- It's from Russia.
- My God.
- It's not one ofthose loud ones?
- No. You can program it so it vibrates...
and lights up
and see it in the dark.
It seems like
a real nice pager.
- Sorry about the hand towels.
You're hard to shop for.
- No, no. I love 'em.
- Every time I wash my hands,
I will think ofyou.
- All right, I gotta go.
- Merry Christmas.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Chuck! Keys!
- Thank you.
- That reminds me. I almost forgot.
I have one more present
foryou.
Only this isn't an "open in the car"
kind of present...
like, say, hand towels.
Which were a joke,
by the way.
I'm terrified.
Just take it and hold onto it,
and you can open it...
on New Year's Eve.
And I love you.
I'll be right back.
[ PlaneJolts ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey, Al, where are we?
Somewhere over
the Pacific Ocean.
Ha, ha, ha!
You pilots, you're funny.
Tahiti Control,
FedEx 88.
Position Jenna
at 1 526—
Is all this turbulence from Santa
and those eight tiny reindeer?
Tamara at 1 620.
Erick is next.
- Fuel: niner-five-decimal-five.
- [ Static Over Radio ]
Blaine, tell them we're
deviating south forweather.
Make another position plot
on your deviation left.
[ Blaine ] Tahiti Control,
FedEx 88.
Position Jenna at 1 526.
- Flight level 350.
- I got us plotted.
We're 200 miles south
ofour original course.
[ Kevin ] Continue plotting,
and check contingency procedures.
Tahiti Control, FedEx 88.
Broadcasting in the blind.
How do you read?
- [ Static Over Radio ]
- [ Blaine ] l've never been
out ofcomm this long.
Did you try the higher
H.F. frequency?
Tahiti Control, FedEx 88.
[ Al ] Better buckle up, Chuck.
It's gonna get bumpy.
Tahiti Control,
FedEx 88.
Do you read?
Tahiti Control,
FedEx 88.
Position Jenna at 1 526.
Flight level 350.
Expecting Tamara at 1—
[ Toilet Flushes ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Pilot Yelling ]
Fire! Explosion!
Let's get a hose!
Hold on to it!
Come on!
Seat belt!
We may have to ditch!
Okay?
Fire in the hold!
We're goin' down!
Mayday! Mayday!
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
[ Pilots Shouting,
Alarm Buzzing ]
Bringing it down and out!
Ten thousand feet!
Masks off!
Chuck! Life vest!
Chuck!
Chuck, stay there!
Where's your life vest?
Ditching switch on!
I've got visual!
Brace for impact!
[ Creaking ]
[ Engine Roaring ]
[ Groaning, Wheezing ]
Hello!
Anybody!
Help!
[ Thudding Sound ]
[ Leaves Rustling ]
[ Thud ]
What is that?
Hey!
Anybody?
[ Thud ]
[ Grunting ]
Hello?
[ Gasping, Crying ]
Get! Go, go.
Go! Go!
"Albert R. Miller."
Not Alan. Albert.
So, that's it.
Hey! A ship!
Hey! Hey!
A ship! Over here!
Over here! Over here!
Over here!
Help me! Help!
Right here! Right here!
Help! Look here!
Look, look, look!
S... O... S!
Please!
Help! Come on!
Help!
[ Yelling ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Muffled Yelling ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Wind Howling ]
[ Clicking ]
[ Groans ]
"Happy birthday."
"The most beautiful thing in the world is,
ofcourse, the world itself.
Johnny, have the happiest birthday ever.
Score. Your Grandpa."
Ew.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
[ Groaning ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Screaming ]
You wouldn't have a match...
by any chance, would you?
Oh, oh, oh!
The air got to it.
The air got to it!
Come on, come on.
Come on.
[ Gasping ]
I did it.
Fire!
There you go!
Light it up!
Come on!
♪♪ [ Singing ]
Ouch!
[ Laughing ]
♪♪ [ Continues ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
Here you go!
It's a signal fire!
And it spells out
S.O.S!
Whoa!
It's a meteor shower!
Fireflies!
Go! Run!
You're free! You're free!
Ouch! Ouch!
Yeah!
Yes!
Look what I have created!
I have made fire!
I... have made fire!
Mmm!
You gotta love crab.
In the nick oftime too.
I couldn't take much more
ofthose coconuts.
Coconut milk's
a natural laxative.
Things that Gilligan
never told us.
Oh.
Pretty well-made fire,
huh, Wilson?
[ Thunderclap ]
So... Wilson.
We were en route...
from Memphis
for 1 1 and a half hours.
About 475 miles an hour.
So they think that
we are right here.
But...
we went out
of radio contact...
and flew around that storm
for about an hour.
So that's a distance
ofwhat, 400 miles?
Four hundred miles squared.
That's 1 60,000...
times pi— 3.1 4.
[ Mumbling ]
Five hundred and two thousand,
four—
That's a search area
of 500,000 square miles.
That's twice the size
ofTexas.
They may never find us.
[ Thunderclaps ]
[ Groaning ]
This tooth isjust killing me.
It started outjust hurting
when I bit down...
but now itjust hurts
all the time.
All the time.
It's-It's a good thing there's
not much to eat around here...
because I don't think
I could chew it.
Just keep sucking on all that coconut
and all that crab.
And just think...
I used to avoid
going to the dentist...
like the plague.
I put it offevery single chance I got.
But now...
oh, what I wouldn't give...
to have a-a dentist
right here in this cave.
[ Groans ]
In fact,
I wish you were a dentist.
Yeah.
Dr. Wilson.
You wanna hear
something funny?
Back home in Memphis...
my dentist's name is
Dr.James Spaulding.
She's much prettier
in real life.
[ Groaning ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Yells ]
[ Thunderclaps ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Clattering Continues ]
Shut up!
"Bakersfield"?
Bakersfield!
This could work.
[ Softly ]
Twenty-two-
Forty-four lashings.
So-
We have to make rope again.
Wilson, we're gonna have to make
a hell ofa lot of rope.
Eight lashings
ofthese structurals.
That's 24 apiece.
That'll be 1 00— 1 60.
Here we are today.
That gives us another month and a half
until we're into March and April...
which is our best chances for the high tides
and the offshore breezes.
We need—
We need 424 feet...
ofgood rope, plus another 50 feet,
say, for miscellaneous.
Round that offto
475 feet of good rope.
Now, ifwe average
1 5 feet a day—
Plus, we have to build it...
we have to stock it,
we have to launch it.
That's gonna be tight.
That is not much time.
But we—
We live and we die by time,
don't we?
Now, let's not commit the sin
ofturning our back on time.
[ Laughs ]
I know.
This is it.
That's all that's left.
I checked over the whole island,
and that is all that's left.
So we're gonna be short.
Short.
We'll just have to make some more
out ofthe videotape.
Yes.
No, we have time.
We do. We have time.
Look!
The wind's still blowing in
from the west.
I know!
Yeah, I know— I know where
there's 30 feet ofextra rope!
But— But I'm not
going back up there.
There, there.
There, you see? Huh?
There.
Are you happy?
Do you have to keep bringing that up?
Can't you just forget it?
Huh? You were right.
You were right. It was a good thing
that we did a test...
'cause it wasn't gonna be
just a quick little snap.
I would have landed
on the rocks.
Broken my leg or my back or my neck.
Bled to death.
But it was the only option I had
at the time though, okay?
It was what, a year ago?
So let'sjust forget it.
And what is your point?
Well...
we mightjust make it.
Did that thought
ever cross your brain?
Well, regardless, I would rather
take my chance out there on the ocean...
than to stay here and die
on this shithole island...
spending the rest of my life talking
to a goddamn volleyball!
Shut you up.
Wilson! Wilson!
Wilson!
Wilson.
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, God! Wilson!
Wilson!
Oh! Oh!
Never again.
Never again, never again.
You're okay.
You okay? Yeah.
Yeah, I know you.
I know you.
So, we okay?
Okay?
Okay.
You still awake?
Me too.
You scared?
[ Wind Howling ]
Okay.
Here we go, Wilson.
You don't have to worry
about anything.
I'll do all the paddling.
You just hang on.
Not yet!
Hold on!
Stand by, Wilson!
Hold on, Wilson!
[ Laughing ]
I think we did it!
Wilson!
[ Whale Calling ]
[ Thunderclaps ]
Oh! They're gone!
I don't know why!
[ Whale Spouting ]
Where's Wilson?
Wilson, where are you?
Wilson!
l'm comin'!
Wilson—
[ Gurgling ]
Wilson!
Wilson! Wilson!
[ Gasping, Panting ]
[ Coughs ]
Wilson!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Wilson!
Wilson, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Wilson!
[ Sobbing ]
I can't!
Wilson!
[ Sobbing Loudly ]
I'm— I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[ Whale Calls, Spouts ]
[ Whale Spouts ]
[ Horn Blows ]
[ Alarm Blaring ]
[ Whispers ]
Kelly.
[ Ringing ]
Hello?
Oh, how are you?
Okay.
Forty-five minutes.
One Dr. Pepper.
Two cups of ice.
I like ice.
Well, here's the drill.
Um, plane pulls in,
we get off...
and there's a little ceremony
right there in the hangar.
Fred Smith
will say a few words.
All you have to do is smile
and say "thank you."
Then we'll take you over
to see Kelly.
She's actually gonna
be there, huh?
Well, that's what
we have arranged.
I mean, ifyou're sure
you wanna do that.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
I don't know what
I'm gonna say to her.
What in the world
am I gonna say to her?
Chuck, Kelly had
to let you go.
You know?
She thought you were dead.
And we buried you.
We had a funeral and a coffin
and a gravestone.
The whole thing.
You had a coffin?
What was in it?
Well, everybody put
something in.
You know,just a cell phone
or a beeper, some pictures.
I put in some Elvis CDs.
So you had my funeral...
and then you had
Mary's funeral.
Stan, I'm so sorry
I wasn't around when Mary died.
I should've been there foryou,
and I wasn't.
I'm so sorry.
Fouryears ago...
the FedEx family lost
five ofour sons.
That was a terrible
and tragic day.
But today,
one ofthose sons...
Chuck Noland,
has been returned to us.
Chuck, welcome home.
[ Applause ]
[ Male Newscaster ] Just moments ago,
Fred Smith welcomed home Chuck Noland.
- How about it, Michelle?
- It's such an incredible and amazing story...
- to come back from the dead.
- Well, it's so amazing that
Smith himselfwelcomed him back.
And Fred acknowledged that,
"While time waits for no man...
we take time to pause
to honor one ofour own."
Now, that's an expensive pause.
[ TV Continues ]
I'm-I'm sorry.
I must be in the wrong place.
No, you're in
the right place.
You probably don't remember me. I actually
did root canal on you about five years ago.
Jim Spaulding referred you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm Kelly's husband.
Jerry Lovett.
Kelly wanted—
Kelly wanted to be here-
Look, this is very hard
for everyone.
I can't even imagine
how hard it is foryou.
Kelly, uh—
She's had it rough.
First when she thought
she lost you...
and now dealing
with all ofthis.
It's-It's confusing.
It's very emotional for her.
She's-
She's... sort of lost.
Maybe you could just
give her a little more time.
Anyway, uh...
I'm sorry that—
[ Inaudible ]
Okay, people, let's go.
Party's over. Let's go home.
Let's go home.
[ Maynard ] You're definitely gonna
have to go down to the DMV.
Okay, Maynard, let's go.
Chuck's had a big day.
- I have to briefthis man
on his meetings tomorrow...
- I know.
with the accountants
and the attorneys, all right?
I will see you bright and early
in the morning.
- Hey, Chuck, welcome home. We love you.
- Becca, I need to speak to you.
You know, Chuck, we gotta catch up
on some ofthat fishin', now.
Take care.
- Good night.
You got everything
you need? Okay.
Well, ifyou need anything,
just sign for it...
and I'll see you
in the morning.
Get some sleep, okay?
We got another big day tomorrow.
It takes a lot of paperwork
to bring back a man.
- Bring you back to life, man.
- [ Becca ] Bye, Chuck.
- Take care, now.
- Tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're gonna
bring you back to life.
How long are you
gonna be, man?
Well...
- how long will that buy me?
- About ten minutes.
I'm awake.
I sawyour taxi drive up.
Get in here
out ofthe rain.
I saw you
down at the hub today...
so I knowyou were down there.
Let me get you a towel.
They're sleeping.
Ifyou come in,
I'll make you some coffee.
It's a nice house.
Yeah, we got
a nice mortgage too.
What's your daughter's name?
Katie.
- She's a beautiful little girl.
- She's a handful.
Just let me get
one thing straight here.
We have a pro football team now,
but they're in Nashville?
[ Sighs, Chuckles ]
Um, yeah. Oh, my God. Okay.
They used to be in Houston.
First they were the Oilers,
and now they're the Titans.
The Houston Oilers
are the Tennessee Titans?
Yeah.
But that's not all.
They went to the Super Bowl
last year.
- And I missed t hat.
- You would've died. It was so exciting.
They almost won by one yard.
One lousyyard right at the end.
I got whole milk,
2% and nonfat.
I don't have any half-and-half,
and that's what you like.
That'll do fine.
What happened to you
becoming a professor?
You're not
Dr. Kelly Frears-Lovett?
When you, um—
When your plane went down...
everythingjust sort of
got put on hold.
I think about
taking it up again, though.
I came out here
to give you this.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry it doesn't work.
And I, uh,
I kept the picture.
It was all faded anyway.
I want you to have it.
I gave it to you.
That's a family heirloom,
and it should stay in your family.
That's everything I have
from when you went down to now.
They said they never figured out
what caused the crash.
Probably some mislabeled
hazardous material caught fire.
So here's where
that ship found you.
You drifted about 500 miles.
This is where
your island was...
about 600 miles
south ofthe Cook Islands.
And these are
the search grids.
Ships went back and forth
for weeks looking foryou.
I never should've
gotten on that plane.
gotten out ofthe car.
I wanna show you something.
Come here.
This is-
This is our car.
You kept our car.
All right, now,
this is weird.
It's a good car.
Had a lot of memories
in this car.
Two very nice memories.
Oh, that trip
down to the Gulf, yeah.
So, can I drive it?
It's your car.
That's good, 'cause my-
my taxi's gone.
Um—
Let me get some stuff
out ofthe back.
You thinkyou're gonna
have more kids?
I don't know.
It's kind ofconfusing
right now.
Well, you should.
I mean, really,
you should.
I would.
So, what now?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
[ Starts Engine ]
You said
you'd be right back.
I'm so sorry.
Me too.
Chuck!
I always knewyou were alive.
I knew it.
But everybody said
I had to stop saying that—
that I had to let you go.
I love you.
You're the love of my life.
I love you too, Kelly.
More than you'll ever know.
Chuck?
You have to go home.
We both had done
the math, and—
Kelly added it all up.
She knew she had
to let me go.
I added it up,
knew that I'd—
I'd lost her.
'Cause I was never gonna
get offthat island.
I was gonna die there...
totally alone.
I mean, I was gonna get sick or I was
gonna get injured or something.
The only choice I had...
the only thing
I could control...
was when and how...
and where
that was gonna happen.
So... I made a rope.
And I went up to the summit
to hang myself.
But I had to test it,
you know?
Ofcourse.
You know me.
And the weight ofthe log...
snapped the limb
ofthe tree.
So I-I—
I couldn't even kill myself
the way I wanted to.
I had power over nothing.
And that's when this feeling came over me
like a warm blanket.
I knew...
somehow...
that I had to stay alive.
Somehow.
I had to keep breathing...
even though there was
no reason to hope.
And all my logic said that I would never
see this place again.
So that's what I did.
I stayed alive.
I kept breathing.
And then one day
that logic was proven all wrong...
because the tide...
came in,
gave me a sail.
And now, here I am.
I'm back...
in Memphis, talking to you.
I have ice in my glass.
And I've lost her
all over again.
I'm so sad that
I don't have Kelly.
But I'm so grateful that
she was with me on that island.
And I know
what I have to do now.
I gotta keep breathing.
Because tomorrow,
the sun will rise.
Who knows what the tide
could bring?
♪♪ [ 1 950's Rock On Radio ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
Hello!
[ Whistles ]
FedEx!
[ DoorAlarm Beeping ]
- You look lost.
- I do?
Where are you headed?
Well, I wasjust about
to figure that out.
Well, that's 83 South.
And this road here will
hookyou up with I-40 East.
Ifyou turn right...
that'll take you to
Amarillo, Flagstaff...
California.
And ifyou head back
that direction...
you'll find a whole lotta nothin'
all the way to Canada.
I got it.
All right, then.
Good luck, cowboy.