[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is KPOP STAR
Season 2!
I will introduce the TOP4 and the 3
judges that will prepare with them.
First is Park Jin-young of
JYP and Bang Ye-dam!
They look good.
Those socks are
impressive.
Looking forward
to his song.
Next is Yang Hyun-suk
of YG and 2,000 won!
We also look forward to 2,000 won
that transformed into YG style.
Last of all is BoA of SM, Andrew
Choi, and Akdong Musician!
They look like a team walking out
while holding hands. They look good.
Another round of applause to
the TOP4 and the 3 judges.
This casting audition is
on a different level.
We're casting them as if they
are our agency's celebrities.
My goal is to make
both of you pass.
It's possible.
[Genius siblings
Akdong Musician]
[Potential recognized every round
Every song they sing becomes a hit!]
["Crescendo" seizes
the music chart!]
["Officially Missing You" gets
a million views in 6 hours!]
[Gets the highest score
from the judges!]
I'm curious what song
they will get from SM.
[KPOP STAR's X-man
Andrew Choi]
[Unexpected victory!
Winning rate is 100%!]
[Moves them with music!
Praise after praise!]
He's consistent and makes
continual improvements.
He'll easily make it
to TOP3 silently.
[Best friends duo
2,000 won]
2,000 won is the dark
horse of live broadcast.
2,000 won made me think that I
shouldn't make rash judgments.
They took an upturn which
is really something.
I anticipate that they
will make it to TOP3.
Ye-dam is truly
frightening.
He doesn't sound like Justin
Bieber when singing his songs.
He had his own colors when
singing Michael Jackson's songs.
I don't think he's
afraid of anything.
The 3 agencies' pride
is at stake here.
I'm curious what stage will come
out when we work with them.
[TOP4's huge clash
towards the semi-finals]
[Who will get eliminated?]
Hi, I'm KPOP STAR's
MC, Yoon Do-hyun.
Only 3 battles left
until the finale.
The casting audition prepared by
SM, YG, and JYP starts today.
The agencies devoted all their energy
to form a project team for the TOP4.
I anticipate the agencies' battle to
be as fierce as the contestants'.
I believe the judges are more
nervous than the contestants.
- JYP?
- Yes?
Could you tell us the points we
should focus on for their battle?
Since this program is
coming to an end...
We think, "What if we make
them as one of our artists?"
As a producer, I observe
more objectively.
- Alright... YG?
- Yes?
When you casted 2,000 won
last week, it was unexpected.
Was there any reason
for that decision?
They were pointed out the most and
received almost no compliments.
My plan is to get them
a lot of compliments.
Since they're confident, they'll
present an enjoyable stage.
Looking forward to that.
- BoA?
- Yes?
Since you had great results in
last year's casting audition...
There were talks of promoting you to
vice chairman of SM Entertainment.
It's your first time working
with Akdong Musician...
Should we look
forward to it?
I worked hard to draw out
200% of their charms.
- You should look forward to it.
- Then we shall.
We request a fair and
careful judgment.
Judges' scores are 70% and
viewers' votes are 30%.
One team with the lowest total
score will be eliminated.
The TOP3 will each get casted to the
3 agencies and go to the semi-finals.
I will announce the order and
the contestants' number.
He has a soft charisma.
No. 1 Andrew Choi.
A little giant on stage,
No. 2 Bang Ye-dam.
KPOP STAR's dark horse of live
broadcast, No. 3 2,000 won.
Growing like "Crescendo",
No. 4 Akdong Musician.
You can choose who will
make it to the semi-finals.
Boom will explain in detail how you
can become a national panelist.
Hi, I'm MC Boom and I'm
here with the audience.
We're now at a crossroad
towards victory.
Many were eliminated
and only four remain.
Who will advance to
the semi-finals?
It all depends on you. I'll
explain the voting system.
Open the messaging on
your phone and...
Text #0606 with the finalists'
Korean name or number.
You're rooting for more
than one? That's fine.
You can vote for more
than one person.
But you can't make multiple
votes for one person.
Voting is also possible
via mobile messengers.
Victory is near.
We request active voting with
your objective eyes and ears.
Not only will you watch the TOP4's
intense competition live, but...
Also a special stage performed
by the TOP4 and a guest.
Stay tuned for that
historic stage.
Are you curious?
Should we start?
Fine. I introduce
the first stage.
Women will love it. Andrew
Choi is waiting for you.
Together with SM!
KPOP STAR!
[Voting Begins]
[Text #0606 with the finalists'
Korean name or number]
[He beats the strong
and wins every round!]
[Andrew Choi has
amazing potential]
We're amazed at his silent
growth in every round.
He truly is KPOP
STAR's X-man.
What's important now is that you
draw out as much as you can.
I chose Lee Moon-sae's
"In the Rain" for Andrew.
How will it sound with his
R&B soul with a little Blues?
It'll be different from
the song we're used to.
[SM's strategy meeting!]
[Kim Tae-sung
Arranger]
It's good!
I knew it!
[I'm the queen in
music selection]
How do you
sing like that?
Please tell me.
I just practice a lot.
[Starting from styling
to staging]
[SM experts have a heated
discussion for Andrew!]
I wrote music for 15 years and
wanted to be a composer.
No matter how hard I tried,
it never worked out.
It was hard and I even
thought of giving up.
I feel happy to make it this far
because I didn't give up.
[A grateful friend who
supported his dreams]
I recommended that you
try out on KPOP STAR.
I gave you that push since you're
the best singer out of all I know.
It's amazing you
made it this far.
I know, right?
Do you know
what this is?
It's SHINee's album.
We worked on this 2 years
ago and it's out now.
If you debut as a singer,
we're still partners, right?
Thank you for arranging
this song for me.
I'll do well on stage.
Yeah!
[In the Rain - Lee Moon-sae
(arr. by Kim Tae-sung)]
We enjoyed this song that was
reinterpreted by Andrew.
We're curious of his
score and commentary.
It was really moving.
I don't know how
to explain that.
You had this amazing ability
for the past 15 years.
I thought why you couldn't
get good results quickly.
There's only one reason.
Your breathing and vocalization
were bad because of your habits.
During this program, there was a change
3 weeks ago and now you have no flaws.
On top of that musicality, you have
an open voice and breathing.
It was moving. I want to
use you in a handbook.
I want a before and after of
Andrew Choi in a handbook.
Your vocalization 3 weeks ago
and then 3 weeks later.
It really moved me.
I enjoyed it.
That was a good
commentary.
Wants to use him in a handbook,
but what about his score?
JYP's score is...
You forgot, huh?
It's 96!
That's high!
He got a high score as
much as his commentary.
We're curious of his next
score and commentary.
Why am I trembling?
Maybe it's because this
is the casting audition.
Even BoA told me during the song
that her palms were sweaty.
In the video clip, we saw
Andrew shedding tears.
But his tears are different
from Shin Ji-hoon's.
He talked about how
he had a hard time.
This song is
Lee Moon-sae's.
Many people go
to his concerts.
I don't think it's because
he's a good singer.
He doesn't have an
exceptional voice.
What I want to say
to Andrew is...
A feeling that comforts the heart
or makes us search our memory.
Even though you don't speak Korean
well, you expressed the song well.
Since Andrew is too old
to be an idol singer...
I hope you become a singer that makes
the audience search their memory.
YG's score is...
That was a good
commentary.
But what about
the score?
- It's 90!
- Thank you.
That's high!
Last is the score and
commentary from SM.
I was nervous as if
I was the one singing.
Sooner begun,
sooner done.
I feel proud that Andrew, who was
trained at SM, had a good start.
This song is actually sung
at many auditions.
But this song sung in your R&B
and soul style is only on...
Umm... I'm trembling so
much that I can't speak.
- You're trembling a lot.
- What do I do?
Why don't you give her a
hand? She's trembling a lot.
Since this is the
casting audition.
This is why I hate
the casting audition.
- It's burdensome.
- But we like it.
It's something only
he could do.
I feel proud that you made
a good stage. Thank you.
- SM's score is...
- It's SM's score.
It's 95!
The judges' score is 281.
That's a very high score.
If you want to hear more
of Andrew's sweet voice...
Please text #0606 with
"Andrew Choi" or "No. 1".
This stage was by
No. 1 Andrew Choi.
Now we begin the stage prepared
by JYP and Bang Ye-dam.
[Writes a new history in
auditioning every week]
[The youngest TOP4 casted
to JYP - Bang Ye-dam]
I never expected to
make it this far.
A stage where he can show his
singing, dancing, and performance.
That's his strength and
I want to focus on that.
[Next day after live broadcast
Goes straight to select song]
[Park Nam-jung's
"Missing You" (1989)]
Next one.
[Kim Gun-mo's
"First Impression" (1992)]
I want him to
sing a gayo.
I made him sing
Park's "Missing You".
Then I made him sing
Kim's "First Impression".
What about you?
- "You're the One"...
- "You're the One"?
["You're the One" arranged
in a rock & roll style]
It's cute.
I wanted to avoid my song since I was
afraid my colors would stand out.
But he sang that the best
and in his own colors.
You sing this well.
Thank you.
Excited?
Yes.
[Selection finished]
He's hearing me sing his song
and he's going to evaluate.
I'm curious and excited what
score and commentary I'll get.
[Intense training that night]
I'm happy every time I pass, but
the practice is hard and tiring.
It's only 1 min from
the practice room.
I'd be playing soccer or baseball
with my friends if I was at school.
I feel sad that I'm
here practicing.
You're going home.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wow!
[Runs without stopping!]
[Home for the first
time in 3 months]
Grandma!
You grew, huh?
He was up to my chest,
but now he's up here.
Home cooking
was really good.
[It's good]
Can you shampoo
by yourself?
Yes...
I was worried
before you left.
I don't need
to bathe you?
Can you do it
by yourself?
- Should I show you?
- No. It's okay.
I was happy and it was
fun seeing my family.
I said I was going
to KO JYP.
I'm going to prepare a
secret weapon to KO BoA.
He KO'd me.
[Will his plan
be a success?]
I'll enjoy this stage and
show that I'm doing well.
Yeah!
[You're the One - JYP
(arr. by Wasabii Sound)]
It was a cute and exciting
stage by Bang Ye-dam.
What score will he
get from the judges?
I'll go first.
I'm curious. Did JYP make
you say that narration?
Yes.
You can't use
such a gimmick.
I think it was to
captivate you.
What are you
doing with a kid?
It was cute.
Your high notes were unstable
before, but now they sound firm.
It sounded much better.
I told you last time that your
pronunciation wasn't clear.
That got better. Overall, it was
a fun and exciting stage.
Thank you.
- SM's score is...
- It's SM's score.
What will he get?
- It's 93!
- Thank you.
That's high.
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
It's hard to judge a contestant who
received training from another agency.
In other words, it's hard
to say something bad.
Does that mean you want
to say something bad?
Bang Ye-dam... No, no.
When I heard he's singing
JYP's "You're the One"...
There was a misunderstanding.
"He's making him sing his song?"
But there was a reason.
The reason Bang Ye-dam is great, in
my previous commentary, is that...
He's different from the contestants
on "Star King" that imitate adults.
He has skills to compete
with even professionals.
When I heard he's singing that,
I thought he might be in a crisis.
Since this song is fairly new
and there are many moves...
I was worried that he
shouldn't look like little JYP.
That is why I said that
earlier as a joke.
Actually, you couldn't
get rid of that image.
Since I view your potential in high
regards, maybe I had a high expectation.
I was expecting the arrangement and
choreography to have changed more.
But it wasn't enough.
YG's score is...
He said it would've been better
if there was some change.
It's YG's score.
- It's 85!
- Thank you.
Last is JYP's score
and commentary.
It's not easy singing while dancing, and
it's even harder when the tempo is fast.
And it's hard to sing when you dance
with your lower body most of the time.
More than half of the choreography
utilizes the lower part of the body.
It's hard to explain this
if you haven't tried it.
He really did well if you take that
difficulty into consideration.
- JYP's score is...
- Thank you.
It's JYP's score.
What will it be?
- It's 94!
- Thank you.
The judges' score is 272.
If you want to root for
Bang Ye-dam next week...
Please text #0606 with
"Bang Ye-dam" or "No. 2".
This stage was by
No. 2 Bang Ye-dam.
I'm curious how they changed
through YG's producing.
2,000 won's stage
begins now!
They're the dark horse
of live broadcast.
No one expected them
to make it to the TOP4.
[Advances to TOP4 by
getting cast to YG]
As a producer, I wanted
to cast them to YG.
- Come in, have a seat.
- Hello?
- First, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You guys remind me of last
year's Lee Seung-hoon.
I thought you guys would never
make it, but you came this far.
It's not luck. You guys have the
power to appeal to the masses.
I want to explode
that here at YG.
We always went on stage
thinking it's the last.
But that changed when
we made it to TOP4.
We feel we could approach
it differently than before.
We're doing this thinking
this is the beginning.
The 3 agencies' pride
is at stake here.
I'll try hard to make
them advance to TOP3.
[Robin - composer]
I think it's great that
they're fully supporting us.
Everyone is doing their
best to fully support us.
We feel burdened but also
confident that we won't lose.
[Suddenly during
the interview...]
[Global star PSY]
You're pretty good.
[He said I'm good]
[And]
It's Lee Seung-hoon!
We were surprised.
But seeing him was
sort of like a healing.
Many people compare
me to 2,000 won.
But after hearing
them sing...
I think they will break that
parallel theory today.
[D-3 - mid-term
evaluation]
This is the best from
all the songs you sang.
[Praised]
Wow! It could be fun!
It's groundbreaking!
That selection is like
taking a huge risk.
We're singing Shim Soo-bong's
"One Million Roses".
[What's the reason for this
unexpected selection?]
We chose this because YG
told us to tell our story.
While searching for a song where
we could put in our true hearts...
Unconditional love,
love without hatred...
We felt that it was
a mother's love.
If we tell our story through a mother's
love, I think people can relate to it.
"A stream washing over me from the
world like a desert." This is good.
- You wrote this?
- Yes.
This is the first time I thought
you were good at writing lyrics.
- It's really good.
- Thank you.
When we were young, we told our
parents we wanted to do music.
Of course, they
were against it.
I was immature then, but I thought
running away would solve everything.
I think that is when
we broke their heart.
I want them to feel, "My son is
becoming a singer," and be happy.
I didn't express it well, but
I'm grateful and love my mom.
Mother... I'll say mom.
Mom, you raised me well until now.
I hope this stage will repay the favor.
I love you, mom.
[One Million Roses - Shim Soo-bong
(arr. by Robin)]
At the age of 17, I broke your expectations
I blindly went to the streets for my dreams
I returned home after days of wandering
You were waiting for me with open arms
You embraced me with trusting eyes
Don't chase after my shadows
I know your sadness, rest now
The great comfort you raised
You were once a fragrant rose
Your youth withered for me
The pain you bore for a thorn like me
But you always and forever smile at me
You're the dam that blocks the
World that's like a flood
You're the stream washing over me
From the world that's like a desert
Until a million roses bloom in my life
You're the sun silently shining from above
I always complained without thanks
But you gave everything to me
I'll take the burden from your shoulders
Don't worry. I'll close the gates of worries
Stay beside, I'm not good at expressing
Thank you although all was not conveyed
I'll do it all here
For you in this world
It was a touching
stage by 2,000 won.
I'm curious how the
judges heard it.
I'll go first.
This was an unexpected
stage by 2,000 won.
I read Il'do's rap while
listening. It was well-written.
Since it's your story, your use of
empathy was better. It was good.
But Hyo-bin's old style of singing
came out even more in this song.
That was a pity, but overall it was
amazing that you had this side.
SM's score is...
She said it was a new
side. SM's score is...
It's 95! That's high!
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
I froze when Hyo-bin
started singing.
I pestered Andrew Choi with
vocalization and he changed it.
I pestered Hyo-bin with his old
style of singing from the start.
He was correcting it a little, but went
back to square one with this song.
I was taken aback at the
introduction and froze.
But I also thought this.
He could be first in another
program other than KPOP STAR.
They compared you to last
year's Lee Seung-hoon, but...
Putting skills aside, he's like
next generation's singer.
His thoughts and expressions
are unlike existing singers.
Both of you have exceptional talents,
but you guys are like existing singers.
I think that's the difference
between us and other programs.
JYP's score is...
It's JYP's score. How
much will he give them?
It's 82!
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
It's so tense today.
- I gave Ye-dam a low score.
- Sparks are flying.
It seems you're taking
revenge on 2,000 won.
Both of you should
shake hands.
Sparks are flying. I'm sorry to
say this, but it was fun for us.
I'm just joking.
Both BoA and JYP said that their singing
is old-fashioned. They said it many times.
But I don't agree
today because...
Shim Soo-bong's
song is even older.
I told 2,000 won...
I told them to forget the singing
style since this song is old.
Just sing in the old-fashioned
way as much as you want.
Changing your singing style and
vocalization isn't important.
Do you change a trot
into an R&B?
No, right?
I thought Hyo-bin's old-fashioned
way would go along with this song.
It's a pity that you were nervous.
I thought you would do better.
You don't need anything else
in this song about a mother.
The feeling the lyrics
gave was touching.
It was a good stage where
I thought of my mother.
YG's score is...
It's YG's score. I'm
really curious.
It's 88!
The judges' score is 265.
If you think 2,000 won's
stage was good...
Please text #0606 with
"2,000 won" or "No. 3".
This stage was by
No. 3 2,000 won.
Now we have the
last TOP4 stage.
SM and Akdong Musician worked for
the first time. I wonder how it was.
It starts now!
[Gets the highest judges' score
Akdong Musician is moving up!]
[Got casted to SM
for the first time!]
[What if SM's colors are added
on to Akdong Musician?]
Do you know 10cm's...
"Love in the Milky Way Cafe"?
- Yes, I know.
- I know.
- You know that?
- Yes.
I started writing songs
because of that song.
Really? I think we're on
the same wavelength.
The first song I wrote after
hearing that song is "Galaxy".
Then I wrote many
more afterwards.
I like the song, but I was worried
where to start in arranging.
That went on for two
days without eating.
Then we had a
meeting with BoA.
She said many good things
and that gave me ideas.
You could connect the titles of
your hit songs and write a rap.
"I met Soo-hyun at the Milky Way
Cafe and she was attractive."
"Brother, don't cross your
legs. That's disgusting."
Or Soo-hyun likes
some guy in a cafe.
[Oh]
But her brother is
keeping her in check.
Yesterday I wore a dress and he said,
"Your dress is getting shorter."
You're old-fashioned.
She should take care of herself, but
she spreads her legs when sitting.
It's unfair. He says to me why
am I always around guys.
But wherever I go, there
are always guys around me.
But she's different when
she's with me and not.
- When?
- You did.
Akdong are just mischievous.
That's what they are.
A freshness and cuteness that
people around their age can show.
I want their colors
to become brighter.
[But one problem...]
But we don't know what
a Korean style cafe is.
[They don't know?]
- Where is it?
- Milky Way Cafe is...
Does it even exist?
I think that's it.
[Milky Way Cafe was the
motif of the original song]
Even 10cm wrote their
song in this place.
I think I could write good
lyrics receiving that vibe.
I'm sorry to them, but...
Their pain gives
us great joy.
So we always expect
something from them.
[Love in the Milky Way Cafe - 10cm
(arr. by Hwang Chan-hee)]
It's him again today
Sleeping Lee Soo wakes up
She turns around when a man appears
Practices on making sheep eyes
You are double-faced
Everyone adores you
I'm not jealous
I just hate you
You clumsily crossed your legs
But it makes you look wealthy
Your disgusted look at the menu
Makes you look attractive
Why don't you snap out of it?
Hey ugly! We need to get our act
The coffee water's not hot
My nagging is in crescendo
US, Canada, Ulan Bator, Mongolia
I can't fly to those places
It comes after listening to
Akdong Musician's song
Their witty ideas stood out.
It was like seeing a musical.
We're curious of their
score and commentary.
YG and I fear
BoA the most.
She always brings out the best
in the people she works with.
So I took her out to drink
several weeks ago.
I was afraid that those
skills would come out.
Andrew Choi's stage
was the best today.
It was a repertorie where he
showed everything he could.
But Akdong Musician's repertoire didn't
have a chance to bring something out.
You didn't do anything wrong, but
you didn't have room to explode.
I enjoyed it.
Let's see JYP's score.
What will he
give them?
It's 85!
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
It's hard to
score them.
I thought for
a long time.
As I watched them the
past several months...
As producers, we want to change
contestants like this and that.
We tested their limits even in
last year's casting audition.
But the result? We should
leave Akdong Musician alone.
They're unique.
BoA, have you tried
"chapaguri"?
- A few years ago.
- Really?
I tried it in my 20s.
- Have you?
- No.
- Did you find out recently?
- Yes. I just found out.
There's none like Akdong Musician
in the exciting gayo world.
There was a news article titled,
"What are you, Akdong Musician?"
That's right.
If I call this song theirs,
it can be their song.
But since they showed many
good things with their songs...
I think they shine more when they sing
their song and not someone else's.
YG's score is...
It's YG's score. What
will he give them?
It's 88!
Last is SM's score
and commentary.
I don't agree with
their commentaries.
It's because I wanted something
from Akdong Musician.
They always shrank from the burden of
their songs. How could I make them enjoy?
What song could draw out the
liveliness in teenagers?
The point of this song was
actually Chan-hyuk's rap.
The lyrics were great, everything was
great, but why did you forget the lyrics?
That was a pity, but I was satisfied
even though I made this stage.
I'll give a good score.
SM's score is...
What score is
a good score?
SM's score is 95!
The judges' score is 268.
If you're rooting for
Akdong Musician...
Please text #0606 with
"Akdong Musician" or "No. 4".
This stage was by No. 4
Akdong Musician. A hand.
Now all the TOP4
stages are over.
According to the judges' score,
2,000 won has the highest...
I'm sorry, Andrew Choi
has the highest score.
But we don't know
the results yet.
But your votes will
determine their fate.
We'll give you one last chance to
vote as you watch the highlight clip.
Text and mobile voting
will be over soon.
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
Voting is now over.
We'll soon have the
total score, right?
That's right.
While it's being tallied, we
have a special performance.
Boom, please tell us.
Since we're here together,
you might have expected it.
Increase the volume and
just enjoy the show.
The TOP4 got into two teams
and prepared a special stage.
That's right. Looking
forward to it.
First, Akdong Musician and
Bang Ye-dam are in a team.
Do you know their
group's name?
- Of course, I do.
- What is it?
One more Akdong,
so it's Akhachu.
- You knew?
- Of course.
They'll be performing
together again.
The big brothers formed a team -
2,000 won and Andrew Choi.
- I can't wait.
- Me, too.
First is KPOP STAR's brilliant dark horse,
2,000 won, and sweet voice, Andrew Choi.
Please look forward to it.
Let's watch the stage by
2,000 won and Andrew Choi!
[She Was Pretty - JYP]
I got a shock looking at her
She was so pretty
Her deep charm is like espresso
Who wouldn't fall for her?
Looking here and there like Dooly
She's perfect wherever she goes
She's like a twinkling star
So she glimmers when she turns
[f(x) Sulli
special guest]
She's a cut above from head to toe
So she doesn't care if a man comes near
I'm not tired of her
She doesn't get bumped
My heart's always aflutter
If I borrow her name for a sec
She's the truth in life
KPOP STAR's best stage!
- Wow! That stage was great.
- I enjoyed it. It was good.
It was crazy here.
We were dancing.
You didn't see me dance?
It was really crazy here.
- Can you show us?
- Alright.
That's good.
Sulli was the "she"
of "She Was Pretty".
Yes it was.
I envy you guys for
performing with her.
- I held you back from going up.
- But she's very attractive.
- You shouldn't do that.
- I'm sorry.
The next stage is
even more special.
It's Akhachu - Bang Ye-dam
and Akdong Musician.
There's going to be
a special guest.
- Excited?
- I sure am!
Let's watch the next
stage together!
[Don't Hate Me - Epik High]
[Epik High
special guest]
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Survial Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2!
The TOP4 stages prepared with the
3 agencies were fiercer than ever.
The results have
been tallied.
Judges' score is 70% and
viewers' votes are 30%.
One team with the lowest total
score will be eliminated...
The remaining three will each
get casted to SM, YG, or JYP.
They get the honor of advancing
to KPOP STAR's semi-finals.
Which teams will advance
to the semi-finals?
The judges just
got the results.
Before you see the results, is there
someone you would like to cast, BoA?
- It's a secret.
- Did that person pass?
It's a secret.
- A secret... okay.
- I don't know either.
- Of course.
- Yes.
Please open the
envelope and check.
They're checking it.
The one who's eliminated
is in the envelope.
Looking forward to if the one they
casted passed or was eliminated.
Only the three teams that
made it can get casted.
A pity, but the eliminated
cannot get casted.
We will now begin casting
by SM, YG, and JYP!
The team that isn't called to
the end is eliminated today.
We will now start
casting one by one.
First is...
JYP! Please begin casting.
I felt heavy because talented people
got eliminated starting last week.
But it isn't important what
rank you get in this audition.
What's important is what
did you learn from it.
I want to comfort you with those words
whether you get first or get eliminated.
When we start this program, we see you
as a contestant from a judge's view.
Towards the end, our views change
as representatives of each agency...
And we think as we see you, "What if
they become our agency's artist?"
This is when we
think about that.
Singing and dancing abilities
are very important, but...
The decisive factor for me is
whether you seem natural.
- JYP will cast...
- A natural musician...
They sing and do music
naturally as they are.
- Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
They got casted to JYP and
advance to the semi-finals!
Congratulations.
Akdong Musician,
do you have a mike?
How do you feel?
We thought we were going
to get eliminated...
Thank you for saving us.
We will learn a lot.
You were worried because the
judges' score wasn't high...
Anyways, you got
good results.
Please move over there, and
why don't we give them a hand?
Akdong Musician
got casted to JYP.
Next is SM's turn.
Please begin.
[Who's the second?]
The one who will advance to
the semi-finals with SM is...
- I'm curious.
- Really...
If I saw all of his skills, I'm
curious what his limits would be.
The semi-finalist
casted by SM is...
The semi-finalist is?
- Andrew Choi.
- Congratulations!
He got casted to SM and
advances to the semi-finals.
You got casted to SM.
How do you feel?
I feel great.
Thank you.
Please move over there.
SM casted Andrew Choi. We're
curious how far he'll go.
Only two teams
remain on stage.
One of them will leave KPOP STAR
and one of them will get casted.
As of now, Andrew Choi got casted
to SM and Akdong Musician to JYP.
Ye-dam, how do
you feel?
I'm trembling and I wasn't
satisfied with this stage.
- Worried?
- Nervous and trembling.
Nervous? He's known for not trembling,
but how can he not at this moment?
2,000 won, how
do you feel?
We're very nervous, but we'll
humbly accept our result.
Alright. One seat remains and
the final decision goes to YG.
Please begin.
[Who's the last semi-finalist
and who is eliminated?]
This must have been expected. 2,000
won got the lowest score from JYP...
Bang Ye-dam got the lowest score
from me. Only they remained.
We have a tremendous
responsibility.
When they reach the TOP10, rather
than congratulating the winner...
We feel sad in sending away
those that got eliminated.
There's something global star PSY said
that made a deep impression on me.
He said, "I was never the best, but
I never stopped giving my best."
Although younger than me, I
thought he's a great talker.
Bang Ye-dam and 2,000 won.
I have mixed feelings.
Whether you pass or get eliminated,
everyone here did their best.
The last finalist
casted by YG is...
This is the last finalist.
I can't believe they're here, and they
especially battled each other the most.
Who is the last
to get casted?
The fans' cheers are
growing louder.
- I'll announce it.
- Please do so.
- Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He became a semi-finalist
and got casted to YG.
2,000 won put on a great stage,
but now they will say goodbye.
They really did well. They showed
us how they tried and improved.
Although criticized, they were positive
on stage and truly did their best.
They said they would humbly accept it,
but any last words to your fans?
We finally get to have this interview
we prepared for since the TOP10.
The judges did that because there's a saying,
"A child you care for gets an extra lash."
We'll be a team that will always
challenge with a humble heart.
We got close to our fans, staff,
writers, producers, and directors.
We feel sad to leave, and I thank
my family for supporting me.
I want to say thanks to Hyo-bin
for bringing me on this program.
Thanks man.
A word, Hyo-bin?
We always took the challenge
thinking it was our last.
It was a great
honor for us.
We thank everyone
that cheered us on.
We'll show you how well
we're doing. Thank you!
A hand for 2,000 won for
showing a great stage!
2,000 won unfortunately
got eliminated.
Next week will be an
even fiercer semi-final.
See you next week!
Goodbye!