Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
[After last week's TOP8 battle]
[Jang Hanna and Bae Mina
were eliminated!]
[Another sad parting...]
[The TOP6 finalists say
bye to their two friends]
Four have already left the women's
lodging after making it to the TOP10.
The room will be...
empty now...
[They feel sad since their
friends are gone]
[But the production crew
arrives with boxes]
Someone's here.
- Hello.
- What are these?
- What is it?
[Letters of support
sent by their fans!]
[5,565 letters]
[KPOP STAR letters of
support event]
[Handwritten letters!]
[Even the male contestants!]
[Hae-yong translates for Sam!]
"I always watch KPOP STAR
because of you, Jina."
This person wants to watch us
perform in person before she dies.
I want to go and sing for her.
We even have "samchon" fans.
These letters mean a lot to me
because I was having a hard time.
I'm surging with energy.
I thank everyone that's
rooting for me.
We'll continue to do our best.
Thank you very much.
[The TOP6 battles start now!]
[Live from Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3!
I introduce you to the TOP6 finalists
that will put on a great performance.
Another round of applause for
the TOP6 finalists performing...
On a more impressive stage
before more people.
Glad to be here.
I'm the MC for Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3.
I'm Jun Hyun-moo the
face of KPOP STAR.
You are watching the 6 teams that
made it after the fierce competition.
Their performances last week were
unexpected with twists after twists.
We look forward to their
performances today.
Many came with banners and wearing
same colors to cheer the 6 teams here.
We are proud of the TOP6 that
they have so many fans.
Other than the battles, the TOP6 prepared
a special stage. Look forward to that.
I introduce you to the judges
that will judge impartially.
First is JYPE's Park Jin-young!
YGE's Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Music's You Hee-yeol!
[JYP, YG, You Hee-yeol]
I have to ask them again.
You Hee-yeol? We did our first
live show together. How was it?
I'm getting more nervous because
KPOP STAR is being televised...
But putting that aside, this concerns
the future of the contestants.
So I feel more responsible.
It will be tense because we're
helping them to start off.
That's right. We're proud how they
act like pros, albeit nervous.
But they could get nervous since
the stage is bigger with more people.
Does JYP have any tips
for such a situation?
Well... I can't give such tips
because they will be nervous.
It's important to do well and
have fun although nervous.
We look forward to a
great performance.
They should remain composed
even though they are nervous.
YG? This season begins the 3 agencies week
and this week was YG week. What happened?
Our relationship with the finalists
were professional until now.
During YG week, I met with the
finalists and had a meal together...
I asked if they have any difficulties
so it was more like a personal meeting.
2 teams will be eliminated
in this TOP6 battle.
They must have been nervous last week
since it was their first live show.
I think there will be great performances
today because they will be less nervous.
Alright. There is an agency they
are and are not thinking of...
Aren't you curious which
agency they're thinking of?
We heard that they spoke their mind
so we will watch that right now.
Let's watch it!
[The day after the first live show]
[They were called by the production crew
and gathered at a certain restaurant]
[Why are they here?]
[OMG!]
[YG appears!]
[Dumbfounded at the
unexpected meeting]
[A special meeting with YG
since YG week began]
[This is overwhelming!]
I wanted to meet with them and
figure out their disposition.
I wanted to find out if the ones
I have in mind wants to come to YGE.
It was like going on a
blind date during college.
Didn't you write which agency you would
like to go to when you first applied?
[No way]
Many things happened
since then so...
Heejun doesn't want to come.
It was long ago...
I heard there's a video clip.
Should we watch it now?
[On no...]
- I'm really curious.
- Wait...
[Their intentions are made
public for the first time!]
[Five months from now!]
[The TOP6 finalists came on
KPOP STAR with big dreams!]
[A secret room is on one side...]
[A box for each of the
three agencies is placed...]
[The contestants place a ball into
the box of the agency they desire!]
[What did the TOP6 finalists
think back then?]
[What the TOP6 thought 5 months ago
is revealed for the first time!]
That's not fair!
It was 5 months ago!
[First is Almeng]
[They make a pose
before voting]
We don't need to choose
the same box, right?
It'll be better if we
pick the same one.
[Which box did they vote?]
[Almeng chose YG!]
[Is he pleased?]
[Who's the next contestant?]
[It's Heejun Han who just
arrived from the States!]
[Oh please...]
[That's bold of him
to open the lids!]
[Look at that!]
[Which agency will he choose?]
[Heejun Han chose JYP!]
[Why you...]
[Next contestant is...]
[Kwon Jina]
It's me!
[Pays close attention]
[Looks at the box carefully...]
[She can't make up her mind]
I look stupid.
[Which one?]
[She chose Antenna Music!]
[I see...]
[Each agency got
one vote each...]
[Which contestant will
upset the balance?]
[The Shorties]
[High school girls that
just came up from Daegu]
I don't think it's recording.
It is recording.
I look ugly.
There's another one up there!
[They're amazed at the cameras]
It's Antenna Music, stupid!
- What did she say?
- "It's Antenna Music, stupid!"
Everyone for JYP!
- Everyone?
- Yeah.
OMG!
[Focused]
[Ryu Tae-kyung chooses JYP!]
[Park Na-jin chooses JYP!]
[Yeo In-hye chooses JYP!]
Oh man...
[He's smiling on the outside...]
[Next is Sam Kim]
[Go KPOP STAR!]
[Fastest voting ever!]
[His fast vote caught
them off guard!]
I was told to do that!
[The last TOP6 finalist]
[Bernard Park]
[Bernard Park from Atlanta
chose which one?]
[JYP - 2, YG - 2, Antenna Music - 1]
[Which is it?]
[Bernard Park chooses JYP!]
[Oho!]
[The TOP6 finish voting...]
[JYP - 3, YG - 2, Antenna Music - 1!]
[We found out their intentions]
[But who does YG have in mind?]
So Kwon Jina chose
Antenna Music.
Did you have this feeling?
No. All three agencies are great...
I just did this and picked it.
You Hee-yeol must feel sad.
But...
[What does she think now?]
And the Shorties chose JYP.
[Pricked]
But you came to YGE for
the casting audition.
Which is it?
Keep your spirits up!
Especially...
Sam Kim and Almeng!
I was joking.
Since this week is YG week...
I'm providing the TOP6 with
all of YGE's resources.
They'll hear my advice and meet
2NE1, current senior artists.
I believe there is advice
that artists can give them.
It is my wish as an adviser that they
present their best performance this week.
We just confirmed what they
thought five months ago.
We don't know if it changed since
five months passed. We'll find out later.
I'll explain today's rules.
Today is different from
last week's 1:1 battle.
It will be an absolute evaluation.
Judges' score 60% and viewers' vote 40%
will be calculated for the total score.
The 4 teams with the highest total score
will advance to the TOP4 live show.
The remaining 2 teams will depart from
KPOP STAR when it's over today.
I'll announce the finalists'
number and their order.
No. 1 is Almeng. We always look forward
to what performance they'll show us.
No. 2 is Bernard Park. He has a touching
voice that sways women's hearts.
No. 3 is the Shorties. These three
girls sing a heavenly harmony.
No. 4 is Sam Kim. He is a guitarist
endowed with both talent and soul.
No. 5 is Heejun Han. He attempts
at transforming in every round.
No. 6 is Kwon Jina. She has a
thousand faces and various charms.
These 6 teams will be
evaluated by all of you.
It's not an exaggeration to call this
the finals since they're likely winners.
Since your votes are 40% of the score,
your votes are very important.
Yoo Hye-young will explain
how the voting is done.
Yoo Hye-young?
I'm here with the audience.
Hi, I'm Yoo Hye-young,
KPOP STAR's cheerleader.
It didn't start yet but
things have sure heated up.
You can cheer them here or at your
home in front of the TV by voting.
I'll explain how you can vote.
Text the contestant's name in Korean or
their number to #0606 on your phone.
Please keep in mind that you can
vote for more than one contestant.
But you cannot make multiple
votes for one contestant.
Since voting is possible via KakaoTalk,
those abroad can also participate.
Sam Kim made it due to your votes.
So we ask you to vote this week.
Let's watch the first performance.
It's Almeng, KPOP STAR's sole duo.
Let's give them a hand since they could be
nervous from going first. Voting starts now.
[Text voting begins]
[Text the contestant's name in Korean or
number to #0606 (10 cents data charge)]
[No. 1 Almeng]
[Almeng is at YGE that
they dreamt of]
[They express their joy
with their body]
[All I see is YG]
[Can't be happier than this?]
It's the agency we dreamt of.
It's such a big and great agency that
we can't say yes or no in coming.
It was like a dream.
[They're practicing harder]
[But someone's here to
watch Almeng practice]
Hello.
- Do you know her name?
- Yes, I do.
- She's C...
- Choi Rin.
She's CL...
[Choi Rin, Lee Chae-rin]
Since we're both CL...
Please be good to me.
Curious about something?
Rapping... isn't something
I have been doing.
Why am I so nervous?
I started rapping here and
I was told I was good at it.
I didn't rap when I first came to YGE.
I didn't get in here for rapping.
There must be a reason
if YG told you to rap.
So have confidence.
[Even a hug of support]
- Do your best.
- Thank you.
[Almeng received energy from CL]
[What is Almeng singing?]
It's a song from a YG artist.
It's PSY's "Blue Frog."
The lyrics of this song mean
"We'll do what we want."
It has a message that
suits Almeng.
I don't think it's just going to be fun,
but they'll also make it serious.
The first time I acted like a little devil is
when I told my parents I'm doing music.
Even though I'm a big fish in a small pond,
I'm going to do it because it makes me happy.
Certain melodies will sound familiar
when you listen to the song.
One of Lady Gaga's song is
"Born This Way."
If you translate that song, it goes
exquisitely well with "Blue Frog."
The word "blue frog" could seem playful
but it contains a heartfelt message.
This is PSY's "Blue Frog" but
we want to make it our "Blue Frog."
[No. 1 Almeng]
[Blue Frog - PSY]
I couldn't listen to others
Ever since I was young
Maybe because I was young
But I still don't listen
I have my own center so
People try to lift me but can't
What I heard the most is
What do you think you'll be?
What I wanted to say the most is
I'll do it the way I want
I'm a blue frog
I am me no matter what they say
I'm happy as a big fish in a small pond
That is who I am
Ribbit ribbit goes the frog
It croaks very loudly
Two blue frogs are singing
It's breathtaking
I'm a big fish in a small pond but
Made it here cuz I didn't hesitate
Do you see the size of my pond?
Even in the stormy weather
I push them back to you
No matter how many times I fall
You'll get used to me getting back up
Get up, don't cry, sing
When I do cry out loud
It's a symphony of fate that
Resounds in the pond
I'm a blue frog
I am me no matter what they say
I'm happy as a big fish in a small pond
That is who I am
I'm a blue frog
I am me no matter what they say
I'm happy as a big fish in a small pond
That is who I am
Just wait and see who succeeds
You'll be ashamed and jealous
You'll start to like me
Blue frog
This stage was by No. 1 Almeng with
their uniquely exciting performance!
They sang PSY's "Blue Frog."
She dropped her bracelet...
It was a great performance.
What did the three judges think?
Let's hear the commentaries and score.
Who'll grab the mike first?
Calculating the scores first...
- It's You Hee-yeol.
- I enjoyed it.
There's something I felt today.
We always talked about Choi Rin.
She has great ideas and is like
a scene stealer but today...
I kept on seeing Hae-yong.
Hae-yong also held the balance of
this team and was the mainstay.
You have a nice voice.
We always complimented Choi Rin but
Hae-yong's voice stood out today.
It went well and you
chose a good song.
Antenna Music's score is...
I give you a 90.
Antenna Music gave a 90.
Who'll go next?
JYP is going next.
I look at two things - how good
you are and how new it is.
There are so many great singers.
Why do we need Almeng?
We don't need you if there isn't anything new
because we have so many great singers.
You two are really good and
Hae-yong especially sang well.
The problem is that Hae-yong's
singing wasn't in a new color.
You enlarge your voice when you try
to sing the high notes powerfully.
It's a style used by many
established singers.
It'll be new if you sing the high notes in
the same voice you use for speaking.
No one has your voice but you.
Try to find a way to sing in your voice.
On the other hand, Choi Rin sings in
the same voice as if she's speaking.
Be more confident and show off
your talents on stage.
That was a bit unfortunate.
JYP's score is...
He spoke of originality
and confidence.
It's 82!
Alright. All that's left is YG.
Judging them is vague because they said
in the clip that they want to go to YGE.
The viewers could take it the wrong way
if I give them a high score today.
I believe you'll be
objective and impartial.
I half agree with JYP when
he said they weren't new.
I agree with him on
the singing part.
I think Almeng is new because there is
no mixed duet like them in Korea.
Lee Seung-hoon from Season 1 was
also unique and was scouted by YGE.
This was sung by PSY and GD
but it didn't remind me of PSY.
As you two said, it was like your
"Blue Frog" so it was good.
YG's score is...
It was a different opinion.
The score...
It's 90!
We heard the judges' score
and commentaries.
The judges' total score is 262.
Text voting is still going on.
Those cheering for Almeng can
text "1" or "Almeng" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Almeng!
People I don't even know came
to see me and cheer me on.
They even had my name on posters.
I was really happy about it.
What about Bernard Park?
I'm singing Sung Si-kyung's
"You Touched My Heart."
"You Touched My Heart"?
Give me a minute to think.
I don't think you ever succeeded in
singing gayo all this time, right?
I told you to sing pop since
there isn't much time left.
I wanted you to have an advantage but
this is a mountain you must climb.
I'm more comfortable
singing pop songs.
But I need to sing gayo if
I want to live in Korea.
[What do the other judges think?]
Really?
I never expected this.
It's gayo but it'll be good.
It's a melody that he can sing
but the problem is...
It's crucial how much he can feel
and express the Korean lyrics.
I'm trying to use more
Korean to improve.
I translated the lyrics into English
to be able to understand.
[His efforts to express the
sentiments of the song]
I gave my all thinking
this will be my last.
I'll do my best to show
that I can sing gayo.
[No. 2 Bernard Park]
[You Touched My Heart - Sung Si-kyung]
[Music director - Kwon Tae-eun
Bandmaster - Seo Young-do]
This stage was by No. 2 Bernard Park
who presented a sweet ballad.
Not only women but he also
melts men's hearts as well.
Let's hear the commentaries and
score on his performance.
I tell my artists before recording that
singing is just adding notes to the words.
For example, there's a way to say
"Yeah, that's how it was."
There are expressions and way of
speaking that only Koreans use.
Since you're not good at Korean,
you don't have that way of speaking.
You don't know how to move your eyebrows
or breathe when you say such things.
Basically, you're just reading.
There's a limit to you in singing gayo
unless you improve in Korean.
Despite that fact, I still get the chills
when you sing the high notes.
It was unfortunate but just as
what You Hee-yeol said before...
You can't change class.
JYP's score is...
JYP's score...
It's 86!
Alright. Let's hear the next
commentary and score.
It's been a while since
I agreed with JYP.
- It's been a long time.
- It sure has.
I don't watch dubbed movies. I listen
to it in English and read the subtitles.
I don't understand English but what
they are saying conveys the mood.
Bernard Park is a gold worth a million
dollars but with a small crack in it.
I was rhyming (gold and crack
sounds the same in Korean).
For him to sing gayo with
his pronunciation...
He doesn't have any habits for
someone born and raised in the US.
I think he'll improve but
it wasn't good enough.
I was a little strict in scoring
since your performance was a pity.
YG's score is...
YG's score...
It's going up...
It's 89!
You Hee-yeol is next.
Today's performance
cleared up one thing for me.
YG once compared you to a heavyweight
saying you're heavy without minor skills.
But a world champion wins with a
powerful hook and not with jabs.
You're born with a great talent.
You sang Michael Buble's "Home"
and said how you missed home.
But I don't think it's time
for you to go back home.
I'm curious of his score.
Antenna Music's score is...
Antenna Music's score...
He talked about a
powerful punch.
It's 92!
The judges' total score is 267.
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "2" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Bernard Park!
[After last week's live show]
[They finally burst into tears
at Jang Hanna's elimination!]
We were hurt and sad that Hanna was
eliminated because we were close.
We felt that maybe we're next.
[A few days later, they practice
for their next performance]
[They're usually boisterous...]
[At this moment!]
[Someone approaches
the practice room!]
[Guess who]
[They didn't notice her yet]
[2NE1's Bom]
[Surprised]
[They became polite girl fans]
I'm watching you three.
[They're dumbfounded and can't
believe what's happening]
- Please don't come near!
- Why are you running away?
[Someone might think
she's trying to get them]
You're cute because you're short.
So that's why you're the Shorties.
- Then...
- We're really short.
I want to hear you sing.
[They sing for her the song
they're singing for the show!]
[She pays attention]
It was good.
[Heartfelt advice for parts
they're not good at!]
She pointed out our problems
after listening to us once.
We felt singers are different.
[They're just amazed]
- Good luck!
- Thank you.
[Even a hug filled
with good energy!]
[The Shorties have
fully recovered!]
[Now that they're lively again,
what are they singing?]
[Beyonce's "Listen"]
[Became well-known as
"Dreamgirls" OST!]
They're going to be big.
I think this will be their
best performance so far.
I look forward to it and can already
picture their harmony and solo parts.
We're going back to where we
started with this performance.
We want to hear
"The Shorties are back."
With the heart before we started Round 1
and when we first came to the station...
We want no regrets with
today's performance.
[No. 3 The Shorties]
This stage was by No. 3 The Shorties.
They are the beautiful divas.
They're getting more beautiful as
they improve in singing every week.
They're really beautiful. I wonder
what their commentaries will be.
JYP?
Another broadcast told me that they
should apply lip balm on the lips.
I see that they were
careful today.
I said this because there are those that
listen to advice and those that don't.
I feel like being a judge because
The Shorties listen to advice.
I told them not to breathe a certain
way and they stopped doing that.
Ever since The Shorties made it to TOP10,
I asked, "Why force yourself to be loud?"
"Why force yourself to
sound deep and wide?"
"You didn't do that in the beginning.
Just sing as if speaking." But today...
They sang in the voice they speak in
and were also loud at the same time.
It was a proud performance that
we can present anywhere in the world.
I hope Beyonce and Destiny's Child
could listen to this as well.
I was proud of this performance
and you did very well.
JYP's score is...
I'm curious of the score.
JYP had his uniquely
satisified look... it's 96!
That's a very high score!
It's the highest so far.
Let's listen to the next one.
When you were picking an agency,
you pronounced mine as Athena.
You look like Athenians. I think I saw
something similar in the Olympics.
You look like goddesses.
You were like three goddesses
in the world of singers.
It was the best song choice.
And I think it was the best out of all
your performances this season.
I'm saying this again but
the Shorties are really good.
Thank you.
Antenna Music's score is...
After such compliments,
what is the score?
It's 95!
They have the highest score.
What will YG give?
It was hard for their voices to stand out
in last week's song with a full band.
But in this song, they were able to
sing the harmony they're best at...
And they were able to
explode at the high notes.
We three judges felt the same.
I felt cold as I was listening.
My back felt itchy.
I felt a shudder.
But since they chose JYP
five months ago...
I'll be strict in scoring.
YG's score is...
We don't know what they're
thinking now. YG's score...
It's 96!
They have the highest score at 287!
Those cheering for The Shorties can
text "3" or "The Shorties" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 3 The Shorties!
[Sam Kim made it to TOP6
last week due to the votes]
[He's on the phone with
his mother in the US]
You didn't sleep
to vote for me?
They voted for you in the US.
That's why you made it.
What time is it there?
You didn't sleep until 3 AM?
[His mother didn't sleep
to cheer him]
Tell dad that I love him too.
I once said that I'm
going to be eliminated.
But I didn't think how much that
hurt those that cheered me.
That's when I thought
I should try harder.
[Few days later at YGE]
[Sam Kim is busy practicing]
[A surprise visit by
2NE1's Dara!]
Hello...
[Dumbfounded]
[Sam Kim's blushing]
[His face is about to explode]
[He's cute]
I'm your fan...
Is there an interpreter?
[He's surprised and
forgot Korean]
Were you practicing?
[He can't breathe]
I was sleepy and tired
before she came in.
But she suddenly came in
saying she's cheering me.
I've been encouraged...
I want to do well.
[JYP gets Sam Kim's
song choice]
[What song is it?]
[JYP's "You're the One"]
What gets me excited
as a composer is...
How will he play this on the guitar
with what chords and what strokes?
My heart is already pounding.
I haven't been playing
the guitar that long.
So I think I showed
everything I could.
It's hard because I have to show
something new this time.
We'll be able to see his ability
in interpreting gayo.
[Gayo interpretation is crucial!]
I wonder but I also feel uneasy.
I made it here with votes
and not my skills.
Now I have this desire.
Even though I'm eliminated, I want to
give my best performance at least once.
So I'll do my best.
Go Sam Kim!
[No. 4 Sam Kim]
[You're the One - JYP]
This stage was by
No. 4 Sam Kim!
He must be feeling good doing ad-libs
and gestures he never did before.
Let's wait since it'll take some
time for him to come down.
He should be coming down a wire.
A great performance from a high stage.
Let's hear the commentaries
as he makes his way down.
Singing, skills, and theory can be
taught and efforts can be made.
But soul can't be taught.
Sam's a soul man.
The stage was covered in soul that
I didn't hear his singing or anything else.
The amazing thing is that Sam used
to lose breath at the end like this.
And he strained his throat
when singing the high notes.
I don't know why those two
things suddenly disappeared.
It's completely gone.
But I can't give you 100 because
you still breathe with your chest.
That's a pity but let's work
on that during JYP week.
JYP's score is...
He has soul but breathes with
his chest. What's his score?
It's 97!
- It's the highest ever!
- Thank you.
Is JYP now a Samaholic
and not a Beraholic?
Let's hear the next one.
It's not that Sam can't sing.
It could be impossible to sing well
to play such groove and sing.
I wasn't listening but dancing.
That is music's spell.
It's a great ability that a 16-year-old
can make us dance with just a guitar.
Today was the best out of
all your performances.
YG's score is...
It's another compliment.
What score did YG give?
It's 95!
You Hee-yeol is next.
Among the TOP6, when looking
just at their musical level...
I dare say Sam Kim is at the top
even though he's the youngest.
The chords, playing solo, sense
of rhythm, and everything else.
KPOP STAR is exciting because
we see the beauty of a gemstone.
We're seeing him sprout.
Compared to a gemstone, Sam Kim is
a diamond hidden in the ground.
Antenna Music's score is...
What does Antenna Music give him
with all these compliments?
It's 97!
He is first 1 with the
highest score at 289!
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "4" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 4 Sam Kim!
Is it because Sam got energy from Dara?
He beat the Shorties by 2 points with 289.
Since this order can change,
please vote if you haven't.
We are here live and now
there are only 2 teams left.
They are Heejun Han
and Kwon Jina.
How much more nervous would
they be when even I'm nervous?
Please give him a big hand.
It's No. 5 Heejun Han!
[Last week's final announcement]
[Heejun Han barely made it
from being eliminated]
[But another farewell with
friends he became close with]
All my friends were non-Koreans.
I've never interacted closely with Koreans
or even shared from the same bowl.
I've never even laughed
out loud together.
It might not seem like much
but it does build up.
Maybe because I never experienced it,
I didn't know it would build up like this.
I've trained together and was eliminated
in American Idol so I know the feeling.
Since they're Korean like me,
they're like my brothers.
And I know what they like since
we spend time together.
[He had experienced many
farewells in auditions]
[But never this warm feeling]
I knew about this and applied
but it's different here.
The difference is that it feels like
I'm pushing my brother with my hands.
[With such mixed feelings,
he's in another survival]
[His attempt at another classic ballad
Lee Seung-hwan's "For a Thousand Days"]
[Piled with music sheets]
This one isn't it...
I was very sensitive in
my choice this time.
I sang many Korean songs
from each generation.
But you never heard and
don't know gayo.
Actually I didn't have any
knowledge on gayo.
Gayo was hard for me since
I immigrated when I was 12.
The reason I keep attempting gayo...
And came on KPOP STAR is to be
loved by the Korean people.
If I'm loved for this attempt
and if it's because of gayo...
It'll be worth it.
I can see his efforts of wanting
to be loved by the Korean people.
He's been singing different
styles in every round.
Every round is like a war for him.
You can tell just by the song choices.
The title of being TOP6 or TOP4
doesn't matter anymore to me.
To put on a great stage and challenge
myself every round in my motherland...
It's very precious to me
and I'm happy.
[No. 5 Heejun Han]
[For a Thousand Days - Lee Seung-hwan]
This stage was by No. 5 Heejun Han.
It was a moving and pathetic stage.
What did the judges think? Let's
hear the commentaries and score.
Who'll go first?
You Hee-yeol.
Heejun Han's song choices
until now are significant.
He started off with James Morrison's
"You Give Me Something" in Round 1.
Then it was Kim Jo-han, Kim Bum-soo,
Kim Tae-woo, JYP, Kim Bum-soo, Regret...
Every song he sang was gayo.
Heejun's speciality is pop.
He knows that and doesn't sing it.
I understand that.
You will be a singer loved by the
Korean people so don't worry.
Antenna Music's score is...
He's born again to KPOP STAR
from American Idol.
It's 90!
YG?
You sang passionately today.
I'll be saying something different
from You Hee-yeol for the first time.
The Shorties and Sam Kim
performed before you.
I felt something when
I watched their performance.
Is there a female trio like them?
Is there any current female trio?
Is there any other singer who
could sing "Listen" like them?
Even Sam, is there anyone in Korea
with such skills at that age?
I gave them a generous score
because of such thoughts.
Heejun sings very well
because of experience.
But while listening, I wonder how
Lee Seung-hwan would sing this.
How would Sung Si-kyung sing this?
I can't help but compare him.
I had this question if Heejun
sang this better or not.
Remember when I asked
Who are you?
Rather than advancing or
becoming the winner...
If you want to be at the top,
like I always told you...
You need your own
powerful weapon.
YG's score is...
YG's score...
It's 85!
Next is JYP.
You went all out in singing
"I'm free" in the middle.
But you didn't look free.
You don't look free whether you sing
pop or ballad, talk, laugh, or cry.
You're being cautious.
You think and worry.
What can make you relaxed?
When YG asked who you are last time,
that question is still hanging over me.
This isn't a problem
regarding your singing.
The powerful weapon YG talked about
is you, Heejun. But who are you?
What is your voice? Your singing style?
What is your expression when you speak?
Are you bright and frivolous
or cautious? I'm not sure.
That is what I think, but
I was just speaking my mind.
That was a pity.
My score is...
JYP's score...
It's 84!
His score is 259.
Those cheering for Heejun Han can
text "5" or "Heejun Han" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 5 Heejun Han!
- I'm curious of Kwon Jina's choice.
- It's 2NE1's "I Don't Care."
"I Don't Care"?
I don't know if it'll be a tasty
song if it's mixed with you.
What I want to hear from you,
everything was good until now...
But you need something new.
Since you've been singing gayo,
I think pop isn't a bad idea.
I also agree with him that
I need something new.
But I'm worried if
I can do well.
[Her first attempt in pop
after thinking it over!]
[He get's Kwon Jina's
song choice]
Does she know this song?
She's finally going head on.
[Sting's "Fields of Gold" released in
1992 even before she was born]
[Remakes by many female musicians
including Eva Cassidy are well-known]
Her arrangements for gayo
had the four steps.
But this song doesn't have that.
It just flows.
I'm not sure if she can
make this song her own.
This is my first attempt in pop.
I'm at a loss since I need to prepare
many things with less than a week left.
[She tries to devote herself to
practicing but her worries linger]
[2NE1's Minzy]
[Frozen]
I watched the show and
saw you dancing.
[The growling goddess]
You were good.
You have talent.
Call me if you need help.
I'll give you lessons.
[A promise by dancing queen
Minzy for lessons!]
[Should I dance next?]
Any hardships while
doing the live show?
I had many compliments so...
- You're burdened?
- Yes, I am.
It's all in how you look at it.
Instead of thinking, "I'm going to do well"
or "I'm going to do it no matter what"...
If you just enjoy it
and have fun...
You'll get better results than when
you thought, "I should do well."
Have peace of mind and enjoy.
Thank you.
I'm not washing my hand!
[She blew her worries away
with support from Minzy!]
I look forward to it
the most because...
It'll be very different from what
she had shown until now.
I'm a bit worried because it's going
to be different from what I've shown.
I think it will be a
moving performance.
[No. 6 Kwon Jina]
This stage was by
No. 6 Kwon Jina.
What did the judges think of
Kwon Jina's performance?
I don't need to listen to JYP.
I can tell just by his looks.
But let's hear him first to
see if my hunch is correct.
If there's a great singing instructor
whether it's in the US or England...
I sign up several months in advance
and get lessons. I still do that.
All those great instructors have
different teaching methods.
But the one common thing is...
We are told to relax when singing,
especially the high notes.
Every instructor says
that same thing.
Not a single one of Kwon Jina's muscles
are stiff when singing the high notes.
Thus you sing with such skill.
This song is hard.
Sting's songs are hard.
It starts in minor and ends in major.
The eight measures go on like that.
So the song has this strange mood,
but you even do that perfectly.
I listened as a fan
this time around.
JYP's score is...
What's JYP's score?
He said he's her fan.
It's 96!
Next is YG.
Even though this is a live show,
I'm going to be honest in judging.
As a fan of Kwon Jina...
Today's performance wasn't
that impressive for me.
It's because this is your first attempt in
pop and it must've been a difficult task.
Since you sang gayo well, I thought
maybe you only did what you're good at.
When you sang Sting's song, I was thinking,
"Let's see how she sings this one."
Her voice reminded me of Adele or Laura
even though the voice is different.
Her strength is taking any genre
and making it her own.
Today's pop was less impressive
than the gayo last week...
But I'll give a generous score
since this was your first attempt.
YG's score is...
It was a different commentary
but what is YG's score?
It's going up.
It's 90!
Next is Antenna Music's
You Hee-yeol.
No matter which singer sings
Sting's "Fields of Gold"...
The song itself wasn't made
to captivate us.
Let's say we were to listen to this at
home at night and not at an audition.
It'll make our hearts sink.
Kwon Jina is very good at
interpreting this song.
She's good with songs that have groove
but this song's melody is monotonous.
Yet she captivates us with
her voice with just a guitar.
I want to believe in
that power of music.
Antenna Music's score is...
She makes people's heart sink
but what is her score?
It's 96!
Her total score is 282.
Those cheering for Kwon Jina can
text "6" or "Kwon Jina" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 6 Kwon Jina!
That was like a sunrise. The TOP6
performances ended with Kwon Jina.
Sam Kim is currently first
with a score of 289.
But your votes can change the order.
If you haven't voted, please do so now.
They barely had time to practice
but even prepared a special stage.
Looking forward to the stage
prepared by the finalists?
Let's watch it now!
[1, 2, 3, 4 - Lee Hi]
I won't pity you anymore
I'm out of coins to continue this love game
It's game over like the arcades
I'm way out of your league
Like breaking a ten for a dime
(It's 50 cents) Actually it's a dollar
Got it? I'm way out of your league
This is KPOP STAR Season 3
broadcasting to you live.
They sang Lee Hi's "1, 2, 3, 4"
since this is YG week.
She's a YG artist and also
their senior in KPOP STAR.
There's not much time
left for voting.
Your votes are 40% and will
determine their fate.
Voting will end soon.
Text and mobile messenger
voting will end in 1 minute!
[No. 1 Almeng]
[No. 2 Bernard Park]
[No. 3 The Shorties]
[No. 4 Sam Kim]
[No. 5 Heejun Han]
[No. 6 Kwon Jina]
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[Live from Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is KPOP STAR Season 3
broadcast to you live.
The announcements remain.
It was a fierce competition
reminding us of the finals.
Judges' score 60% and viewers' vote 40%
are calculated for the total score.
Among the six finalists, only four will
advance to next week's TOP4 stage.
Two from among them will
depart from KPOP STAR.
The names of those that passed are in an
envelope given to me and the three judges.
I haven't opened mine and
neither have they.
We will now announce
the final result.
Who will go first?
- I'll open my envelope.
- JYP will open his.
He has a smile on his face.
So who passed?
The first one who passed is the
one I gave the highest score.
- Who is that?
- Sam Kim.
- Congratulations.
- It's Sam Kim!
The first to advance
to TOP4 is Sam Kim.
Out of the total score,
he's the first to advance.
Please move to the winners seat.
Who'll announce the second?
- I'll go next.
- YG, please open it.
That's a meaningful smile.
I wonder what that
smile means.
I held back the score for this
person. The second finalist is...
- Who is it?
- Kwon Jina.
It's Kwon Jina!
She's the second to advance
to next week's TOP4 stage.
Congratulations Kwon Jina.
Please move to the winners seat.
Now only two teams remain.
Only two from the four. Half will
pass and half will be eliminated.
You Hee-yeol will
announce the third.
Before I open it, I thought
about this at home.
I can't imagine who among
the TOP6 will be eliminated.
Can you make a guess now?
Even pro musicians can't satisfy viewers
every week by arranging a new song.
I applaud them for
overcoming such hardships.
Let's give them a round of applause.
You are already future K-pop stars.
But half will remain and half will depart.
You Hee-yeol, please make the announcement.
He seems a little surprised.
Who is it, You Hee-yeol?
The TOP4 finalist is...
Before I announce it, I want to
say that all of you did well.
- The TOP4 finalist is...
- The third finalist is...
- The Shorties.
- The Shorties!
They received a lot of
compliments today.
The Shorties are the third to advance.
Please move to the winners seat.
There wasn't much difference
in how the viewers thought.
Now only one seat remains for
next week's TOP4 live stage.
From among Heejun Han,
Bernard Park, and Almeng...
Only one will advance to
next week's live show.
The remaining two will
unfortunately depart.
I don't know what you think.
The last envelope is
in my hand.
Even the judges don't know.
The total score from judges' score 60%
and real-time viewers' vote 40%...
I will announce the
last TOP4 finalist.
Who do you think it is?
All of you are cheering but
I didn't understand a single word.
I will now open it.
The result is out.
The last one from among the three that
will advance to next week's live show is...
Please congratulate this person
for all those hardships.
Please congratulate this
person with a warm applause.
The last TOP4 finalist is...
Bernard Park!
Congratulations!
He remained steadfast and
attempted a Korean gayo.
He must have not understood
the lyrics but tried to do so.
In the end, he dramatically
advanced to TOP4.
Please gather everyone.
Kwon Jina and the Shorties are
encouraging the eliminated with tears.
Would one of the judges say
something for the eliminated?
JYP?
The judges and viewers won't remember
what place you got in a few years.
What's important is the song and
performance you're giving.
No one will remember what
place you got in a few years.
Try harder with what
you learned here.
Go Heejun and Almeng!
Do your best.
Thank you.
Almeng and Heejun Han were
shockingly eliminated.
Tune in to next week's live show.
Look forward to what changes there
will be since next is JYP week.
This was KPOP STAR Season 3, a real
audition where dreams turn into reality.