[Broadcast live from
SBS Prism Tower]
[Ten dreams in one place]
Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2!
I introduce to you those that
advanced to the live broadcast.
Choi Ye-geun and
Akdong Musician!
Raccoon Boys and
Lee Jin-woo!
Andrew Choi and
2,000 won!
Bang Ye-dam and
Sung Soo-jin!
And the girl group, YouU!
Another warm applause to the
9 teams that made it here!
Hello, I'm the MC for KPOP
STAR Season 2, Yoon Do-hyun.
Many talented people were
also discovered in Season 2.
They started a lot of talk and we
finally begin the live broadcast!
After 7 months, they will battle
to become the next K-pop star.
I introduce the 3 judges that will
judge and appreciate their music.
BoA of SM!
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
Looking sharp.
- First, BoA.
- Yes.
- It's been a while.
- Same here.
- I only saw you on TV.
- I only heard your voice.
You must have gotten very
close with them until now.
How do you feel
seeing them now?
I remember the good and
bad times we went through.
I'm surprised at how classy they
are. They look like celebrities.
Most of all, Ye-dam
got a haricut.
Yes, he did.
- I look forward to it.
- I think he got cuter.
And Yang Hyun-suk?
After 7 months, do you have
any advice for the finalists?
This is their first
ever live broadcast.
I don't need to tell them
to not tremble here.
Even existing singers tremble
and I'm trembling up here too.
But keep in mind that twists
and miracles come from tension.
It's okay if you tremble. We look
forward to a miraculous stage.
Thank you for the advice.
And Park Jin-young?
Do-yeon, unfortunately,
decided to withdraw.
I heard the judges had a
long emergency meeting.
Could I ask about the
outcome of that meeting?
We were at a loss since
it happened suddenly.
Because we need
10 finalists...
The three of us gathered
and it took a long time.
Fortunately, the three of
us picked the same person.
Among the two left from
the consolation match...
Our decision was based on potential for
growth since that's important here.
I'm curious.
Now I reveal the result
of their meeting.
We need to discuss if we'll
consider another candidate.
Only Yoon Joo-suk and
Shin Ji-hoon were eliminated.
We need to pick
one of them.
If the three of you disagree,
there will be another rematch.
Will it be Yoon Joo-suk
who is well-developed?
Or Shin Ji-hoon who is
a diamond in the rough?
[Who did they choose?]
The three of us had
a long discussion.
I choose...
Looking at their potential for
growth, I also choose...
I also choose...
[The two judges
are in agreement]
I feel the same.
[YG also makes the
same decision!]
[Who did they decide on?]
- Hello?
- Hello.
[The last finalist
Shin Ji-hoon]
We chose Shin-Ji hoon
from the two because...
Of her potential
for growth.
That standard never
changed in KPOP STAR.
Since you barely made it...
Try hard to show a good stage
where you move many people.
I'll do my best so the judges who
picked me again will not regret it.
Shin Ji-hoon is our
last TOP10 finalist!
Congratulations!
Please come to the front.
You must be very happy.
Another round of applause
for our TOP10 finalists!
I'm very proud to see
our TOP10 finalists.
Aren't you curious
how they will battle?
The live broadcast stage is
a prelude to becoming a pro.
And it maximizes the
beauty of survival.
Let's watch how they
were until now.
The day of the TOP10
admission ceremony.
KPOP STAR training system
for the live broadcast!
The contestants are amazed
at their accommodation.
[Spacious accommodation
for the 8 male contestants!]
[Raccoon Boys and
Bang Ye-dam's room]
Individual beds and gifts to
make themselves feel at home.
Is this the closet?
[Eye opener]
You could even
sleep here.
[Female contestants arrive
at their accommodation!]
[Soo-hyun and
Ye-geun's room]
[Gifts on their beds!]
[Clothes according
to personality]
It's pretty.
- We have the biggest room?
- Yes.
Is this ours?
This is great!
[Headphones for practice]
- This is awesome!
- It's so pretty!
[Skin care cosmetics]
[That evening...]
[They write their resolution]
I believe we will get what
we deserve if we try hard.
[They stuck theirs
on the ceiling]
I'll go on a diet, be diligent,
and make it to TOP3. Yeah!
Before I left, my mother
put a letter in my pocket.
It gives me strength.
I'll try hard to make you
proud. I love you, mom.
- Good night.
- Turn off the lights.
Night.
[As soon as the
lights are off...]
[Ten dreams toward
being a K-pop star]
We're choosing a K-pop
star on this program.
Preparations for becoming
a star officially begin.
I'll be giving you
medical treatment.
Their voices will be
cared for systematically.
Professional trainers from the
3 agencies will train them
To have the best
live broadcast.
[Jang Jin-young
SM vocal trainer]
[Lee Soo-jung
JYP vocal trainer]
[Choi Won-suk
YG vocal trainer]
[Mq - rap trainer]
[Lee Jae-wook
YG dance trainer]
[Beat Burger
SM dance trainer]
[Chung Jae-yong
WaWa Dancer]
They go all out on practicing for
the eagerly-anticipated day.
But one day...
I, Yoon Do-hyun, had a
special meeting with them.
The first live broadcast...
Will be very interesting.
[A special method?]
It will be a 1:1 battle!
You don't believe me?
I was surprised.
"What battle?"
Even professional singers
compete every day on stage.
The fierce contests will take them
closer to the professional world.
This is a process they
must go through.
You have to pick
your opponent.
Who against who? What team
against another team?
You get to pick the
opponent you'll battle.
Who wants to go first?
Who will volunteer...
Oh? Shin Ji-hoon
is going first.
Alright, come here.
Please choose.
[The fated moment]
Alright!
Please choose one.
She chose one.
Untie it first.
One of you will
battle her.
It's Raccoon Boys!
[Shin Ji-hoon vs Raccoon Boys]
[The others cheer]
[Raccoon Boys are panicking]
I'm afraid.
I thought it would be
great if it wasn't us.
But we're doing a battle
on live broadcast?
Please choose carefully.
[Who will go against
Akdong Musician?]
Guess who by
their reaction.
It's Andrew Choi!
[His face turned pale]
- It's over for us.
- How can it be him?
They're roommates.
He always does this.
- I'm getting goosebumps.
- He always does this.
Ye-dam, please choose.
I'm excited and nervous.
Please choose carefully.
[Who is it?]
Please show them.
[Lee Jin-woo?]
[2,000 won?]
Please show them.
It's 2,000 won!
[Discouraged]
[They're close but
have to battle!]
[YouU's turn!]
Is that it?
[Only 3 female
soloists remain!]
[They take a peek]
[Startled]
[What does their
reaction mean?]
Who is it?
[YouU vs Sung Soo-jin]
- We share the same room.
- You're in the same room?
I wonder what you'll talk about
at night when it's quiet...
On the night before
the live broadcast.
Now, Choi Ye-geun and
Lee Jin-woo are left.
It's like a bolt
from the blue.
My entire body
is trembling.
I was about to cry
when I got picked.
Let's do it,
Choi Ye-geun!
[The immense pressure!]
As you just watched, it's
going to be a 1:1 battle.
The finalists chose
their own opponents.
The first live broadcast will
air this week and next week.
3 groups will
battle this week.
Only 3 will pass
after the battle.
Those who pass go
to the next round.
Those who lost are in
danger of elimination.
After all the battles finish,
of the 5 teams that lost...
Two teams with the highest
viewers' votes will pass.
And one team with a
wildcard will pass.
To have a fair voting count,
it will be done in sections.
Votes will only be counted
during two battles.
You can vote for a certain
finalist only at that time.
I will tell you the order
of the 1:1 battle again.
The 1st battle will be dark
horse, No. 1 Lee Jin-woo.
And consistent genius,
No. 2 Choi Ye-geun.
It won't be an
easy battle.
2nd battle is KPOP STAR's
girl group, No. 3 YouU.
And with an indomitable
spirit, No. 4 Sung Soo-jin.
We look forward to it since
their colors are different.
3rd battle is national sibling,
No. 5 Akdong Musician.
And he who sways women's
hearts, No. 6 Andrew Choi.
He's No. 6. Real musicians
will have a head-to-head battle.
They're singing songs related to
their dreams. Looking forward to it.
Judges' commentaries are important
as well as the viewers' votes.
Please place your votes
actively and carefully.
Boom will explain the
voting system in detail.
Hi, I'm MC Boom.
Season 2 introduces
a 1:1 battle system.
I'm also curious who will
pass in the 1st broadcast.
If you want to see your
favorite in the next round...
You must vote.
First, select the messaging
icon and text #0606.
Type their name or number in
the message and press send.
Remember one thing.
You can vote for more
than one person.
But you can't vote multiple
times for the same person.
You can also vote via
mobile messaging.
KPOP STAR Season 2
begins now!
Did all of you get it?
The names must be in Korean,
especially the girl group.
Since voting is in sections, vote
when your favorite is battling.
Their fate is in your hands,
and now we begin the battle.
1st group is Lee Jin-woo
and Choi Ye-geun.
Voting will also
begin now.
[Lee Jin-woo vs Choi Ye-geun]
I felt hopeless and
didn't know what to do.
I knew it won't be easy,
but my opponent is...
I don't know. She's
like a genius.
She has the ability to arrange
and such voice at that age.
She's explosive and
has great talent.
Jin-woo practices even
when we're resting.
She practices late at night
when everyone went home.
Lee Jin-woo and
Choi Ye-geun.
Hard worker vs genius?
I don't know
who will win.
From what we've seen yet,
Ye-geun is much superior.
But Jin-woo's last
stage was shocking.
Jin-woo competes with a voice
that moves people's hearts.
I wanted to sing a gayo where
I could convey the lyrics.
[What song did the genius
and hard worker choose?]
[A plaintive breakup song
Kim Bum-soo's "Sad Inflection"]
[The best song to beat
her greatest opponent!]
I only thought of making
it to the live broadcast.
Who's less tense and does
better is more important.
I hope I go to
the next round.
[No. 1 Lee Jin-woo]
[Sad Inflection - Kim Bum-soo]
Another hand since she must've
been nervous for going first.
This stage was by
No. 1 Lee Jin-woo.
Choi Ye-geun is
a born genius.
Her arrangements
are unexpected.
What's even amazing
is that she's 17.
I did many arrangements
while on KPOP STAR.
I'm ashamed because
I can't read music.
[She can't read music
but arranges?]
[How does she arrange?]
I use symbols only
I understand.
[Ad-lib line is
a wavy line]
[Words get bigger
for crescendo]
[Genius's arrangement notes
realized through self-study]
My original dream was
to be a dancing singer.
There used to be a huge
mirror in the house.
I always danced and
practiced in front of it.
Seeing BoA sing and dance on
television gave me that dream.
So the music I
chose is BoA's...
"Girls on Top".
I'm getting scared.
Why my song again?
It's unpredictable.
I'm going to show you a
different style than before.
Please be kind and
look forward to it.
[No. 2 Choi Ye-geun]
[Girls on Top - BoA]
This was an intense
stage by Choi Ye-geun.
Who will be the victor
of this 1:1 battle?
I watched them during rehearsal,
but they were more nervous now.
What do the judges think?
Let's hear the commentary.
You must've been very nervous
since you were first today.
And you didn't show 100%
of your skills due to that.
In Jin-woo's case,
who started first...
The live broadcast could be
called the battle of nerves.
Jin-woo chose a song true to
her feelings to do well, but...
Your will was too far ahead,
and during the middle break...
You had to get the correct
pitch during the silence.
It's a pity how the sound
and voice didn't match.
My song was reinterpreted
by Choi Ye-geun.
I was amazed at how you
made it funky in a rock style.
I never saw you dance
while singing.
It was good to see you
take on a new challenge.
I felt, "She has nerves of
steel and doesn't tremble."
I enjoyed it.
That was BoA's commentary.
Lee Jin-woo, your
clothes are beautiful.
The clothes look good on
you, but most importantly...
The song didn't suit you.
On the other hand, I wanted
Ye-geun to wear slimmer clothes.
Just as Bang Ye-dam
sang without the guitar...
You dancing while singing
without the keyboard...
Shocked me as much
as Bang Ye-dam did.
The clothes didn't suit
you, but the song did.
The clothes and song were
opposite for the both of you.
Good job.
That was YG's
opinion. And JYP?
I looked forward to
this battle the most.
It was a close match
as expected.
They said many good things
so I'll say some bad things.
I was worried when Jin-woo
started singing because...
Her shoulders were up
the moment she started.
It's impossible to have a
good sound in that position.
If you were relaxed, you could have
done that at an important point.
Because you were tense
from the beginning...
It made no difference
later at the climax.
You tried to be clear
with your pronunciation.
You couldn't convey the feeling
since it didn't feel like speaking.
It's a pity that you
tried to do too well.
But your explosiveness at
the high notes were great.
I think differently from
YG about Choi Ye-geun.
It was great when you were
at the keyboard. It was soulful.
It changed to pop later, but
you still sang in soul.
You were behind
the beats.
Important thing is to be in
rhythm, not how well you sing.
You tried to show many things
and didn't understand the genre.
Thank you very much.
As much as they were first,
they must've been nervous.
We heard some mixed
commentaries.
Who is the victor
of this battle?
Please announce the victor.
I'll go first.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
- Choi Ye-geun.
- It's Choi Ye-geun!
YG chose Choi Ye-geun.
Must feel stable.
Next?
The victor chosen
by SM is...
SM chooses...
- The victor is Choi Ye-geun.
- It's Choi Ye-geun!
Now it's decided that she
goes to the next round.
And who did you
choose, JYP?
JYP also chose
Choi Ye-geun.
Choi Ye-geun is the 1st
to make it to the TOP8.
Congratulations!
Jin-woo put on a great
stage though nervous.
Unfortunately, you lost
but it's not the end.
This isn't the final decision.
After next week's battle...
You have a chance to return
and there's the viewers' votes.
So have hope.
They were tense
the 1st battle.
The 2nd 1:1 battle is
YouU and Sung Soo-jin.
[YouU vs Sung Soo-jin]
Five against one?
You can't underestimate even
Sung Soo-jin's presence.
This happened since
you chose me!
I'm just imitating.
She's worried and afraid
that she's up against us.
Why?
First, there's five of us...
Is it okay for me
to say this?
These pretty girls...
She said it!
She said why does she have
to go against pretty girls.
We don't think so.
We prepared
2NE1's "Ugly".
There was a time when
we were all ugly.
Including KPOP STAR, I went
to more than 50 auditions.
There was a time when
I was fat and ugly.
I didn't know how to make
myself pretty and shut myself.
I couldn't say that I
wanted to be a singer.
I almost debuted
in a girl group.
I was treated as an
invisible person.
Each of us came
together as a group.
After coming together, I think
we are a more powerful group.
I don't think I could
come this far alone.
We really practiced a lot.
We all improved and
I think we will win.
We could win
with our energy.
Soo-jin, let's battle
out of good will.
Let's go, YouU!
[No. 3 YouU]
[Ugly - 2NE1]
Look at the stage! Pay attention
As the day goes by, so does tension
No one can stop us
(I got a boy) Like Girl's Generation!
Hey Hey, I'm 15 years old
I get a five-star rating
Even though I'm young
My potential is like my height, Uh!
No need for words, look here
We will seduce you secretly
They're KPOP STAR's girl group.
Their group dance was impressive.
This stage was by
No. 3 YouU.
I went to 30th place.
Those who started with me
came out on television.
"This could happen." They
were walking a different path.
I envied them.
Now that I'm doing that,
I feel very happy.
I always thought this was
the best she could do.
Since Season 1 so...
I was sure that it wouldn't
be easy for you to change.
But you did really well
and showed I was wrong.
I never heard that
many compliments.
I felt great.
My mother cried after
I made it to the TOP10.
She didn't want me to have a
hard time, but she was pleased.
I'm curious how you
will sing ballads.
I will be singing
Ne-Yo's "So Sick".
I'm taking this challenge since
many doubt if I could sing R&B.
Never expected it, huh?
I hope she can show again this
time that that wasn't everything.
I now believe that
she could do it.
What I couldn't do last season,
I hope to do more this season.
[No. 4 Sung Soo-jin]
[So Sick - Ne-Yo]
Soo-jin showed a new side.
YouU, please join her.
Their battle ended.
We're curious of the judges'
commentary. Let's hear them.
I'll go first.
Sung Soo-jin amazes
me after every round.
I didn't expect you to
sing "So Sick" this well.
When you sang "Invitation",
you were very attractive.
Today, you were able to
show the song's features.
YouU did as much
as expected.
But I want to give some advice
apart from your performance.
When you practiced at YG,
you didn't get good results.
You got good results when
you practiced for the rematch.
Today's stage was good,
but there's one problem.
You tried to show
too many things.
2NE1's charm is enjoying
it with less choreography.
You weren't able to enjoy since
there was a lot of choreography.
I could say that since you're
my singers. You both did well.
That was YG's commentary.
Let's hear the next one.
What amazed me about YouU is
that So-yeon's singing improved.
The ones who improve after
every round are different.
I think today's stage was
difficult for Song Ha-ye.
You sang the high notes alone
and were in a hurry later.
I hope your skills as a team
improve to share the burden.
I liked the performance where
the others held a member's mike.
Sung Soo-jin removed the old
feel and is maintaining it well.
Your voice is in a bad condition, but
you delivered your charming voice.
The dance was unexpected, but
I liked the moves. I enjoyed it.
That was BoA's commentary.
Last is JYP's commentary.
When we start a new girl group or
boy band, they're somewhat formed.
They're almost ready
before they start.
We saw YouU being formed
and will have shortcomings.
Regardless of your shortcomings,
your improvements draw us in.
There's this personal
appeal that pulls us in.
Sung Soo-jin did
very well today.
Until the high notes.
You did well until then.
But your throat
hurts, right?
You knew you couldn't
sing the high notes.
You started to squeeze it out
thinking you can't do it.
The problem was your
old habits resurfaced.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Both YouU and Sung Soo-jin
received good commentaries.
Let's hear the announcement
for the victor of this battle.
I'll go first.
The victor
chosen by SM...
It was hard to choose.
The victor is YouU.
Congratulations, YouU!
BoA chose YouU.
Next?
You would have anticipated this
after hearing my commentary.
The victor
chosen by YG...
YG chose...
Do you know
who it is?
- Sung Soo-jin.
- It's Sung Soo-jin!
Now it all depends on JYP's
choice. You must feel burdened.
It was very hard
for me to choose.
Since I need to choose,
after some hesitation...
Who am I curious about? Who
do I want to see improved?
- The victor chosen by JYP...
- The victor is...
- YouU.
- Congratulations, YouU!
They pass to the
next round.
Congratulations.
I see they're happy.
Soo-jin, don't be disappointed.
You still have a chance.
You will get another chance
through the viewers' votes.
And also through the
judges' wildcard.
Good job on the
splendid battle.
The next 1:1 battle is between
Akdong Musician and Andrew Choi.
[Akdong Musician vs Andrew Choi]
I resented my hand for
pulling out his name.
We're against Andrew,
the best in ad-lib.
[Even the judges are speechless
at this unpredictable battle]
The factor that decides
this battle is clear.
It all depends on the song
chosen by Akdong Musician.
[What will they sing?]
[Lee Soo-hyun (3)]
[Lee Chan-hyuk (6)]
My dream was to be a
celebrity since a child.
I liked music
since I was young.
I feel great when
people watch me.
I wanted to be a dancing singer
then someone who sang ballads.
My dream of being a
singer didn't change.
I liked drawing, dancing, and
wasn't bad at my studies.
As I started composing, we applied
for KPOP STAR and reached TOP10.
Our dream is getting bigger.
I want to be a singer
and a songwriter.
Now my dream is certain.
The song we're singing
is "Is It Ramen?".
They told us after picking
us at the battle audition...
"Do what you're good at
and feel confident about."
"Is It Ramen?"
popped up.
I want ramen now.
There's going to be a
difference on the big stage.
The music stays, but other
things must be strengthened.
I think our colors have
to stand out more.
I'm drawing characters
to be shown on screen.
We lost to Ye-dam at
the battle audition.
Since we tasted defeat,
we don't want to lose.
We want our stage like
that in rounds 1 and 2.
[No. 5 Akdong Musician]
[Is It Ramen? - own song]
I'm hungry. Hey, Lee Soo,
Is there anything to eat?
Let's see what we have
Oh! We have ramen again?
I don't remember what I did
Is there a morning for me?
I woke up
Around 12PM
Today is Confession Day
Everyone is confessing
I confessed my faults
To my friend
I slept over 12 hours but still sleepy
Every day's the same, I'm sick of myself
I'm tired of walking so I lay down
I don't need a rag since it's clean
It's cleaning. One folded egg
A welcome sight on the table
It's a pie in the sky
I open the cupboard every day
I find yesterday's half-eaten
Is it ramen? Is it ramen?
Is it ramen? (My lunch today is)
Is it ramen?
I don't remember what I did
Is there a morning for me?
I woke up around 12PM
(Through the curtains)
The sun shines
I'm excited
I didn't brush my teeth and played
I regret it when it's night
This is not how I feel
So many things to do
I want to put my mind
Spend a meaningful minute
Television is on all day
It's filled with laughter
My reflection on the television
I'm gradually becoming obese
My future being like
A swollen
Is it ramen? Is it ramen?
Is it ramen?
Heartburn (My lunch today is)
Is it ramen? Is it only me?
If it's a (dream) (Let's Go!)
Ramen's ready!
They used their ace in the hole
by singing their own song.
This stage was by No. 5
Akdong Musician.
[The next day after
choosing opponents]
The first day was
very awkward.
[Andrew doing vocal exercise
amidst the awkward atmosphere]
He's doing that. Maybe he was
trying to make me feel small.
No! That's not it!
I believe you
will do well!
[His parents cheer
him from the States]
I prepared G-Dragon's
"That XX".
This is in a funky style,
but I changed it to R&B.
Women will go wild.
I want to sing
like that too.
[Highest compliment]
[No. 6 Andrew Choi]
[That XX - G-Dragon]
Andrew Choi has a voice
that sways women's hearts.
Can he pass beating
Akdong Musician?
Let's hear the commentary from
the judges on their thoughts.
How Akdong Musician made the
stage into a pot looked cute.
It was good to see your
bright energies again.
I was able to hear Soo-hyun's
high notes. I enjoyed it.
Andrew Choi has a sweet
voice and it was good.
I think you had fear in
the high notes midway.
You were slightly off key, but
I applaud you for finishing it.
It's hard to compare them since
they have different charms.
This is really hard.
BoA's commentary
was that it was hard.
They're evenly matched.
Next commentary?
Many viewers, including myself,
waited for your mischievous side.
You expressed "12PM" in
the lyrics as "12 hours".
"Half-eaten" and "My future
is like this swollen ramen."
The lyrics are very witty
and they are at key places.
It has to come together
and move the people.
But it wasn't as
moving as expected.
The most touching song Andrew
sang was BoA's "Only One".
But G-Dragon's "That XX"
was more touching for me.
Since BoA's a good singer, and
you sang in a different style...
G-Dragon's a rapper. His
individuality is in his songs.
Just as JYP said, I don't
know if his voice was open.
But I like those high
notes that were closed.
I almost had the chills
because it was good.
I was thankful there was someone
who could express it like this.
I enjoyed it.
Good job.
That was some good
commentary he received.
Next is by JYP.
Akdong Musician's songs
always make me tilt my head.
The 2nd chord in the beginning
is something composers don't use.
I always spend 30 seconds,
"What was that chord?"
Even now, I'm not sure.
Except for that, the rest
are in a money chord.
The rest are in a popular form
except for that slight twist.
It's an exceptional
skill in composition.
High chances of getting a
hit song by doing that.
From that view, it
was well-composed.
You composed well, but
one unfortunate thing...
We couldn't understand it
until we read the lyrics.
There were too many words.
Next time, make it less.
So we don't need to read the
lyrics. It's a waste of good lyrics.
I personally root
for Andrew Choi.
I also want to continue
singing on stage.
I want to see you on
stage as a great singer.
One of the reasons why
that never happened...
Singing with your throat narrows
the amount of people you can move.
If you open your voice,
you have no weaknesses.
Thank you very much.
JYP liked them both, but
they had some to be desired.
Please tell me later
what that chord was.
Please announce the
victor of this battle.
JYP told Minh Son Ha and
Andrew to open their voice.
I want JYP to
open his heart.
The victor
chosen by YG...
You might have guessed.
It's Andrew Choi.
Congratulations, Andrew Choi!
He was chosen by YG.
He got one.
Next please.
I had to consider the music and
composition for Akdong Musician.
It's hard to decide who's
better with singing alone.
Considering music and composition,
JYP choses Akdong Musician.
It's Akdong Musician!
It's neck and neck!
It now depends on
BoA who passes.
She already decided,
but I'm curious.
The victor
chosen by SM...
The victor is...
Andrew Choi.
Congratulations, Andrew Choi!
He goes to the next round.
Akdong Musician also put
on a fun, good stage.
Unfortunately, you lost but
it's too early to give up.
The viewers' votes will decide if
Akdong Musician passes or not.
Voting for the 3rd battle
will end in a moment.
This ends the battle for
the six contestants.
Three teams passed
after the three battles.
Let's watch the clip.
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
[Broadcast live from
SBS Prism Tower]
Congratulations!
After the three battles,
three teams have passed.
Choi Ye-geun, YouU, and
Andrew Choi passed.
Unfortunately, Jin-woo, Soo-jin, and
Akdong Musician were defeated.
But the decision isn't final.
After the four teams'
battle next week...
The five defeated teams get
a chance via viewers' votes.
Please look forward to
next week's face-off.
Next week, we have Bang
Ye-dam, 2,000 won...
Raccoon Boys and
Shin Ji-hoon.
See you next week!
Goodbye.
[TOP8 decided next week]