[After last week's broadcast]
[The judges gather]
If there are any tasks to
check last, discuss them...
Those that got good comments,
have a low chance of success.
They shouldn't be singing in a
register they're comfortable in.
Each of them has to show
the limits of their skills.
- Then we can cast them.
- That's right.
[Casting!!]
The casting audition
finally begins.
We will give the TOP5
a casting mission.
- It's ominous!
- What is that?
Casting mission?
TOP5 Raccoon Boys
Casting Mission
We want to confirm these if
we want them as our singer.
That is their mission.
I want to hear Soo-hyun and
Chan-hyuk's voices closely.
Do you know this
song? I don't!
Do you know?
They kept in tune with eye contact
before, but now they don't do that.
They need a song with
a strong offensive.
I want to hear Andrew sing
"When I Was Your Man".
I'm worried that Koreans won't be
immersed if it's an unknown song.
He needs a popular song
that can reach everyone.
How about "Red Dragonfly"?
[Ye-dam is going to sing
Cho Yong-pil's classic?]
This is hard.
They need sincerity in this
battle and not showmanship.
It's hard because they
sound like existing singers.
Then Hyo-bin has to
sing halfheartedly.
[This is hard]
It's going to be a very
difficult stage because...
They have to do what we ask
and not what they're good at.
Watching to cast and watching
to judge is clearly different.
They need to show their
skills, not a good stage.
How much of the mission can
they complete in a week?
That will be our standard
in the casting audition.
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2!
I announce the TOP5 that will
take on each other to get casted!
First, they are the dark horse
of live broadcast, 2,000 won!
I look forward
to their stage.
Teenage singer-songwriter threatening
the gayo world, Akdong Musician!
They look nice in
matching outfits.
He always makes a new
record every round.
He is the youngest TOP10
finalist, Bang Ye-dam!
What a cute walk.
Next is KPOP STAR's greatest
harmony, Raccoon Boys!
Will they show some
great harmony today?
Sentimental vocalist continuing
his challenge, Andrew Choi!
What a cool walk.
Another round of applause
for the TOP5 that will battle.
Hi, I'm the MC, Yoon Do-hyun,
for KPOP STAR Season 2.
KPOP STAR's live broadcast
started out with ten teams.
Through the 1:1 battle
the past four weeks...
Five teams were eliminated
and only the TOP5 remain.
The TOP5 will not
have a 1:1 battle.
It will be done in
a different way.
The TOP5 were given
a special mission.
I will tell you
what it is later.
Also look forward to the special
stage the TOP5 prepared.
The pressure will be
great for them.
I introduce the judges that
will determine their fate.
BoA of SM!
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
The crowd's going wild.
- BoA?
- Yes?
I heard today's battle isn't
1:1 but a different method.
May I ask what it is?
Scoring is back and that means
we expect a fierce battle.
Their total score will be our
scores plus the viewers' votes.
The four teams with the highest
scores will get casted.
The one team with the lowest score
won't get casted and will be eliminated.
I see. That means the
casting audition begins.
JYP, I heard they have a special
mission. Could you tell us?
We created missions to check last
what we want in them as our singers.
What missions...
We chose songs that will draw
out what we want to confirm.
Ah, I see.
Lastly, YG.
The 3 agencies will be casting...
Many of your fans are here.
Why don't you greet
your fans first?
You're a star.
The contestants are desperate since
the 3 agencies will be casting.
Do you have any advice, request
or encouragement for them?
In Season 1, we already expected a
winner like Lee Hi and Park Ji-min.
Every time I speak with BoA or
JYP before coming up here...
We can't anticipate who will be
eliminated and who will win.
I want them to do their best as
practiced and get good results.
I understand. We request a
fair and careful judgment.
Today, judges' score is 70%
and viewers' votes are 30%.
The team with the lowest
score will be eliminated.
The TOP4 will get casted
to SM, YG, or JYP.
They will get systematic training
and prepare for the next round.
It's going to be exciting.
I will now announce the
order and their numbers.
The top dark horse of live
broadcast, No. 1 2,000 won!
Excellent rhythm and youngest
finalist, No. 2 Bang Ye-dam!
He has a sweet voice,
No. 3 Andrew Choi!
The strongest harmony born in
KPOP STAR, No. 4 Raccoon Boys!
Charming singer-songwriter,
No. 5 Akdong Musician!
Your votes can change
and determine their fate.
Boom will explain how you
can be a national judge.
Hi, I'm with the audience.
Give me a shout!
Hi, I'm KPOP STAR's
MC, Boom.
I know you're curious
who will be in the TOP4.
It all depends on you.
I will explain the
voting system.
Open the messaging on
your cellphone and...
Text #0606 with the Korean
name or number of the finalist.
You can vote for more than one person,
but no multiple votes for one person.
Keep that in mind.
Voting is also possible
via mobile messengers.
Today you can vote starting from
the first stage until the last.
Who will get casted and
who will be eliminated?
That fated stage will unfold
today. Please watch to the end.
Voting will begin, and are you
curious of their fated stage?
We will start now!
[Voting Begins]
[Text #0606 with their
number or name]
We were overzealous.
"Kim Hyo-bin is
not excited."
I wanted to show that I
could, but I went too far.
[Calmly monitors their
previous performance]
I thought I was excited,
but you were more excited.
I was trying to follow
your excitement.
I thought we were going
to be eliminated...
We agreed to have no regrets and
give all our energy even if we lose.
We had to play by
the rules...
The judges pointed
that out.
What 2,000 won
needs the most is...
Not trying well, but
showing something new.
Singers that sing in a refined
and trendy style are loved.
2,000 won are like last
generation's singers.
The judges want us to
show something refined.
What if 2,000 won
sings ___?
I love that song.
I think they'll do well.
Hyo-bin has to sing
halfheartedly.
We are singing
2NE1's "Lonely".
[This song has a different feel
from what they've been doing!]
How could we keep the original
style and add our color to it?
We've been thinking
the past two days.
It's troubling us.
A refined voice and
Il-do's sincere rapping...
I want that combination.
They now have to sing to move
the heart and not the eyes.
[No. 1 2,000 won]
You might get hurt from
What I'm about to say
We might need to put
A comma between us
It's hard to see you cry
That is why
I'm doing it before you get hurt more
I don't deserve you who is kind
Don't do that with me. Lonely
Find someone better than me
[Lonely - 2NE1]
I'm going to be a bad guy
Let go of my hand. I'm expired
This is my farewell song to you
Please leave. Leave me alone
Say I'm selfish, rather hate me
Erase me from your mind. Empty it
Where I used to be at your side
I can no longer be your No. 1 fan
Sorry girl. I can't be your sun
Cause you can't shine next to me
Sorry for not considering you
I don't want to see your sorrow
I thought it would be good
Since you laughed
Sorry, sorry, I'm sorry
Compared to their other
stages, they were calm.
What did the judges think?
I will start first.
It was new to hear men
sing 2NE1's "Lonely".
Il-do mixed in some melody
in his rap in the introduction.
When a rapper sings, there's
something that reaches us.
Maybe it's because the
lyrics were conveyed well.
You had a great start, but
one thing was unfortunate.
I could see Hyo-bin trying
to get rid of the old style.
I thought why you sounded old.
You always bend the first note.
Although you get rid of the vibrato
at the end to not sound old...
You started off sounding
old. That was a pity.
I liked how Il-do
was well-organized.
The rap was first calm and
then exploded in the middle.
It would've been great if
Hyo-bin exploded together.
You were stable, but you put too
much importance on it at that part.
Overall, you performed the
mission well. I enjoyed it.
She said they were stable
but somewhat lacking.
- What is their score?
- I'll announce it.
- SM's score is...
- It's SM's score.
It's 89! They got
89 from BoA.
We're curious of the next
commentary and score.
My commentary is very
similar to what BoA said.
I wanted to talk about the
note bending, but she did.
To add to that...
Even though you tense your body
and singing, never the mouth.
Tensing the lips and chin
make you sound old.
You didn't do that
in the first part.
But you tensed your mouth
later and sounded old.
She said she wanted you to
explode towards the end.
Don't try to explode with singing.
Get immersed in the lyrics.
When your emotions explode,
singing will naturally explode.
You could make a better climax if
you take care of it with emotions.
Il-do, you were great.
The flow was a bit monotonous.
Get in rhythm in different ways.
JYP's score is...
He said emotion is better than
skills. What's their score?
It's 85!
Last is YG's score
and commentary.
The interesting thing
here on KPOP STAR is...
I don't give a detailed
commentary on singing.
Since BoA and JYP are singers,
they comment on the singing.
I didn't because I
don't sing well.
But this commentary
is going to be mixed.
I think differently
from BoA and JYP.
Each song has a mood. You
were excited every stage.
But you were stable today.
You sang while sitting down.
That was a new stage for you.
But just as I said before...
Il-do's voice and motion is the same
whether the song is slow or fast.
For example, if Min-suk of
Raccoon Boys rapped this...
His rap would've went along
with Hyo-bin's singing.
Your actions were bigger
than the music.
That was a pity, but it was new
to see you sing while sitting.
Good job.
YG's score is...
He said their new image was
impressive. What's the score?
It's 87!
The total is 261.
If you liked it, text #0606
with 2,000 won or No. 1.
This stage was by
No. 1 2,000 won!
Bang Ye-dam needs
a new image.
It's time for him
to actually sing.
Putting aside the
excitment, he should...
Since "Baby", he danced
and performed.
Now it's time to show
off his singing skills.
[What mission was
given to him?]
I was surprised when
I received my mission.
Starting with the title,
I never heard this before.
I was curious why they
chose this song for me.
[What song is it?]
["When a Man Loves a Woman" was
well-known due to Michael Bolton]
There's a lot of high notes
and I never heard it before.
It was hard.
I don't understand the
lyrics because I'm young.
So I asked Brian for help.
Here, because a man
loves a woman...
I know that feeling
because I'm a man.
- Have you felt that?
- No, no.
- You do, don't you?
- No, I don't.
- None.
- Really?
- What was her name?
- No, I don't.
- There isn't anyone.
- Think about her and sing.
- What are you talking about?
- Why are you blushing then?
I don't have much experience
liking someone like the lyrics.
I'm worried who to think
about as I sing this song.
What about BoA?
Ah...
That's good.
[He'll think of BoA]
What expression do you
want to see on JYP?
[He's casted to JYP
with that look!]
I'm worried because
this is very hard.
His skill has to go up
another level to sing it.
If Ye-dam could
sing this...
All three agencies will
wage a casting war.
The song I'm going
to sing is very hard.
I will try hard to
put on a good stage.
Yeah!
[No. 2 Bang Ye-dam]
[When a Man Loves a Woman - Percy Sledge]
The crowd's going wild.
Bang Ye-dam, he's just...
The harmonica playing, ???
pink jacket... He was cool.
We're curious what the judges
thought and what the score is.
I'll go first.
I was at a restaurant and got a
text that Michael Jackson died.
But for no reason, I cried.
That's how much I liked him.
When you hear him sing "Ben", the
songs he sang when he was young...
You can hear the sound at the top of
the skull when he sings the high notes.
Singers know what that is.
Ye-dam makes that sound
at the high notes.
People who know that
are knocked senseless.
From low to high, he doesn't
strain the sound with his muscles.
What's amazing is that he got
that during this program.
My previous commentary was
to explode with emotion.
Towards the end, Ye-dam
didn't explode with singing.
He made the lyrics he couldn't understand
with the heart and exploded it in singing.
Lastly, the timing can make the
ad-lib sound refined or not.
His timing was very refined
that it's unexplainable.
Since I don't have
much time...
- From that expression...
- First time having tears...
JYP's score is...
I'm very curious what he'll
give since he praised him...
Bang Ye-dam got 98!
Wow, a 98!
He said his emotion
was good.
Let's hear the next score
and commentary.
I'm not amazed at
Bang Ye-dam anymore.
You can't explain
this in words.
The viewers might think why
we are complimenting him.
There are many children participants
in a program called "Star King".
There's a difference between
them and Bang Ye-dam.
They're good at imitating while
he has skills pros don't have.
You just talked about
Michael Jackson.
He moved many people when he
sang with The Jackson 5.
Today's stage by Bang
Ye-dam was the best.
- That's a good commentary.
- YG's score is...
We're curious of
YG's score.
He praised him highly,
and the score is 95!
That's a good score.
Did he think of BoA as
he sang? Right, BoA?
Did you think as you saw me? Sorry.
Did you think of me while singing?
Did you? It's okay,
tell the truth.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry?
Can I change my score?
I'm going to change it.
He's still young
so it's okay.
He has a sense of rhythm and the
skill to make the song his own.
Ye-dam's breathing is short
and voice is unstable.
People might think, "Why are the
judges going wild over him?"
In terms of instruments, a violin
sounds different from a cello.
A person's body is
also an instrument.
His soundbox is small since
he's not fully grown yet.
But the skills and sense
of rhythm he possesses...
I thought if there would
be another like him.
Since they said many good things,
I'm going to point out some things.
I always felt this, but you
don't fully convey the lyrics.
It'll be great if you
are able to do that.
Considering how you sped up during
the break, I announce SM's score.
This is SM's score.
What will he get?
It's 93!
The total is 286.
If you liked it, text #0606
with Bang Ye-dam or No. 2.
This stage was by
No. 2, Bang Ye-dam!
Which opponent do
you fear the most?
Andrew...
Andrew... You just can't...
You can't beat him.
Andrew...
Andrew won all three.
[He won against Akdong Musician,
Choi Ye-geun, and Raccoon Boys]
He's on the rise
every round.
Andrew Choi put on a lot of showy
performances during the live broadcast.
I chose this thinking it's time
he moves us with just singing.
The judges gave you a
mission. What was it?
The song title...
It's Korean and long...
Sorry, I don't remember.
Tell us as much
as you remember.
Sleep... Sleepless Night?
That's correct, right?
- I don't think so.
- That's not it?
[Embarrassed]
Sleepless Rainy Night.
[Kim Gun-mo's unique style
and soul that is hard to sing]
This song will push
his voice to the limit.
His singing style is more liked
by YG than either SM or JYP.
If he sings this well, I
might be more interested.
He could make it to TOP4
if he sings this well.
Because it's in Korean, I write
the translation to understand.
There's a rap in
the original.
[Arranging the rap
part in his style?]
I'm going to change it
into an R&B, soul style.
Anything hard?
There's a lot.
- What's the most difficult?
- The most difficult is...
My parents are in the States, and it's
been over 3 years since I saw them.
[No. 3 Andrew Choi]
[Sleepless Rainy Night - Kim Gun-mo]
He sure has a sweet voice.
That stage was by Andrew Choi.
We're curious of the
judges' commentary.
Before you started, everyone said
they were afraid of you in the video.
I think you're like an X-man,
KPOP STAR 2's X-man.
I thought you would
never come this far.
But every round you
showed something new.
Overall, I liked the song. I
think JYP will also compliment.
His voice was open, right?
When you started with, "Outside
the window, it is raining"...
I saw you many times, but it's my
first time hearing such a voice.
I was surprised. I just gave you a
nickname, KPOP STAR 2's X-man.
I enjoyed it.
YG's score is...
He said good things.
I'm curious of his score.
It's 90!
Next commentary and
score is by BoA.
If I remember correctly,
this is a 90s song, right?
- Right?
- You're right.
A 90s song was rearranged, and
you changed the melody, right?
He had a great sense in arranging it
that it didn't sound like an old song.
You showed today what a
well-organized song is.
You started off softly
then hit the climax.
Lastly, you finished it off with
a voice that melted my heart.
It was a perfect stage.
High notes, singing...
I think it was a perfect
stage. I enjoyed it.
SM's score is...
She gave good compliments,
but what is the score?
SM's score is 93!
He's getting high scores.
Last is JYP's score
and commentary.
There's something I learned
being a KPOP STAR judge.
If something's really good,
I shouldn't say that it is.
I shouldn't compliment since
it has a negative connotation.
- I learned it...
- But you used it.
I learned it, but I
use it because...
I can't fix it overnight since
I used it for a long time.
So I thought he couldn't fix his
old habit of straining his throat.
But he did it for the
first time last week.
This morning I was praying that
he doesn't go back to his habits.
But that vocalization
is now set in him.
It was great to hear.
Now that you have that vocalization,
you don't need to focus on it anymore.
Just sing naturally. When you were
focused on that vocalization...
The space between your mouth
and chin was opened too much.
That vocalization will come out
even when you sing comfortably.
I enjoyed it.
JYP's score is...
He said his unfixable
vocalization was fixed.
It's 90!
The total is 273.
His father is in the audience.
Why don't you say something?
My brother's here too.
- Your father's there, right?
- My brother as well.
Oh? Say something
to him too.
He greeted them in
an American way.
If you liked it, text #0606
with Andrew Choi or No. 3.
This stage was by
No. 3, Andrew Choi!
We received a wildcard two
weeks ago and also last week.
Since the live broadcast began,
preparation became difficult.
We felt burdened performing with a
live band and other new sounds.
We don't know what
that other 2% is.
That's our biggest concern.
The most serious is
Raccoon Boys.
I don't understand how they
did "Thriller" with one guitar.
How was it exciting
with one guitar?
I think they get stiff because of the
Korean lyrics, especially McKay.
I think the biggest
difference is...
Brian and McKay did sing passionately
for their part, even with a head voice.
They killed their part to come
together. That couldn't come out.
Raccoon Boys aren't bad.
Since they raised the
public's expectations...
They should choose a song where
each can show off their skills.
[He thought of a song?]
This is a well-known song.
- This is how it's done.
- Everyone knows this.
This part is where
Min-suk raps.
Great!
This is it.
They can show off all their
skills in singing and rapping.
Don't make it exciting, but
make it touching throughout.
Each of us will have a part in the
beginning to show our strengths.
As we finish it off
with a harmony...
A gospel choir will enter
and explode the stage.
Explode?
What am I supposed to say?
[Anyways they're preparing
a moving climax]
It's sad but also touching.
I wrote lyrics on thanking people
around me that I don't really know.
[Another nerve-racking
competition ahead]
[They're most grateful
to their members]
If the Raccoon Boys
sing this well...
Not only JYP, but BoA and I
would also like to cast them.
We will show you again
how strong we are.
Raccoon's back!
That was awkward.
[No. 4 Raccoon Boys]
You are the reason I dream
The reason I'm breathing now
[I'll Be Missing You - Puff Daddy
Original (Every Breath You Take - The Police)]
Your eyes are my sole mirror
The stars that shine on me at night
Your existence is like a shadow
You breathe silently at my steps
From my voice, eyes, nose, mouth
They are all traces of you
The pain I gave might be deep
So I bite my lips
It's okay. Put me down now
Time, stop. You can rest
Your hands, I want to hold them
So you can hold me tight
Their harmony is the best.
It was No. 4 Raccoon Boys.
I'm curious what the
judges thought.
Please tell us the score
and commentary.
I enjoyed it.
McKay is... I'm sorry, Min-suk
always relays the lyrics well.
I can't find any
flaws for this stage.
Today's song was...
Brian did explode
in the high notes.
But more importantly, the
ad-lib after the high notes...
May have ruined the song.
That's a pity, but
the mood was great.
The vocal aspect
was a bit lacking.
McKay, is your throat condition
worsening? Is it better?
It was a pity since your voice
sounded like it was closing.
I enjoyed it.
SM's score is...
It's SM's score.
The mood was great
but lacking... It's 88!
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
Raccoon... I am your fan.
Since I said many times that
your combination is great.
The first and second half of a
soccer game is 45 minutes each.
I don't know about nowadays,
but boxing has 12 rounds.
The biggest reason people
watch boxing or soccer is...
They wait for that one
punch in boxing and...
Watch 90 minutes of soccer
for that one goal.
What I felt now and before
about Raccoon Boys...
It's like you're trying to
win boxing with a call.
You're trying to
keep it safe.
You throw jabs and no
strong counterpunch.
You win in the end, but we
don't remember anything.
I wanted you to do well, but I
couldn't forget that impression.
But it was a good
stage. YG's score is...
He said there was
no special punch.
YG's score is... 83!
Last is JYP.
You can't tell if a person dances
well or not with a fast song.
Same with singing.
There's not much difference when music
is fast and there's a lot of instruments.
Singing skills stand out when there are
no instruments and it's medium tempo.
I felt it again today.
McKay and Brian have many problems
with vocalization and breathing.
You weren't good and fixed it.
But it felt like you regressed.
It's like if Andrew was open,
he's voice is strained again.
You don't sing with your
head in the high notes...
And your chest in
the low notes.
We can't listen for long since
you sing everything here.
I want Min-suk to change
the flow with the song.
It's a pity you're
using the same flow.
I want Raccoon Boys
to explode again.
I think you should practice
on fixing your basic flaws.
JYP's score is...
He spoke mostly
of their flaws.
The score is... 85!
The total is 256.
If you liked it, text #0606
with Raccoon Boys or No. 4.
This stage was by
No. 4, Raccoon Boys!
[After last week's
live broadcast...]
[Chan-hyuk secretly
cries alone]
After being complimented, now
I'm getting recognition too.
I feel great with the good results
as a composer and lyricist.
[Akdong Musician deals the gayo world
a severe blow with "Crescendo"]
It was a perfect song.
I always think, "Wow."
It was amazing.
I want to hear Soo-hyun and
Chan-hyuk's voices closely.
I'm curious what voice Soo-hyun
could give if she really sings.
They haven't sung a song that
showed their singing skills.
The song we requested is Tamia's
"Officially Missing You".
Some Korean singers made
a remake of this song.
A genuine stage with Soo-hyun's
charming voice and Chan-hyuk's rap.
A high chance that it could
be better than the original.
This is hard.
I don't feel good.
After Ji-hoon got eliminated,
Soo-hyun is now alone.
That was on my mind, and
I decided to be with her.
When I went over...
It's empty compared
to the men's room.
No one got eliminated in the
men's room and it's amicable.
The names are still there in the
women's room, but it's empty.
So this is what we thought.
That lonely and empty feeling...
If we express that in
the song, it'll go well.
We thought we could
express our feelings better.
We arranged it by putting
in Korean lyrics and a rap.
This song is based
on our experiences.
We could put on a genuine
stage. If that's conveyed...
Then it's a success.
I missed them at times.
I'll be singing
with that heart.
Why don't you send a
video message to them?
Are you doing well?
I really miss you.
[Suddenly tears...]
I didn't how hard it
was without all of you.
I really miss you.
This song is for you.
Please enjoy it.
[No. 5 Akdong Musician]
[Officially Missing You - Tamia]
One by one, they start leaving me
I might meet them as a different person
I thought I wouldn't be sad
Just full of traces
The memories where
we laughed and cried
Past memories, grew colder from summer
A hope I dreamed of even today
Hearts grow deeper on the same path
Happy at night even if goings are rough
The lonely air drove out the warmth
The redolent songs we sang here and there
Your names are
still on the door
Scratch paper filled
with musical notes
I felt sorry as you left
Hope you return with same dream
One by one, they start leaving me
I might meet them as a different person
Akdong Musician's charming
harmony stood out in that song.
What score will they receive?
Tell us the score and commentary.
No matter how well someone sang
last year, I didn't cry or anything.
Did I grow a year older?
I don't know why the tears fall.
You must have been moved.
They're young, but the feeling that
comes when they sing from the heart...
With their voice without habits
can't be described in words.
I thought, "How well would Soo-hyun
sing if she receives lessons?"
Actually, it was Chan-hyuk who made
me cry when he sang towards the end.
He sang really well.
I truly enjoyed it.
Until now, teenagers sang
songs that had to do with them.
Teenagers sang, but the lyrics and
music were mostly written by adults.
But the two of you sang
your songs in your voice.
I think you two are
precious. JYP's score is...
That's a good commentary. They
sang their song in their voice.
The score is 98!
They got a high score.
Their genuineness
was effective.
Next please.
Because JYP said
he shed tears...
I thought it was due to
her singing with her heart...
After she talked about how
the girls left in the video.
But you shed tears
because they sang well.
What you and I
feel is different.
It touched me when
she cried in the video.
So I read the lyrics
while they sang.
It's very well-written.
It's great.
"Past memories, grew
colder from summer."
This rhyme... every rhyme
in the lyrics were clever.
While listening, I thought
of the friends that left me.
Putting aside whether
you sang well or not...
The lyrics and song were
genuine and moved the heart.
Good job.
YG's score is...
I'm curious. He had a
similar opinion to JYP.
It's 95! They got
a high score.
Last is BoA's score
and commentary.
Soo-hyun, before you started
singing, you watched the video...
Did you almost cry
because of the video?
- Yes.
- I know!
Don't show that before they
sing. It'll be hard for them.
Soo-hyun's voice was thick
and pressed than usual.
I thought maybe it's because you
tried to suppress those emotions.
I think Akdong Musician is good at
combining what they face to the lyrics.
I was touched as I saw
the video and lyrics.
I'm starting to fall for Chan-hyuk's
charms since the live broadcast began.
Whether it be singing or rap.
It was as good as her
voice. I enjoyed it.
- SM's score is...
- It was a compliment.
What is BoA's score?
It's 94!
They currently have the highest
score with a total of 287.
Give them a hand!
If you liked it, text #0606 with
Akdong Musician or No. 5.
This stage was by
No. 5, Akdong Musician!
All the TOP5 stages
are now over.
Currently, Akdong Musician has
the highest score with 287.
But it's not final. Your
votes can change the order.
We will show TOP5's
highlight video.
Who will advance to TOP4?
Place your final votes.
Voting and mobile messenger
voting will soon end!
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
Voting is now over.
Who will make it
to TOP4? Who?
It's amazing.
As the results are being tallied,
a special performance awaits.
You, the viewers, turn up the
volume and put down the remote.
Why? Just enjoy.
Are you ready to enjoy?
KPOP STAR 2 prepared
this special stage.
The 1st stage is the five male
finalists that only competed.
They transformed to charming guys
and prepared a fantastic harmony.
Let's meet them!
KPOP STAR!
[Billie Jean - Michael Jackson]
Amazing, just amazing!
This is KPOP STAR!
I also look forward
to the next stage.
This stage will have Soo-hyun,
Min-suk, Il-do, and Ye-dam.
I can't imagine
what it'll be like.
Then confirm with your eyes.
Are you ready to enjoy?
Shout "STAR" when
I shout "KPOP".
KPOP!
[What Should Have Been (own rap) - PSY]
You left me, a passionate goodbye
The paradise we had is no more
Our memories were so beautiful
It's a waste to throw it away
Thinking of it now, it was art
Recalling makes me drink in the day
I wonder if you were here
I still can't forget your habits
Sometimes I miss your smile
I'm also doing okay on my own
Pillow and toothbrush are still here
The photo album became our memory
In your arms I always loved
The dream we saw on the same spot
We should be happy in our own paths
Goodbye my fan, my eternal friend
If I held on to you then
I wouldn't eat ramen sadly
If we didn't breakup
If you didn't leave me
Although our game of love is over
I have one last thing to say to you
Please remember me
Remember this rap to you
The streets we walked lingers
I'm falling down like a leaf
Memories grow in my head
I fall at the passing wind
Goodbye. I have one request
Don't cry with another man
You were with me a long time
Live happily and don't get sick
The TOP5 put on a great stage!
Another round of applause!
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Surival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2.
This TOP5 stage
was the fiercest.
The results have
been tallied.
The announcement remains.
The judges just
got the results.
In the red envelopes are the
results and the one eliminated.
Please open them.
They don't know.
BoA was a bit surprised, but
we can't tell by their looks.
Does it match with the viewers or
not? We can't tell by their looks.
A pity, but the eliminated
can't get casted.
Only the four that
pass can get casted.
SM, YG, and JYP will
now begin casting!
According to what you already
chose, you will begin casting.
First is JYP.
First, it's a pity that a talented
team will get eliminated.
Of the four that advanced,
the one casted by JYP is...
Someone I think I will
have fun working with.
- Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He's the first TOP4 finalist
and got casted to JYP.
Please move over there,
and give him a big hand.
Bang Ye-dam advanced
to TOP4 and YG is next.
Only Akdong Musician came to YG
twice and the rest never came.
I will cast the one
that I want to fix.
- The finalist YG will cast...
- The finalist is...
It's 2,000 won.
Congratulations! They
got casted to YG!
They were surprised.
They advanced to TOP4.
Please move over there.
Please come closer.
Currently, 2,000 won and
Bang Ye-dam advanced.
They got casted
by JYP and YG.
Now BoA, who
did SM cast?
The TOP4 finalist
casted by SM is...
I'm making another
unexpected choice.
I'm excited to work with them
and I think it's going to be fun.
That finalist is...
- Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
They got casted by SM
and are TOP4 finalists.
Please move over there.
So far, Bang Ye-dam to JYP, Akdong
Musician to SM, and 2,000 won to YG.
Now only one
spot remains.
SM gets the final casting.
Who is the last to get casted?
Will it be Andrew Choi
or the Raccoon Boys?
One of them will get eliminated.
BoA, please start casting.
It's a pity that one will get casted
and the other will be eliminated.
The one that will prepare
with me for the next round is...
This is the final casting.
Casting or elimination?
Who will SM cast?
Andrew Choi and the
Raccoon Boys are on stage.
- It's Andrew Choi.
- Congratulations!
He got casted to SM
and is a TOP4 finalist.
Unfortunately, Raccoon Boys
got eliminated today.
They tried hard for a better stage
and harmony, and to improve...
But they got eliminated.
Raccoon Boys... Guys,
you did great until now.
You did great. Any last
words for your fans?
We thank you for
loving our music.
Another big hand
for Raccoon Boys.
KPOP STAR continues
next week. Goodbye!