Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
[Battle audition
T-minus 3 days]
You have to write down
who will battle first.
[They have to write down their order
without knowing the others' order!]
[What will the fated list
come out to be?]
[And now the day has come!]
[The judges arrived 2 hours early]
The agency's pride is on the line and
there's an odd mix of emotions.
Since we train them and
present to the public...
This round gives us a
tremendous burden.
I couldn't sleep... maybe 2 hours.
I even had a stomachache...
It's like I'm taking an exam...
I've never been this nervous...
The list is out?
This is important...
[The judges receive the list!]
I can't feel at ease for
any of the battles.
I'm suddenly losing confidence.
They have to make it...
[Announced to them as well!]
1st place advances to TOP10!
2nd place gets a rematch!
3rd place is eliminated!
[They're more nervous than ever]
[The first battle]
[JYP's Nam Young-joo]
[I hope it isn't me!]
[YG's 1Minute]
[Antenna Music's Kwon Jin-ah]
[OMG...]
This must be some fated day...
I didn't know I would
run into her...
I'm worried how I'll be compared to
Young-joo who has similar strengths.
It was a shock.
They're both tough opponents.
I feel burdened facing
any one of the 16...
[Everyone is a strong
opponent and rival!]
All 18 teams now have an
opponent to battle.
They look tense during practice
as the time draws near.
[Dress rehearsal 30 minutes
before the battle audition]
Who will take the honor of
advancing to the TOP10?
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[The fated stage where the
TOP10 will be determined!]
[You Hee-yeol arrives first again]
[He looks tense than ever!]
[The thing that came
into his view is...]
[The special stage for
the battle audition!]
[Each agency's contestant
will appear through those]
[And...]
[There's one for Antenna Music!]
[The battle audition - the fated
prematch for the TOP10]
[YG appears!]
[They greet each other]
[Soon there's a strange
feeling of tension...]
[JYP runs up]
- You're here.
- Yup.
[A heavy silence after
the greeting...]
[The tension forewarns
a tremendous battle!]
Preparation for the battle audition
was the most difficult in my life.
Not Toy's first album?
Compared to preparing an album
or getting into college...
Those things concern you but
this concerns the contestants...
Look at all the gray hairs.
- The gray hairs...
- In just a few days?
I didn't have any
and now I do.
This is really... and I also
have enteritis.
- I slept for 2 hours.
- Really?
Today's recording has to be
interrupted a couple of times.
- During the recording.
- He needs to use the restroom.
If I make this expression, I'm either
moved or need to use the restroom.
[Hope today goes well...]
Let's start!
This is the battle audition
determining the TOP10.
Among the 18 teams, 6 from each of the
3 agencies, 8 teams will be eliminated.
You must be very nervous but
put on a great performance.
This is the first battle.
Nam Young-joo fom JYP.
1Minute from YG.
Kwon Jin-ah from Antenna Music.
Please enter the stage!
[The first battle for the TOP10!]
[Nam Young-joo is more gaunt]
[Kwon Jin-ah walks out modestly]
[Meanwhile, YG's 1Minute...]
[Walking like a catwalk model?]
[1Minute members are talented]
[One of them will make it
into the TOP10!]
[Deeply moved by their
imposing figures!]
[Who will be the first to
advance to the TOP10?]
You can see each agency's styling.
- Soo-hyun.
- Yes?
- You look like a celebrity.
- Thank you.
I think I'll be seeing
something new from her.
Your singing changes when
your looks change.
I look forward to her.
Young-joo had a sore throat
and wasn't able to sing.
Are you better now?
How is it?
It's better than before but
I haven't fully recovered.
She's singing a difficult song...
[What song could it be?]
All of you are here representing
each of the 3 agencies.
This group will be fierce but it's unavoidable
since there are strong ones in other groups.
This isn't about your singing anymore.
It's about who has more guts.
Who will forget everything and
lose yourself in singing?
That will be your victory.
Be bold and lose yourself
on stage today. Good luck!
Will the first contestant
get ready?
[She looks more gaunt than
in the previous round]
[The ones waiting their turn
are also very nervous]
Nam Young-joo received
training from JYP.
But I'm concerned of your
throat's condition...
How bad is it?
I couldn't speak at all
up until yesterday.
- Really? Is it the flu...
- I don't have the flu.
- I practiced...
- A lot?
I shouldn't push myself but I had
to practice even in that state.
[What happened to her?]
Nam Young-joo has a
great voice and feel.
But she keeps on relying on that.
She needs to show off her singing.
So we chose a song that went
as low and high as possible.
[Her final task to make it
into the TOP10!]
[Toni Braxton's "Un-Break My Heart"]
You have to show that you can sing the
high notes since you never showed it.
I felt great at first when
I heard the song.
But it was hard when
I started singing it.
The emotions of this song were
different from what I'm used to.
It's not even in Korean and
I have to sing with pop vocals.
[When she sang in front of JYP,
she had a bigger problem...]
[The extreme high notes!]
This determines victory. You go to
TOP10 if you do it or you don't.
[The burden of overcoming the
limitations of her range!]
I can't do it...
"Why can't I do it? Why?"
Even though I practiced...
There's not much time...
And my throat is bad...
[In the end, her throat is sore...]
[She's in her worst crisis!]
[She doesn't have much time
but the tears won't stop]
It was really hard because
nothing worked out.
[The tears are about to fall
thinking back to that time...]
I can't cry. If I cry,
my voice will go out.
[Can she overcome her
worst difficulty?]
You chose Toni Braxton's
"Un-Break My Heart."
Until now, you heard you have
great feel but not singing.
You need singing skills
for this song.
This could be your challenge and hurdle.
It could also be a starting point.
You have to overcome it.
Everything becomes hard if you
think of trying to advance.
But everything becomes easy if you
just do your best in singing.
Forget everything even the
condition of your throat.
[Her worst crisis since
starting KPOP STAR!]
[Will she finish without a hitch?]
[She tries to sign the pianist]
[But can't calm herself]
[Un-Break My Heart - Toni Braxton]
[He can feel her throat is
in a bad condition...]
[Slowly building up to
the extreme high notes]
[Soon it's the high notes!]
[Finished without incident]
[Lets out a deep sigh of relief]
[JYP encourages her
with a smile]
[What did the other
judges think?]
I enjoyed it.
I took your throat condition
into account as I listened.
Despite your circumstances,
you finished the match.
I want to applaud you for that.
It's the first time I heard you
sing like that in the chorus.
I haven't really heard you sing
in a strong tone for that part.
But you attempted that jump.
[She wasn't daunted by her throat
condition and sang the high notes...]
Attempting this song and this stage will
be a great help in your singing career.
[It was hard, but she took the
bold challenge in this stage...]
[She received a positive commentary
for attempting something new]
[YG has a heavy look.
What is his commentary?]
[It's not easy for him to speak]
The battle audition is an important
round determining the TOP10.
I completely understand JYP for
taking a risk with Nam Young-joo.
I also heard her throat is
in a bad condition.
This round is too important
to be taking risks.
I heard you many times, but
you used a voice you didn't use.
And you sang in voices
I never heard before.
It was like...
You sang in a key or two lower
than your tessitura.
[She did her best in that difficulty]
[But lost half her charm!]
This is really hard for me.
I have to watch what I say.
It was good to see you do your best
despite your bad condition.
[YG's commentary leaves
her in wanting!]
[Then what is JYP's commentary
since he saw her tough fight?]
If you want to succeed as a singer
for the rest of your life...
I thought it would be better
if your high notes were open.
I wanted to attempt that.
Changing one's vocalization
requires continuous efforts.
But you practiced a week and
couldn't practice for 2 weeks.
As Hee-yeol said, I compliment you
for finishing regardless of that.
[Finishes with a warm compliment...]
[She did her best despite the
many unfavorable conditions]
[What is her fate?]
Let's have our next contestant.
[YG's 1Minute]
There was a member change from
Jang Hanna to Abigail Kim.
Kim Soo-hyun shed tears and they had a
mental breakdown when I announced that.
I kept on crying since I was at a loss.
It wasn't because I hated it.
Everything had to start all over.
I didn't know how or where to begin.
So I actually cried a lot.
The feeling was different and
it was great when we started.
Now I think it's good.
Thanks.
It must have been hard
for you too, Abigail.
I was scared at first.
[A shocking confession]
They have strong voices but
also strong personalities.
I was worried, shocked,
and taken aback.
[Drastic measures to be a team!]
[Show us your talents, Abigail]
[It's not easy for her
to assimilate]
Don't be like that, Abi!
We tried hard to bring out
Abigail's talents.
[Trying hard = forcing her
to do random dances?]
[Her seal is removed]
As I kept on doing it,
they had bright energy...
And I became brighter
due to the synergy.
[1Minute is now turning
into a real team]
We prepared 1Minute in a way as if
they'll appear on a music program.
We put the most effort
into this team.
[He carefully checks their
singing and choreography]
[YG tries to instill
his agency's colors]
As we practiced for the
2 weeks we were there...
I thought, "Am I really at YGE?"
because we might never go back.
- On the last day of practice...
- We kissed the wall.
We kissed the wall and
left our lip prints.
- Saying, "We'll return."
- That's right.
[How will the performance by
these 3 desperate girls be?]
[Ain't No Other Man - Christina Aguilera]
[Starting with a Blues feel
different from the original]
[Choreography with feeling
utilizing the chair]
[Changes to a fast tempo
that grabs attention]
[Cho Yoon-kyung's voice and
moves are filled with groove]
[Even looks brimming
with confidence!]
[1Minute's performance
makes them smile]
[Their families cheer them]
[These 3 girls are still nervous]
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
I felt something amazing as
I watched your performance.
And that is...
I only heard your singing before,
but now I see the whole picture.
Your clothes, the performance
on stage, and the dance moves...
I used to think it was something
to spice up your singing...
But the entire stage is as
important as the singing.
I now see the overall picture and was
amazed at how refined you became.
You're like pros now.
Now I see that YG doesn't make
people stand out for no reason.
That's how well you absorbed it
so I was pleased with the performance.
[How will his compliment affect
their decision on the TOP10?]
If judges can get enteritis from being nervous,
the contestants would be really nervous.
I have to take that into consideration.
You must have been nervous and burdened.
And... the good thing...
Yoon-kyung's voice was open
and had a full sound.
I thought of wanting to hear her
sing alone from beginning to end.
We're sensitive in saying good or bad things
to those that came to one's own agency.
Complimenting seems like
we're defending them...
And we feel they'll be eliminated
if we point things out.
This is really hard.
It is.
I'll quote You Hee-yeol.
[You Hee-yeol's commentary
that they were like pros]
[In the case of their performance
as 2Minute with Jang Hanna]
You were like amateurs
but natural.
Today, you were like pros
but not as natural as before.
[He points out things that are necessary
even though he trained them]
[Will 1Minute advance
to the TOP10?]
- This is hard.
- Today is hard.
Alright!
The next contestant is
Kwon Jin-ah from Antenna Music.
[Antenna Music's
Kwon Jin-ah (18)]
[A historic moment as the first
contestant for Antenna Music]
Someone interview her.
[He's more nervous than her]
You went to Anttenna Music.
I meant Antenna Music.
Did you practice in the
new practice room?
Yes.
Please tell us one good and
bad thing about Antenna Music.
The good thing is that the
practice room was very cozy...
[You can feel the breath of
the person next to you]
- The bad thing is...
- He doesn't give food, right?
Uhh... kimbap.
Then the bad thing is
that you ate kimbap?
[It was good]
That was some good kimbap
I even bought you sikhye.
She's singing a song
that I really like.
It's Taeyang's "I Need a Girl."
She received a lot of compliments
for singing JYP's songs.
We're going to show that she can
also sing our rival YG's songs.
After she completes that, she'll sing
Antenna Music's songs in the end.
[Why is You Hee-yeol confident?]
[You Hee-yeol invited some of the
best experts for evaluation]
["God of vocals" - Kim Yeon-woo]
[Powerful vocals - ALi]
She's really good.
She has a clean, beautiful timbre,
and also has her own color.
She has groove and a
good sense of rhythm.
I like her innate timbre
and rhythm.
[She can't believe she's
being complimented]
[Maestro of acoustic guitar
Ham Chun-ho]
The mood is great. Structure it
well centered on that.
The part where you go
all out is really good.
As you are now, I'm confident
whoever your opponent is.
[She received the highest
compliments from experts]
[But...]
I never imagined I would
make it this far...
I thought I would never
even make it to Round 1.
Since You Hee-yeol and the others
said I'm doing really great...
I have to do well to be able
to face You Hee-yeol.
Honestly, I'm really burdened.
[She lacks in many aspects
to think on her own]
Since this is the battle that leads to the TOP10,
I have the desire of being on live broadcast.
[Will she put on a good performance
as much as You Hee-yeol is confident?]
[I Need a Girl - Taeyang]
[A clean timbre with power
echoing on the stage]
[Sensibility can also be felt in
her exquisite guitar playing]
[She closes her eyes gently
and immerses in the music]
[She explodes in the high notes]
[You Hee-yeol finally relaxes]
[She brought the house down]
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
I didn't hear Taeyang's
"I Need a Girl."
I only saw Kwon Jin-ah.
She can express such emotions
and has her own things.
[Her own color and sensibility
stood out on this stage!]
When she made a wink in
the middle of the song...
[Her aegyo wink blew YG away]
That's a huge change since
she never did that before.
It's my first time seeing that.
She mustered up the
courage to do that.
It's like a shy person shouting,
"I love you" in a loud voice.
Wow. I didn't know she had
such a side. It was new.
I think I can focus and look
forward to her in the future.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[What is JYP's commentary?]
The first thing I felt...
You know how to sing sad songs
but not happy songs.
[Her emotions don't go well
with happy songs?]
"I Have a Girl" and "Bad Guy"
are heartbreaking, sad songs.
How you pushed out the sounds
went well with such songs.
You have to sing in staccato,
playfully, and bend it...
But the lyrics and the song
didn't go together at all.
That was the biggest problem.
Your interpretation of the lyrics
was what was great all this time.
On the other hand, what was amazingly
good was when you sang the high notes.
You sang the high notes with
perfect vocalization.
Another thing is when you played
the guitar in 24th notes.
That's hard for high school girls, especially
women, since they lack finger strength.
I was amazed at how you
played it almost perfectly.
You did well.
[JYP pointed things out and
also complimented her]
[Mixed feelings...]
Our commentaries are brutal
and cold-hearted, right?
We don't care what others think.
We just say what we feel.
It feels like I'm being scolded.
That's how you feel in
the battle audition.
I almost grabbed his neck.
[The sorrow of being
a rookie judge...]
That's how sensitive this
battle audition is.
As I trained with Jin-ah
for the past 3 weeks...
I used to have interest because you
played the guitar and interpreted well.
The most amazing thing during those weeks
is that I started seeing her as a vocalist.
Her timbre, vocal range, high notes,
bending, and others aren't like anyone.
I was mesmerized by your charm
every time I listened to you.
I was very happy to have heard
that during those weeks.
I wanted to compliment and tell you that.
Looks like I get that chance today.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[The judges discuss to choose
the TOP10 finalist]
[Nam Young-joo, 1Minute, and
Kwon Jin-ah stand on the stage]
[As the discussion goes on]
[The contestants are tense]
[Who will be the first
TOP10 finalist?]
[Discussion is over]
All three teams did well.
All of you must have been
nervous for going first.
Now it's the decisive moment.
This is the first group
of the battle audition.
1st place was picked unanimously.
[Nam Young-joo who gave
her all in the high notes]
[Kwon Jin-ah who showed her
high notes and new charm]
[1Minute presented a stage
worthy of YG artists]
[Who will be the first to
make it into the TOP10?]
It's Kwon Jin-ah. Congratulations
on advancing to the TOP10.
[Congratulations]
Now I'm actually doing what
I only watched on television.
I'm surprised but also
look forward to it.
I'm also worried.
[She's still dazed]
[Time to announce
2nd and 3rd place]
As you all know, 3rd place is
automatically eliminated.
2nd place gets another chance.
Since we trained you for a long time,
affection and pity crosses our mind.
This is really hard.
It is hard.
Alright.
We'll announce 2nd place.
Both teams didn't do well
compared to last round.
The one we want to see again has
potential as a singer and strengths.
2nd place is...
[Who will get the chance
for the rematch?]
JYP's Nam Young-joo.
Congratulations.
[2nd is JYP's Nam Young-joo]
[YG's 1Minute is eliminated]
1Minute had a member change and showed
a performance you never did before.
You had to think of many things.
I think you were nervous today but
you will have future opportunities.
I would like to say something
since I trained them.
1Minute did well. I don't
think you were nervous.
You didn't make big mistakes
and was the most confident.
I feel sorry because I think the
member change produced this result.
But it was every bit as good when
compared to 2Minute so cheer up.
We can meet again when
the opportunity arises.
You did well to make it
this far, right?
During my 2-3 months stay in Korea,
I got to see my grandmother...
I never studied music or did any of
these things before so it was fun.
I'm grateful to have made it
all the way to TOP18...
Don't say TOP18. If someone asks,
tell them you went to TOP11, okay?
I truly think you are TOP11.
I thank you for this opportunity
I had never imagined.
I'm biracial and grew up in Korea.
It was hard growing up in Korea...
I was hated and had
low self-esteem...
[Her father is heartbroken at
the times she went through]
I met many great people
on KPOP STAR...
I thank you.
People around me said you were pretty.
That's how you looked to them.
Now that everyone knows about
your beauty because of KPOP STAR...
If you now take the time to
let your skills be known...
I believe you'll be
a great singer.
I had a good time and
hope to see you again.
Good job and let's finish
with an applause.
[The judges feel sorry and sad]
[She cries endlessly
because this is the last]
We made it to TOP18...
I can't go there because
I think my dad is there.
[Their families are waiting
with warm smiles]
[Abigail cries like a baby
in her family's arms]
It's okay, Abi.
[Soo-hyun's father gives
her a warm embrace]
- Why are you crying?
- I'm not crying.
I think she learned a lot and
it was a good experience.
I'm grateful since it was an opportunity
for her to grow in various aspects.
There are many opportunities
waiting for her.
[May your time on KPOP STAR
become a precious foundation...]
[They feel sorry and despondent...]
This is hard.
No one is saying let's
start the 2nd battle.
Next is the death round.
[Who is in the death round?]
We have Hong Jung-hee
from Antenna Music.
[Stable high notes!
Excellent singing!]
[Hong Jung-hee with
Korean sentiments]
Bae Min-ah from YG.
[Innate soul! Female version
of Bruno Mars!]
[Bae Min-ah with R&B
soul sentiments]
Almeng from JYP.
[Overflowing with ideas!
Likely TOP10 finalist!]
[Almeng is a mixed duet
like a national treasure]
Please enter the stage!
[Group 2 of the
death round enters!]
[Each agency's styling
stands out in the clothes]
[An extraordinary black dress!]
[This group's victory
is unpredictable!]
[Who will take first and
enter the TOP10?]
The clothes are...
[Each agency's color is obvious!]
Hong Jung-hee, Bae Min-ah,
and Almeng are...
In my opinion, the death group.
This is a group of
talented people.
Let's listen to your thoughts
since you know each other now.
Before going to sleep,
I hoped it wasn't Almeng.
But here they are, and I was in
a team with Jung-hee before so...
They hugged and cried.
This is like a twist of fate.
And Hong Jung-hee, who did
you want to avoid the most?
Almeng, Bernard Park,
and the Shorties.
Not Min-ah?
I never imagined because
we used to be partners.
Jung-hee looks very
pretty today.
Thank you.
I wondered what the concept was
looking at your clothes...
But I got it after looking at
what song she's singing.
[What song is it?]
It's my hidden card!
It's going to sink or swim.
Please pay close attention
with affection.
What the judges said the most about
Jung-hee is, "What is her color?"
That was pointed out
the most for her.
[She represented Antenna Music
during the warm-up match]
She sang a ballad, her specialty,
during the warm-up match.
Unfortunately, Hong Jung-hee
takes 3rd place today.
[It seems she accepted
the result calmly]
[But she felt deep regret]
[That was eating him...]
Luckily it was only a
warm-up match, right?
[He carefully pats her so that
she won't lose confidence...]
[But the next day]
[She cries during practice]
A singer has to have a unique
voice or move the people.
But I don't have that.
All I have are techniques...
[She slowly lost self-esteem
due to worrying a long time]
This won't do.
If drastic measures aren't taken,
she will get eliminated.
[The drastic measures he took...]
I worried over this for several days.
This is just my suggestion to you.
I thought of you attempting
what you are best at.
Do you know Choi Baek-ho's
"Regarding Romantic"?
- No.
- Not at all?
[This song came out in 1995
before she was even born]
[It's an adult contemporary
contemplating on life]
[She listens to the song]
[What does she think?]
I might sing in a teuroteu style
since this is an old song.
The song is great but I thought,
"What should I do?"
What do you think?
It's good but...
I might sing in a
teuroteu style.
- Without realizing it?
- Yes.
I'm not telling you to
sing in a teuroteu style.
I thought of people's reaction
if you sing this like a ballad.
I would be surprised as a judge.
"I'm Hong Jung-hee.
Only I can do this."
I think showing such a performance
would be our strongest hand.
Great!
- Right?
- Yes.
After giving it some thought,
the moment she said yes...
That's when the burden
became bigger for me.
[Her bold challenge begins]
It's much more overwhelming
compared to before.
There's this power
that pulls us in.
He was more like a father
than a judge to me.
I was grateful.
She has to do well
and fight well.
All the hardships, sorrow, and
pain she went through...
This will be the moment when
she will run into all of that.
The weight is on both
of our shoulders.
[Will their challenge end
with a happy ending?]
Her clothes and the song
go well perfectly.
I have to tell you in advance
regarding this person.
You see her with the instrument?
It's called a bandoneon used in tango.
Helping out is Koh Sang-ji
who specializes in tango music.
Are you ready,
Hong Jung-hee?
Yes.
Break a leg!
[Her mother watches from
the monitoring room]
[She was used to be known
as a teuroteu prodigy]
[She takes courage in attempting
a genre she's familiar with]
[What will be the result?]
[Regarding Romantic - Choi Baek-ho]
[She closes her eyes gently
and immerses in the music...]
[The bandoneon echoes sadly]
[It's as if she left her
body to the music]
Thank you.
[He smiles brightly as
soon as she's done]
[But]
[They look serious!]
[Did her performance
not move them?]
[It's not easy to speak]
This is hard.
You were known as a
teuroteu prodigy, right?
Just as You Hee-yeol said...
This is a sink or swim.
He took a risk because...
I think he wanted to encourage her
to do what she does best.
Choi Baek-ho's
"Regarding Romantic"...
During my three years on KPOP STAR,
it's the first time such a song was chosen.
I never judged this before...
[Will it be a harsh criticism?]
This song might not go
together with KPOP STAR.
But...
If this was a dice
she can roll only once...
I think she swam.
[A positive commentary
for her bold attempt!]
You wore clothes that really
went well with this song.
Your gestures and look... I saw a new side
to you and how well you sing these songs.
It's my first time seeing
such a performance.
It was interesting
and I enjoyed it.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[She finally receives a
compliment from YG]
[Next is JYP!]
[Sigh]
[What's the meaning of his sigh?]
There are two people that break my
heart this season on KPOP STAR.
One is Heo Eun-yul and
the other is Jung-hee.
[What breaks JYP's heart?]
I don't know but when
I look into her eyes...
It breaks my heart.
The things that made me sad for Eun-yul
became brighter and disappeared.
But it's deepening for
Jung-hee each round.
It drives me crazy when
I look into her eyes.
"What song am I supposed to sing?"
You're still troubled by that.
[It's as if he saw
deep into her heart]
It felt like, "Okay, I'll sing
this song as best as possible."
[We can feel that they want
to help her in some way...]
Jung-hee...
The conclusion...
Your emotions have to come first.
It's not about what genre to sing.
First find what song moves you.
What song makes your heart to explode
when you listen to and sing?
Thank you.
[They gave their commentaries]
[It's now You Hee-yeol's turn!]
[What will he say?]
I cried as I watched because...
It's not due to the times we spent but
the fact that I know what you went through.
You were known as a teuroteu
prodigy since you were young.
That broke your heart.
You came on KPOP STAR
with a different genre.
But you had to meet me, of all people,
and decide on Choi Baek-ho's song.
I'm watching you from a different
angle than the other two judges.
When we think of KPOP STAR,
the music is trendy and young.
That's how all the contents were.
But...
No one can sing this
song better than you.
Compared to acting, you were
the best child actress...
And has considerable effort
compared to others.
It's as if you experienced
more than the judges here.
Despite the fact that you could
have sung this in a teuroteu style...
You controlled yourself and all of
these things moved me to tears.
So I want to lavish you
with applause.
[Heartfelt gratitude]
Good job.
[Will she advance
to the TOP10?]
Min-ah, please get ready.
[Group 2's second contestant]
[YG's Bae Min-ah (16)]
[The next stage is getting ready]
[You Hee-yeol can't take his
eyes off Hong Jung-hee]
JYP and I love Keyshia Cole's "Love."
You Hee-yeol must like it too.
I didn't want her to take on a new
challenge since she's from abroad.
I gave serious thought on what
song she could sing the best.
I thought she could sing
this song passionately.
So she focused only on
this song and practiced.
[Lee Hi was complimented first for this song
during Season 1's live broadcast]
I was worried and nervous of
being compared to Lee Hi.
[Battle audition
T-minus 3 days]
[Since she's worried, YG personally
coaches her late into the night]
I don't have much confidence.
But I was complimented as
YG gave me lessons.
I gained confidence and
I think I got better.
[KPOP STAR preliminaries at
Busan 5 months ago]
I used to sing because
I enjoyed it.
But I was complimented here and
recognized for what I'm good at.
I liked it and thought
I should become a singer.
Even though I get eliminated
at TOP9 or TOP8...
I want to enjoy the live stage
at least once in my life.
I think this is the start.
I want to think of KPOP STAR
as my beginning.
[Will her desire for the
TOP10 come to fruition?]
[Love - Keyshia Cole]
[She's completely immersed]
[She sang this distinct ad-lib
according to her feelings]
[She's singing with her soul
different from the original]
Thank you.
[It's as if she was lost in
the music and returned]
[Even her mother in the
monitoring room is relieved]
[Time for the commentaries]
This is a good example of training.
And a good example of producing.
She can do it but it felt like
there was a filter in her stage.
She could do it if that
filter is removed.
I feel better now.
[She broke through her limits!]
Vocalization and feel...
Ad-libs aren't something
that can be taught.
But there were a couple
I didn't imagine.
I loved the high notes.
It felt like all my worries
were blown away.
It was a great chemical reaction
between YG and Bae Min-ah.
It was great.
I really enjoyed it.
[The others are getting
more uneasy]
[What is YG's commentary?]
It was better than I thought.
Usually, people are worse on
stage than during practice.
She changed a couple of the lines
from last time I checked.
I don't know if you remember
but I asked for two things.
"Love" is the point so just sing it.
Don't put in any unnecessary ad-libs.
And put in your own R&B ad-lib
in the latter part of the song.
I love this arrangement.
[She interpreted it with her soul
different from the original!]
I like your version the best
out of all the versions I heard.
It was new. I didn't know you
could sing it like that.
There's Hong Jung-hee's extreme emotion
and Bae Min-ah's completely different one.
I saw two different sides.
It was the best out of all
your performances.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[They're getting more pressure]
The two contestants were complimented
and Almeng is the last contestant.
They were complimented every round.
Almeng, please get ready.
Usually, when those in front do well,
those in back get afraid and can't do it.
But I think Almeng will do better
if those in front did well.
A real superstar has to...
Hit a homer at the bottom of the 9th
with 2 outs, 2 strikes, and 3 balls.
When you're nervous and burdened.
Burden is written over his face.
[First time seeing Almeng tense]
How's your condition?
I'm at my worst.
My throat is in panic.
It doesn't feel like mine.
I went to the hospital
this morning.
I was told that there's a tear in the
mucous membrane of my vocal cords.
Maybe that's why it hurt. It hurt
yesterday when I was breathing.
[A week before the
battle audition]
[She has to sing the extreme high notes
with her throat in its worst condition]
I can't sing in falsetto.
- It sounds bad.
- It is.
[The morning of the
battle audition]
[She couldn't finish the
rehearsal due to the pain!]
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Yeah...
[She couldn't speak properly
until she got on stage]
I don't know if
we can do it.
[A desperately dangerous situation
with the TOP10 prematch ahead!]
The things we experienced in our
brief preparation as singers...
We were also pointed out
for our appearances.
It started since high school
and it's still ongoing.
Despite the good ratings I received,
it never went well in the end.
I wasn't told directly maybe
because I was a woman...
But beating around the bush made me
feel bad since I know what it's about.
I was hurt when I was young
but it hurt my mother more.
[JYP training four days
before the battle audition]
Every word of the lyrics are great.
You'll win whoever you're up against
if only the lyrics get conveyed.
Different from the previous rounds
where we just made it fun...
This time we want to say,
"Listen to our story."
God is so cruel. I don't know why
my throat is in such a condition.
I hope you'll listen without missing
a single word of the lyrics.
[They prepared more earnestly
for this performance]
[But will she be able to
finish the entire song?]
[She tries to warm up her voice]
[Ugly - 2NE1]
I start singing but
No one listens to me
I am not pretty
I am not beautiful
You sing well but
You don't fit this concept
It's not that you're bad
Being a member doesn't suit you
What must be the problem?
When I withdrew myself
Someone told me this
You have to be prettier
Since when did
Artists have to be pretty
The answers that came to me
Were always NO, you know
I'm pretty enough
To be singing
The others are just
Prettier than required
I'm getting angry
Why tell me my looks aren't enough?
This lilting voice can only come
From a gorilla-looking face
That's right
Hear my instrument
Don't approach me
I hate such attention
You'll want to use me
And train me
When you hear this song
You think I'm ugly?
This melody will change that
I'm here so listen to my voice
You still think that way?
Don't say to my face
Cause we're artists
You think I'm ugly?
My face makes an impact on stage
I'll fly great and far
Watch me to the end
So don't talk like that
Cause we're artists
You think I'm ugly?
My face makes an impact on stage
I'll fly great and far
Watch me to the end
So don't talk like that
Cause we're artists
You say "God is fair" but
It's unfair when you see us
Those thoughts make you live
Every day in this unfair world
We don't mind such attitude
Snore
[Listen to my voice...]
Do I still look ugly?
Yup!
[They lavish them with applause for
displaying their fighting spirit]
[Can't tell what they're thinking...]
I'll be frank.
This performance wasn't fun
like your other performances.
[It wasn't fun?]
But I was amazed as
I saw the lyrics.
The lyrics are well written.
What I mean by that is...
What JYP talked of the most
this season is sincerity.
You were telling your story
and not someone else's.
In this song "Ugly," you said
if you had to be pretty to sing.
Writing lyrics is as hard as
writing the music.
You can take out good words from
a book and add them to it.
But that's not important.
Is this person telling his/her story?
It's about how well one can
express those sad emotions.
Just as JYP always said,
your story was in it.
I was amazed at
Almeng's talents again.
[She cries silently]
Why are you crying?
I don't know...
A lot must be on your mind
like how hard it was...
[So many emotions went through her
as she thought of the hard times]
Alright!
Let's stop the tears.
As I listened to this song,
you asked a question at the end.
"Do I still look ugly?"
Not at all.
You're the prettiest
and the coolest.
I wanted to say that first since
you asked the question.
This is the best song out of all
that you have shown here.
The reason is...
You did a lot of songs that were
like a musical filled with ideas.
But this song didn't
have much of that.
I get surprised with the other songs
when I see them for the first time.
But I didn't want to
listen to it again.
Yet I want to listen
to this again.
You can add this song if
you produce an album.
It's like you're taking your
first step with this song.
[They can add this song to their
first album with confidence!]
I was especially moved
even more because...
Even if I was a part of this group,
the lyrics would still work out.
[JYP failed innumerable
auditions in the past]
Did you write this?
I even thought, "How did
they know my past?"
It's like this.
You couldn't sing the first verse
well due to the inflammation.
But you kept on singing the
high notes and didn't avoid it.
And it opened in the end.
[She finally overcame it!]
I think that's how
Almeng's life will be.
You hit a wall, but you keep
at it and it opens in the end.
When you sang the high notes at the end,
it worked because you didn't avoid it.
It was a great performance.
And I would like you to continue
and put on the best performance.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
I want to know
why you are crying.
Choi Rin, tell us
[She kept on crying during
the commentaries]
- Since I couldn't sing...
- Because your throat hurt.
When I sang the high notes...
[Her throat was in its worst condition.
"Maybe this is as far as I go..."]
Because it didn't come out...
I screamed my lungs out.
You sang it well. Right?
It came out well in the end.
She's upset.
That's when I felt like crying.
It's fortunate you got good results
despite your bad condition.
- You did great.
- Thank you.
[They now discuss to choose
who makes it to the TOP10!]
Will the other two join
them on stage?
This is really...
It's as we expected.
[It's hard to choose
who was better!]
Since they all have different
colors, this is really...
Let's make this simple.
Who is first among them?
This is hard...
It's a shame because
this one did better.
[The discussion gets longer]
[They give much thought
since the battle was fierce]
[Discussion is finally over]
[What is the result of
the long discussion?]
It was hard for us because all
three turned things around.
First, we expected an exciting
performance from Almeng...
But they shocked us
with a serious song.
We wondered if Bae Min-ah could go
to the next level as a singer.
But she showed us how she
took that leap overnight.
And we knew Jung-hee sang well
but not to this extent.
We really want all
three to pass.
But we have to rank you.
We'll announce the first place
we decided in our discussion.
The TOP10 finalist is...
It's Almeng.
Congratulations.
What we never imagined
just happened.
I don't think it hit me yet.
I'm really happy but because
I was crying before...
I never imagined we'd
make it this far.
[Time to announce
who's eliminated]
The one that takes 2nd
will have a rematch.
The one that takes 3rd is
unfortunately eliminated.
[The judges know the result]
Since both of you went through
a lot to make it this far...
It's hard for us to
let one of you go.
3rd place is...
[Announcement for 3rd place!]
[Who will be eliminated?]
Hong Jung-hee.
[Hong Jung-hee is eliminated]
[Her mother confirmed
her elimination]
[She tries to remain calm]
You did great.
You really did.
Your wanderings...
How you feel lost...
We feel it because all three of us
worried about that once in our life.
"What music should I do?"
We all have that worry.
You didn't say much about it, but
your worries were conveyed to us.
You would have made it to the TOP10
if you were not in this group.
Thank you.
I think You Hee-yeol would
have something to say.
[He can't bear to see her
with tears on his face]
Jung-hee, you really did well.
It might be weird to say this...
But I think you should cheer Hee-yeol
and not the other way around.
I'll come on your show.
You did well.
You really did.
I really like your attitude
and the way you sing.
I'm the one who actually learned
a lot during those 3 weeks.
In the future, whether you're on
another stage or a recording studio...
Just as we practiced, you will
be singing along a piano...
I'll be playing the piano
when that time comes.
Promise to meet again.
Thank you.
Good job.
[Seeing her for the last time...]
Let's take a break.
[She tried to hold it in...]
You Hee-yeol treated me more like
a daughter than a student.
We became close the
past 3 weeks.
Just as he said, I'll be a
great artist somewhere.
I would like to see him
again on stage.
You did great, my daughter.
Subtitles by SBS International