Episode 17
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3!
I introduce you to the TOP8 finalists
that advanced to the live stage!
A warm round of applause for them
that made it after 8 long months!
Happy to be here.
I'm greeting you live.
Welcome to the first live stage
for KPOP STAR Season 3.
I'm Jun Hyun-moo the
mascot for KPOP STAR.
Glad to be here.
They were chosen by the three judges and
the audience judging panel last week.
These 8 teams received the honor
of performing on the live stage.
Since they came this far
after a fierce competition...
We look forward to their
performances today.
There will be 5 live shows
including the one today.
Then Season 3's winner
will be determined.
Please tune in to all 5 shows!
The winner of KPOP STAR Season 3
will be awarded a cash prize of $300,000.
And receive a mid-size and
compact diesel sedan.
I'll introduce the three judges that are
gaining as much attention as the finalists.
They're like parents.
First is JYPE's Park Jin-young!
YGE's Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Music's You Hee-yeol!
Good to see you three.
You must be pleased looking
at the TOP8 finalists.
They should be nervous right now.
Any words for them, YG?
JYP is currently a singer and You Hee-yeol
hosts a live show so they're less nervous.
I do a live show only once a year
and that is here on KPOP STAR.
They must be really nervous since my heart
was pounding before coming up here.
They might not see
or hear anything.
All of you made it this far
because you are all good.
Please give us a good performance.
Thank you.
You Hee-yeol is on this live show
for the first time with me.
Are you nervous?
Yes, I wasn't able to sleep.
You weren't able to sleep again?
I'm getting thinner.
But they must be more nervous.
Why don't we give them a hand?
I see you're trying to
make them relax.
And don't cry You Hee-yeol
because this is live.
JYP, I heard there's a reason why
this season has the most tension.
It's because the winner of this season
gets to announce their agency of choice.
So we three judges are nervous.
I think I should talk less about their
bad points and start complimenting.
I guess you'll finally
understand how they feel.
Starting this season, the judges will
be waiting desperately to get picked.
We'll now begin today's battle.
Curious? I'll show you
how it's done.
Let's watch how the
battle is done.
[T-minus 6 days to
the live show]
[The TOP8 wait in tension]
OMG! He scared me!
[Surprise appearance by
MC Jun Hyun-moo]
I'm happy to see you. Congratulations
and give yourselves a big hand.
[Congratulations to the TOP8]
Do you have any idea
why you are here?
This week is the live show.
We're choosing the order for the
live show and it'll be a 1:1 battle.
Today's a very important day where
you choose your opponent.
You have to choose from these 8 envelopes
and the one you pick is your opponent.
Who'll go first?
I'll go.
[Almeng has nerves of steel
and goes first again!]
[Those watching and choosing
are both very nervous!]
Since you do a diverse performance,
from a viewer's standpoint...
It'll be great if you went
head on with the Shorties.
Who's the best performer on stage?
I want you to go against the Shorties.
This one?
[Who is Almeng's opponent?]
[Almeng chose the 3rd envelope]
Hae-yong, pick another one.
- Pick another one.
- Should I?
Do you want to?
- They're all the same...
- I'll go with that.
Here I go!
- Can't he change it now?
- Nope. It's too late.
Man, you should let him.
[A battle between pros
Almeng vs Heejun Han]
[A bolt from the blue]
[They're stupefied]
I said to pick the 2nd one!
I said pick the 2nd one...
My eyes told him not to pick it
and I even shouted it out.
But he did it.
I have fear whether
I could beat them...
And sadness that I need to
compete against Hae-yong.
[Second is Sam Kim]
[They are all likely winners]
[He chose the middle one]
[Who is his opponent?]
[A battle between guitarists
Sam Kim vs Kwon Jina]
[Sam Kim's opponent is
Kwon Jina the dark horse]
[Third are the Shorties!]
[Only Bae Mina, Bernard Park,
and Jang Hanna are left]
[Who did they boldly choose?]
- I'm having indigestion.
- Are you really?
Really? Is it because this is
going to be you or not?
It shouldn't be you?
[Best friends and same age
The Shorties vs Jang Hanna]
For real?
The Shorties are really good.
I didn't want to battle them.
I'm burdened since this is 1:1.
[A battle between soul singers
Bae Mina vs Bernard Park]
- I think I lost.
- Why?
- He's really good.
- Because he's good?
[Even he's at a loss...]
I can't believe this!
At least you got 3rd place.
I was a candidate for elimination.
[No one can predict the
outcome of these battles]
[Heejun Han vs Almeng]
[Sam Kim vs Kwon Jina]
[Jang Hanna vs The Shorties]
[Bae Mina vs Bernard Park]
[The battle will begin soon!]
As you have just watched, they
chose their opponents in advance.
The 4 victors from the 4 battles will
advance to the TOP6 live show next week.
The 4 that lost will become
candidates for elimination.
Real-time voting by the viewers and the judges'
decision will determine who is eliminated.
It's going to be a 1:1 battle and
I'll repeat the order once more.
The first battle is...
No. 1 Heejun Han goes beyond
his limits in every performance.
No. 2 Almeng is a mixed duet
full of character and skilled.
The second battle is...
No. 3 Sam Kim is a guitar whiz.
No. 4 Kwon Jina is a dark
horse with a charming voice.
This is a battle between
guitar geniuses.
The third battle is...
No. 5 Jang Hanna is the
possesser of a soulful voice.
No. 6 The Shorties are hardworking
with a fantastic harmony.
This is a battle between
girls of the same age.
And the last battle is...
No. 7 Bae Mina is an R&B diva
making a sudden emergence.
No. 8 Bernard Park has a sweet
voice that sways women's hearts.
It's going to be a close match
where the outcome is unpredictable.
It's hard to decide the outcome.
What do you, the viewers, think?
You can participate by
text voting in real time.
Anchor Yoo Hye-young will explain
how text voting is done.
Yoo Hye-young?
Things are heating up here.
Glad to be here. I'm anchor
Yoo Hye-young here live.
Your votes are very important.
I'll explain how you can vote.
Text the contestant's name in Korean or
their number to #0606 on your phone.
Please keep in mind that you can
vote for more than one contestant.
But you cannot make multiple
votes for one contestant.
Since voting is possible via KakaoTalk,
those abroad can also participate.
We will now begin the TOP8 battles
for KPOP STAR Season 3.
The first battle is very intense.
It's Heejun Han with unlimited potential
against Almeng the fantastic duo.
Text voting begins now!
[Text voting begins]
[Text the contestant's name in Korean or
number to #0606 (10 cents data charge)]
[Heejun Han]
[Almeng]
[Heejun Han vs Almeng]
I personally wanted to avoid Almeng
when I heard it was a 1:1 battle.
I'm really close to Hae-yong,
a member of Almeng.
He's like a little brother.
He's very kind and
takes good care of us.
He's very playful.
[I'm sorry]
I felt a connection with him
the moment we started rooming.
It's ironic but I'm fortunate
to go against Almeng.
I'll battle fair and square
with my favorite team.
There's nothing for me to lose
whether I win or lose.
So I look forward to
a great performance.
[He receives Heejung's song choice]
[What song is it?]
He sings my songs well.
Maybe we have similar sentiments.
[JYP's "Your House"]
I don't know how he'll sing this
because most of it is in falsetto.
I don't know if he'll sing in
falsetto or in his voice.
It's unpredictable.
I wanted to express a man's cry
who is deep in sorrow.
There's going to be
a grand orchestra.
I had this desire to make
something like a musical.
This is going to be a challenge
but what about 8 beats like rock?
I won't hold back and will show
everything I have on stage.
I'll show everything
without regrets.
[No. 1 Heejun Han]
[Your House - JYP]
[Music director - Kwon Tae-eun
Bandmaster - Seo Young-do]
He should have been nervous for
going first on the live stage.
Another round of applause
for Heejun Han please.
He sang JYP's song
in his own color.
But what did the judges think?
Let's hear the commentaries.
I'll go first.
I found out this song can be dramatic
after watching your performance.
The arrangement went beyond
what this song originally has.
This live stage expressed the sadness
in the song most dramatically.
It was very good that I wanted to
recommend JYP to use it in his concert.
I always say this but
you are smart.
You know how to create such a stage and
convey your voice, maybe it's experience.
You need that in music because
you are creating your own story.
I truly enjoyed it.
Good job.
I was actually worried
when you chose this song.
What if he dances as
he sings like JYP?
I hate this "house"
move the most.
It was an appropriate amount. He just
danced where it was needed most.
I don't know why but many contestants
on KPOP STAR sing JYP's songs.
But it's always better than
JYP's performance.
It's easy to be better.
I expected several things that
he would do with this song.
But his performance was very fresh
because it wasn't how I expected it.
He looked the most relaxed out of
all his performances. Good job.
I agree with what they said.
You looked relaxed and the
performance was awesome.
But the unfortunate thing
was your voice.
It felt like you were
singing with a deep voice.
I like it when you sing comfortably
as if you are speaking.
But you sang throughout
in a deep voice.
So I wasn't able to hear
your voice that I like.
It's a pity that you didn't sing
comfortably as if you were speaking.
If you do advance, sing
as if you are speaking.
It's most Heejunesque when you sing
comfortably in a voice as if humming.
Those cheering for Heejun Han can
text "1" or "Heejun Han" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Heejun Han!
[Checking Almeng's song choice]
Really?
They're singing this?
[Panic's "Bus Stop"]
Since Almeng has a remarkable ability
to make any song into their own...
I look forward to how
they'll arrange this.
Almeng has a distinctive
feature in their genre.
I don't know how they'll interpret
this or create their performance...
Since this song is mainly vocals.
[What is Almeng's plan amidst such
anticipation and concerns?]
There's more singing. There is
rapping but it's just an element.
We're a team but we haven't
sung in harmony before.
We're trying hard to
show our singing.
I wanted to hear at least once how
they'll sound if they sing sincerely.
They'll win if they sing well.
[Who is the "you" in the song
that Almeng is thinking?]
We agreed to never talk about
our mom on KPOP STAR.
It's obvious and everyone's
grateful to their mom...
We searched for that "you."
Who could that "you" be?
It would be a lie if
it isn't our mom.
Of course, we're grateful to
all the mothers in the world.
I should say "thank you" more often
but couldn't because I got used to it.
It's overwhelming
every time we sing.
My heart is pounding
when we're done.
It hurts... I don't know what it is but
I think we can sing from the heart.
[No. 2 Almeng]
[Bus Stop - Panic]
You finally found me
And silently smiled
That smile finally spoke
"It's okay. Good job."
It was faintly rolling
My lips opened and it ran down
You are clear to me
But now it's clearer
You blamed others and not me
I was foolish for lamenting
You said I will shine
To cast away the sadness
I was harsh and made excuses
I hurt you and made you cry
Now I lean against you
I alluded all hardships to you
Now I will never think
Que sera sera.
This was a moving stage
by No. 2 Almeng.
Let's hear the commentaries.
I think it's getting harder
to judge because...
There's a certain emotion and we also need
to find the reason why in such a short time.
Why did we like it and why
did we think it was a pity?
Both of you sing very well and
have solid fundamentals.
It was great that
I could feel that again.
But there's one thing.
The world of singers need Almeng,
but when you sang this song...
Whether it's a fast song, slow song
or a ballad, we need Almeng.
I wasn't excited because
I couldn't find your unique color.
I felt that you are needed in the world of
singers when you first sang "Blurred Lines."
It's a pity that I couldn't
find your unique color.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
There were many times when JYP
and I had conflicting opinions.
It's the same for Almeng.
I liked it because your
uniqueness wasn't there.
I thought you didn't have any skills and were
trying to cover that with your uniqueness.
You made a good plan today.
Not only do you put on an enjoyable
performance, you showed you have skills.
With the right mix, you can satisfy
both JYP and me next time.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
This battle is really hard to judge since
these two teams are the most professional.
This is not a song that a mixed duet
can sing but you arranged it well.
You rapped in the middle and I thought if
that would go with this song but you did it.
I had the same thought as YG.
You usually presented a fun
performance but in this stage...
Wow. They can also sing.
They can sing ballads.
I wondered what your limit is.
I look forward to it.
You did well.
Thank you.
Those cheering for Almeng can
text "2" or "Almeng" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Almeng!
You just watched the first battle of the
live show between Heejun Han and Almeng.
The decision won't be easy since
they are the most professional.
One of them will advance to the
TOP6 live show next week and...
The other will be a candidate for elimination
waiting the judges' and viewers' decision.
Please announce the results
if you are ready.
I'll go first.
Both did well so it
was hard to choose.
We need to be objective but we
couldn't ignore our preferences.
The victor chosen by
Antenna Music is...
Heejun Han! Congratulations!
Antenna Music chose Heejun Han.
Let's hear the other judges.
Both had a twist in
their performances.
My standard is...
Heejun Han had a twist
in his song choice.
Almeng had a twist by getting rid of
the prejudice against singers.
I choose Almeng for having
a comprehensive twist.
YG chose Almeng.
Their scores are tied.
JYP's choice will determine who
advances to the live show next week.
Who does JYP choose?
Since both had their pros and cons,
I would like to give them the same score.
But only one can be chosen.
Considering their overall performances...
I thought of who would have a slightly
higher chance in having a twist next time.
I choose Almeng as the victor.
It's Almeng!
They won the first battle and advance
to next week's TOP6 live show.
Heejun Han is not eliminated.
He's a candidate for elimination.
Those cheering for Heejun Han can
still vote by texting to #0606.
Let's now begin the second battle of
KPOP STAR Season 3's live show.
The second battle is between
Sam Kim and Kwon Jina.
[Sam Kim]
[Kwon Jina]
[Sam Kim vs Kwon Jina]
It'll be hard for me to win
whoever I'm up against.
[When opponents were announced]
I didn't like it.
I'm done for!
What do I do?
Sam is the one I feared the most.
I first saw him in Round 1.
I happened to hear him practicing
and he plays very well.
I thought he was in college
but he was younger than me.
That's when I thought someone
that young can play like that.
I think this will be the most
dangerous round for Sam because...
Kwon Jina's rise is amazing.
But there's a variable.
We don't know how Sam will
change since he's young.
[What song did Sam Kim choose that
went beyond everyone's expectation?]
[Michael Jackson's "Billie Jean"]
[Moonwalk and spin dance became well-known
in this masterpiece by the "King of Pop"]
This song can be sung with
feel and not vocal skills.
So it gives Sam the highest
possible chance to win.
I never heard "Billie Jean"
sung to a guitar.
I'll get that chance now...
To hear "Billie Jean"
played by a 16-year-old.
[How would "Billie Jean"
sound on a guitar?]
You'll be singing before
thousands of people.
Thousands?
Where are they from?
Why is there so many?
I'm really nervous and
I don't know if I can do well.
[No. 3 Sam Kim]
This was his rendition with
excellent grooving on the guitar.
This stage was by
No. 3 Sam Kim!
Let's hear the commentaries.
The guitar playing during
the interlude was shocking.
Putting the notes aside, he was
playing along such amazing beats.
I have nothing more to say about your
musicality. I compliment you on that.
Now, only if your singing...
I'm not saying it's bad. If you
just learn the fundamentals...
If you learn breathing and singing,
you'll be a force to reckon with.
Your singing was a slight pity.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
Sam was like a soul musician
who's been playing for years.
He was also like a folk
or rock 'n' roll singer.
I can't believe a 16-year-old
can have such groove.
Just as JYP said, I don't know how to
play the guitar but I can hear it.
It's amazing he could play like that
on a live stage before many people.
I'm more curious how he'll be
in a year and not right now.
Just as JYP said, if you get the singing down,
you'll be world best and not only in Korea.
Good job.
All my prejudice were broken down
as I became a judge for KPOP STAR.
I rarely watched auditions and thought
everyone would be at a certain level.
My thoughts for this season is that
young people today are so good.
I'm amazed every time at
how good they are.
Today's K-pop is
mostly computerized.
Even GD, for example, even though he's
Korea's top producer and performer.
I firmly believe that you'll develop a
new genre in K-pop with your guitar.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "3" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 3 Sam Kim!
[Kwon Jina suddenly
emerged as a likely winner!]
Kwon Jina's rise is amazing.
Kwon Jina is in her prime.
There are no holes in
her fundamentals.
[She's rapidly rising and the
first to advance to the TOP8!]
I'm happy because I didn't
expect this at all but...
I'm worried whether I can do
better than the previous round.
[TOP8's practice room]
There are rumors that
Sam is doing very well...
What are you doing?
Why do you ask?
Show me a little. Just the
beginning first 3 seconds.
[Are you playing with me?]
- Just a little more...
- How about the middle?
You want a beating?
He showed others but
he didn't show me.
- Did you show him yours?
- Nope. Never.
[What's her ace that she's
been hiding until now?]
[Sunmi's "24 Hours"]
[A shocking "sexy dance"
stands out in this song]
I've seen clips of
Kwon Jina singing.
She arranges the song well that
we forget the original singer.
I look forward to how
she'll change my song.
Is she singing barefoot?
The choreography is
important in this song.
I wonder if she can give the same
inspiration with just her guitar.
I look forward to it.
I didn't know I would
make it this far.
I'll do my best and enjoy it
since I came this far.
I'll show my version of "24 Hours."
Please look forward to it.
[No. 4 Kwon Jina]
[24 Hours - Sunmi]
This stage was by No. 4 Kwon Jina who
changed a dance song to an acoustic.
What commentaries did the
judges make? Let's hear it.
I don't know if I can say this but
I think Kwon Jina is crazy.
Kwon Jina is currently the only one
who can change her tone skillfully.
She changed the tone and sang the
high notes in her voice and in falsetto.
All the notes in the ad-lib
at the end were perfect.
Even her sense of rhythm when
she played the dotted 24th note...
She played the shuffle exactly
like a professional musician.
The shocking thing, as a composer...
The third chord she played
was a minor sixth.
But she changed it to a major.
Her sense of arrangement is...
Musicality, guitar playing, sense of rhythm,
vocalization, musical interpretation...
It was a perfect performance.
If I were to score you, I would have
given you the highest score possible.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
I laugh when JYP talks about sixth or
seventh (in Korean it ends with "do")...
I know Jeolla-do and
Gyeongsang-do but...
This battle was between
Sam Kim and Kwon Jina.
If a comparison is made...
Sam Kim has a fancy groove while
Kwon Jina has a stable groove.
Since Sam Kim's groove is fancy,
I have to pay attention or I'll miss it.
What is he going to do next?
I don't need to do that for Kwon Jina
because it just comes to me.
I feel comfortable
so I hate her.
If she lacks in something, I can point
that out and do my thing as a judge.
But it was a stable performance
without lackings. Good job.
- You're really good.
- Thank you.
I trained both Sam Kim
and Kwon Jina.
I was really nervous when
she chose this song.
I thought she made the wrong
choice, but lo and behold.
It's ridiculous that I worry
about her when she's this good.
Putting musicality, guitar
playing and everything aside...
According to my preference, she's the
best vocalist among the contestants here.
You feel like listening to her.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
I have a question.
Did you change the chord or was it
a suggestion by the musicians?
I did it.
Those cheering for Kwon Jina can
text "4" or "Kwon Jina" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 4 Kwon Jina!
The second battle was between
Sam Kim and Kwon Jina.
It was a battle between
two guitar genuises.
Since both received compliments,
we're curious of the outcome.
Please announce the result.
The victor I choose is...
I'm sorry Sam but Jina
was better. It's Kwon Jina.
JYP chose Kwon Jina.
Next?
Antenna Music...
I can't believe this.
The victor chosen by
Antenna Music is Kwon Jina.
It's Kwon Jina again.
YG?
It's a pity for Sam because he lost
even though he did his best.
I also choose Kwon Jina.
Kwon Jina advances to next
week's TOP6 live show.
KPOP STAR is where Sam Kim can
become a candidate for elimination.
That's how high the standard is.
Please watch to see the outcome.
Let's now begin the third battle of
KPOP STAR Season 3's live show.
It's between Jang Hanna
and the Shorties!
[Jang Hanna]
[The Shorties]
[Jang Hanna vs The Shorties]
[After opponents were picked]
[They're speechless]
I'm close to them. I visit their room
often to play, talk, and chat.
I'm battling them...
this is unbelievable.
Less than a week left
until the live show.
Why don't we cheer up by
dancing like crazy?
[Tae-kyung's sudden proposal
to liven up the mood!]
[We are KPOP STAR's diva!]
[And!]
[She's here!]
Should I start over?
[OMG]
[Kwon Jina the growling goddess!]
[Group dancing to blow
their worries away]
[Hanna looks brighter now...]
[They're back to being
their cheerful selves...]
[Unavoidable battle!
What is her song choice?]
I'm going to sing Yoon Mirae's
"Good Bye Sadness, Hello Happiness."
I practiced to become the main person
of this song and lose myself.
I think it's a good choice.
I think she can come out saying
"I'm Jang Hanna" with this song.
I do well during practice but
get nervous up on the stage.
I'm worried that I have
stage fright.
I read the lyrics and practiced
putting in emotion while singing.
I did a lot of image training so
that I'm ready to sing whenever.
I'll be confident and show
that I can enjoy this time.
I want to make it
to the TOP6.
[No. 5 Jang Hanna]
This stage was by No. 5 Jang Hanna
with a soulful voice and sentiment.
Let's hear the commentaries.
We three judges always talk about
you when the recording is over.
If she could only properly use
that million dollar voice.
She could unleash it if she adds
only passion and emotion into it.
You do have a million dollar voice.
All you need is to open your mouth.
It always wasn't enough but...
Out of all your performances,
this one hit the spot.
But...
It's still a pity.
You're still in your right mind.
How do we know that?
I want you to be excited and your gestures
to be out of control somewhere in the song.
You improved a lot and
showed your potential but...
We can tell if you're in your right mind
or not by looking at your gestures.
But you made remarkable progress.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
You felt it was a pity and even cried
that you can't unleash your potential.
Stick a flower in your head next time
to show JYP that you lost yourself.
I was joking.
I think today was your
best performance ever.
Thank you.
You have a great voice and timbre
that we judges talk about.
I think this was a song where
you could show all of that.
I believe you'll become uncontrollable
once you're on an upward swing.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
I agree more with JYP.
The expression that you should
look like you're not there...
You shouldn't be there when you
are singing but somewhere else.
You have to fall into the
meaning of the lyrics...
Then the gestures become natural.
The subtle movement of the eyebrows,
breathing and such allow you to empathize.
Yes, you did sing the best
out of all the songs you chose.
It's a pity that you didn't have
the power to pull us in.
I want to see your performance where
I get pulled in as soon as possible.
But you did well.
Good job.
Those cheering for Jang Hanna can
text "5" or "Jang Hanna" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 5 Jang Hanna!
[I. The Shorties Begins]
Our teacher called us shorties
when we walked side by side.
You three are really short.
You really are shorties.
We accepted it the moment
we heard it. It's inevitable.
[That's how the Shorties were born!]
[II. The Shorties Rise]
[In the waiting room
during the last battle]
You'll fly when I hit you.
[Last night at their lodging]
Good night. Bye.
They can't go to sleep
now because of us.
Sorry.
Song choice is the most
important for this team.
Wow...
Really?
For real?
I didn't expect this.
I thought someone would
sing this song but...
The Shorties are singing
"Let It Go."
[Including Hyolyn of SISTAR!]
[Many singers went wild
over this song!]
I never heard an a cappella or
harmony version of "Let It Go."
Many female solo artists sang this
to show off their singing skills.
But I think the Shorties'
version will be very good.
[A certain day before the battle]
What do we wear?
- Frozen's...
- Elsa's dress?
You have to wear it since
you're in the middle.
[They search Elsa's dress!]
We picked a dress that make
us look like a goddess...
- I said not to use that word.
- Alright, alright.
Say that it's soft and light.
- Don't have such a mind.
- That word is dangerous.
[It sure is soft and light]
The live show begins once
we leave this room.
We'll do our best to do well and
put on a good performance.
[No. 6 The Shorties]
[Let It Go - Idina Menzel]
You just heard a harmony
version of "Let It Go."
What did the judges think of
No. 6 The Shorties' stage?
Let's hear the commentaries.
This wasn't an easy choice and
I believe you knew that.
Many female artists sing this song
to show, "Hey, I'm a great singer."
You chose a song with a
high level of difficulty.
None of the contestants here, except
for you, could sing this song.
Due to the high level of difficulty,
I felt uneasy at certain parts.
But that's not important.
What's important is how well you
sang the parts you sing well.
When you sang the climax, it was
as beautiful as Yuna Kim's jump.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
It was better than your
previous two performances.
You sang much better.
Our hearts are open due to your
efforts and the thought you put in.
After I told Na-jin to breathe
from her belly and not chest...
She never breathed from her
chest. That's what's amazing.
But why am I not KO'd despite
the fact that you sing well?
There are many great singers
all over the world.
What happened to your way of speaking?
The Shorties' way of speaking...
I think that's what's
keeping me together.
Be like the new generation you are.
There are already many great singers...
You have your generation's way of speaking,
pronunciation, and expression different from them.
I hope you bring that.
As your singing improves,
my heart doesn't flutter as much.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
I think I heard "Let It Go"
the most among the 3 judges.
My daughter...
Now that there's VOD service...
She wears the same princess dress
and dances along it day and night.
I hear it in the restroom and when
I go to bed. I'm sick of it now.
"Let It Go" played a big role in
making the movie a success.
So I had high hopes
for the Shorties.
I thought, "How much will they move
me with their singing abilities?"
Your harmony wasn't as beautiful as
I wanted due to the size of this place.
JYP's commentary would have been better if
you sang your very own touching harmony.
It was a pity because
I had high expectations.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Those cheering for the Shorties can
text "6" or "The Shorties" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 6 The Shorties!
Isn't this cruel? This was a battle
between friends of the same age.
This is like an Elsa Beauty Pageant with
four Elsas here. They're very beautiful.
This was a cruel match...
But one team will advance and the other
will be a candidate for elimination.
Please announce the result.
Today's performance was their best
compared to their recent performances.
But both teams' color, emotion,
and individuality were a pity.
So I chose the one that
sang a little better.
I choose the Shorties
as the victor.
JYP chose the Shorties.
You Hee-yeol?
They're all basically good
if they're in the TOP8.
The difference is who was
less or more nervous.
The victor chosen by
Antenna Music is...
Jang Hanna.
It's Jang Hanna!
Currently, it's a tie.
YG's decision will now determine
who advances to the live show.
What is YG's choice?
To be honest, this is really hard.
I gave much thought and finally
made a decision right now.
I gave 51 points to the team whose
performance I want to see next time.
The victor I chose is...
The Shorties.
It's the Shorties! They advance
to next week's TOP6 live show!
Jang Hanna is a candidate
for elimination.
Those cheering for Jang Hanna
can still vote by texting to #0606.
They're congratulating and
cheering up each other.
Let's now begin the last battle.
The fourth battle is between
Bae Mina and Bernard Park.
[Bernard Park]
[Bae Mina]
[Bae Mina vs Bernard Park]
I said that Bernard Park was a
heavyweight compared to boxing.
Then that would make
Bae Mina a lightweight.
I think this battle would put
her at a disadvantage.
Mina has to put on her
best performance ever.
[Her worst crisis ever!
How is she feeling?]
[Sigh]
I thought, "What do I do?
I'm going to be eliminated."
I think this will be my last.
[What song will she sing
thinking this is her last?]
[Mariah Carey's "Whenever You Call"]
[Subtle R&B sentiments and
ad-libs stand out in this song]
If I can sing the beginning in detail
and the high notes well later on...
I think it'll be a good performance
and that's why I chose this song.
She'll sing this well.
Her attempt is close to
being a miracle.
But she does have a chance.
I received many compliments
from the beginning.
But it seems that Bae Mina
is improving every time.
I don't know what
will happen.
[She's really worried but
she has a big support]
My dad always told me to focus
on my studies and not singing.
He came for the first time during
the TOP10 performance.
I think he changed his mind.
He called me saying that my
studies are important but...
Since I made it this far,
I should focus on singing.
I was happy. I felt I was being
recognized and he was proud.
I want to go up on stage
and make my family proud.
[No. 7 Bae Mina]
Thank you.
This stage was by No. 7 Bae Mina
who sang with a unique timbre.
Let's hear the commentaries.
This was your best so far.
But...
People don't sing well because
they are great singers.
There is a way of singing
being led by one's emotions.
Even though the same high notes
were sung exceptionally well...
A song that is sung by thinking,
"I need to sing well" and...
A song that is led when one's
emotions run high are different.
Since you're still young...
you're only 16 right now.
You sing as if you're studying.
"I should sing this like this."
What I want to see next time...
Let your emotions lead the song.
Some contestants sang poorly but got
high scores because of their emotions.
I hope you can think about it.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
You were pitted in an
unfavorable pool.
As you said in the clip
before coming on stage...
You said you'll sing as if
this was your last.
Instead of listening to you sing,
I felt sad after hearing that.
It felt like you were
telling the truth.
You're the youngest from the TOP8
and even shorter than the Shorties.
I sympathize with you.
I'm already sad that you
might be eliminated.
I compliment you highly
on doing your best.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
I'm not sad.
I'm happy because
she did well.
Thank you.
If you do become a singer later on,
you think the others sing well, right?
But there's something
only you are good at.
You're the best in singing the high notes
of an R&B song in a pretty way.
Don't be envious and try to
be good at everything.
Even singers might or might not
get a good song in their lifetime.
They can be loved or not
by that one hit song.
Trust in yourself because
you have the talent.
- Just do music.
- Thank you.
- I enjoyed it.
Those cheering for Bae Mina can
text "7" or "Bae Mina" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 7 Bae Mina!
[Bernard was always complimented but
barely made it from being eliminated]
Of course, I'm thankful.
[What is Bernard singing?]
I'm singing Michael Buble's "Home."
[The song is about longing for
home after a long journey]
[When he first arrived in
Korea last October]
[His childhood in the States]
[The other contestants meet their
family after every round is over]
[To his parents who weren't
able to come to Korea]
[No. 8 Bernard Park]
This last stage was by No.8 Bernard Park
whose voice melts women's hearts.
Let's hear the commentaries.
I don't think you saw
that behind you.
It was a clip of you
when you left home.
I almost cried again.
I see that you're back.
Thank you.
I was worried because you
looked gloomy and depressed.
But I think you found it
with this song.
It was the best!
Thank you.
Putting aside whether
you sang well or not...
I felt sad. I don't even know
the lyrics of this song.
But I felt sad.
I want to go home.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
We three judges gave you a very bad
commentary in the past two rounds.
Your singing was dead
and it didn't move us.
I thought about it.
You can't even speak
properly in Korean.
We're comfortable in Korean but
you're comfortable in English.
It's impossible for you to get
the emotion in Korean.
So your singing was dead but
when you sang in English...
My body froze when you sang
you wanted to go home.
As I said earlier, your emotions
were leading the song today.
It was truly...
The best performance.
Thank you.
You sang gayo in the
last two performances.
What JYP said is correct.
I wouldn't give the same feeling
if I sang in English. It's the same.
When I heard you're singing "Home,"
just as I worried about Bae Mina...
I was thinking, "Take it easy."
It was the best out of all
your performances.
You stole my heart the most
with today's performance.
It was a great performance.
And for your next one...
Don't sing gayo because you
can't even speak Korean well.
Sing what you're good at.
Then it'll be competitive.
It was a great performance.
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "8" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 8 Bernard Park!
The final battle of this live show was
between Bae Mina and Bernard Park.
These two possess R&B sentiments.
I wonder what the outcome will be.
Let's hear what the result is.
Please make the announcement.
You Hee-yeol said that
Bernard is back but...
I'm back. Beraholic is back.
I choose Bernard Park
as the victor.
It's Bernard Park! Congratulations!
Bernard got one vote. You Hee-yeol?
Antenna Music chooses
Bernard Park as the victor.
It's Bernard Park! YG?
Not only the three judges, but I think
even the viewers would think the same.
Today is Bernard Park's
complete victory.
Good job.
This makes Bernard the fourth to
advance to the TOP6 live show.
Bae Mina is not eliminated but
a candidate for elimination.
Please continue texting
your votes to #0606.
Heejun Han, Sam Kim, Jang Hanna, and
Bae Mina are candidates for elimination.
Voting is still in progress so
please text your votes to #0606.
Many celebrities came to the
live show of KPOP STAR.
Let's call Yoo Hye-young.
Are you there?
This is already a festive party
filled with cheers and tears.
I'm Yoo Hye-young here live
where things are heating up.
Almeng, Kwon Jina, the Shorties,
and Bernard Park advanced.
Heejun Han, Sam Kim, Jang Hanna, and
Bae Mina are candidates for elimination.
Their fate is now in your hands.
If you didn't vote, please do so.
We have welcome guests today.
Hello Hyolyn.
Hi, I'm Hyolyn of SISTAR.
How was the performance?
I always feel their passion and
love for music and singing.
Thank you for such happy
performances. Thank you.
Thank you to Sunmi and Orange
Caramel for coming as well.
We're here live and will show the highlight
clips of the elimination candidates soon.
Voting will end at the same
time the clip is over.
Please hurry with the votes.
Here are the highlight clips.
[No. 1 Heejun Han]
[No. 3 Sam Kim]
[No. 5 Jang Hanna]
[No. 7 Bae Mina]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[Voting is over]
[Live from KINTEX]
All the battles are now over.
I would like to thank the viewers
again for participating by voting.
The candidates for elimination are Heejun Han,
Sam Kim, Jang Hanna, and Bae Mina.
I'll announce just one person chosen
by the viewers to advance to TOP6.
I'll announce who among the four gets to
advance to next week's TOP6 live show.
I received an envelope but do not know
the result because I didn't open it.
I'll open it now.
I'll announce who among the four gets to
advance to next week's TOP6 live show.
The 5th TOP6 finalist determined by
the highest total of real-time votes is...
I'll announce it now!
Among the four...
1st goes to...
Sam Kim!
Sam Kim received the most votes.
Please move over there
with the other finalists.
Alright. Sam Kim is the 5th to receive
the honor of advancing to the TOP6.
Among the remaining three, only one
can advance to the TOP6 live show.
And the remaining two will
depart from KPOP STAR.
Alright.
Heejun Han, Jang Hanna, and Bae Mina
are waiting for the judges' decision.
Sam Kim is in the winners seat
due to the viewers' votes.
Only one from the remaining three
will go to next week's TOP6 live show.
Today will be the last
for the remaining two.
What decision did
the judges make?
Please announce the result
if you are done discussing.
Even the viewers will have conflicting
opinions since no one thinks alike.
I felt pity for Bae Mina
and said she'll go far.
I had my eyes on Jang Hanna
during this season.
And Heejun Han had
many complications.
I think only the strong
can survive now.
Since the next round is
going to be more intense.
The last TOP6 finalist
chosen by the judges is...
Heejun Han.
Heejun Han is the last finalist!
Jang Hanna and Bae Mina are leaving
KPOP STAR with today's performance.
They went through a lot.
Please come and cheer them up.
They really did go through a lot.
Congratulations to Heejun Han
once again for advancing.
The judges have mixed feelings but
say a word for Bae Mina and Jang Hanna.
We are not that disappointed
even though you are leaving.
Just as we said in the commentaries,
both gave your best performance.
That gives us hope.
We know you gave your best.
Both of you did very well.
Thank you.
Since YG and You Hee-yeol aren't ready,
do you have anything to say, Bae Mina?
I didn't know I would make it this far.
I made great memories and experiences.
I thank my parents, the three judges,
the KPOP STAR staff, and the emcee.
I'll do better. Thank you.
Thank you, Bae Mina.
And Jang Hanna?
First, I thank you for giving
me this great opportunity.
I thank the three judges,
my parents, and friends.
I'll also do better.
Thank you.
Jang Hanna and Bae Mina are
unfortunately eliminated.
We'll see you again next week
at the TOP6 live show.
Starting with the TOP6 live show,
for the first time on KPOP STAR...
We'll have YG week, JYP week, and
Antenna week spread over 3 weeks.
It will be the 3 agencies week.
Look forward to the
performances next week.
This was KPOP STAR Season 3, a real
audition where dreams turn into reality.
See you next week!
Subtitles by SBS International