[The result of last
week's battle!]
[TOP8 - Choi Ye-geun]
[TOP8 - YouU]
[TOP8 - Andrew Choi]
[Lost - Lee Jin-woo]
[Lost - Sung Soo-jin]
[Lost - Akdong Musician]
[3 teams - candidates
for elimination]
[The battle continues!]
Bang Ye-dam vs 2,000 won.
This could be the most
exciting battle of all.
We're in trouble. This
pressure is different.
I'm afraid. I tried hard
but it's complicated.
Since there's no draw.
It's a battle on who
has more nerves.
[The final battle
for TOP8!]
Raccoon Boys vs Shin Ji-hoon.
She's a terrifying
contestant.
I think Shin Ji-hoon
prepared a lot.
Raccoon Boys have
their own style.
I'm burdened that
it's 1 against 3.
It's important how much
we show what we practiced.
It's going to be
a huge battle.
[Who else will advance
to the TOP8?]
[The battle for TOP8
begins now!]
[Broadcast live from
SBS Prism Tower]
The battle of Season 2's
TOP10 finishes today.
I present the four teams
that will battle today.
2,000 won!
Bang Ye-dam!
Shin Ji-hoon!
Raccoon Boys!
Another round of applause
to the teams battling today.
Hi, I'm the MC, Yoon Do-hyun,
for KPOP STAR Season 2.
Today is the last
TOP10 battle.
Two teams will be
eliminated today.
I expect another
heated battle.
2,000 won and Bang Ye-dam,
Raccoon Boys and Shin Ji-hoon.
Don't miss the special guest
performance we'll have later.
Now I introduce the 3 judges
that will judge objectively.
BoA of SM.
Yang Hyun-suk of YG.
Park Jin-young of JYP.
The crowds going wild.
Last week, when JYP said
to open the voice...
You amusingly told him
to open his heart.
If you have anything to say
to him, say it before we begin.
I was just joking around
since we are very close.
I say worse things to
him in the waiting room.
JYP's face tells the
contestants everything.
In most cases, they don't
sing well if he looks bad.
And they sing well
when he looks good.
I always tell him in the waiting
room to put on a poker face.
I joked around telling him
to make his face unreadable.
If I say something harsh, I want the
viewers to understand that I'm joking.
I believe everyone
would understand.
I'll explain again how
the battle system works.
The TOP10 battle
is a 1:1 battle.
Winner passes and loser will
be a candidate for elimination.
Continuing from last week,
four teams will battle today.
From the 5 defeated teams,
3 last week and 2 today...
2 with the highest viewers'
votes go to the next round.
And 1 with the judges'
wildcard will pass.
Boom will tell us how
the voting system works.
Hello, I'm Boom.
Give me a shout!
Things are really
heating up here.
We will send that
heat to you.
Viewers, your votes
are very important.
Your votes decide
their fate.
You can start voting when
your favorite begins battling.
Keep in mind that voting ends
when their battle is over.
I'll explain how to vote.
Turn on your cellphone,
open the text window...
Text #0606 with the Korean
name or number of the finalist.
There's one important thing.
You can vote for more
that one person, but...
You can't make multiple votes
for your favorite, got it?
Please keep that in mind.
You can also vote through
mobile messaging.
It might be a simple text,
but their fate depends on it.
We request your participation.
Before we start, Yoon Do-hyun
will announce the battle order.
Let's hear it. This is
KPOP STAR Season 2!
Thank you for that detailed
and enthusiastic explanation.
I will announce the order and
opponents of the 1:1 battle.
The 4th battle is...
The duo with the unique
personalities, No. 7 2,000 won.
And the youngest TOP10
finalist, No. 8 Bang Ye-dam.
I expect an exciting battle.
The last TOP10 battle is...
Beautiful voice that moves
the heart, No. 9 Shin Ji-hoon.
And a cheerful harmony maximizing
individuality, No. 10 Raccoon Boys.
We look forward to it since
they have different colors.
The two battles
won't be easy.
You can leave your comments via
SBS mobile application, SOTY.
We will begin with the 4th battle,
2,000 won vs Bang Ye-dam.
Voting for them will
also start now!
[2,000 won vs Bang Ye-dam]
How is Bang Ye-dam?
I'll explain it in one
word. It's potential.
He's one of those whose eyes
change on stage. We're afraid.
If you look at him,
he's a baby.
When I listen to 2,000 won,
they have a lot of energy.
I tried hard, but I think
I'll lose. It's complicated.
- Are you close to Ye-dam?
- Yes, of course.
Like a little brother.
2,000 won takes
good care of me.
[Shampoo his hair!]
[They're his dad here]
We play together...
They spin me around...
We carry him on our back.
So our backs hurt.
It's good, but...
It's 2,000 won!
It's heartbreaking that we're
labeled as winner and loser.
You didn't go beyond
our expectations.
It felt like your growth
plates are closed.
We were sad since that means
we have no chance of growing.
We became unyielding.
We gave performances where
we interact with the audience.
The live broadcast stage is where
you watch us with the audience.
I think we can show
our strengths.
The song we chose
is JYP's "Elevator".
When I was his backup singer,
I sang this song many times.
It's an exciting song and I always
wanted to sing this on stage.
We put our ideas into it
and changed some parts.
Now it's time to
explode a bomb.
This battle is going
to be exciting.
I want this stage to be 20 million
or 200 million won, not 2,000 won.
Our challenge on KPOP STAR
is our last and our dream.
We did well and became finalists.
I don't want to be eliminated.
Our wish is for people to
hear more of our songs.
[No. 7 2,000 won]
[Elevator - JYP]
My ideal woman gets on at 1st flr
It's easy to hit on her
I carefully speak on the 3rd flr
It's obvious she likes it (wants)
I hold her hands on the 6th flr
I infer my dating experiences
I target her on the 8th flr
What I want is to steal a kiss
She gets on as expected on 1st flr
Even the talking on 3rd flr
People rush in on 6th flr
My plans went down the drain
(You're a beautiful Venus
I stopped dead)
Stop!
Thought we would succeed
like JYP's song
And everything was possible
on the elevator
Reality has exceeded, she left
Our relationship goes astray
Thought everything would go well
But now, what's all this?
No. 7 2,000 won heated up the
stage with their unique energy.
[The youngest TOP10 finalist
Bang Ye-dam (12)]
Do you remember what you
grabbed during "doljabi"?
My mom said I
grabbed the mike.
[Music is my destiny?]
I don't know. Because my
parents are musicians...
I heard a lot of songs and
followed to their recordings.
That made me
close to music.
During the Children's Song Contest
in the 1st grade, I danced and rapped.
[Wrote his own
rap lyrics!]
I was 1st, and that is when
I started to like music.
I like Michael Jackson and
I'm singing "Black or White".
[He'll challenge one of
his idol's top songs]
I watched his video with
my dad when I was young.
That's when I wanted to be a
singer like Michael Jackson...
Having charisma and able
to move the people.
So I want to try it.
Since I'm singing Michael
Jackson's song...
I have to dance. I
think I'm doing well.
The scary thing is that he's
not nervous on stage.
That's right.
I'm not nervous...
I'm worried because
I have a cold, but...
I want to be on stage.
No contestant is good
at every round.
But Ye-dam showed improvement
on almost every round.
He never messed up.
It's frightening.
On the other hand, I think
he'll have a lot of pressure.
Mom and dad, I'll do well
and tell you the good news.
[No. 8 Bang Ye-dam]
[Black or White - Michael Jackson]
That was Bang Ye-dam's
cute and charismatic stage.
The judges were smiling brightly.
Will he advance to TOP8?
We just watched 2,000 won
and Bang Ye-dam.
Let's hear the judges' commentary
on what they thought of the stage.
It's hard for us when you throw
a strong punch from the start.
I'll start with 2,000 won.
I liked the energy. I felt proud
that you are back to your old self.
Seems the live broadcast
suits you guys.
Hyo-bin's voice and
Il-do's rap were good.
One advice, Hyo-bin should be more
playful and smile while singing.
Ye-dam, you're 12, right?
Someone your age can't
do such a performance.
My voice is trembling
because I'm overwhelmed.
Dance, gestures, tune...
It's truly frightening.
You'll become great.
One advice, when you sing while
dancing, you look at the ground.
A singer needs to pull
in the audience.
Make more eye contact.
I really enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
She was very excited.
Let's hear the next one.
Bang Ye-dam was good in the
preliminaries, but had a problem.
His voice is very small.
You press your throat to make
the sound and breathe from top.
Thus, the ringing of your voice
is small and sounds thin.
On the first lesson, you switched
breathing from top to bottom.
Do you remember the two
ways to lift your chin?
These two things can't
be corrected overnight.
It takes several months to
switch breathing position.
Even pressing the throat.
How did you correct
those two?
Practice...
Did you think about
it as you sang?
Umm... no.
It's like changing the batting
stance during a baseball season.
It's like changing the stance
and continually making home runs.
It's incredible.
I always said rhythm is more
important than singing.
You showed how it is
to sing with rhythm.
You also showed how it can be
dynamic when the voice is open.
Vocalization and breathing were
perfect. I couldn't find any flaws.
Thank you.
If it wasn't for Ye-dam,
2,000 won would have...
It was shocking. I think
it was the best you did.
The idea was great and
the arrangement was great.
Since stage production and
arrangement are skills...
It was an excellent stage.
One thing was unfortunate.
Il-do's rap was great.
But Hyo-bin still sang in an
old style pressing the throat.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you JYP for
your commentary.
Both received good
compliments.
Now it's YG.
What BoA said was correct.
It's been a while since a
12-year old frightened me.
I mean, there never was.
When he sang Justin Bieber's
"Baby", I thought, "Oh? Look at that."
When I saw today's stage,
it was incredible.
Ear, rhythm, ability, talent,
cuteness - he has it all.
The amazing thing is that...
Even existing singers can't just
sing Michael Jackson's songs.
This was a hard stage trying
to interpret this song.
Last week, the girl group messed
up trying to show many things.
But he knew the points
where to sing and dance.
He was focused when singing
and focused when dancing.
His dance wasn't flashy, but it's
frightening that he knew how.
On the other hand, 2,000 won
did well like what JYP said.
But you met the wrong
opponent. You had no luck.
One advice, Il-do is
overexcited on stage.
But Hyo-bin's not excited.
Hyo-bin should enjoy more
and Il-do should refrain.
Anyways, I felt great watching
both of your performances.
Thank you very much.
The commentaries were long.
That means it was good.
Please announce the
victor of the 4th battle.
It's going to be hard.
It is hard.
I'll go first.
The victor chosen by SM...
It was very hard.
2,000 won is back to their old self
and Ye-dam showed his potential.
They were evenly matched.
The one who captured my heart...
The victor chosen by SM is...
- Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
Please announce
the next victor.
Both put on their
best stage so far.
Especially 2,000 won. I wondered
if they had more, but I enjoyed it.
Since I need to choose, the
victor chosen by JYP is...
Good thing we're not scoring
or I would've given a high score.
- It's Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He made it to TOP8, but
let's hear YG's choice.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
I like those who enjoy
themselves on stage.
I gave many compliments. He
enjoys it and isn't nervous.
- It's Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
Bang Ye-dam is the
4th finalist for TOP8.
2,000 won put on a great stage
but faced the wrong opponent.
You lost but aren't eliminated.
Your votes decide whether
they advance to TOP8.
Those cheering for 2,000 won,
please vote for them.
Now we have the last 1:1 battle.
Shin Ji-hoon vs Raccoon Boys.
[Raccoon Boys vs Shin Ji-hoon]
[Looks at the match between
Shin Ji-hoon and Raccoon Boys]
Shin Ji-hoon...
What is she going to do?
She's facing her
toughest opponent.
[Toughest opponent!]
What do I do?
I hoped it wouldn't be us,
but when she picked us...
We collapsed. I
fell from my chair.
I didn't know how
to accept this.
When I opened it,
I saw an "S".
When I saw that letter, I had
goosebumps from my legs up.
Shin Ji-hoon barely
made it to TOP10.
But it's just her luck
to face Raccoon Boys.
It could be her misfortune
or her greatest chance.
[Can she turn this crisis
into an opportunity?]
I'm singing Michael Jackson's
"You Are Not Alone".
[Shin Ji-hoon arrives 20
days later than the others]
Let's welcome her!
Give her a big hand!
Since I came later
than others...
My time to practice is
shorter compared to them.
So the pressure is great.
I spend most of
my time alone.
I'm alone on the
rink when I skate.
I'm singing alone on
stage for KPOP STAR.
I practice skating alone
and I'm on stage alone.
I'm used to fighting
against myself.
The live broadcast
is also my fight.
I want to win that fight
and put on a good stage.
Raccoon Boys are perfect.
But Shin Ji-hoon is not.
It'll be a miracle if she beats
them; something extraordinary.
Although I joined late...
I'm more desperate to
fill the days I missed.
Please look forward to it
since I did my best.
[No. 9 Shin Ji-hoon]
[You Are Not Alone - Michael Jackson]
With a memorable faint voice, that
stage was by No. 9 Shin Ji-hoon.
[7-year old Brian Shin
loved to sing and dance]
The three of us were born and
raised in different places.
The music genre we enjoy
and style are also different.
We three are different,
but through KPOP STAR...
Raccoon Boys were born.
We're close now, and play music
together like real brothers.
What I wrote means to
work hard and play hard.
[But someone makes
them nervous...]
[16-year old
Shin Ji-hoon]
She's better than expected.
The song really goes
well with her voice.
I knew she was good,
but not to this extent...
She's a frightening contestant.
She has a strong high range.
You only work here
if you lay your arm.
But you work all
this if you don't.
[Very flexible!]
[Raccoon Boys feel small?]
We, Raccoon Boys, are singing
Beyonce's "Love on Top".
We chose this because we
need to show a new image.
We chose our first love
song, "Love on Top".
I wrote the rap lyrics
thinking of my girlfriend.
They will be surprised at
first but will like it.
We made the stage
where we can enjoy.
I hope you have fun.
That was awkward!
[No. 10 Raccoon Boys]
[Love on Top - Beyonce]
Uh. Had a hard time, right?
I thank you for waiting
You don't need to go on a diet.
A soft pillow's better than skinny.
Let's be closer together
Play our love beautifully
My heart's in crescendo, getting bigger
As time goes by, it gets deeper
Sometimes I blink like the traffic light
But you smile and say, "You're the best"
You make me smile
I'm happy you're with me
Hey, it's a happy thing
To be someone's soulmate
A day is short when I'm with you
Hold my hand and hug me tight
Girl, we're like Beyonce and Jay-Z
You like dejavu, I'm a crazy in love
Cross out your needless worries
Flower you all night than for a smoke
Three created the best harmony. That
stage was by No. 10 Raccoon Boys.
I'm curious of the
judges' commentary.
Let's hear them.
Since I worry the
most about music...
I particularly say a lot on
vocalization and breathing.
Like Shin Ji-hoon
and Bang Ye-dam...
When I hear the sound that
rings from a relaxed body...
I want the others
to do that as well.
So I say that in
my commentaries.
Ji-hoon's entire body is
open. Even Bang Ye-dam.
Amazing thing about him is
correcting what he couldn't do.
Ji-hoon was able to
do it from the start.
Brian couldn't sing the high notes.
A weird sound came from his throat.
He fixed it during
this program.
It's amazing. It can't be done
overnight. Those who did it...
McKay also improved.
Could there be happier days?
We saw the best of you both.
Thank you very much.
You looked very bright
just as YG had said.
Let's hear the next one.
The contestants have to put on a
good stage for good commentaries.
The three of us feel great since
the four teams did well.
I feel great too.
I want to compliment
Shin Ji-hoon.
I don't know if you
sing well or not.
There's something in your
voice that touches us.
Sometimes I feel
like crying.
To compliment
today's stage...
You cried after making
a mistake last time.
And you were eliminated.
You made the same
mistake but smiled.
That's what people
on stage need.
When composed singers make mistakes,
they change it to their advantage.
I want to compliment
you for that.
Raccoon Boys are
always above average.
It's ambiguous for us to
point out your weaknesses.
I made a lot of food
comparisons last season.
Raccoon Boys are
like kimchi stew.
Whatever you add to the
stew, it tastes good.
Tuna, eggs, fishcake, mackerel
pike, ramen... there's a lot.
That's a lot.
Whatever they sing, they
interpret in their style.
That's something I want
to compliment on.
Because both teams did well, I
have to think who to choose.
Good job.
That was a good commentary.
Now BoA is the last one.
Since they heard good things, I'll
say something to help them improve.
Shin Ji-hoon has a voice
that moves people's hearts.
I expressed that voice
as being faint.
What if you add skill
on top of that?
Your singing is clean and
high notes are flawless.
If you study vibrato and
how to end the last notes...
You'll be a vocalist
to contend with.
McKay put aside his guitar and
danced, but was it awkward?
It was cute and
I enjoyed it.
I thought you have
good teamwork.
Brian was nervous. His high
notes were a bit closed.
Ji-hoon's high notes and Brian's
skills combined will be good.
I enjoyed the battle between
the two of you.
I think she said
good things.
I'm also curious who
the victor will be.
Please announce the victor.
[Shin Ji-hoon vs Raccoon Boys
Who is the victor?]
YG's decision is...
I had a hard time
since both did well.
Raccoon Boys always wore black,
but they have bright colors today.
YG's choice is...
- Raccoon Boys.
- Congratulations!
Please announce
the next victor.
We said good things
for their commentary.
I'll say something
contrary for both.
Shin Ji-hoon made a
mistake in the middle.
You can't do that every stage.
Don't do that anymore.
Raccoon Boys' arrangements
were always briliant.
But compared to other songs, it's a
pity you changed this this way.
That was unfortunate
for both of you.
However, who's strength
was stronger?
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
- Shin Ji-hoon.
- Congratulations!
Now the score is 1:1.
BoA's decision determines
who goes to the next round.
Please make the
announcement!
Both of you did well.
I thought I should
judge by skills.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
- Raccoon Boys.
- Congratulations!
They are the last finalist
for TOP8. Congratulations.
Shin Ji-hoon lost,
but it's not over.
Don't be disappointed. There's
the viewers' votes and wildcard.
This concludes all
the TOP10 battles.
Voting will end soon.
Now all the TOP10
battles are over.
It's time to decide on
the TOP8 finalists.
Of the ten teams, which
two will be eliminated?
Unfortunately, the candidates for
elimination are Lee Jin-woo...
Sung Soo-jin, Akdong Musician,
2,000 won and Shin Ji-hoon.
As all of you know, two teams
with the highest votes pass.
So your votes are
very important.
For those who didn't vote,
this is your last chance.
I will call out their
numbers slowly.
Lee Jin-woo is 1.
Sung Soo-jin is 4.
Akdong Musician is 5.
2,000 won is 7.
Shin Ji-hoon is 9.
To help you in voting, video clips
of their performance will be shown.
Don't miss the video of the
TOP10's makeover as well.
Final voting begins now!
[No.1 Lee Jin-woo]
[No. 4 Sung Soo-jin]
[No. 5 Akdong Musician]
[No. 7 2,000 won]
[No. 9 Shin Ji-hoon]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
The TOP10 takes a step from
amateurs to professionals.
We reveal KPOP STAR's
TOP10's makeover!
[Live Broadcast D-30
b&A Clinic]
How will you present yourselves
before becoming a star or debut?
How do you want people to view you?
We do image-making in this place.
We will do our best.
Will you cooperate?
Yes!
Looking at you...
The men need skin care...
And the women need
to lose weight.
Does it hurt?
Isn't that used
in surgery?
[I'm scared]
Skin care to upgrade
their image!
The path to becoming a
K-pop star isn't easy.
[The oldest is sleeping
peacefully?]
This will make your
skin supple.
[34-year old's problem is
supple skin, not pimples]
- Is this your first time?
- Yes.
- What are your thoughts?
- Excuse me?
How do you feel?
- McKay's enjoying this.
- Why?
He made it to
TOP10 for this.
[I love skin care]
[While men receive skin care,
women receive 1:1 counseling]
You have a problem
with how you walk.
Using your ankles makes
your calves bigger.
Using your thigh muscles
spend the most calories.
We will fix your walking, and
you need a beautiful shape.
[TOP10's personal trainers]
[Training for an even
perfect stage begins!]
[Song Ha-ye does intense
step aerobics]
This is hard!
[Architect major Lee Jin-woo
begins body architecture]
Only the stomach!
I gained a lot
in the middle...
Don't film it!
[Meanwhile]
You're 46kg?
- I'm 42kg.
- You're fine.
[What about Jeon Min-joo,
YouU's leader?]
You're very elastic.
Your body is like
that of a gymnast.
Min-joo needs upper
body workout.
I was told to maintain my
weight, not lose them.
[Keeping in shape to be
at their best condition]
I feel bad for them.
[Live Broadcast D-7
Profile Shots]
It's the day for
their profile shots.
Never had this haircut.
[Makeover into a
bobbed hair!]
[This is...]
[Dazzling Chan-hyuk]
[What will Ye-dam do?]
[Tough blonde?]
[Lovely curls?]
- I like them all.
- All of them?
I promised to cut my hair
if I go on live broadcast.
I didn't want to, but I need
to keep my promise as a man.
I'm not sure, but people
told me it looks good.
It's a relief.
[Style makeover]
[This beautician is in
charge of the TOP10!]
[Jung Saem Mool
Makeup Artist]
End the eyeliner here.
Make it short to look sharp.
[Eyes look sharper]
[What are Kim Hyo-bin's
makeup points?]
Don't make it too dark
since he's dark-skinned.
[Gentle man
Kim Hyo-bin]
You are charming.
[Who is she entranced by?]
Do I look pretty?
[Bombshell]
[Profile shooting begins]
[Passionately drawing out
the TOP10's best pose]
[Kama Jo
Kama Studio]
[Fancy styling]
[Even charismatic advice!]
[Jung Bo-yoon
London Pride]
- He's good.
- It's going to be good.
[Who's getting
their attention?]
Bang Ye-dam is showing
off his hidden talent.
Go back a little.
[Charisma]
He's a man.
[But]
[Akdong Musician are
a bit embarrassed]
[The others feel
awkward as well]
[Receiving the photographer's
meticulous instructions]
[A great jump pose]
Chan-hyuk, that's
a great jump
They were awkward at first,
but now it's natural for them.
They look professional now.
Now it's time to end the voting
for the KPOP STAR TOP10 battle.
The five candidates
are waiting nervously.
There will be a special performance
as the votes are being counted.
Look forward to it.
We now end the voting that
will decide their fate!
[Voting is over]
[Broadcast live from
SBS Prism Tower]
For me, KPOP STAR
is "dream".
It was a dreamlike time
as if I was under a spell.
I was very happy and
many memories were made.
I'll be singing what I sang
during the audition as a singer.
I think I'll be
more nervous.
[Park Ji-min
Season 1 Winner]
[Over the Rainbow - Judy Garland]
That was great.
She's good, huh?
She's last year's winner and moved
many as soon as she debuted.
As soon as you win on
KPOP STAR, you debut.
Your dreams will
become reality.
More importantly, I have
stars right next to me.
They are Season 1's TOP10!
Welcome Baek A-yeon, Park
Je-hyung, and Yoon Hyun-sang!
Please rise and
greet them.
The three of you were on
stage exactly one year ago.
How do you feel watching them
after you debuted, A-yeon?
I was there last year, but
as I watch them from here...
I'm also nervous and
it took my breath away.
I see. What about
you, Je-hyung?
I'm also nervous and they were
good when I saw them on television.
But they're really good
as I see them live.
Alright. What about
you, Hyun-sang?
You were watching
them like a judge.
I was surprised because
they were really good.
I think the judges adore
them more than us.
I feel a little upset.
He also expressed
he was upset.
Voting is over and only
the results remain.
Viewers, who will smile?
Please watch with us.
Now I hand the mike
over to Yoon Do-hyun.
I heard you
loud and clear.
Glad to see last
season's finalists.
I now announce the result of
KPOP STAR's TOP10 battle.
First, the five teams that
won advanced to TOP8.
Of the five teams next to me,
two with the highest votes...
And one with the judges'
wildcard will pass.
Of the five teams, who
will advance to TOP8?
In my hand are the voting
results. I'll open them.
I will now announce the TOP8
finalists chosen by the viewers.
I will first announce the
one with the highest votes.
The TOP8 finalist chosen
by the viewers is...
Who will it be?
I will call out the team that
received the highest votes.
The TOP8 finalist chosen
by the viewers is...
I will announce it.
It's Akdong Musician!
Congratulations!
They got the highest votes with the
viewer's overwhelming support.
Congratulations for
advancing to TOP8!
Please join them
over there.
They didn't look bright
even though they passed.
It's because of the
friends they left behind.
Anyways, I have to
make the announcement.
I will announce the 2nd team
that the viewers chose.
The one I will call is the
last one all of you chose.
The TOP8 finalist chosen
by the viewers is...
I will announce it.
It's proof that person
received your support.
That person's charm was
shown to the viewers.
I will announce it now.
Who will it be?
Shin Ji-hoon, 2,000 won,
Sung Soo-jin or Lee Jin-woo?
The last finalist chosen
by the viewers is...
Not even the judges
know who it is.
Because these are results
from your votes...
They are curious who
passed and are nervous.
I hope you, the viewers, will
also guess who passed.
I'll announce it.
It's Shin Ji-hoon!
Congratulations!
The last TOP8 finalist chosen
by the viewers is Shin Ji-hoon.
Congratulations
on advancing.
She, too, doesn't look bright.
Please join the rest over there.
Only Lee Jin-woo, Sung Soo-jin,
and 2,000 won remain on stage.
Only one will pass with
the judges' wildcard.
The other two, unfortunately,
will part from KPOP STAR.
Right now, the judges
are in discussion.
They are having
a hard time.
Even I'm nervous.
All three did well and got
good commentaries, but...
Since this is a survival,
a choice must be made.
Did you decide?
I think they're done.
BoA, YG, and JYP discussed
who will pass with a wildcard.
They thought much about it.
Please make the announcement.
This will be the
last TOP8 finalist.
We have to send two
away from the three.
I feel sorry to make
this announcement.
Only one from among you
will advance to TOP8.
After our careful discussion...
First, we will announce the first
person that will be eliminated.
All of you did well, but
on this live broadcast...
We have to consider who
did well without mistakes.
Unfortunately, the first
person to be eliminated is...
You're announcing the
eliminated first?
You sang off key
in the middle.
Lee Jin-woo is the first
to be eliminated.
They're giving her
a round of cheers.
Lee Jin-woo, please
move to this side.
2,000 won and
Sung Soo-jin.
BoA and JYP had
conflicting opinions.
We thought who will be more
competitive and survive.
- TOP8 finalist is...
- The finalist is...
Who will it be?
- It's 2,000 won.
- Congratulations!
They became the TOP8
finalist. Congratulations.
It's unfortunate, but
Sung Soo-jin is eliminated.
After 7 long months, Lee Jin-woo
and Sung Soo-jin will part.
Their friends are
cheering them up.
Lee Jin-woo, it was
tough until now.
How do you feel?
It's amazing I made to TOP10.
It was a good experience.
Thank you for
all that time.
Please give her a
round of applause.
All that time must
have been hard.
Sung Soo-jin, you rechallenged
after all the ups and downs.
Unfortunately, you couldn't go
all the way. How do you feel?
My dream was to make to TOP10 so
I feel very good that it came true.
You answered very calmly.
A round of applause
for her as well.
Will the judges also give
them words of encourgement?
Honestly, you two are eliminated,
but we wanted to see your next stage.
Lee Jin-woo, this stage was lacking,
but you showed an unforgettable stage.
We really wanted to
see your next stage.
Sung Soo-jin, you showed
an amazing transformation.
You made me think I thought
wrongly of you last season.
We wanted to see you both, but
since we needed to choose one...
We chose one, but we truly
wanted to see both of you.
Especially, Sung Soo-jin changed
amazingly compared to last year.
Thank you for allowing us
to hear some good songs.
Thank you very much.
Can each of you say
something, BoA?
I became close to them
as we trained together.
They showed a new side
and we became close.
Both of them sing well
and they are beautiful.
I hope to see you on a gayo
show and not at an audition.
It's a pity since
we got close.
- It must be.
- It is.
Both of you are pretty!
She wants to see them
on a gayo show.
It means she wants them
to continue music.
YG, a word please?
Since they spoke, I'll give advice
to the TOP8 finalists instead.
Before that, there's something
BoA and JYP said to me.
They said they couldn't forget
Bang Ye-dam's stage.
It really moved us here.
But the sound on television is
different from the sound here.
I heard that Bang Ye-dam's
voice was small.
If possible, come here
and watch them.
Since they are witnesses.
There was one thing I didn't
get to say to Bang Ye-dam.
You have all this talent, but
the frightening thing is...
You don't get stage fright.
To all the TOP8 finalists,
especially Shin Ji-hoon...
Enjoy the stage. When you enjoy,
we and the viewers can enjoy.
Keep that in mind and prepare
a stage you're satisfied with.
Thank you very much.
Don't you have anything
to say to the eliminated?
- I might cry so I can't.
- I understand.
Unfortunately, Lee Jin-woo and
Sung Soo-jin are eliminated.
Next week will be an even
fiercer battle among the TOP8.
We're curious who
will battle who.
We're also curious who
will win that battle.
Please look forward to next
week's unpredictable battle.
See you next week!
Goodbye!