[A drama showing how dreams
are turned into reality]
There were a lot of amazing contestants
that showed us different colors and styles.
[Amazing contestants with
a variety of talents!]
Will we ever find such diverse contestants
as we did in this season's K-POP STAR?
To be able to find potential where others
did not see, that is the most rewarding.
An unimaginable challenge
for our friends..
Also, a leap for those who haven't
been able to get much experience.
While watching these auditions,
it's just like a drama.
I'd like to think that the main point of
K-POP STAR is to find talented individuals..
That can go outside of Korea and grab the
attention of the world, 2-3 years later.
Finally today..
Another K-pop star
will be born!
I wish that you give them
your whole-hearted support.
Survival Audition
K-POP STAR Season 2!
The anticipated, final stage where
our current finalists will compete!
Let me introduce the three judges that
have been with us for the past 8 months..
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
BoA of SM!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
They are more determined than
ever since this is the finals.
Our audience members, please give
them a large round of applause!
Hello! I'm your MC, Yoon Do-hyun, for the
Survival Audition of K-POP STAR Season 2!
This show started a lot of talk and
created twists the past 8 months.
At last, the anticipated final
stage has now begun!
From today's stage, a new star
from K-POP STAR Season 2 will emerge..
They're the youngest, yet strongest two teams
that overcame their competition to be here.
Making history in this audition,
let me introduce you to the TOP 2!
Our first runner-up..
Making a clean sweep in each audition
round and made it all the way here.
He may be small, but he's the youngest
in audition history to make TOP 2..
Bang Ye-dam!
Our second runner-up is shaking
up the Korean music scene..
Teenaged singer-songwriter..
Charming brother-sister duo..
Akdong Musician!
The cheers from the crowd
are pouring in!
Let's give another big round
of applause for the TOP 2 finalists!
I think Ye-dam
is really scary.
I think Akdong Musician
are really scary.
Congratulations, Bang Ye-dam!
He's constantly developing..
Each performance gets a good reaction..
How did you even write lyrics
with these kind of ideas?
I think of you two
as very precious to me.
Music-wise, Akdong Musician
are definitely at the top.
They persevered after
many turnovers.
- He was so good.
- Man, Ye-dam..
At one round, Ye-dam won..
Another, they performed together as Akhachu..
And it just so happens, that
these two are now at the finals..
A cruel fate?
How well will
Ye-dam sing?
Or will it be Akdong
Musician's musicality?
Ah, it's difficult..
[Who will become
the final winner?]
The audience is wilder than
ever. Give me a shout!
- Yang Hyun-suk!
- Yes?
How are you? So, the final
stage remains today..
I'm sure you're filled with memories after you've
watched over these entrants all the way through..
How do you feel right now?
It's been about 5 or 6 months..
K-POP STAR Season 2 had its run
and today is the final stage..
Frankly for me, even if
K-POP STAR ends today..
I feel K-POP STAR will still be
continuing even a year from now..
Because the entrants here today are going
to debut and then continue to be active..
Even when I saw Lee Hi or Park Ji-min,
I thought of them as K-pop stars in the past..
Whether these finalists take
1st or 2nd place today..
I just hope to inspire them to bring
a new energy to the music world.
Thank you very much.
With today being the final stage,
our finalists will be performing 2 songs..
Alright, today's mission!
I'm sure you're all curious..
BoA, could you tell us
what is taking place today?
They will each choose a song the
other sang during this audition.
Simply, you could call it a very
distinguished, final mission..
Since you've already sang your rival's music,
it's important how you would interpret the music..
And finally, you will perform a song
that one of us judges has chosen.
Got it. And that makes the
two songs they'll be performing.
- Now, Park Jin-young!
- Yes?
Our TOP 2 finalists are
both very young entrants..
I'd like to ask for a word of encouragement
so that today's performances will go well.
What I can offer you
as your senior..
People will surely forget who was
1st or 2nd place after a few years..
It's not what rank you placed
in that they remember..
But the songs you sang and the impressions
left by your performances that they'll remember..
So don't worry about which rank you'll
place but have a good time while performing.
That's sincerely appreciated,
thank you very much.
I'll also ask the judges to be
fair and careful today as well.
Now, before we start today's final stage,
we have something special from our TOP 2..
Let's check it out right now!
[April 3, 2013
4 days before the Final Stage!]
[Producers waiting for the TOP 2!]
Hello! Why are there cameras?
Today, we're going to have a
pop-up performance on the street.
- If I knew this, I'd clean up beforehand!
- Oh my goodness!
- I didn't even do my hair or make-up!
- No way..
The reason why we're doing
a surprise performance..
We'll leave the final
stage aside for now..
And we're going to go
back to the basics..
[After applying for K-POP STAR..]
[Ye-dam performed out on the streets
with his dad to build up his courage]
[Before they came out
on K-POP STAR..]
[Akdong Musician worked up their skill
by constantly performing on streets]
After competing in K-POP STAR, let's see
your changed self in those same places.
[Then, where will it take place?]
Wow.
[In front of Dongdaemun Shopping Center]
[A standing, outdoor stage!]
[Less than an hour till
their performance!]
[The people are showing interest
to the pop-up performance]
[However, most of them keep
up their busy pace]
[Will they be able to put on a
successful, pop-up performance?]
[Current time 7:20 PM
40 min before show!]
[With not much time left,
the ambitious, TOP 2 practice]
[However]
Ah, I wish I could change my clothes.
Soo-hyun, what're you
doing right now?
Putting on my own make-up..
You con-artist!
What do you mean con-artist?!
[I'm a lady too, you know~]
[Current time 7:35 PM
25 min before show!]
[A number of people gather
in front of the stage]
[Could they be waiting for the
TOP 2 pop-up performance?]
How many people are there?
I don't know, either.
There could even be no one.
That happened to us a long time ago..
- Nobody came.
- There was no one.
So we just sang in the
street by ourselves.
Just shouting into the
air, "How are you!"
[There's no way there
could be no one today too?]
[Friends happy to
be just singing]
[What kind of performance will
they put on for the pop-up stage?
[Current time 7:59 PM
1 min before show!]
[Finally leaving to put
on a pop-up performance!]
- 1, 2, 3.. Let's go!
- I don't look good today.
If there's no one there at all,
it'd be really funny..
But if there's only a few people
out there, that's embarrassing.
If there's only a few people
I think I'll want to cry!
[Will the TOP 2's worries
be a reality?]
[And if not..?]
[An outpour of shouting!]
[An immense crowd!]
[Astonished]
[An unbelievable sight]
[A very large turnout in
that short amount of time!]
[The people warmly welcome them]
We should say hello..
Hello, we're K-POP STAR's TOP 2..
Akdong Musician..
- And I'm Bang Ye-dam.
- Hello!
Wow..
We had no idea there would
be this many people!
There are many of
you that came out.
[Packed with people!]
At first, I seriously didn't
think there would be that many..
But there were so many!
I was so surprised that
I started getting anxious.
[Which song will Akdong Musician
present to their audience?]
[Their own song's "Crescendo"
is being warmly received]
[Akdong Musician you got
charm! The best! Fighting!]
[Their voices are amazing!]
[The moment of climax!]
[But]
[How could this..!]
The guitar cord was still plugged
and I was trying to be quick..
But the fans watched me
with amusement..
[Back into it!]
[Akdong Musician gain energy
from the fan's cheers]
[Now, Ye-dam's "Baby"]
[The girls go wild]
[Ye-dam, it's your sister!]
[Ye-dam, even your auntie's here!]
[A big hit with the girls!]
[He's so cute!]
When I performed in the streets,
I got lots of reactions..
So I think I could do better
during the live broadcast.
[Encore! Encore! Encore!]
I didn't know there would be so many
people waiting and cheering us on..
But, I learned that there were many
people that show us support..
And it gives me the strength to do
even better for the final stage.
[We wish the TOP 2 a good fight!]
It seemed like a performance where the
TOP 2 could really sense their popularity..
I hope that you received everyone's energy and
support and put on amazing performances today.
Now, before we really get to the performance,
I'm going to address the finalist's numbers!
Tiny on stage and hard-to-believe
he's only 12; No.1 it's Bang Ye-dam!
Making a fresh jolt in the music world, the
teenaged singer-songwriter; No.2 it's Akdong Musician!
You'll be able to personally vote for
the winner of K-POP STAR Season 2..
MC Boom will go into details
on how you may vote by text.
Make some noise! Yeah!
Hello everyone!
I'm MC Boom!
The long-awaited winner will be
revealed today at the finals.
Everyone, who do you
think will take 1st place?
Bang Ye-dam?
Or Akdong Musician?
We will find out today as you can
personally vote for your favorite..
Here is how you can
text in your votes!
Just open your text messaging app
in your phone and enter #0606..
And enter in the name you're
voting for in Korean..
Or you may enter in their
unique number and text it in!
I'm sure you all know by now. You
can vote for more than one person..
However, multiple votes for the
same candidate is not allowed..
Also, you may use your messenger
app on your smartphone to vote.
Now, we're not only having
a contest for our TOP 2..
We also have special performances that
you won't be able to catch anywhere else.
Stay tuned as we find out who will become
the winner that will go down in history!
We also have a welcoming performance.
It's a special stage with the TOP 10!
Also, they're the best stars
to ever appear on K-POP STAR..
Our very own, Miss Park Ji-min is
revealing a new song here today!
Recorded live, this is
K-POP STAR Season 2!
The text voting for the
final round has now begun!
[Text voting has begun]
[Text in your votes by entering the
name or number of the finalist]
To determine the winner
of K-POP STAR Season 2..
We'll take the total of the judges' scores (70%)
and the viewer's texting votes (30%).
Bang Ye-dam and Akdong Musician..
Can we find a winner between the two?
Starting from now, the fate of those two teams
are hanging as the final contest unfolds.
First, it's the final mission of K-POP STAR
where they will sing one of each other's songs..
Each team will pick a song that the other
team sang throughout the audition..
Which song will they pick?
And how will they interpret it?
But first, picking a song that Akdong Musician
performed, Bang Ye-dam's stage is about to begin!
[Last week, after the broadcast]
It's a mission!
I don't want it!
[Mission.. I'm scared..]
[The mission being delivered,
with suspense in the air]
[What could the first mission
of the final round be?]
[Looking it over and over]
These are all the songs that
Bang Ye-dam has done so far..
What! No way!
[The same final mission in
Season 1's final stage?!]
[Switch songs?!]
No way!
I was like, "No way! No way!"
"Please don't let it be!"
I was just, astonished.
Ah..
Singing each other's songs..
By making them sing a song from each other,
makes you able to compare those two singers.
If they can sing it better than the original
singer, it could be a keypoint for them to win.
Frankly, it's a mission that these
singers would be afraid of the most.
[Ye-dam's expression looks especially gloomy]
I don't think the songs
we wrote would suit you..
The song I think would
suit you the most..
"One of A Kind"?
What if you did "I Want You Back"
but in your style..
No one's going to think
that you'd do this song..
- How about "Breathe"?
- I don't think "Breathe" would be good..
You know, their originally written
songs received good reviews..
But if I sing those songs again,
there's a chance I could do worse..
It was very hard to pick a song.
[Which song did Ye-dam eventually pick?]
Oh! This suits him well.
This is a song that really
gave me a huge reaction..
This might be difficult for Ye-dam.
Hm..
I'm imagining.. How would Ye-dam
interpret this song?
I think he would do really well!
I know for a fact he'll
do really well!
[Which song did Ye-dam pick that's
mixed with expectations and worries?]
[The song "Officially Missing You"
which gave the most reaction]
A score of 98 points!
95 points!
94 points!
Akdong Musician just received
the most points ever from the judges!
I really liked their performance,
when Akdong Musician sang that song..
So I wanted to try that song
but done in my own style.
When Akdong Musician sang this song,
they were telling us a story..
It felt like they
were talking to us..
I think Ye-dam could
give us a different reaction.
When Akdong Musician sang
"Officially Missing You"..
Emotionally, it was done in
a slightly sad way..
And even though, there may be
sad times in our memories..
We also have good
memories with us too.
As I was doing K-POP STAR,
I got to stand a huge stage..
I got to be on television..
I got to meet a lot of celebrities..
I got to live with older "brothers" and
spend some time away from my parents..
It was a lot of fun.
I'd hope that when you hear my song,
you'd remember more happier times.
Ye-dam's Mom: [Akhachu]
Ye-dam's Dad: [I'm happy I have you~*]
[TAMIA - Officially Missing You]
Bang Ye-dam just gave us a different take
on Akdong Musician's "Officially Missing You"..
I'm really curious what the
three judges will score.
When you first started and
came out to give your audition..
You made us three judges very thrilled
and I couldn't hide my expression..
The reason for bringing that up, is that
I get that same feeling after hearing this.
He plays with the timing..
Singing fast and then slow..
He even plays with the melody..
He changes the melody, but
not into obvious ones.
But it's sung in a way
most people wouldn't imagine..
Also, you play the
harmonica very well..
I think that's what really
makes it your own song..
I think I heard every
type of vocalization..
I heard falsetto, head voice, and even
a little chest voice for the first time..
Gee, I really enjoyed watching
your performance..
Here's JYP's score..
Now for the score.
He got very high praises.
What will JYP's
scoring be?
- 98 points! Wow!
- Thank you!
He got a really high score..
Let's find out the score
from our next judge.
My overall commentary after seeing
him the past several months..
He still can't win with
singing alone.
The audience is reacting to
Jin-young's expression..
It's all over his face.
If there was a part that
I thought was really amazing..
When you first opened your song with that voice,
it gave me goosebumps and it was charming..
And Bang Ye-dam's key is actually
higher than most guys can sing..
Last week, when he sang "Bad Boy" with
Taeyang, he was singing 3 keys higher..
Even in "Where Is The Love?" he
sang it in a women's part in one key..
And even though, there was a slight
flaw in your sound today..
But because I got such a shudder
from listening to your nice voice..
I want to give you a generous
score than one would expect..
Alright, here's YG's score..
If so, what would be that
generous-than-expected score be?
We're going to find out..
- 95 points! That's definitely a high score.
- Thank you!
He must feel great..
Lastly, let's find out the
score from SM's judge.
Personally, I really liked Ye-dam's
version better than Akdong Musician's.
The reason why..
Ye-dam's true feelings were
conveyed in the rap lyrics.
He's actually..
There's a lot of laughs today
because of Jin-young's expressions.
For a 12-year-old to partake in
this 8-month long survival...
I'm sure you went through a lot of
hardships, physically and emotionally..
But your rap was given
while still intact..
And I really loved listening to your
beautiful voice and harmonica playing..
But, when you first started singing
I thought your tone seemed shaking..
So I'll give you a
considerable score..
Here's SM's score..
Here's SM's scoring..
The two judges had given high scores..
- 96 points!
- Thank you!
Bang Ye-dam received a total of
289 points from the three judges!
He received a very high score..
Now, for those who think that Bang Ye-dam
should be the winner of K-POP STAR Season 2..
Please text 'Bang Ye-dam'
or the number '1' to #0606..
That was candidate No.1, Bang Ye-dam!
Up next, we're going to see
Akdong Musician's performance..
Let's find out which song of Bang Ye-dam's
had Akdong Musician selected to perform!
How about this one?
I like this one.
"Isn't She Lovely" wouldn't
be so bad either..
"Sir Duke" would be good too..
Since Ye-dam sang
so many good songs..
I always got envious..
Whenever Ye-dam would sing a song,
I'd wonder how I would sing that song.
[I should try that one next time~]
After Ye-dam sang that song,
I couldn't stop singing it..
After hearing Ye-dam, he
thought it sounded so great..
It was just addicting!
[The addicting song Ye-dam sang?]
[Akdong Musician's selected song unveiled]
They picked a very suiting song.
[Slightly hesitant JYP]
If Akdong Musician wants to put on
a good performance with this song..
They'll need an entirely
new interpretation..
It may be difficult, but if they can
do it, it'll be that much more amazing.
I don't think it's going to be
an easily predictable performance..
Akdong Musician..
"MMMBop" Hanson..
When I first heard Ye-dam's performance,
I was really shocked and liked him ever since..
You sang so well!
When he first sang this, we thought
he was like Michael Jackson.
Akdong..
Ah..
He did almost every stage
without criticisms.
We couldn't find a song
we wasn't good at.
No matter what, the burden
would be just the same.
I can imagine the voice
those two would sing it in..
But since, Ye-dam is by himself
and we have both of us..
We can create a harmony..
I feel like they'd do
much better than me..
Also, for us we have
creative writing..
Ye-dam sings original songs as they are..
And he'll be told that he
has a good sense of rhythm..
So I'm going to give it a
new melody and witty lyrics..
And a new arrangement in
an Akdong Musician-style..
I think that will
be our strengths.
It's not going to be easy.
But I'm looking forward to it since
Akdong haven't sung much rhythmical songs..
To see what kind of new ingenuity
Akdong Musician will show us today..
That's most critical!
Please look forward to
our own take on "MMMBop"!
- Fighting!
[Hanson - Mmmbop]
A different take on Bang Ye-dam's
song "MMMBop" by Akdong Musician!
That was very fresh
and fun to watch!
Let's find out how our judges
watched their performances!
Personally, out of all the performances
Akdong Musician has done so far..
I don't know if this was their best one,
but I do think it was their most natural one.
Frankly, I don't know if it's because
Bang Ye-dam is still 12 years old..
I saw him feeling embarrassed
or pressured a few times.
Since they were having fun, their
interpretation was different.
Since they're siblings, they were
in perfect step and it was great.
Alright, here's YG's score..
A very natural performance..
What score will he give?
The points are climbing up..
Was there an error?
The numbers are going
back up again..
98 points!
That's a very high score.
Let's find out our
next judge's score..
Personally, I really thought
this round was very difficult..
First off, I think Ye-dam's
version gave us a huge reaction..
But for Akdong Musician..
Watching them reach all the way to the final
rounds on live-television was very fun..
It was very enjoyable..
I enjoyed listening to "MMM Bop" which didn't
remind me of Ye-dam's version at all..
I really thought over how Akdong
would sing this very, rhythmic song..
But Miss Soo-hyun, sung it with a
great sense of rhythm and modesty..
This one's very hard
for me to evaluate..
Here's SM's score..
Her judging was filled
with lots of compliments..
She said this
one was hard..
96 points!
That's definitely a
very high score..
Lastly, let's find out
how JYP will judge them..
We can't evaluate Akdong on
singing and performance alone.
Firstly, I definitely asked for your own
interpretation of the song "MMM Bop" itself..
This song is usually sung in
a 24-note shuffle rhythm..
But you guys took it and
made it into a 16-note..
And sung that rhythm without any flaws..
I was very surprised by that..
Not only that, combining elements from
your previous songs, all into one song..
Doing that so seamlessly
is a very astonishing feat..
It really makes me think that
I can't overlook this song..
How did your parents
raise you two so well?
If I had kids one day, and had them take supplementary
classes, training, private lessons and such..
Would they turn out like that?
They're such precious kids!
Here's JYP's score..
JYP's score is climbing up..
What will it be?
97 points!
That gives Akdong Musician a total
of 291 points from the three judges!
For those who think Akdong Musician should
be the winner of K-POP STAR Season 2..
Text 'Akdong Musician' or '2' to #0606..
That was Akdong Musician, No.2!
It's getting hotter and hotter in here!
Right now, it's a very close match!
There's only two missions left,
who will ultimately become the winner?
Stay tuned to find out!
At the moment, Akdong Musician are in the
lead by a few points, with a total of 291!
However, that can quickly change..
Now we've prepared something
to get things even hotter..
The winner of K-POP STAR Season 1,
Park Ji-min, has prepared a performance..
15& will be revealing their
new song "Somebody" on this stage..
It's their first performance, but it was at this stage
they first started singing and became a K-pop star..
And now they're returning
to this stage..
Everyone, please welcome them
with a warm, round of applause..
15& "Somebody"!
[Season 1 Winner: Park Ji-min]
["From a powerful voice to vocalization,
Park Ji-min has everything." - BoA]
Our final winner is..
Park Ji-min!
[Winner of K-POP STAR Season 1
"A dream fulfilled"]
K-POP STAR to me is like a dream..
Being able to sing on stage is like a dream..
[Returning to her dream stage]
[Special Stage: Park Ji-min as 15&]
[15& - "Somebody"]
Seeing Park Ji-min return to stage
really makes me feel complete!
JYP was also dancing
as he watched.
Things are getting hotter here at the
K-POP STAR Season 2, Final Stage..
We're down to our very last song..
This second mission involves
a song picked by the judges..
I believe they will do their
best since this is the last.
First, let's start with Bang Ye-dam!
- What is that?
- What?
- Why another mission?!
- Really?
[The envelope containing the second
mission is delivered to the TOP 2]
[What could this mission be about?]
I think we need to give Ye-dam
something where he can sing more.
The second mission is a song
recommended by the judges.
What song would be the best for
both to show off their skills?
[What was Bang Ye-dam's
selected "mission" song?]
[Culture Club's "Karma Chameleon" (1983)]
JYP and I were in the
same waiting room...
We play songs that YG and
I heard when we were young.
During the semifinals, I suddenly
heard this in Bang Ye-dam's voice...
I thought this would be a great
song for Bang Ye-dam to sing.
Since I've only heard
it for the first time..
It might be hard but
it'll be fun.
This song will show everything from his singing
skills, rhythm sense and harmonica skills!
It'll bring back old memories
and I think it will be fun.
This is the final stage.
I'll do my best because
this is the last.
I want to enjoy it more.
What is KPOP STAR to you?
I think "dream".
My dream was to be a
singer on stage.
I was on a big stage
through KPOP STAR...
My dream turned to reality.
I want to show a stage
I won't regret.
You need to monitor this
video of your practice.
[Thorough preparations -
monitoring his practice]
[But...]
I'll start.
Hi, Ye-dam. It's me.
Uncle "Pung Pung".
You were five when we started
recording "Farting King Pung Pung".
I'm proud that you've grown up and
made it to TOP2 on KPOP STAR.
Since you tried hard, you
will do well. Go, go, go!
Hey, it's me Sung-jin.
I'm so proud that you
made it to TOP2.
Hurry back so
we can play.
You did really well.
Hurry up and win
so we can play.
You can do it!
One, two, three...
Go, Bang Ye-dam!
It's me Jung-hwan. You have
to win. Go, Bang Ye-dam!
[Thanks guys]
[Who's next?]
- Hi, Ye-dam.
- Hi.
It's me, dad.
There's one more
stage to go.
I don't know if you saw
the sign I always held.
I wrote, "Enjoy music."
Whether you win or not,
whatever the results...
I hope you will
just enjoy it.
During last week's broadcast...
Someone was moved by your singing and said
to us, "Thank you for giving birth to him."
We were proud of you
and touched by that.
We're thankful that you
were born as our son.
Let's live happily.
I love you.
- You're a good son.
- Yes you are.
I love you.
Go, Ye-dam!
[He's overwhelmed
and is speechless]
What is this? I thought I was
supposed to monitor my practice.
Mom and dad, thanks for
calling me a good son.
I'll do my best in the final
stage because I'm a good son.
Thank you.
[Karma Chameleon - Culture Club]
We saw his excellent rhythm.
Let's hear the score.
Actually, I don't
know this song.
I only know the chorus part.
I thought that Ye-dam
would sing it differently.
I also thought why you didn't
play your harmonica.
It was plain.
I enjoyed it.
SM's score is...
She said it was plain,
but what's the score?
- 94 points!
- Thank you.
Let's hear the next score.
I thought the same thing.
JYP and I recommended this
because of the harmonica.
We were waiting for the
harmonica, but it ended.
Ye-dam's friends came
out on the video clip.
It made me realize
how young he is.
Why did we compliment him?
People his age cause trouble
and are hard to control.
But he reinterpreted this song
that we heard when we were young.
People around BoA's age might not know,
but middle-aged people like JYP and me...
This brought back
old memories.
It was great.
YG's score is...
This is YG's score.
What will he give him?
- 93 points!
- Thank you.
That's a high score.
Finally, we have JYP.
One amazing thing... those that
learned music from their parents...
They sing in an old-fashioned
way because of their parents.
Ye-dam learned from his dad,
but he doesn't sound old.
It's amazing how polished
he sounds without habits.
Another thing is that melody changes
slightly whatever the melody may be.
Not anyone can do that, especially
when it turns out good.
That's amazing about him.
But in this song, the music director
and many other things didn't go along.
But Ye-dam sang well.
I think we were trying to have our own way
by making him sing an 80s song in a week.
But he sang well.
JYP's score is...
This is JYP's score. He said
something wasn't right...
- 94 points!
- Thank you.
He received a total
of 281 points.
Bang Ye-dam?
Now you're done
with every stage.
Yes. I feel light.
- You do?
- It's over now.
Seems like you're happy. It must've
been hard for you at a young age.
You did well.
If you think he's the future
K-pop star, the winner...
Please text 'Bang Ye-dam'
or the number '1' to #0606..
That was candidate No.1, Bang Ye-dam!
Next up is Akdong Musician.
What did the judges choose for
them and how will they sing it?
Akdong Musician is next!
For Akdong Musician, we chose
Toy's "Passionate Goodbye".
If "Officially Missing You" was
sorrow in their friends leaving...
This is beyond that.
This song will give them an overall
feeling what this show meant to them.
This will be a mission that will
draw out the best in them.
If you give Chan-hyuk a topic, he
pieces it together and makes something.
[Genius composer's workroom]
I stayed up all night.
All night? After the
street performance?
I'm tired. But I'm done.
It's great.
[Arrangement finished]
I want to create
a touching stage.
I felt many things I never felt
before coming on KPOP STAR.
You can't know this if
you don't experience it.
So that everyone can
feel the same...
I hope we can walk together from our
first to final stage through the lyrics.
What are we filming?
A sketch?
[They turn the TV on]
What is this?
Chan-hyuk and Soo-hyun.
It's me, grandma.
- It's already...
- She's nervous.
Do well to the end.
- Yeah!
It's Ye-geun!
It's been a month since
we didn't see each other.
I'm back in school
and my life.
I was worried when I saw you cry
singing "Officially Missing You".
I miss you.
I love you.
[Me too]
Bye.
[She is?]
It's mom!
Chan-hyuk and Soo-hyun,
are you doing well?
Don't worry about me because I'm
doing better than you think.
When you two went to Korea
for KPOP STAR...
We were worried and I wasn't
able to do my work.
I thought of you every day.
I want to make a request
to Chan-hyuk.
I think you're taking good care
of your sister and feel reassured.
We're proud and feel you're trustworthy
for taking care of your sister in our place.
I believe you
two will do well.
Do well. We love you.
We'll do well and not
disappoint them.
I hope they'll be happy.
I think it created
our dreams.
Just a year ago, we were being
homeschooled in Mongolia.
We came here within a year...
It's our first steppingstone in
making our dreams come true.
We can start with this
as our steppingstone.
This is the last slate.
Three, two, one... Go!
[Passionate Goodbye - Toy]
It was a touching song as the
grand finale for KPOP STAR.
Seeing 2NE1 in the audience
also left an impression.
What did the judges think?
Let's hear the score.
Even though this is a live
broadcast and the final round...
I want to be honest.
Bang Ye-dam and Akdong Musician's
previous mission was much better.
Akdong Musician's "Passionate Goodbye"
was like a final song ending KPOP STAR.
I looked at the lyrics.
"Everything ends after tonight."
"With pencils in hand, we
finished the drawing."
"I hang it in a place
within my heart forever."
This is a poem and
not just a lyric.
I'm amazed every time
I look at the lyrics.
It was a good stage.
YG's score is...
This is YG's score. He said the
previous mission was much better...
93 points!
That's a high score.
Let's hear the next score.
Just as he said, we always look
at their lyrics and melody.
How can they write
such lyrics?
If their parents wrote a book,
"This is how we raised them"...
It'll be a bestseller.
- I would buy that.
- I know, really...
In the middle was a riff from
Guns N' Roses "Sweet Child O' Mine".
They fit that title. They really
are beautiful children.
I'm amazed at their musicality and
creativity, but I worry unnecessarily...
I'm always worried when
I see talented people.
No matter how talented, without efforts and
studying, you'll only go on for 10 years.
Most great composers don't
go beyond 10 years.
I'm concerned that efforts and
studying will complement your talents.
That's how talented you are.
JYP's score is...
That was a heartfelt advice.
And their score is?
94 points! That's high.
Finally we have BoA.
This is the last commentary
for KPOP STAR Season 2.
I enjoyed their final stage.
Like YG, I think the previous mission was
more exciting and showed your talents.
In this round, I don't think your
and Ye-dam's stage were great.
But one thing is that Chan-hyuk's
rap lyrics were well-written.
It was moving, and just as YG
said that it was like a poem...
I give you this score as
I was moved by that part.
SM's score is...
She said he writes well,
but what about the score?
95 points!
They received a total
of 282 points.
I'll ask them the same question.
Every stage is now over.
How do you feel?
- It's bittersweet.
- Bittersweet?
And Chan-hyuk?
I wasn't satisfied
with this stage.
He feels sorry that it's over,
but you did well until now.
We need to wait
for the results.
For those who think Akdong Musician should
be the winner of K-POP STAR Season 2..
Please text 'Akdong Musician'
or the number '2' to #0606..
That was candidate No.2,
Akdong Musician!
Now the long-awaited final for
KPOP STAR Season 2 is over!
Who will be Season 2's winner?
Will these people know?
They had a fierce battle
here last year.
Now they returned to us
as genuine K-pop stars.
Welcome Park Ji-min
and Lee Hi!
I'm flabbergasted at how pretty
you became. It's a surprise.
They're your juniors on stage.
They must be very nervous.
Ji-min, how would you
describe their feelings?
They should be very nervous.
Going from TOP3 to TOP2...
But they did well and I'm
thankful for the great stages.
They should be really nervous.
Is there anyone you're
personally cheering for?
Well... I'm cheering
for Bang Ye-dam.
Really? She sure is honest.
Lee Hi is also here.
How was it when
compared to Season 1?
In skills and charms,
which was better?
I recall Season 1 having
many unique contestants.
Season 2 has many contestants
with different charms.
I think it's a close match.
A close match? Okay,
same question.
Who do you think will win?
I want both to do well.
Alright, but you might
be thinking of a winner.
With familiar faces from
both Seasons 1 and 2...
We'll see you next week on
KPOP STAR's dream stage.
Please take interest.
We've seen all the stages filled
with their passions and dreams.
It's over. Who is
the victor?
We announce the results!
I went to Jamsil Gymnasium
and sang with my dad, but...
- He's my son.
- A son?
They thought I was a girl.
While on KPOP STAR,
I grew taller...
I danced and rapped
for the first time.
It's like a dream.
We had no desire in the beginning.
We wanted to see how far we could go.
But we became desperate as
we advanced more and more.
In Season 1, they cried when
they passed and were eliminated.
I couldn't understand that.
Is that something
to cry about?
But it's not. You don't know that
feeling if you don't experience it.
I was overwhelmed.
Pit-a-pat...
I hope I become a
great singer.
We didn't know
our potential...
This place gave
us a dream.
I think we can start with
this as a steppingstone.
The 8-month long journey of
KPOP STAR Season 2 has ended.
Only the results remain.
Seeing these young people trying hard and
experiencing things on the big stage...
Before being an MC, as their senior
in music, I felt many things.
I learned a lot and
also felt sad.
I wanted to cheer them,
sing them a song.
Anyways...
To the contestants of KPOP STAR
Season 2, you did a great job.
[I'm a Butterfly - YB]
[Shin Ji-hoon
Season 2 TOP10]
[YouU
[Sung Soo-jin
Season 2 TOP10]
[Choi Ye-geun
[Raccoon Boys
Season 2 TOP10]
[2,000 won
[Lee Jin-woo, Andrew Choi
Season 2 TOP10]
That was great. Awesome.
YB and our TOP10 put
on a fantastic stage.
Even I was surprised. Another
round of applause for them.
It'll be great if it could
end with all of us united.
But we have to see who is the
winner on KPOP STAR Season 2.
We will announce
the winner soon.
This is your last chance to vote
as you watch the highlight clip.
Who will it be?
I'm looking forward to who
will be the K-pop star.
Stay tuned! Voting
will soon end!
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
Voting is now over.
Another round of applause to the
TOP2 for the impressive stages.
Only one team with the highest
total score will seize the glory.
Bang Ye-dam and Akdong Musician.
Who will be the ultimate winner?
Before I make the announcement,
I'm going to ask how they feel.
You're waiting for the
results. How do you feel?
I'm nervous but happy
that it's finally over.
Since he's young, he's happy it's over.
I don't think he's that nervous.
Akdong Musician,
how do you feel?
We're also nervous, and
since Ye-dam did so well...
Both teams must be nervous.
Folks, who do you
think will win?
Who?
I think the viewers would
be thinking who as well?
Only the announcement remains.
Will it be the youngest winner
in auditioning history?
Or will it be the first teenage singer-
songwriter in auditioning history?
They don't know the results.
I already have the envelope with
the results of today's winner.
Who will be the winner of
KPOP STAR Season 2?
I will now announce the results
of KPOP STAR Season 2's final!
I saw it. The winner
is written on it.
Is it the genius teenage singer-songwriter
that amazed us with their many songs?
Or Bang Ye-dam, a 12-year-old who is
well-versed in all genres of music?
I'll now announce the winner
of KPOP STAR Season 2.
Akdong Musician has...
Been on the top of the music charts
surpassing existing singers.
That isn't an easy feat. And
it was with their own songs.
Bang Ye-dam, as you saw
what YG had mentioned...
You'll know if you look at his friends.
They're coping with a big stage.
These three are geniuses!
I will now make the announcement
who among them is the winner.
The winner of KPOP
STAR Season 2 is...
Akdong Musician!
Akdong Musician has finally
won on KPOP STAR Season 2.
Please give Bang Ye-dam a hand
for making this far as runner-up.
Their colleagues came out
to congratulate them.
Akdong Musician, could
you step forward please?
Congratulations!
You finally won.
How do you feel?
We never thought we'd make it this far.
Everyone did well on the TOP10 special stage.
I can't believe we surpassed
all of them to be here.
There are so many
I'm thankful to.
- I first thank God...
- Who do you think of the most?
- My mom and dad...
- Are they here?
Yes, they came to watch.
Chan-hyuk had a word,
and Soo-hyun?
- She's crying.
- We...
Give her a hand.
We shouldn't be here,
but we won...
You're humble. Anyways,
congratulations.
Bang Ye-dam, could
you come over here?
I admire you. At
the age of 12...
You should be playing with your
friends, but you became a runner-up.
How do you feel?
Even though I didn't win,
I did all that I could.
I put on a great stage and I'm happy
because I have no regrets.
He's so cute.
Do the judges have
anything to say?
YG?
Akdong Musician are a new discovery
of artists hidden away in Mongolia.
As I said before, the stage with
Yoon Do-hyun was memorable.
That stage showed how the contestants
shined with a reliable senior with them.
I hope to see the winner, runner-up, and
all the contestants in the music scene...
If you meet great seniors
and a great agency...
You are talented people that will
show an even brighter stage.
All of you guys did really well!
Thank you!
Next week will be the dream stage where
singers from Seasons 1 and 2 will perform.
I'll see you all next week..
Thank you!
Thank you all so much!