[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
Survival Audition KPOP STAR Season
2 had a long 8-month journey.
There are only two competitions left
until a new K-pop star is born.
I introduce the TOP3
of the semifinals!
[Bang Ye-dam is the youngest
TOP3 at the age of 12]
[A little giant who
doesn't know fear!]
[Akdong Musician swept the music
charts with their original songs!]
[They now have popularity!]
[Andrew Choi's voice
is in full swing]
[Overcame his weaknesses!
Close to completion!]
We didn't plan on picking
them for Season 2's TOP3.
But each is different
with their own colors.
Will the winner be
the oldest ever?
The youngest ever?
Or the first teenage
singer-songwriter?
It's going to be exciting.
[Little giant
Bang Ye-dam]
[A stage beyond
expectations!]
[Unlimited potential beyond
one's imaginations!]
Which K-pop star can show
his/her talents abroad?
I believe Bang Ye-dam's
future is most exceptional.
First, we have the one who writes
a new page in auditioning history.
The youngest TOP3 at the age
of 12, he is Bang Ye-dam!
[Andrew Choi's 14-year dream
of becoming a singer]
No one could have
expected this.
He made it to TOP10?
He's in the TOP5?
Now he's in TOP3.
Lately, I think
he's like a bull.
It's like something heavy
is slowly approaching.
[A shower of good comments since
the live broadcast started!]
We're frightened of him since
we don't know his limits.
The 2nd TOP3 finalist has a silent,
strong charisma. Andrew Choi!
[Genius musicians
Akdong Musician]
They're unique characters we
never saw in the gayo world.
[These sibling musicians
form a fantastic combo!]
[He's 18 and she's 15
Their skills grow daily!]
Putting aside whether
you sang well or not...
The lyrics and song moved
the heart. It was genuine.
They're natural. They
express what they feel.
It's beautiful.
The last TOP3 finalists
are Season 2's artists.
The attractive sibling duo,
Akdong Musician!
A round of applause to the TOP3
for making it to the semifinals!
Hi, I'm KPOP STAR's
MC, Yoon Do-hyun.
This is the final gateway
to become a K-pop star.
We have high hopes for the TOP3 that
received the agencies' training.
I introduce the 3 judges that
will give a fair judgment.
First is BoA of SM!
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
The crowd's going
wild again.
- BoA?
- Yes?
These three teams...
Is your voice okay?
- I caught a bad cold...
- A hand... she caught a cold.
Did you expect them to
make it to the semifinals?
I never expected them.
Just seeing them...
I could see that many talented people
with diverse personalities attended.
Since this stage is important, do your
best to perform at your optimal level.
Thank you. I hope you
get well from your cold.
- YG?
- Yes?
There was a lot of tension in
the commentaries last week.
We were nervous, but it was exciting.
Are you guys going to be nice today?
Well, the weather's
great today.
- You must be feeling great.
- Yes, I am.
Since BoA's sick,
let's not fight.
You guys are fun.
These three teams have
different charms.
JYP, is there anything you want to
say to them before they begin?
First, congratulations.
It's a tremendous thing to
have made it to the TOP3.
Only one of you will be
3rd, 2nd, or the winner.
But in five years, we won't be sure
who was the winner or who was 2nd.
People won't remember your rank. It's
the stage and song they'll remember.
Just enjoy regardless of being
the winner or runner-up.
That was very important.
We ask for a fair and
careful judgment today.
Before we begin the TOP3 semifinal
where we expect a fierce match...
They visited a special place.
We now reveal what
they experienced!
We're going to meet the
viewers that love the TOP3.
The TOP3 will be guests
on a radio show tomorrow.
Ra... radio?
- I'm not a good speaker.
- Guess that leaves only me.
It's a radio show so
I have to speak a lot.
I don't know
what to do.
[KPOP STAR's TOP3's
radio show appearance]
[Mar 26, 2013
Radio show]
Let's listen to
our songs.
I'm excited.
- Wait! This isn't exciting.
- Well, I thought it was.
[This is the
exciting part!]
[Excited to appear on
another broadcast]
[Going to get some nice clothes
since it's a "watching radio"]
[Akdong Musician's concept?]
Our concept is to look
cute with polka dots.
Andrew got clothes to
look young and bright.
[Ye-dam looks colorful]
[1 hour before the
radio show!]
[What radio show are
they appearing on?]
Wow! Escape 2 PM.
Cultwo Show!
- Wow!
- It's pretty!
It's a watchable
Cultwo Show.
[Can they do well
without mistakes?]
Andrew's nervous
right now.
I was sweating and thought
of questions they'd ask.
I was that nervous.
[Radio show begins!]
[They start with a
lively opening]
[But the TOP3 are...]
[Pit-a-pat]
- They're good.
- What do we do?
[While they go on a
commercial break...]
[The TOP3 enters!]
We can do it!
[As soon as they
enter the studio]
[A big applause!]
[That's a lot of cameras!]
[The popularity they
didn't feel hits them!]
Andrew Choi, Bang Ye-dam, and
Akdong Musician join us today.
Chan-hyuk, you
wrote 48 songs?
- Actually, it's 54.
- It increased?
It increased during our
time on KPOP STAR.
Can you give one of
your songs to us?
Don't if you
don't want to.
- He was like this for a while, "Uh..."
- Don't hesitate when an adult asks!
It's my first time on radio
so I was really nervous.
But when I actually went,
the MCs treated us well.
And the audience gave
a great response.
It felt natural.
That gives us strength.
Andrew, you don't
need to be stiff.
Can you sing a little of BoA's
"Only One" for your girlfriend?
- Could you do that?
- This is Andrew Choi.
[Their eyes are filled
with expectations]
[His voice flows sweetly]
[Forgets the tension and
immerses in the song]
[The female audience
is mesmerized by it]
[The studio is filled with
cheers and applause]
She's about to cry.
You're good!
Ye-dam, can you
sing "Sir Duke"?
Yes.
We'll be grateful
if you do.
[Clear high notes!]
[Oh]
[He's good!]
[They spice it up by
singing with him]
[Even the production crew
exclaim with admiration!]
[Applause from everywhere!]
[Even he ends it well]
They want you to sing
"Don't Cross Your Legs".
[This song amazed everyone
during Finals - Round 1]
[Applause filled with
expectations]
[Beaming with happiness]
[They're absorbed
in the music]
[As if answering
to their response]
[They sing even more
passionately]
[Explosive cheers
and applause!]
I guess we're musical people.
We're more relaxed after singing.
We want to come back on this show
when we become big entertainers!
I'm confident I'll do better
if I get another chance.
It was a fun experience. I'll try
hard to put on a great stage.
[We wish you well
on the semifinals!]
They must have been nervous
since it wasn't an audition.
But I think they had
fun and did well.
Looking forward to it.
Other than the TOP3 stages,
we also have 3 special stages.
It's a collaboration by the TOP3
and artists from SM, YG, and JYP.
First is Bang Ye-dam and
BIGBANG's Taeyang.
Next is Andrew Choi
and SHINee.
It will be meaningful.
And JYP mobilized 2AM, Wonder Girls,
and miss A for Akdong Musician.
Looking forward to it.
Before we begin, I will
announce the TOP3's number.
Can't believe he's 12. With nerves
of steel, he's No. 1 Bang Ye-dam!
He became a likely winner with
his potential. No. 2 Andrew Choi!
A shock to the gayo world. It's teenage
singer-songwriter, No. 3 Akdong Musician!
You can choose who will
advance to the finals.
Boom will give you the
details on the voting.
Hi, I'm KPOP STAR's MC,
Boom. Glad to be here.
KPOP STAR's semfinal is the
final gateway to victory.
It will soon be broadcasted
here at Bucheon Gymnasium.
We earnestly want
your votes today.
I'll tell you
how to vote.
Open up the messaging
on your cellphone...
Text #0606 with the finalists'
Korean name or number.
You're rooting for more than
one person? No need to worry.
You can vote for
more than one person.
But you can't make multiple
votes for the same person.
Even one vote counts.
You can also vote via
mobile messengers.
Who do you think will be
Season 2's winner?
Bang Ye-dam, Andrew Choi,
or Akdong Musician?
We'll have those
results today.
Please vote.
We now begin voting
for the semifinals!
[Voting Begins]
[Text #0606 with their
name or number]
Judges' score is 70% and votes are 30%.
The total determines who advances.
The one with the lowest score will be
eliminated and the rest advances.
Who will advance to
KPOP STAR's finals?
The semifinal prepared by SM,
YG, and JYP will soon begin.
People have expectations as he
was casted to YG for the first time.
We will start off
with Bang Ye-dam!
It'll be the most
tense stage.
How will he release his potential
again with training from YG?
That's why it's hard.
You have to draw something out
that you never showed before.
He can't do it today since he's
emotional because of 2,000 won.
Get some sleep and we'll
discuss tomorrow.
[Next morning]
[Turns over a new leaf!
First day at YG]
I want to get
there quickly.
[Has high hopes since
it's his first time at YG]
[But]
[Stops at a new place]
- Get off, Ye-dam.
- Here?
[Where is this?]
[He enters a big gym and
not YG Entertainment]
[A shiny vehicle
approaches him]
[The one riding it is...]
[Ye-dam's idol - G-Dragon]
I was surprised.
I really liked GD...
I mean, I really
like him!
I thought, "What would
give Ye-dam strength?"
I thought his role model is G-Dragon,
who came to YG at the age of 13.
[G-Dragon approaches
Ye-dam during his break]
Wait, wait!
- Hi.
- Hello.
[GD puts out his
hand first]
[When GD looks at him]
[He's frozen]
It's good to see you in
person and not only on TV.
You wrote your own
rap lyrics, right?
You wrote about BoA.
[GD remembers his stage!]
Want to stand there?
[Ye-dam standing on
a world tour stage?]
[A real K-pop star's stage
and not an audition stage!]
This is the center.
[He's speechless]
I wanted to become a great singer
later and stand on that stage.
It was awesome.
[A high five wishing him
to advance to the finals]
I'm giving you energy.
[Signs it and writes
a message for him]
"Come to me after you
become a great singer."
[Receiving GD's energy, his steps
are light as he arrives at YG]
[Begins choosing a song]
One of the shocks I received this season
is when Ye-dam sang Bieber's "Baby".
"Huh? He's better at
rapping than singing."
It's due to his exceptional
sense of rhythm.
His rapping was good and I
wanted to show that again.
So I chose The Black Eyed Peas'
"Where Is the Love" for him.
When I used to rap, it was
just a little in the middle.
Since this is a hip-hop song,
I have to rap correctly.
He raps better than me.
Thank you.
I think Tablo should
look over the lyrics.
The results of those that came
to YG weren't that great.
I have to turn that around at
least once before the show's over.
[Victory]
I could speak of this
in my heart, but...
I didn't know how to
express this in rap.
Tablo helped me how to
express that and rhyme.
"I'm not used to this
situation. I'm wandering."
[Unexpectedly, his
diary is serious]
I'm in a surival audition.
I felt sad and lonely as
they left one by one.
But I find hope since
I have music.
People might think he's simple because
he's 12, but he's not. He has depth.
I'm envious of him.
Because of him,
3 YG studios...
No artist at YG
does that.
Many people at YG are helping me.
So I think I have to try harder.
Please look forward
to it. Yeah!
[Where Is the Love - The Black Eyed Peas
(arr. by Tablo, PK, Lydia Paek)]
It made me dream
It made Michael Jackson sad
I'm afraid of the adults' world
My shoulders are small but feels heavy
Ye-dam has no brothers or sisters
But those that are like brothers or sisters
Leave and that makes me shed tears
I feel lonely to return to an empty room
Even though I am lacking
Music filled me with joy
I love you. Watch me
Thank you so much
We could feel his thoughts in the rap
lyrics and arrangement. It was impressive.
We're curious of his
score and commentary.
I enjoyed it.
You said you wanted to turn
the tables and hit a homer.
It was the best stage that
YG could come up with.
It was a great stage that was
in YG and Ye-dam's style.
I thought if there's a show like this where
contestants change during the show.
If you compare his first stage
and this stage side by side...
His voice was barely audible
before and wasn't confident.
Now he has charisma, swag,
vocalization, and breathing.
It was a great stage.
One thing was
unfortunate.
A few weeks ago, your father said,
"Be careful not to go too fast."
I think you were excited - you
liked the song and everything.
Your beat and dance got fast.
That was it. I enjoyed it.
- JYP's score is...
- Thank you very much.
That's a lot of compliments.
But the score is...
- It's 92!
- Thank you.
It's a good score.
- BoA?
- Yes.
This is Ye-dam's first time at
YG and we saw their combination.
I think this hip-hop
style really fits him.
It finished like a club which is YG's
stlye. The exciting stage was great.
I still think you need more work on your
pronunciation - English and Korean.
Pronunciation is important
especially in rapping.
You need to make
efforts for that.
SM's score is...
She talked about pronunciation,
but what is SM's score?
- It's 89!
- Thank you.
Last is YG's score
and commentary.
This song isn't really great in showing
off one's singing skills or dance.
Even The Black Eyed Peas don't do
much at their concert with this song.
You can't dance or show
off your singing skills.
I thought of how to interpret
this song for Bang Ye-dam.
Since he showed many things,
I don't know if you felt it, but...
I refrained him from dancing since
the viewers said they can't hear him.
As he refrained from dancing and
focused more on rapping and singing...
For me, the motions
were a little wanting.
I think it's hard even for me to
arrange and do this in a week.
I want to give you a
high score for that.
- YG's score is...
- It's YG's score.
He did the producing.
The score is...
- It's 90!
- Thank you.
The judges' score is 271.
As YG said, it's not easy for someone
so young to do this in a week.
What was the hardest
during that week?
A week is short.
Singing, dancing, rapping were hard
because I had to rush things.
It was hard, huh? He's also at the
age where he needs plenty of sleep.
He didn't get much sleep.
I heard you were sleepy.
- Uh... yes.
- Good job.
Good job. A
hand please.
If you think Bang Ye-dam
is the next K-pop star...
Please text #0606 with
"Bang Ye-dam" or "No. 1".
This stage was by
No. 1 Bang Ye-dam!
Next is another stage prepared
by SM with Andrew Choi!
[Advances to the semifinals
with terrifying force!]
[Andrew Choi's
voice is flawless]
If he showed his singing
skills with that song...
What song will make him
go over that limit?
The next round is
the semifinals.
You have to show the end
that no one ever expected.
Let's make a stage that will
catch them off guard again.
So we chose Justin
Bieber's "Baby".
[Justin Bieber's "Baby"?]
[The song that released
Bang Ye-dam's potential]
Andrew Choi and Justin
Bieber's "Baby". What?
Andrew Choi singing Justin
Bieber's "Baby" is new.
Now we need a stage
with such a twist.
[Andrew tries singing...]
[Completely different feel!]
When I first heard it, I thought,
"Wow! 'Baby' can change like this?"
We can beat Ye-dam!
Let's make it bling-bling
as if it's a live show.
[Seo Han-young
designer and stylist]
[Hong Joo
hair designer]
I love that hair.
There are many people helping me. I
couldn't make it this far without them.
Hi, Andrew!
[Andrew's other
supporters, SHINee]
Congratulations on TOP3!
[SHINee cheers and
congratulates him]
[They give him their autographed
album he worked on as a gift]
[A few days later]
[Where did Andrew arrive?]
[Andrew's friends!]
[So far, he looks
the happiest]
It gives me strength that
they came to cheer me.
[Baby - Justin Bieber
(arr. by Kim Tae-sung)]
Andrew singing "Baby" was new,
but what did the judges think?
Please tell us the
score and commentary.
I think JYP, me, and the viewers were
surprised that he was singing "Baby".
I gave a good commentary for
last week's song because...
When he interpreted it in an R&B style
for the Koreans that knew that song...
It satisfied those in Korea and
those that enjoy R&B songs.
Bang Ye-dam also sang
Justin Bieber's "Baby".
I know why BoA made
such a dangerous move.
Since only the TOP3 remains,
she had to take a risk.
Kim Yuna wouldn't perform a risky ad-lib
or technique right before the finals.
It's important to take such risks
and try during the preliminaries.
But in the TOP3...
We call it a "risk" or "challenge"
because that's how dangerous it is.
It was better than expected but
not enough to call it a twist.
YG's score is...
It's YG's score. He said
the twist was weak...
- It's 86!
- Thank you.
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
It's true that Andrew showed the most
terrifying transformation since TOP10.
I thought his bad habits in vocalization
and breathing would never change, but...
It's incredible that he changed
his 15-year-old habits.
It was shocking.
I thought, "What was
the reason behind it?"
Among the TOP10, he didn't
strive to be the winner.
Thus, he was always relaxed
and naturally made good sounds.
He wanted to win for the
first time in the semifinals.
Of course, you should.
But that made you stiff.
You started straining your
voice again here and there.
Maybe you were nervous
since it's the semifinals.
Bang Ye-dam just sang his song
but, it wasn't about singing.
Rather it was how well he got it and
performed on stage and was in rhythm.
You chose a great song to show
off your singing skills, but...
Unfortunately, you
didn't explode.
It didn't meet my
expectations.
JYP's score is...
It's JYP's score. He said
that he was nervous...
- It's 89!
- Thank you.
Last is the score
from BoA of SM.
This is the 2nd stage
we prepared at SM.
Our plan was to have
a 30s "Baby".
You know Andrew Buble? We made
Michael Buble into Andrew Buble.
If you had fun, were happy, and sang
without greed, it would've been great.
You were stiff today compared
to when you were practicing.
As JYP said, I think you wanted
to win for the first time.
It's a pity that your
voice wasn't as open.
It's true that this song
was too much for you.
But I'll give you a good score
for putting on a great stage.
SM's score is...
It's SM's score. She said
he was very nervous...
- It's 90!
- Thank you.
The judges' score is 265.
On the stage... were you
satisfied with the stage?
- It was a pity...
- What was?
- I was in bad condition...
- Oh, your condition?
It was a pity that I couldn't
do as much as I could.
Who comes to mind
right now?
A lot of people...
- First, my family...
- Your family?
- My parents...
- They're over there.
My friends that cheered
me and my girlfriend.
And I also thank all the
people that helped me.
Okay. It was pretty long.
If you liked Andrew
Choi's stage...
Please text #0606 with
"Andrew Choi" or "No. 2".
This stage was by
No. 2 Andrew Choi!
Next is the last TOP3 stage. It's
a great stage prepared with JYP.
Akdong Musician's
stage will start now!
They sang 4 songs for me saying that
they wanted to sing their songs.
Among them...
What's "Foreigner's Confession"?
[A unique title that
piqued JYP's interest]
We're singing our song,
"Foreigner's Confession".
A foreigner from abroad comes and
awkwardly confesses to a Korean.
It's interesting and I kept on
laughing at the first part.
The chorus is
the problem.
Rewrite it and
make it fun.
- I can do that.
- You can?
You'll do well.
There's a small book I give
only to our composers.
JYP gave us a small notebook that
contains his composition know-hows.
I think he's passionate. He calls us
every day and tries to teach us.
It wasn't our day for shooting,
but he will personally call us.
He will hear our songs and teach
us how to supplement it.
[JYP's ultimate
passion project!]
Since our concept
is confession...
I have to get that feeling to
write the chorus part well.
Lee Soo, who's your
ideal person?
Hurry, who?
And Chan-hyuk?
- Suzy.
- Suzy?
[He's a big fan of
miss A's Suzy]
Take him to the set then.
He'll have the
heart to confess.
He has to see her to
be able to write.
To see Suzy...
I was given that privilege.
You're blushing.
[Off to Yongin where
Suzy is filming!]
- Hello?
- Hello.
I think she's
in that car.
Hello.
[Suzy - Korea's first love
with a beautiful face]
[Dumbfounded by this
dreamlike realtiy]
I'm your fan!
The sun's in my eyes.
[He's senseless because of
her beauty that's like the sun]
I love that song...
"Crescendo".
[As soon as she's
done speaking]
[Preparation done]
[A song for Suzy]
[Akdong Musician and Suzy
unite with "Crescendo"]
All together now.
Do you have a song you
are singing this time?
We're singing our song
about confession...
If I see you, then I...
[He's embarrassed to continue]
Can I hear that too?
Of course!
- It's "Foreigner's Confession".
- He's even kneeling down.
[She follows him
and sits also]
[Even listening to music
is like a photo shoot]
- That's it.
- That's great!
It'll be a hit.
I'll give you
some energy.
She's prettier in person.
[They receive all
of her support]
She said she's our fan
and treated us well.
I think that gives us strength
and we can do better on stage.
Will we see you again?
Their music and stage
upgraded one level.
Look forward to it.
[Foreigner's Confession - own song
(arr. by Wasabii Sound)]
It was their new song. What
did the judges think?
Let's hear the score
and commentary.
Why are the contestants off key
and not in rhythm today?
Not only you guys, but also
Ye-dam and Andrew Choi.
Soo-hyun, when you
started the song off...
You missed the first note and Chan-hyuk,
even though the register was low...
You were unstable.
The music was great but since
you two were unstable...
I want to listen to
the sound source.
The lyrics were cleverly written
as expected from you guys.
You guys are the greatest and
cute when you sing your songs.
I enjoyed it.
SM's score is...
She said the lyrics were
clever, but they were unstable.
The score is... 91!
That's a good score.
Let's hear the next
score and commentary.
I felt the same
thing BoA said.
This happens a lot even to existing
singers. I know JYP did well, but...
It would have been stable if
the key was a half note higher.
It's true that it
was low for them.
The title of the song is
"Foreigner's Confession".
Just looking at the title, "How could
they write lyrics with such an idea?"
I always think that
they're unique.
As BoA said, I read the
lyrics as they sang.
Since a foreigner can't speak Korean
well when confessing to the woman...
It was clever how they used
simple English words.
Maybe it's because it's their own songs,
I don't feel like I'm watching their stage.
It always feel like an existing
singer announcing their new album.
YG's score is...
It's YG's score. He said
their lyrics were clever.
It's 92! That's
a high score.
Last is JYP's score.
I was excited to work with
them this week because...
They're the only contestants I could
see composing and write music.
I always tell my
junior composers...
Whenever you start writing, start with
the heart and complete with the head.
The music written by Chan-hyuk
was only from the heart because...
Unexpectedly, he doesn't know
any chord progressions.
I taught him a few simple things since
he doesn't know what he's doing.
He really enjoys studying. Usually,
sentimental people don't like it.
I teach him a little
and he's having fun.
He writes it down and
starts memorizing.
I felt that he'll now write music starting
with the heart and ending with the head.
I thought that a lot because if
you only write from the heart...
You could get a lot of big hits,
but you don't compose for long.
But if you only write with the head, you
do it a long time without many big hits.
I can't really say this now, but I think
Chan-hyuk will be a great composer.
I think this song will
also be a big hit.
JYP's score is...
He gave much advice
in composition.
It's JYP's score.
It's 94!
The judges' score is 277.
It's the highest so far.
They were unstable but
got a good score.
Chan-hyuk, who did you think
of as you sang? Was it...
Su...
Was it her? Did
it help you?
It was a lot of...
You couldn't even
look at her.
Alright. We'll end
the interview.
If you want to see Akdong
Musician again next week...
Please text #0606 with
"Akdong Musician" or "No. 3".
This stage was by No. 3
Akdong Musician!
The TOP3 stages are now over,
and they all did their best.
I'm very curious who will
advance to the finals.
Akdong Musician has the highest judges'
score, but we don't know the results yet.
According to the votes,
their fate can change.
We have a special program waiting
for us before voting is over. Boom?
Yes, that's right. I'm here
with the audience again.
We now have the
TOP3's special stage.
Increase the volume and
don't change the channel.
Representing artists from
SM, YG, and JYP, and...
KPOP STAR's TOP3
prepared together.
I'll introduce
them first.
SM helped out Andrew Choi
and their artist is SHINee.
JYP helped out Akdong Musician and
Jo Kwon and Changmin of 2AM...
Yeeun of Wonder Girls and
Jia of miss A will help.
YG helped out Bang Ye-dam and
their artist is BIGBANG's Taeyang.
The world's best stages that can
only be watched here will begin.
First up is BIGBANG's
Taeyang and Bang Ye-dam.
[Bad Boy - BIGBANG]
[I Don't Need a Man - miss A]
[Beautiful - SHINee]
Wow! That was great!
It's so hot here!
Thank you for the great stages
that can only be watched here.
Andrew composed the song himself
and sang with SHINee. It was great.
All the stages, including
the specials, are over now.
Who will advance to the
finals? Even I'm nervous.
We will have the
results soon.
Voting and mobile voting
will also end soon.
Now's your last chance.
As you watch the highlight
clip, make your final choices.
We ask for your votes!
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
The fierce semifinals
are now over.
The results have been tallied, and
only the announcements remain.
The final results
are in my hands.
The one with the lowest total
score will be eliminated tonight.
Of the three contestants, who
will advance to the finals?
Bang Ye-dam, Andrew Choi, and
Akdong Musician are anxiously waiting.
Before the announcements,
let's hear how they feel.
Bang Ye-dam, you're
nervous, right?
I'm really nervous.
Do you think all
will be well?
I'm not sure.
Alright. Andrew Choi,
how do you feel?
I'm really nervous because
both of them did well.
He said he's nervous
since they did very well.
Akdong Musician?
It's a pity because we
made a lot of mistakes.
Nervous because you made mistakes.
But all of you should be nervous.
I feel it too. Regardless of rank,
we'll announce who passed.
The results are
in my hands.
Of the three, who
will advance first?
Bang Ye-dam showed a new side
and heard many good things.
Andrew Choi also did well, but
he was unstable and nervous.
Akdong Musician received a lot
of compliments for their song.
But they were very unstable.
Of the three, I will announce
the first one who will advance.
Who will advance first?
Bang Ye-dam, Andrew Choi,
or Akdong Musician?
The fact that they're
here is unbelievable.
It'll be a shock if either
one of them gets eliminated.
Which team will advance first
and get KPOP STAR's honor?
I'll announce it now!
The first one to advance is...
Akdong Musician!
You got a lot of compliments
for your song today.
The lyrics were new. They
advance to the finals.
Congratulations!
How do you feel?
Thank you for choosing us even
though we didn't do well.
And Chan-hyuk?
This week was tough
and we prepared a lot.
I'm happy we passed.
Thank you. The viewers
placed many votes.
A big hand for them as
they move over there.
Only Bang Ye-dam and Andrew
Choi remain on stage.
Even I'm nervous.
They're anxiously waiting
for the results.
The judges are watching
with a hard look.
Their parents and family
are in the audience.
I think they're
more nervous.
These two actually put
on an impressive stage.
Bang Ye-dam continued showing amazing
stages although he's the youngest.
Andrew Choi made it this far like a
veteran showing how he changed.
Is it going to be the
oldest or youngest?
Getting nervous.
After the announcement, one of them will
leave after the long 8-month journey.
Who will advance
to the finals?
I think even Akdong
Musician are nervous.
Should I announce
the results?
Should I?
Here I go.
KPOP STAR's finalist is...
Bang Ye-dam!
Congratulations,
Bang Ye-dam.
For someone so young,
this must be unbearable.
But you made it
to the finals.
As they congratulate and
cheer for Bang Ye-dam...
Unfortunately, Andrew Choi
will be leaving KPOP STAR.
First, Bang Ye-dam?
If it's okay... He's
crying right now.
How do you feel?
Do you...
- I'm very happy.
- Are you?
Why are you crying?
Because Andrew is leaving...
It must break your heart.
A hand for him please.
We were proud of you.
Andrew Choi, you got eliminated
with the finals right before you.
Any last words for the viewers, fans,
and family that cheered for you?
- Can I say it in English?
- Yes, we have JYP.
Could JYP interpret that?
He thanked God
and everyone.
You release an album, get a car,
and cash if you win here.
Can you compare that to a song
sung by a woman who loves you?
That's cool.
Basically, he's already a
winner with that gift.
In many cases, lovers broke up
after the audition was over.
But I don't think this
couple will break up.
That's right. They're
a beautiful couple.
JYP, any advice for Andrew
since you have the mike?
I saw many great stages and towards
the end, you impressed me a lot.
I enjoyed it and
congratulations.
Thank you JYP and another
hand for Andrew Choi.
Do the others want to say anything?
YG? BoA? BoA may go first.
I worked with Andrew the
most and got really close.
I was impressed with his stages that
showed age doesn't matter in music.
Not only as a composer and producer, but
we would also like to see you as a singer.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
The long-awaited finals
will be next week.
See you next week!
Goodbye!