Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3!
I introduce you to the TOP3
that made to the semifinal!
[Sam Kim the dark horse
of live broadcast!]
[The appearance of boy genius!]
[He's moving upward
without any difficulty!]
You're a soul man!
You're a diamond
hidden in the earth!
[Sam Kim is a gem that
was discovered!]
[He possesses talent
to be world best!]
[Overflowing with talent!
Soul flows in his body!]
[He evolves every round!]
[His potential is limitless!]
Our first TOP3 is Sam Kim!
He is rapidly rising and gives an
amazing performance each round!
[Kwon Jina turns into a
goddess from a girl!]
[A female vocalist with
a new sentiment!]
[Musicality, guitar playing, sense of rhythm,
vocalization, and musical interpretation]
[Kwon Jina in crazy mode!]
[She could become the best
female ballad singer!]
[She is skilled in her
varied voices!]
[That is frightening!]
Our second TOP3 is Kwon Jina!
She is loved immensely for her
captivating timbre and voice!
[Bernard Park has a voice
that touches the heart!]
[Set a record with
a score of 299!]
[His voice is a masterpiece!]
[Lavished with praise
by the judges!]
[His voice and timbre is
in a different league]
[A heavyweight in the world of
singers going beyond KPOP STAR!]
[Anticipating a stronger punch
than the previous one!]
Our last TOP3 is Bernard Park!
He is a sentimental singer
in a different league!
Another round of applause for the
TOP3 that made to the seminfinal!
Hello to the viewers
watching this live.
I'm Jun Hyun-moo, the emcee
for KPOP STAR Season 3.
We now have one round left for
the K-pop star to be decided.
The outcome is unpredictable and one
of them will be the 3rd K-pop star.
Please tune in to the end.
The winner will be awarded a cash prize of
$300,000 and a midsize diesel vehicle.
The runner-up will get
a compact diesel vehicle.
I introduce the three judges that are
more nervous as we reach the finale.
JYPE's Park Jin-young!
YGE's Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Music's You Hee-yeol!
Every live show was hard...
But it's hard to predict who
will be eliminated today.
YG, how do you predict
today's performance?
I think this round is more important
and tense than the finale.
The strange thing is...
JYP complimented Bernard Park from
the beginning and said he's a Beraholic.
I wasn't able to but You Hee-yeol
recognized Kwon Jina at first sight.
I don't know if you remember but...
I predicted Sam Kim to be in TOP3
after watching his first performance.
It's interesting that the person
we're each rooting for are here.
It feels more like a battle between
the 3 agencies and not amongst them.
Do your best and we won't be
cutting you slack in this round.
Whether you did well or not
in the past isn't important.
We'll judge solely on how you
do today so do your best.
This will also be a standpoint on
whose prediction is correct.
JYP, you said the winner you're thinking of
changes every week. Is that actually true?
I'm not saying this because we're on
broadcast but I honestly don't know.
But as we saw until now...
Bernard Park has the voice...
Kwon Jina has the technique...
And Sam Kim has the feel.
That's a close match.
Who will use their skills to
the fullest? That is the key.
This is a battle between
voice, technique, and feel.
You Hee-yeol, this past week
was Antenna Music week.
JYP and YG had a strong week.
Were you able to inspire them?
We did our best but I don't
know what they thought.
They're already like fellow
singers and juniors to me.
I look forward to the best performance
but there is one thing I can't get over.
JYP's shirt is cut
fairly low at the neck.
I thought it was stretched.
I can see his collarbone and
I am very uncomfortable.
Well, he is fashion forward.
But we do see some skin.
Let's watch how You Hee-yeol
inspired them as a musician.
[It's Antenna Music week!]
[For this week...]
[They're visiting the office
of Antenna Music!]
The other two are
Korea's best agencies...
But we are more like a family and
I wanted to make them feel that.
It's been a year since every artist
under our label gathered.
Thanks to them, we're having something
like a welcome party for freshmen.
We prepared a little get-together.
[How did they prepare the
welcome party for the TOP3?]
[Party balloons]
[Refreshments]
[Welcome banner]
[And...]
[A surprise welcome party!]
Suddenly I'm shy.
[Jung Jaehyung, 45, 20-year veteran
the oldest in Antenna Music]
[Lucid Fall, 40, 14-year veteran
coo and gurgle singing style]
You're nervous because there
are a lot of cameras, right?
[The biggest event since the agency
was founded! They're all nervous...]
[Peppertones, 11-year veteran
Antenna Music's idol group]
[Park Sae Byul, 30, 7-year veteran
the youngest in Antenna Music]
I'm so nervous! Wait...
- How do we use this?
- Smile naturally.
[Unnatural...]
Make a comfortable smile.
I'm nervous because
I can't do that.
I'm feeling nauseous.
[Can they do this properly?]
[Outside the door...]
[You Hee-yeol waits nervously]
Why are you looking at
pictures of women?
Don't surf the web.
Do something like excel!
[He nags at them because
he's feeling nervous...]
Don't you have different slippers?
[While he's waiting nervously...]
[They arrived!]
[They don't know a surprise
welcome party is prepared]
[They go inside for now...]
- Quiet, they're coming.
- He startled me.
I'm nervous...
[Sigh...]
Stay close then
we'll tremble less.
[They enter the office]
[He greets them calmly
with a smile]
- I think they're here!
- They're here.
[Frozen]
He's our CEO.
[It's peaceful out here...]
[But they're nervous inside!]
[What do we say?]
[Welcome]
Alright! Let's go in!
[The time has come!]
[Welcome]
[Antenna Music's artists have
all gathered after a year]
[They were a bit clumsy
in the surprise]
[But the response was great!]
[A simple party prepared
by their seniors!]
This is embarrassing...
Sit over there for now.
We haven't been on
television that much.
Because of our age, we also
felt a little embarrassed.
We felt both excited and
awkward at the same time.
[The TOP3 welcome party
officially begins!]
[Sam Kim introduces first...]
Stand up.
Hi, my name is Sam Kim and
I'm the youngest here.
- How old are you?
- I'm 16...
What happened to you?
[I'm joking]
[Next is Kwon Jina]
Hi, my name is Kwon Jina.
Time for the talent show.
[The talent show is the
centerpiece of the party]
- Here you go...
- No, not that.
Since she's already
good with the guitar...
I heard that she's good
at the "Growl" dance.
[Her "Growl" dance
is now a legend!]
[It's an unusual scene since there is no
dancing singer in Antenna Music!]
[They're singing a dance song?]
[Can she do the "Growl" dance
along their singing?]
[Here she goes]
[The legendary growling
goddess is back!]
[Making a racket]
[They applaud enthusiastically!]
Bernard looks really...
[He can't avoid it]
He's like this and not smiling.
First time seeing him flustered.
[Bernard Park's turn]
Hi, my name is Bernard Park
and I'm 22 years old.
[As soon as he's done...]
Now it's your turn...
[What is he going to do?]
He's good at dancing
Beyonce's "Single Ladies."
[Really?]
[He's doing this dance?]
You will sing and dance for
the first time without music.
[Bernard's "Single Lady" dance
started with a tip-off from Sam!]
[It's a big hit]
[Bernard's was the best]
They have nowhere to go
but Antenna Music, right?
That's right.
Is there any other?
This show was planned
centered on Antenna Music.
There's a place called YG and
what was the other one?
It belongs to Jin-young but
I forgot what it was called.
I heard the JYP building
belongs to Cho Yong-pil.
[JYP = Cho Yong-pil?]
There's a place called JYP that
he's renting from Cho Yong-pil.
YG looks great, right? But most of
their income is from the cafeteria.
[They stop with the gag and
make a toast to their welcome!]
[Someone arrives in
front of the agency!]
[Who is this charismatic man?]
[Who is it?]
[It's Yoon Jong-shin!]
[You Hee-yeol invited
Yoon Jong-shin in secret!]
[They're dumbfounded]
- I'll introduce him...
- This is my branch.
[He's the CEO of an agency that has
musical ties with Antenna Music]
I'm sorry. I can't see.
You wore that just for
your entrance?
I wanted to look tough.
I called him saying that
the three of you are coming.
He said he wanted to meet you,
and we often meet like this and talk.
Next week is the finale and
one of them will be eliminated.
There's a new rule where the winner
gets to choose his/her agency.
- On the spot?
- On the spot!
As a CEO, give them some advice
to make the right choice...
Putting CEO aside...
This is the only agency that
will do everything for you.
[Are they that desperate?]
[Seems like he hit the mark]
You won't get better treatment than 2NE1
even though you become the winner.
But here...
You will get treated well
even if you get 3rd place.
How did I do as a rookie judge?
To put it bluntly...
He wanted to take off
rather than be a judge.
I've never seen anyone do
commercials after being a judge.
He did it for himself and
not for Antenna Music.
[Everyone was all smiles
at the welcome party...]
People doing music nowadays...
Think it's competitive, there's
hard work and unrelenting pain.
But we have fun and are
happy doing music.
We grow and learn from one another
whether you're a senior or junior.
I hope they can feel that
and have hope in that.
I want to give them a present that
they can live their life doing music.
This past week was Antenna Music week.
Were you satisfied, You Hee-yeol?
I feel embarrassed.
It's been a while seeing
balloons at a welcome party.
Our artists blew up all
those balloons.
It was more like a reception.
I'll explain today's rules.
It's absolute evaluation again...
The total score is calculated from
judges' score 60% and viewers' votes 40%.
Two with the highest total score will
advance to next week's finale.
And one will unfortunately
depart from KPOP STAR.
Please stay tuned to find out
who will advance to the finale.
I'll announce their order
and number.
No.1 Bernard Park now touches
everyone's heart, young and old.
No. 2 Kwon Jina is complimented every
round with unexpected performances.
No. 3 Sam Kim is a guitar genius
who knows how to enjoy the stage.
It's fine to call this the finale with
such likely winners competing.
Thus, your votes will be
very important today.
Yoo Hye-young will explain
how the voting is done.
- Yoo Hye-young?
- Yes, can you hear this?
The audience is buzzing with
excitement more than ever.
Hi, I'm Yoo Hye-young.
Your votes are important since
one of them will be eliminated.
I'll explain how you can vote.
Text the contestant's name in Korean or
their number to #0606 on your phone.
You might know this by now.
You can vote for more than one contestant
but no multiple votes for one contestant.
Since voting is possible via KakaoTalk,
those abroad can also participate.
The semifinal will soon begin.
Are you ready to vote?
Text voting begins now!
[Text voting begins]
[Text the contestant's name in Korean or
number to #0606 (10 cents data charge)]
This show is being televised live.
We ask that many of you vote.
Many special stages are prepared.
First is a collaboration between
Kwon Jina and JYP's Sunmi.
Second is Bernard Park and Antenna Music's
Peppertones and Park Sae Byul.
And finally Sam Kim meets them.
There's a collaboration
between 2NE1 and Sam Kim.
There's another special stage
after all of that is over.
Akdong Musician, winners of Season 2,
will be making their debut here after a year.
They're performing two songs for the
first time so please look forward to that.
We will now officially begin.
He received the highest
score ever at 299.
No. 1 Bernard Park is up!
[No. 1 Bernard Park]
[He received the highest score
ever last week at 299!]
I never knew I would get
that high of a score.
That feeling was indescribable.
[He meets his parents after
getting into the TOP3]
You really got me too when
you said "I love you" at the end.
I love you.
That gave me a boost.
I think I can do better.
[They were practicing for the
TOP3 performance one day]
[A very slim man visits them]
Let me try that.
[With one try!]
[He's weaker than
the female staff]
[Weak You Hee-yeol makes
them a surprise visit]
I wanted to give them a
pep talk and cheer them up.
I thought of what could
encourage them.
Inside this envelope...
I'll look at the concerns
you wrote down.
First...
Bernard wrote in English!
[He's taken aback]
[Paper is white, writing is blue...]
Should I read it for you?
[Thank you]
Would I have a successful
singing career in Korea?
People act differently...
- How can I...
- Apply that?
Cultural differences...
if you live in Korea...
If you have a strong desire
to do music in Korea...
You'll get it gradually.
Keep using Korean even though you
speak like a baby or sound stupid.
[You Hee-yeol's heartfelt advice]
[JYP receives the song choice]
[What does his laugh mean?]
He'll sing this better than
"Right Here Waiting."
This is a great choice!
I'm singing The Jackson 5's
"Who's Lovin' You."
Michael Jackson's sweet voice
stood out in this song.
Bernard's voice is the
exact opposite.
It could be a twist if he can
sing it in his own style.
I wanted to show a different color since
I've been singing slow R&Bs and ballads.
I thought of an exciting song
and chose this one.
This will show us a
new side to him.
He was always slow but now
we will see his sense of rhythm.
[No. 1 Bernard Park]
It was a powerful performance
as if he was exploding with soul.
You just watched the performance
by No. 1 Bernard Park.
Let's hear the commentaries.
Bernard sang a different genre and
I saw a different side to him.
This is a Blues style music
in 6/8 time signature.
This is hard for Korean singers
to sing since it's like old pop.
He could have sounded unctuous
even if just one thing went wrong.
But he sang with his unadorned
voice and powerful timbre.
I really enjoyed it.
Bernard's specialty is
the first measure.
You have the power to bring us
to our knees with the first measure.
Antenna Music's score...
What is his score after
all those compliments?
It's going up...
It's 97!
Next is JYP. I'm curious because
your looks changed in the middle.
Just as You Hee-yeol said
about the first measure...
He started off by perfectly doing
an ad-lib in the pentatonic scale.
I thought I was going
to get KO'd but...
As soon as the lyrics came out...
I felt he was singing
regardless of the lyrics.
You did sing well, but the lyrics
are sad and heartbreaking.
It felt the lyrics were gone.
I don't know... maybe it's because
I already knew what the lyrics are.
You were singing but it felt like
the heart was missing.
You just sang well without the heart.
I was taken aback and it was a pity.
But since you have class,
JYP's score...
We couldn't understand since
we don't know the lyrics.
The score is... 92!
The sentiment part wasn't
good enough. YG?
It would be great if I knew the
6/8 time signature and the lyrics.
I just look for the feel.
I said in the video clip that this
is a different style from his.
It's the most rhythmical song
that he sang until now.
Since Michael Jackson
had a sweet voice...
I was both anticipating and worrying
how he would sing this in his lows.
I agree a little with JYP.
I thought at the first measure, "This
heavyweight knows how to punch now."
I was really shocked at each
measure but wasn't KO'd.
My expectations grew because the
Richard Marx song you sang moved me.
YG's score...
It wasn't a good commentary.
What is his score?
It's 93!
He has 282.
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "1" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Bernard Park!
[No. 2 Kwon Jina]
[With the elimination of The Shorties...
Kwon Jina is the sole female contestant]
It is a blessing to
make it into TOP3.
But I felt sad as I saw
them all leave.
I thought it would be okay...
But the place was quieter
and emptier than I thought.
So I tried to make it
as noisy as possible.
[That's when her friends
became her comfort]
I really miss you too!
[She's in good spirits after being
encouraged by her friends]
[But one day]
[She visits JYPE to practice
her collaboration stage]
[Who is she performing with?]
[It's JYP's sexy charismatic Sunmi]
[She's very surprised
and is dumbfounded]
- I'm Sunmi.
- Hello.
How old are you?
I'm 18...
I'll dispense with formality
since I'm older than you.
[That's an honor for me]
You sang an acoustic version
of "24 Hours" last time.
What about doing a dance
version of "24 Hours"?
I'm dancing that song barefoot?
[Jina is doing this dance?]
Want to learn it now?
Now?
[They start practicing]
[How do I do that?]
[Oh God! Why did you
make me do this?]
[Sunmi teaches her step by step]
Jina, how old are you?
[What happened to the flexibility
of this growling goddess?]
I might ruin it if
I don't dance well.
Since I've been given
the opportunity...
I think of it as an honor
and will do my best.
[We'll watch their stage later!]
[Then what is she singing?]
[Primary's "Love"]
I've been singing quiet
and sentimental songs.
I chose this song to show
another exciting performance.
Jina is the only one from the three
who can control her voice skillfully.
That's frightening.
The most important thing for a singer is
to have one's color, style, and timbre.
Jina already had those
from the start.
Jina would debut the quickest
from among the three.
I don't know if I'll be
3rd, 2nd, or 1st place...
But I'll do my best
thinking it's my last.
[No. 2 Kwon Jina]
[Music director - Kwon Tae-eun
Bandmaster - Seo Young-do]
This stage was by Kwon Jina and she
showed potential as a dancing singer.
What do the judges have to say?
Who will pick up the mike first?
JYP?
After Kwon Jina performs
and on my way home...
Recorded versions of the songs
come out and I listen to them.
Even YG said it but it's safe to say that
you have the skills to do a recording.
But there are some unfortunate
things on the live stage...
Since our expectations are high
and I thought what that might be.
We got used to your
soft, resounding voice.
There are singers that sing
as if burning their soul.
Aretha Franklin in the '70s, Pattie LaBelle
in the '80s, and Chaka Khan in the '90s.
You should listen to such singers
if you're going to sing live.
It was a pity that maybe you stopped
showing what you've been showing.
JYP's score...
What is his score?
It's 93!
Next is... YG?
This is a very important round.
It'll be great if the contestant got
the best score for doing well.
I thought about that
as I watched.
Since Kwon Jina showed many great
performances, I also agree with JYP.
Kwon Jina gives off the most beautiful
voice with just a guitar melody.
Maybe she had a lot on her mind
dancing and doing other things.
Like JYP said, it's a pity
since it wasn't new and...
It didn't go beyond your
previous performance.
YG's score...
She had more criticism than
compliments since it's the TOP3.
The score is 93!
It's the same.
You Hee-yeol?
I said this before that it's impossible even
for pro musicians to do this every week.
There are many such shows
and it's really hard.
We have amateurs here
doing this every week.
One of Kwon Jina's greatest strength
is that she never looked nervous.
I never thought she was nervous
and another thing is....
Song choice is important for some
contestants but for Kwon Jina...
She rose not because of song choice
but because she is Kwon Jina.
You're stable and just as he said,
you have no problems debuting right now.
Antenna Music's score...
The score is...
It's 97!
She has 283! It's a point
more than Bernard Park.
Those cheering for Kwon Jina can
text "2" or "Kwon Jina" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Kwon Jina!
[No. 3 Sam Kim]
[It's a fine spring day!]
[Is he enjoying the flowers?]
Where are we going?
We're going to YGE to practice
on your collaboration...
With who? Who?
Who do you want it to be?
Dara.
[Agape]
My face is red again.
[With me?]
[Even Sam's heart is blowing
gently with the spring winds]
[He arrives at YGE!]
This is awesome!
[Will it be Dara as
he hoped for?]
[It really is 2NE1!]
I only bought three drinks.
[He's cute]
None for you then.
I'm sorry.
[It's been a while]
[Dara signed an autograph
during YG week]
[He performed with that guitar
and made it to TOP3!]
She kept on monitoring
your performance.
[She kept on rooting for
Sam since that day]
I wanted to give you something since
your throat hurt and you lost your voice.
[Supplements good for the
throat used by Dara!]
[He's red again]
It's great that I was able to
actually meet awesome people.
Since 2NE1 told me
to do my best...
I'll do my best and create
a better performance.
[After getting recharged by 2NE1,
what song did he choose?]
I'm worried about him.
Depending on his choice...
[What song surprised JYP?]
["Honey" with words
and music by JYP]
It'll be competitive because
out of all of JYP's songs...
"Honey" is the grooviest.
Sam...
He won't be into the rhythm
but playing on top of it.
It'll be another big hit.
I made it all the way here because
the judges and fans believed in me.
Only one round remains. I'll do
my best and go all the way.
[No. 3 Sam Kim]
This stage was by Sam Kim, a
sentimentalist and prince of groove.
That was a great performance. How did his
carefree performance move the judges?
JYP?
I think Sam should
change his name.
To what?
- To Soul Kim.
- Soul Kim.
I'll be making this short but
there's one thing I have to say.
This song is in the blues scale.
But he tossed that away and
changed it to a minor scale.
That isn't easy.
It's really hard.
He changed it to a minor scale
but sang in a blues scale.
And he played the interlude
in a blues scale.
I don't know if he knew that
or not but he's a musician.
It's frightening if he didn't know.
He is Korea's precious
young musician.
JYP's score...
I'm curious of the score
due to all the compliments.
It's 99!
99 is the highest today!
You Hee-yeol?
I was really curious how
he will start off the song.
I never imagined he would
render the intro like that.
It was a shocking intro,
and the second thing...
Sam always does a guitar solo.
How will he play it? It was shocking.
Those people over there are
Korea's best session musicians.
A 16-year-old is creating harmony
with them shoulder to shoulder.
He's putting on a flashy performance
with just a guitar as if this is Inkigayo.
JYP said it's frightening
if he did it without knowing.
- Sam Kim doesn't know.
- He doesn't know?
It's instinct. That's why
we call him a genius.
Antenna Music's score...
What's the score? He was complimented
that it's instinct and not learned...
It's 99!
Let me confirm one thing.
Did you know or not?
I put in what sounded good
so I did it without knowing.
I don't think he understood.
YG?
I would first like to
thank Sam Kim.
This TOP3 is a very
important round.
Bernard Park, Kwon Jina, and Sam Kim
gave a moving performance every round.
But Bernard and Jina's performances
weren't as moving as before.
I thought at least Sam should show
something because he's going last.
And he did show something.
He made the best song choice.
He made the best arrangement.
Third compliment is that
he's crisis resistant.
He's making a frightening upturn
compared to the other contestants.
His skill in amazing us,
the judges, in every round...
You Hee-yeol talked about the session
musicians and they're Korea's best.
It's amazing that a
16-year-old is composed.
That can only be seen in a
20-year veteran musician.
I'll make it short.
YG's score...
He was complimented on singing,
playing, and everything. The score is...
It's 100!
He has 298!
It's a high score.
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "3" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 3 Sam Kim!
[In a moment!]
[The stage everyone's
been waiting for!]
We imagined how it would feel
to release our first album.
We're closer to our dream
because of KPOP STAR.
It's an amazing opportunity
given to us by KPOP STAR.
[Akdong Musician's debut stage
will be shown in a few moments!]
Sam Kim, the dark horse of live broadcast,
is No. 1 with the best compliments.
He's first with 298, but Bernard and
Jina have a one point difference.
This is when your votes
become the deciding factor.
Please hurry if you
haven't voted yet.
A new performance you haven't
seen before will start now.
The TOP3 prepared with artists from
JYP, YG, and Antenna Music.
The first stage was with JYP.
We should ask JYP about it.
JYP, how is it?
Kwon Jina only showed great singing, but
this is a special stage and not a competition.
We wanted her to experience something new
and wish that it will help her in the future.
She will be dancing as she sings.
I look forward to another dance
other than her "Growl" dance.
A big hand to the first stage!
[24 Hours - Sunmi]
That was a great performance
by Kwon Jina and Sunmi.
You Hee-yeol could feel nervous.
What did Antenna Music prepare?
Peppertones and Park Sae Byul
prepared with Bernard Park.
We tried to make the best performance
according to Bernard's color.
It's Extreme's "More Than Words."
Alright. How harmonious
will the performance be?
Bernard Park, Peppertones, and
Park Sae Byul are up next!
It was as if they've been doing
it together for a long time.
We look forward to the last one.
YG, how is it?
Sam Kim and 2NE1 prepared it.
But I don't know
what they're doing.
I was busy and didn't see them and
don't know what they're singing.
I hope they do better than
the ones that already did it.
Alright.
We're more curious of Sam's looks
next to Dara than his singing.
This is the last one!
Sam's adorable look was
memorable in that performance.
These great performances can
only be seen on KPOP STAR.
Text voting will end soon.
Of the 3 likely winners, only 2
will advance to next week's finale.
We have another special stage
as the votes are being tallied.
They were the winners of
last season's show.
They have returned after a year as
full-fledged rookie artists of YGE.
Akdong Musician will be singing
two title tracks for the first time.
It's Akdong Musician's debut stage!
It was Season 2 of KPOP STAR...
[Akdong Musician are
Season 2's winner]
The winners, Akdong Musician, are
debuting on KPOP STAR after a year.
I'm happy.
It's an amazing opportunity
given to us by KPOP STAR.
[Melted - AKMU]
["200%" is AKMU's love song]
[Chan-hyuk draws the
stage for "200%"!]
[He took part in stage design!]
[200% - AKMU]
Akdong Musician made remarkable
progress and returned after a year.
I heard Chan-hyuk came up
with the stage for "200%."
I think the music charts
will be fluctuating soon.
I pray that one of the TOP3 will debut
like them in a year here on this stage.
Text voting will soon end and we'll see
who makes it to next week's finale.
We prepared a highlight clip for
those who haven't decided.
Bernard Park put on a
sentimental performance.
Kwon Jina showed something
new without her guitar.
Sam Kim was composed like a pro.
We'll show you the highlight clip.
All voting will end in a minute!
[No. 1 Bernard Park]
[No. 2 Kwon Jina]
[No. 3 Sam Kim]
[Voting is over]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
midsize diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
We're back here live.
Voting is now over.
Including the collaborative stages,
the outcome is unpredictable.
Let's meet with Akdong Musician
as the votes are being tallied.
- Hello.
- The song was great.
- Thank you.
Chan-hyuk, how does it feel being
here again after a year as a singer?
I was very nervous and couldn't see
anyone or the judges. It was dark.
But I can see each of the
audience's faces today.
I see.
They must be nervous as well.
Anyone you're rooting for?
I'm rooting for all of them,
but especially Bernard Park...
He has a nice voice.
Please say a word of support
to lend him strength.
Please do your best.
Good luck!
I think it'll mean a lot.
They finished tallying
while we were talking.
We're curious of the result.
Which two will advance
to the finale?
It will be announced soon.
I hand it over to Jun Hyun-moo.
Thank you, Yoo Hye-young.
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3.
All that's left is the announcement
for the ones that passed.
I have one envelope and one of
the judges has another envelope.
We don't know whose name is written
inside since we haven't opened it.
The total score is calculated from
judges' score 60% and viewers' votes 40%.
Only 1st and 2nd advance
to next week's finale.
At the same time as they advance,
they will both get the diesel vehicles.
We will open it soon.
Of the three, we will see two next week
and only one will be eliminated.
Before we open the envelope,
let's hear how they feel.
Bernard, how do you feel right now?
I'm nervous and...
I'm grateful to have
made it to TOP3.
It was fun until now.
Does that mean we'll see
you again next week?
Huh?
My English is improving daily.
Kwon Jina? How are you feeling?
I'm nervous but have no regrets.
It's okay even if I'm eliminated.
Anything that was unfortunate
with your performance?
I sang out of tune
in the middle.
- You what?
- Sang out of tune.
That was a pity.
I see. I think the judges
missed that. Anyways.
Sam Kim, how do you feel?
We're waiting for the announcement.
I'm really nervous...
I had fun so I have no regrets
even if I'm eliminated.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
It's amazing to make
it even to TOP3.
JYP, you watched with a pleased
look. Any words for them?
I'm very proud of them. They are
Korea's young musicians.
I think they'll be stars leading
K-pop and the Korean Wave.
It's a big achievement to even
come this far. You did well.
And YG? We haven't made
the announcement yet.
We won't be seeing one
of them after today.
We don't know if it will be Bernard, Jina,
or Sam until we open the envelope.
As I said last week,
they have similar skills.
Not one of them lags
behind the other.
We don't know yet, but I'm sad and
not happy in sending one away.
He said it's a pity to send
one away. You Hee-yeol?
We met almost every week and
got close the past 6 months.
You three did well and were
more than I imagined.
JYP described you as young musicians
but I would like to call you my peers.
Let's continue together.
Good job.
I will now announce the first
finalist for next week's finale!
[Who is the first finalist for
the long-awaited finale?]
I saw the name.
The long 8 months of Season 3
of KPOP STAR will come to an end.
The first finalist to advance
to next week's finale is...
Please congratulate!
This person was great.
It's Sam Kim!
Congratulations!
He gave an overwhelming performance
with the judges' score of 298.
Sam, how do you feel?
I'm really happy.
I'm always nervous before I go up,
but I try to do my best and have fun.
Just fun... I can't even
say it properly.
It was fun. Thank you for your
support and I'll do my best.
Alright.
If speaking in Korean is hard...
Thank you.
Anyone can tell he's first just by
the atmosphere here today.
Congratulations and please
move to the winners seat.
Please give him a hand.
Between Bernard Park and Kwon Jina,
only one will advance to the finale.
Bernard Park has 282.
Kwon Jina has 283.
It's just a point difference
looking at the judges' score.
Then the viewers' votes will
be the deciding factor.
Which judge will announce
next week's finalist?
I'll do it.
Since JYP always rooted for Bernard Park and
You Hee-yeol has affection for Kwon Jina...
I think I'll be less nervous
to make the announcement.
Alright. Please open the envelope
and slowly make the announcement.
Who is the second finalist
for next week's finale?
[Who is the last finalist?]
Is it Bernard Park or Kwon Jina?
There's only a point difference
looking at the judges' score.
Calculating the viewers' vote,
who is in the lead?
I think YG saw it.
Alright.
The last finalist is...
Calculating the remaining 40%
from the viewers' votes...
Was there an upturn
or not in the results?
Who is it?
I will announce it.
The last finalist is...
- Bernard Park.
- It's Bernard Park!
Congratulations!
Bernard Park and Sam Kim
advance to the finale.
Let's first ask Bernard
how he feels right now.
I never thought of the finale
when I came to Korea.
Now...
I'll do my best
and do better.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
Kwon Jina, you were always complimented
and today became your last performance.
How do you feel?
I have mixed feelings but...
I did my best to show something
better so I have no regrets.
I see. Is there anything you
want to say to the judges?
Thank you for the compliments
and for your troubles.
Thank you.
You Hee-yeol was attached to her.
Please say some words for her.
I don't know what to say.
But I am sure of one thing.
The result here is not the end.
This is just the beginning.
You shined the most
in that beginning.
It was great that I was a part of it.
I look forward to working with you.
He encouraged and cheered her by
saying something meaningful.
Only one show remains and
that is the finale next week.
Who will be the 3rd K-pop star?
Unfortunately, Kwon Jina
was eliminated.
We continue next week with
Bernard Park and Sam Kim.
After a long journey of 8 months,
we have reached the final hurdle.
Please look forward to
next week's live show.
This was KPOP STAR Season 3, a real
audition where dreams turn into reality!