Battle Audition - last
gateway to TOP10!
From those in 1st place, there
are those we never expected.
Congratulations on TOP10!
Having twist after twist...
- We thought they'd be 1st.
- But they're 2nd.
While having this
unprecedented twist...
There is tension in the waiting
room for the fierce battle.
I thought you were
going to be 1st.
Isn't this the
TOP10 room?
All these people are good.
The rematch is going
to be more tense.
It's unpredictable due to
all the strong competitors.
We're having a rematch
with all of them.
Wait! Who's left?
[The last group!
Raccoon Boys]
[Yoon Joo-suk!]
[Lee Joo-yeon and
Kim Dong-ok!]
A dark horse can pop
out from anywhere.
They can't let their
guard down.
What if Raccoon Boys come?
Who is the unexpected 2nd?
We will begin the
consolation match.
We wrap up the
decision on TOP10.
Nobody can guess
the TOP10 finalists.
It starts now!
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
[Battle audition is
coming to an end]
I'm going to hit
the slate.
[Bang Ye-dam - the
youngest finalist]
[He's more nervous doing this]
Three, two, one!
Now we have the
last group.
Raccoon Boys
from SM.
Yoon Joo-suk
from YG.
Dong-ok and Joo-yeon
from JYP.
Please enter.
[Strong favorites and...]
[A dark horse dreaming of
turning things around]
What force!
They each have a
big weapon.
It's unpredictable
who will stand out.
[Will there be
another twist?]
I'm at a loss since...
One of them will
be eliminated.
Your possibilities are infinite.
Forget everything and
just have fun.
Yoon Joo-suk,
you are first.
He's back at
the keyboard.
[Happy virus Pooh -
Yoon Joo-suk]
I had many ups and downs
the past four months.
[Complimented and recognized
as likely winner in Round 1]
The results were good at times
as I challenged without fear.
I became excited as I
came out on broadcast.
So a lot of my desire
came out in my singing.
I'm still unstable, but I don't
want to make those mistakes.
My concern is how well I
stay focused while singing.
[Yoon Joo-suk looks more
comfortable than ever]
[Will he advance after
giving his best stage?]
Did you find
your honey?
Yes. I found it at YG
and filled my honey jar.
That's a great start.
[Can he move them as much
as he did the first time?]
[Stand by Me - Ben E. King]
[Sings comfortably
with a relaxed look]
[Pooh bear wants to present
happiness to those who hear]
[He's trying to find
his true self]
[Did the listeners feel
his sincerity?]
[The judges look serious]
If I look at your graph...
It shoots up and then
hits rock bottom.
You're wandering in the middle
and you went up slightly today.
[His efforts were
aknowledged]
Now Pooh is moving like
this and not like this.
The chair was...
It was good to see someone with
a happy virus sing that song.
It's great to see you
back in your old self.
- Thank you.
- I enjoyed it.
You did well. Only
half of you is back.
- Good job. Next!
- Thank you.
[Will he advance
to the TOP10?]
[Became likely winners after
being formed by SM]
Hi, we are Raccoon Boys.
[A simple introduction]
The two of us have a lot of
expectations after the 2 songs.
But your introduction didn't
meet our expectations.
It wasn't creative.
We had a hard time as
much as Joo-suk did.
- Really?
- Yes.
"Sherlock" is dull.
Raccoon, change
your song.
[Change the song
with 10 days left!]
Initially, we were confused.
This is the last audition
before the live broadcast.
We were confused
and tired.
We looked for songs.
[What did they choose?]
We thought "Run Devil Run"
would go along with us.
Brian, McKay, and myself
arranged it differently.
The style is different
from the original.
We're confident.
We'll make it
to the TOP10.
Go, Raccoon Boys!
[Can they advance with a stage
better than the previous two?]
[Run Devil Run - Girls' Generation]
[Starts off with Brian and
McKay's exquisite harmony]
[Min-suk's rap lends
power and tension]
[His rap shines in the
exquisite harmony]
[A surprise performance
removing the mic stand]
[Brian explodes in
the high notes]
[Raccoon Boys display
their masculinity]
[Their amazing growth
after each stage]
[The studio is filled
with applause]
That was fun.
I really hate you.
Why?
I asked about them
in the waiting room.
You said to expect nothing.
You made me lose my
expectations...
And then this twist.
I'm such a fool. I told
Andrew I'm killing him.
[Innocent Andrew is
in the waiting room]
I watched without
expectations.
But it was beyond
my expectations.
It must have been hard
to arrange it like this.
I was amazed at the
arrangement.
I thought you guys
are really something.
If you could arrange a
difficult song like this...
You'll do well at the
live broadcast.
Good job on getting
through this ordeal.
Thank you.
[What about JYP?]
You'll know when you see
my face on television.
I was disappointed
until the middle.
First, it was worse
than the original.
I thought it would be boring
since you took away the energy.
[But]
If you don't have a dime,
use two nickels.
You did it with
your skills.
You made me applaud
you in the end.
The matching of your voice color
and teamwork were excellent.
I think KPOP STAR's greatest
gain is Kim Min-suk.
I thought this is the time
when Korea needs a rap star.
Min-suk is good at
writing rap lyrics.
He's good at writing
and delivering.
He has a talent for making
unrhymable words to rhyme.
As a rapper, he would be a
pro in Korea if he debuted.
You started off unfavorably
but made me to applaud you.
Thank you.
Anyways, you did it.
I think you're better at
practice than at theory.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Good job. Next!
Hi, we are round Dong-ok
and Joo-yeon. DongDongJoo.
[What is their fate?]
Raccoon Boys from SM.
[Shock]
Yoon Joo-suk from YG.
[Made it worse]
[They're in the same group]
Dong-ok and Joo-yeon are
against Raccoon Boys.
They're against strong
competitors.
But if they sing freely, they will
bring an unexpected result.
[Day by Day - Tashannie]
[Complimented for singing the
1st stanza the best and no more]
[Possesses remarkable harmony
and voice but never stood out]
[What they risked in
this final battle]
[Is their desperate song]
[Can they give off an emotion that
will be engraved in the mind?]
Thank you.
[A warm applause]
[But what are the
judges thinking?]
[Can they turn things around?]
Kim Dong-ok's voice
is very beautiful.
I didn't know it was
this beautiful.
Joo-yeon took the low
part with a strong bass.
Overall, teamwork was good
and it was beautiful.
Thank you.
[BoA compliments]
[Will they advance?]
[What about YG?]
I'm in a fix. I want to
say something, but...
[Compliment or criticism?]
You weren't bad, but it
wasn't moving either.
I could see you two were
trying to work together.
I could see with my eyes,
but it didn't reach my ears.
It wasn't good or bad.
Anyways, good job.
[JYP feels frustrated]
[Group six's fated
announcement]
[Dream of turning the tables -
Joo-yeon and Dong-ok]
[Happy virus Pooh -
Yoon Joo-suk]
[A force to be reckoned
with - Raccoon Boys]
[Who will advance?]
I'll make this
simple and plain.
The viewers must
think the same.
Today's 1st is...
As JYP described, "If you don't
have a dime, use two nickels."
Raccoon Boys are 1st.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
1st, move to your seats.
[BoA's palms are sweaty]
I feel great.
I wanted to go to TOP10
to stand in a bigger stage.
I feel great and look
forward to the big stage.
If we try harder and practice,
we could actually win this.
We will try harder and
practice even more.
[2nd - rematch!
3rd - eliminated!]
Kim Dong-ok, Lee Joo-yeon,
and Yoon Joo-suk.
You three are truly remarkable
for making it this far.
I first applaud
you for that.
Unfortunately, the one
who will be eliminated is...
Kim Dong-ok and
Lee Joo-yeon.
I wanted you to pass since
we got to know each other.
But Joo-suk had more
potential. You did well.
My final advice for you is
to have something unique.
We will try harder to
be better singers.
- Thank you.
- You did well.
It breaks my heart.
[Even he goes to
the waiting room]
[Everyone is surprised!]
For real?
[Discouraged]
Rematch is fiercer.
No answer here.
It's going to be tough.
In 30 minutes, we will have
the consolation match.
[Who will the
other five be?]
[Moving to prepare
for the rematch]
[Mixed emotion, determination
and the shock that lingers]
[For the stage that will
determine their fate]
[Additional practice begins]
They have to show their
strength in the given time.
Now they are going
to have a rematch.
They have to quickly
recover from the shock.
I won't cry now.
They need nerves of steel
and do it without trembling.
Singers only need to
prepare singing.
But what can performers
do in that short time?
I'm worried, but I also
look forward to it.
[Jan 07, 2013
10:00 PM]
Let's begin. Will the
7 teams enter?
[The judges are more
nervous than ever!]
[Which five will receive
the honor of TOP10?]
[Goddess of high notes -
Kim Do-yeon]
[Risking injury - YouU]
[Complimented - 2,000 won
and Akdong Musician]
[The best vocalist -
Joo-suk and Andrew]
[Shining diamond -
Shin Ji-hoon]
[The results are unpredictable]
[Which five will advance?]
Should I tell you
some good news?
Yes!
Season 1's winner also
stood where you are.
Don't be discouraged.
No one is good
in every round.
Cheer up and
do your best.
There are 7 teams here.
Only 5 teams will advance.
We remember when
you all did your best.
Seize this final opportunity.
Andrew Choi
will start first.
What did you prepare?
Lee Seung-chul's
"There Is Only You".
We look forward to it.
He would've been 1st since he
showed an amazing change.
If he's composed and
maintains that change...
And is relaxed, I believe
he will advance.
[There Is Only You - Lee Seung-chul]
[A mellow start with
controlled emotion]
[34-year-old's ardent
dream is in this song]
[As a singer and
not a composer]
[Can he go further
towards his dream?]
[His singing is more
heartfelt than ever]
[This could be
his final stage]
[What do the judges think?]
I'll start first.
You fixed what JYP pointed
out in the previous song.
I don't know if you sing
this song often, but...
The corrections you made
are back to square one.
You did sing well.
I wanted you to open at
least once in the high notes.
But you didn't.
You would've been complimented
if you did that at the high notes.
It can't change overnight. He
just switched his batting form.
"You go to the minor league
if you don't get a hit."
If he's told that, he'll
just hit how he used to.
If you sang this how
you sang previously...
You will become
a great singer.
It must have been hard for
everyone including Andrew.
I didn't expect a Korean song
since it's hard for you.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[Will Andrew advance?]
Next is the girl group.
I'm worried because they have
a disadvantage time-wise.
After the 1st round, So-yeon
and Mi-rim got worse.
They came back from the hospital,
but we didn't have time to practice.
I'm getting painkillers
through an IV.
We can't suddenly
become good.
This could be
our final stage.
I won't focus on the
pain in my ankle.
I'll do my best
for the team.
With the heart of
making it to TOP10
I'll do my best
enduring the pain.
I don't want regrets.
We have a keyboard,
guitar, and performance.
We want to show
we can do this.
[What stage will
they put on?]
A keyboard?
- She plays the guitar?
- I know.
[Ha-ye and Min-joo
play instruments]
[So-yeon, Mi-rim, and Yoo-ji
overcoming their injuries]
We'll begin.
Ready?
[This song is?]
[Only One - BoA]
[They never showed an
acoustic stage before]
[They want to be recognized
for this new potential]
[So-yeon and Yoo-ji dances
overcoming their injuries]
[Min-joo's voice is stable
even while dancing]
[Prepared this group dance
forgetting their pain]
[BoA smiles brightly]
[Blank]
[What do they think?]
Wow.
It's like they made 5 goals
after making 3 already.
I lowered my head because the
keyboard and guitar didn't match.
When Yoo-ji and So-yeon started
dancing, they made a goal.
Then Mi-rim did a hat
trick with singing.
If Min-joo stood out
in the previous song...
Yoo-ji was the one who got
the feel of this song.
Only some of you are good.
But the ones that are good
are different in each song.
That means you
have potential.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[The others are nervous]
[What does BoA think?]
Yoo-ji and So-yeon
didn't sing, right?
Mi-rim sang in
the back, right?
Yes.
They sang well even though
they were dancing.
I know that they
didn't sing.
I've been a singer for
18 years and I didn't know.
I saw in the back that
Mi-rim was singing.
When the two sang the mid-range,
Ha-ye sang the high notes.
[They complemented each other]
I think it's hard
to deceive BoA.
You did good as a team
to deceive even me.
This is why a team
is important.
You did well.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[YouU suddenly rises!]
[The rest are even
more nervous]
[Will YouU advance?]
Next is 2,000 won.
[Next is 2,000 won -
Kim Il-do and Kim Hyo-bin]
[They look determined]
We'll talk after
you guys are done.
If things go wrong, this
could really be our last.
There's a song we have in
mind, but I don't know.
But we'll do our best to
not make this our last.
We chose this to show our
witty lyrics, rap, and singing.
We were supposed to have
fun but were too honest.
The lyrics took 10 minutes.
That's how confident we are.
We're going to have fun
since this is our last.
We say this and
always do bad.
[They're in danger since
they lost confidence]
[Can they stir things
up once more?]
[Wild Wild West (own rap) - Will Smith]
[2,000 won]
[2,000 won!]
[Starts by livening
things up!]
[Passionate singing
overflowing with energy]
[Hello]
[Abandon it]
[Stop by]
[Their uniquely witty
and lively lyrics]
[Il-do misses the beat
for the first time]
If 2,000 won gets eliminated
We're basically at a loss
The viewers will
Feel gloomy
They will lament
KPOP STAR
It's simple
Just pick us
[Their determination for TOP10
filled the stage with wits]
[Enormous response
from the others]
[What do the judges think?]
[2,000 won waits
with a hard look]
You did very well. This was
better than the one before.
But something happened
during that time.
Bang Ye-dam sang a
song with this beat.
Kim Min-suk rapped
with this beat.
Ye-dam and Min-suk went
beyond our expectations.
Both of you did well, but didn't
go beyond our expectations.
Comparing this to height,
your growth plates closed.
[They have no potential
to grow on KPOP STAR]
I don't know what more
can come out of you.
You did well.
[How will they change?]
[BoA was the last
to train with them]
I could feel you
were desperate.
I could feel you wanted to
pass and were desperate.
Maybe because I trained you,
I felt how desperate you were.
But your stage
was short of 2%.
What if you sang the previous
song with this energy?
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[Commentary filled
with frustration]
[Will we see them at
the live broadcast?]
Next is Yoon Joo-suk.
[Next is Yoon Joo-suk]
What did you prepare?
It's called "Untitled".
The singer is D'Angelo.
I wanted to sing this song
regardless of the rank.
I thought I would be sincere
if I do what I truly desire.
I will sing this song
without any regrets.
[Untitled - D'Angelo]
[His dream is in each
strike of the key]
[Sang this hundreds of times
dreaming of singing this on stage]
[Will this song make
his dreams come true?]
[Slowly gets into
the rhythm]
[Sings passionately as
if he's absorbed]
[His unique control of dynamics
and sense of rhythm stands out]
[Concentrates to
the last note]
[What do the judges think?]
I don't think you can
sing better than this.
That's how perfect it was.
[A perfect stage even
JYP acknowledges]
But why wasn't
it moving?
[Unexpected criticism]
It seems like you started
music just to sing well.
[Shock]
You're not someone who sang
wanting to say something.
Your purpose was
just to sing well.
I felt something when
I saw you today.
At a certain hotel, there's a
man playing piano for 10 years.
He's great, but he's doing
it because that's his job.
You came on KPOP STAR
because of your dream.
You saw beyond and not to
get something in return.
That is not being
conveyed to us.
You need to think of the
reason why you started.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- You did well.
Only on KPOP STAR will you hear
bad things although you did well.
Next is Akdong Musician.
[Next is Akdong Musician]
I hope they do well.
[They lost to Ye-dam
and were placed 2nd]
What's our next song?
I don't know if we
should do this song.
- We'll do our best.
- You have a lot of worries.
What I'm worried is
not their skills.
Since they're young, how will
they overcome the tension?
You're singing your
own song, right?
When did you make this?
2012...
Okay, last year.
The title?
It's "Optical Illusion".
I'm confused whether I
like that girl or not.
Since it's your song,
sing comfortably.
Okay!
[They calm themselves]
[Everyone focuses since
it's a new song]
[Optical Illusion - own song]
We never showed this
style of music before.
I hope they can see
our versatility.
"Oh, they could sing
these kinds of songs?"
[Odd prelude ends]
Watching you dazed
I fall for you
You make me dizzy
You make me confused
You, yes, you
I saw you from the start
I never spoke but
I looked for a chance
Your eyes and hairstyle are
Not that different from others
That's right
You pull me like a sled
I'm pulled to you like a magnet
My head spins as if
You bewitched me
In a maze called "you"
I had to get out
I'm afraid I'll be confined
I set you into my heart
[Odd melody and
unique lyrics]
[The others start
to sing along]
The reason I like you
Is it an optical illusion?
I didn't feel like this before
But you
Time passed after meeting you
After time passed again
I gradually realized that you
Have a mysterious charm
[A new style different
from their cute songs]
[Will they advance causing
another Akdong syndrome?]
Thank you.
[Can't tell what the
judges are thinking]
[Their style changed. What
do the judges think?]
The other judges might
feel the same as me.
[Nervous]
I was trying to get
that first sound.
I'm trying to figure out
the first chord, but I can't.
You played it not
knowing it, right?
Yes.
That's a very difficult
chord progression.
I wonder how many
his age exists.
I could listen all day
with those 3 chords.
I don't know how the
public will react, but...
Personally, I could
listen to it all day.
This song could represent
the listeners' heart.
You make us confused.
[What does she mean?]
Difficult chords and being
musical is great, but...
If you become more of an artist,
you could lose popular appeal.
It's hard for the public.
Some would say,
"Why is this hard?"
Experts would say, "They're
taking a different path."
That's one good thing about
you Akdong Musician.
- Thank you.
- You did well.
Next is Kim Do-yeon.
[Next is Kim Do-yeon]
[She has a hard look]
[Can she overcome the
pressure and advance?]
[Only Hope - Mandy Moore]
[Calm voice stimulating
sensibility]
[Like the contestants' hearts
with the TOP10 before them]
[This song, "Only Hope", is
about their urgent desire]
[Trembling in the
high notes]
[She gives her all and
focuses on singing]
[This could be
her last stage]
[She's more devoted to
singing passionately]
Thank you.
[She finishes with
all her might]
[What do the judges think?]
Do you remember the
advice I gave you?
To be relaxed...
If you sung this
same song like this...
If you sung calmly
here and there...
The amazing thing about you
is that you took our advice.
Maybe you're not feeling well,
but you're not taking our advice.
It's not going through to
you and I don't know why.
Are you sick?
Let me ask you a
question first.
How was this song compared
to the others you sang?
Are you satisfied or...?
- It's the same.
- You think so?
I think it was better.
I don't know the
reason why, but...
You didn't really move
us the other times.
But you sounded
natural to me.
Thank you.
You did well.
Shin Ji-hoon is the last and
also the last rising star.
[She feels sorry because
Tae-yeon was eliminated]
Ji-hoon is similar to
Season 1's Park Ji-min.
She has to erase that from
her heart and sing freely.
Can she do that?
I'm worried.
[A complicated emotion for
someone young to endure]
[She chokes with emotion
every time she practices]
[Can she settle down and
take the chance to advance?]
You cried a lot.
What's your resolve?
I want to show everything.
You don't need
to do that.
This is it...
It matters whether you believe,
showing doesn't matter.
I believe I can fly.
Simple as that.
You can do it.
Don't think,
"I have to do well."
Just like a duck
flies in the sky.
You're in the
same situation.
Goose, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you didn't
say chicken.
[Quotations from YG specially
good for stage fright]
Let's become a
goose that flies.
[She calms down]
[JYP cheers her
on silently]
[Suppressing her
trembling heart]
[Starts out calmly]
[A clear ringing voice that
makes you listen quietly]
[The live broadcast she dreamt
of is right around the corner]
[She sings with
all her heart]
[High notes that
make you shudder]
[But...]
[She suddenly
burst into tears]
[She can't pull
herself together]
[No one expected this
and is taken aback]
[The song's over, but
she can't stop the tears]
[How should they take this?]
[This young girl is taken
aback more than anyone]
[Silence hangs
in the studio]
[The judges' reaction?]
Why are you crying?
Why did you cry?
Because you trembled?
[She just shakes her
head without saying]
Tell me why.
I just feel sad.
You feel sad right now?
[Tears well up again]
Why are you feeling sad?
Be honest.
I don't know.
[Even she can't explain why]
Alright. You did well.
I think it was a lot
of mental pressure.
This is the most
brutal round.
And since you were last, the
pressure must have been big.
[It was a great song,
but it ended in tears]
Please wait as we
go into discussion.
[Will she advance?]
[Who will take the
five remaining seats?]
[TOP10 decision
last discussion]
[The 7 teams had
a close match]
[Who did they sigh at?]
Remove those two.
This is driving me insane.
[5 advances!
2 are eliminated!]
This is the last round
for the live broadcast.
We have to be
cold and serious.
[Which 5 will receive
the honor of TOP10?]
[Which 2 will leave
KPOP STAR?]
[The 5 finalists
are also nervous]
[Discussion over]
[Who among them will smile?]
[JYP grabs the mike]
There are 7 teams here.
None of you should be here and
we thought why you are here.
Only one team here proved
you don't belong here.
[Which team is it?]
YouU, step forward.
[They shed tears
as they are called]
We didn't expect anything
from you out of the 7 teams.
We gave up thinking what
can you do in 30 miuntes.
But, you were better than
when we helped you.
[They proved their
worth themselves]
This team should advance
with an applause.
[Tears of joy]
It's not because
you are beautiful.
You made it with
your skills.
- Please move to the seats.
- Thank you.
[Hurry]
[They move to the TOP10 seats
applauded by their peers]
Thank you for this
great opportunity.
I'm really happy.
We won't disappoint you at the
live broadcast. Thank you.
[Announcement continues]
Out of the 6 teams here,
we have to choose 4.
All 6 of you were below
our expectations.
Our standard was the one
who had something good.
[Who among them
will advance first?]
The one with the most appeal
in low, mid, and high notes...
Will have a chance if the
right song is picked.
We chose Kim Do-yeon.
[How does she feel
being the 6th finalist?]
I feel sorry and thankful, all
these complicated feelings.
We look forward
to a great stage.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Next...
We chose the one who
changed this round.
Andrew, who showed a new
possibility for a moment.
[The younger contestants
congratulate the oldest]
We will chose 2 more
out of the 4 teams.
You were good at first, but it
seems you can't make your mind.
The one who has the highest
chance to come out of there...
Is 2,000 won.
[Min-suk is happy as
if it was his own]
Your thoughts and resolve?
We thank you.
We're sorry for making it
seem stiff and desperate.
[Overwhelmed to speak]
Thank you.
Only 1 out of the
3 teams will advance.
The rest, unfortunately...
Will end their time
here at KPOP STAR.
[Who is the last finalist?]
We're as sad as you
are for being here.
We had much
love for you.
We didn't say it, but we
considered you as favorites.
[The shocking truth of
eliminating 2 teams]
You three were below
our expectations.
But we chose the one who
had something good.
We...
Want to hear
your song again.
- Congrats to Akdong Musician.
- Thank you.
[Yoon Joo-suk eliminated]
[Shin Ji-hoon eliminated]
[No one expected this
shocking result]
[Akdong Musician don't
know what to do]
[It's okay]
Many encouraged and cheered
us to find back our stage.
We're sorry we couldn't
meet their expectations.
We will prepare a stage
beyond your expectations.
- Please move to the seats.
- Thank you.
[TOP10 finalists are decided]
We can't believe to
see you two there.
In the path of a singer,
all this process...
It's a shortcut or a long way
at times, but we all walk it.
For me, it was a
fun experience.
I'm in my 20s. I'll use
this as a steppingstone.
I think I'll be a great
singer in 4 years.
[Spreading a happy
virus to the end]
And Shin Ji-hoon?
I think many viewers liked your
innocence and jewel-like voice.
Personally, it breaks my
heart to send you like this.
We need to be fair and
the viewers are watching.
I think you will be the most
frustrated and will cry at home.
When I first started
out on KPOP STAR...
I promised my mom
that I won't cry.
But I'm crying my
heart out today.
I was confident with
the last song.
But I'm sorry for crying.
Other than skating,
I also liked singing.
I was grateful.
[Complimented for her voice
but shockingly eliminated]
We don't know if you'll be
a singer or a figure skater.
But take this opportunity
to become stronger.
- Okay?
- Yes.
You did well.
Thank you.
[Frustration and shock]
[Two who shined on stage
with their talents leave]
[TOP10 finalists share
their joy in passing]
I thought I was going
to be eliminated.
Now it actually begins.
We're thankful because
we almost got eliminated.
But we got together and
made it to the TOP10.
It's like a dream.
We didn't expect
this at all.
Let's do it, alright?
One, two, three...
Let's do it!
They have to become professionals
since this is the live broadcast.
They are before the nation,
and mistakes are not allowed.
[The pressure of the live
broadcast is unlike before]
[A grand stage and
a huge audience!]
[The TOP10 practice for
the first live broadcast]
[But one day]
I have nothing to say.
I said to endure
and don't leave.
I thought she would
wait and not leave.
[Did something happen
to someone?]
I don't know.
I can't say
leave or stay.
That's what she wanted.
[One of them is withdrawing?]
[This contestant brought up
her intention many times]
[They came to the practice
room to persuade her]
[The one who
brought this up...]
[It's Kim Do-yeon!]
[What's her reason?]
She thinks she's
harming us...
Everyone else is
passionate...
She doesn't think
she's that passionate.
So she feels sorry and
guilty for being here.
[She was close to Soo-jin and
told her concerns to only her]
[In the middle of practice]
[She spent most of her
time alone in her thoughts]
[She worried alone thinking
she would cause them trouble]
[A few days after
meeting her]
[She heads to the broadcasting
office to reveal her intentions]
[What was her decision?]
I thought this over
again and again.
I had a different heart
compared to the others.
It doesn't mean I took
this lightly or as a joke.
I wanted to be a music
teacher instead of a singer.
I'm someone who sings, but
I wasn't confident in singing.
One reason for coming here
was to gain confidence.
I started thinking this would
be a good experience for me.
As I started getting good
results and advanced...
The pressure was big.
The others thought they will
be singers with this chance.
They were more desperate than me
but were eliminated one by one.
I felt sorry and that it wasn't
right for me to get good results.
I did my best, but it was
mentally burdening.
I made this decision and
I shouldn't regret it.
I'm really sorry.
My parents were happy
because of me...
I feel like I'm letting
them down at the end.
I'm sorry.
[The production crew decided
to accept her decision]
[The day she parted
with her peers]
[Her parents came
to pick her up]
[Her mother is prouder than anyone
that she was on KPOP STAR]
[It's unfortunate, but she decides
to respect her daughter's wish]
I hope that...
They could understand
me even a little bit.
"That could happen."
"There are people like her."
[She left her
final message]
[We respect and
support her dreams]
[Judges' emergency meeting!]
[The judges have an
emergency meeting]
We asked for
your opinions.
As we said earlier,
Do-yeon withdrew.
[It was expected, but
the shock was great!]
[Emergency meeting!]
She couldn't bear the burden.
We can't nurture the
dream she threw away.
The most important thing
is if they want to do it.
The heart is the
most important.
We broadcast it as is and
respect her decision.
What do we do?
We have to discuss if we
go through the list or not.
[Unforeseen occurence! What
about the last TOP10 seat?]
[Who will take the last seat?]