Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
[The result of last week's
fierce TOP6 battle]
[Almeng and Heejun Han
were eliminated!]
[The judges feel sad for parting]
I'm grateful to those that rooted
for me even though I'm lacking.
Being in the TOP6 or TOP8 isn't
important. I gained more things.
I'm truly grateful for gaining
many things in music.
[And another farewell...]
Rin took care of us
like a real sister...
We really miss her
now that she's gone.
Parting with friends we became close,
even though it was a brief moment...
It's really heartbreaking...
Is there a contestant
you have your eyes on?
It changes every round.
Who do we eliminate now?
This is hard.
[Bernard Park has the most
powerful presence!]
[Kwon Jina is making a
frightening upturn!]
We need to watch it
to the end to know.
[Sam Kim is the dark horse
of live broadcast!]
[The Shorties have the
best harmony!]
[They are all likely winners!]
[But one has to be
eliminated today!]
[The TOP4's major
clash begins now!]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3!
I introduce you to
the TOP4 finalists!
They do their best to show
their best every round!
Please give them another
round of applause!
Hi, I'm KPOP STAR's visual
Jun Hyun-moo. Glad to be here.
We began with the TOP8 and now
we're two shows away from the finale.
I really don't know the outcome but
one of them will be eliminated.
Please stay tuned to find out
who advances and who is eliminated.
I will introduce the judges that
will give an impartial judgment.
Please give them a big hand.
JYPE's Park Jin-young!
YGE's Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Music's You Hee-yeol!
[JYP, YG, You Hee-yeol]
We ask for an objective and
impartial judgment today.
Since last week was YG week, it seems
many of them are thinking about YG.
I heard you made efforts since this week
was JYP week. What did you do?
I didn't make any efforts but for them
to choose an agency correctly...
- I told them who YG really is.
- You told him who he is.
- He's different on and off the air.
- Were they affected by that?
They're aware now.
I see.
Starting with this season, the winner
gets to choose from the 3 agencies.
So the battle of nerves between
the judges are also getting intense.
We'll see what efforts JYP made for
the finalists as it was JYP week.
Let's watch it!
[JYP's special invitation
for JYP week!]
We're going to his house.
[Really?]
We'll be departing for
his house right now.
[Awesome!]
[First time ever on KPOP STAR!
A visit to JYP's house!]
[Feeling excited...]
[They head for JYP's house!]
[It's on the outskirts of Seoul]
[They arrived!]
[A big gate is before them!]
[Wow, it's like a palace!]
[It's automatic]
[They're amazed at everything!]
[This is JYP's house!]
[A cute puppy greets them first]
[JYP appears!]
[He welcomes them in
comfortable clothing]
[A moving moment!]
[Welcome]
[The gym equipments they
saw only on television!]
It was amazing. It was my first time
visiting a celebrity's house.
It was amazing but I felt great.
- I forgot my puppy.
- Puppy!
[Time to meet the puppy that
greeted them from the 2nd floor!]
Come here Pie and Walnut.
Want to hold them?
[Right into their arms]
This one is Pie and this one is Walnut for
being pie colored and walnut colored.
It's simple like "Your House."
[Watch your mouth]
[It's okay]
As you can see, these are
all gym equipments.
[They have no place to sit]
The wallpaper is peeling off...
And the curtain is tilted...
I'm sorry if you fantasized how
a celebrity's house would look.
I feel like wasting money
to fix something like that.
Fixing this wallpaper won't help
me in achieving my dreams.
I have all these because...
My goal is to improve in
singing every year.
My dream is to be the best in
singing and dancing at 60.
After becoming a singer...
I practice vocalization, stretch, and
exercise. I do these three every day.
It's been almost six months
since they left their home.
And it was just a series of
fierce competitions.
I felt they must have
become hard-hearted so...
I wanted to bring them to my home, eat
homemade food, and talk comfortably.
[A special meal for
the TOP4 finalists!]
[JYP's homemade smoked
ogyeopsal (pork belly)!]
[Wow!]
[That's awesome!]
The fat is drained so you can
eat a lot and not gain weight.
[Has both taste and nutrition!]
Let's dig in!
Bon appetit!
Take one each.
This is an alpine leek.
Wrap it together.
Thank you.
[JYP wraps one for him!]
[Joy they can't explain
all in words!]
We always talk about who we think
will be the winner after the show.
Didn't know that, huh?
[They didn't know!]
But the interesting thing...
It changes every week.
[It's hard even for the judges
to predict the winner!]
Since all of you are improving...
[Sam Kim especially showed
amazing improvement last week!]
[Kwon Jina improved from a
dark horse to a likely winner!]
[The Shorties overcame several crises and
presented a praiseworthy performance!]
Bernard improves every time
he sings a pop song.
[Keep your chin up!]
Hee-yeol and his unctuous way...
You know when he talks...
He talks and at the end,
for example...
"You're an amateur,
but you're like a singer."
[We know that]
[Extremely unctuous]
[Kwon Jina breaks into laughter]
I also tried it to imitate him.
[Buttery]
You know he does this
with his mouth.
[JYP, why you...]
"I'm a Beraholic!"
If I did that...
It's dinnertime right now...
Anyways, I'm fine with
having Hee-yeol with us...
But YG has a problem because in
the past two years I was with him...
I was the cold, strict judge and...
YG was the kind, humane judge.
But we suddenly have someone
much kinder and more humane.
YG's image is now vague.
You know what I mean?
So it's important how
you set your image.
The funny thing when I watch
it later on television...
YG and I dance a lot.
He's one of the best dancers
in the history of Korea.
But...
When he does this, the beat is...
I wonder what that beat is.
Is that a thirty-second note?
I'm also a dancer but
I don't know what that is.
[It looks right...]
[Maybe not...]
He can just get into the rhythm
but I don't know what he's doing.
I would understand if he didn't dance
but he was a legend in dancing.
It's so fun badmouthing them.
There are 3 shows left.
We were very nervous last week because
we saw you choose your desired agency.
But two of you don't
know how to choose.
[Sam Kim chose YG
five months ago]
[Kwon Jina chose
Antenna Music]
Jina, you don't choose
an agency like this.
You have to think and consider your
color and many things, not like this.
Sam, it's because
you don't know YG.
Look at me. You and
this don't mix.
You don't go with this groove.
[Which agency will
the winner choose?]
Am I really scary?
I'm not, right?
I'm scary?
[Their silence means yes?]
I'm not scary at all.
[They just smile...]
Seeing you like this,
you're very nice.
So I was "unnice" before
you saw me like this?
That's not it!
Now that I see you,
you are nice.
[Tiger judge JYP's wish]
[To be kinder and tender...]
- That doesn't fit you.
- I know, right?
[This definitely...]
[Doesn't fit me, right?]
[JYP was comfortable and cheerful
unlike when he's in the judge's seat]
We only saw him as a judge...
We gained a lot since he gave advice like
a senior artist and taught us like a teacher.
We ate together and
he fed me like a mother.
It was great.
[One-on-one basketball
JYP vs Bernard Park]
[Bernard's on offense this time!]
I've never seen
Bernard this fast.
[Nimble Bernard Park]
[They're excited]
[Who makes the last shot?]
[JYP is exploding with energy!]
They were like amateur
singers on stage...
But when I invited them to my place,
ate and played ball together...
They're just nice kids.
I want them to recharge and relax
during JYP week to perform freely.
JYP week was very aggressive.
We'll give time to the two judges
to dispute what JYP said.
YG?
- I need to dispute.
- Alright.
I'm an expert in dancing.
I don't just get into the rhythm.
I get the beats others can't do.
- A thirty-sixth note shuffle.
- I see that you're one up.
JYP disses me so much that
I want to diss him too.
JYP said that his goal was to
improve in singing every day.
But it's been 10 years.
Why haven't you improved?
That's a good one.
And You Hee-yeol?
Instead of disputing, could you show
us that expression? What is it?
How do you do it?
Everything else was fun, but
when he felt Sam's stomach...
I think he was talking
about his voice.
I'm really worried.
Alright.
That's how JYP week was. We have senior artists
from JYPE that are also fans of this show.
Please give a hand to
the artists under JYPE!
We have miss A's Jia, GOT7,
and Sunmi here with us.
Before we begin, I'll explain
how the battles will progress.
This week will also be an
absolute evaluation.
The total is calculated from judges' score 60%
and real-time voting by viewers 40%.
The three with the highest total
will advance to the semifinal.
And the remaining one team
will depart from KPOP STAR.
I'll tell you their number and order
to help you in your voting.
First is No. 1 Kwon Jina who is
attractive with her twists.
No. 2 Sam Kim is a dark horse
making a frightening upturn.
No. 3 The Shorties sing explosive
harmonies with their small figure.
No. 4 Bernard Park has a captivating
voice that stimulates the emotions.
This is not just a competition
but also a festival.
The TOP4 are not only going to compete
but they also prepared a special stage.
The first special stage is a
collaboration by two guitar geniuses.
Kwon Jina and Sam Kim
prepared a great performance.
Then it's sentimental ballad singer Bernard Park
and The Shorties with heavenly harmony.
Please stay tuned to watch this
performance only shown on KPOP STAR.
Viewers' votes play an important
role just like in last week.
Yoo Hye-young will explain
how the voting is done.
- Yoo Hye-young?
- I'm here in the audience.
Hello, I'm Yoo Hye-young
the mistress of KPOP STAR.
It's a full house as you can see
and it's really heating up.
You, at home, can also participate in
this excitement by texting your votes.
I'll explain how it's done.
Text the contestant's name in Korean or
their number to #0606 on your phone.
You might know this by now.
You can vote for more than one contestant
but no multiple votes for one contestant.
Since voting is possible via KakaoTalk,
those abroad can also participate.
I'm really nervous. Now we will
begin the actual competition.
The first stage is always
filled with tension.
The one who will perform
shines the more we see her.
Please give a big hand for Kwon Jina
and text voting will also begin!
[Text voting begins]
[Text the contestant's name in Korean or
number to #0606 (10 cents data charge)]
[No. 1 Kwon Jina]
I have specially prepared a
private tutor for each of you.
[Private tutor?]
Since I can't be with you
for the entire week...
You will have a teacher
who will teach for a week.
[Anticipation]
The first teacher is for Jina.
I want one of your tones
to be strengthened...
And that's a sharp
penetrating sound.
You have a lot of soft sounds
with good resonance.
But wouldn't it be better if you
had that penetrating sound?
So I want you to watch this
performance for a week.
[Who's her private tutor?]
[Shanice Wilson's "Breathe Again"!]
[This part!]
It fell an octave there.
You're the winner
if you do that.
Alright? Easy?
You can do it.
[At a loss...]
[Jina's practice room]
[She practices according
to JYP's advice]
That was out of the blue...
I was surprised because
I never thought about that...
I watched that clip and
listened to it many times.
I don't have much time for
practice so it's hard...
I have to find the key points
and follow her in my practice.
[Then one day!]
[She's busy practicing
even today]
[Someone came!]
[She isn't aware since
she's absorbed in practice]
[Kwon Suna, 20, older sister]
[Surprise visit by her sister!]
[She's just a child
before her sister]
No, don't cry.
[She burst out crying
because she's happy...]
When I wanted to do music...
My sister made a request
to our parents in tears.
"Jina has to do this
no matter what."
So I'm able to do music
thanks to my sister.
[Her sister always supports her!]
[On a one-day date
with her sister!]
[She blows all her stress away!]
It was fun...
I went shopping with her,
we ate tteokbokki...
We sang and danced
at the karaoke...
We also ate together.
So I had a fun time.
Much of my frustrations are gone.
I feel light now.
[She's strengthened
by their cheers!]
I didn't know there were a
lot of people rooting for me.
I feel great for having
their support.
[She keeps in touch with
her friends in Busan!]
I thank my friends for cheering me
because it means a lot.
I thought I should do my best.
[She's fully recharged!]
[JYP gets her song choice]
Can she create a
strong expression?
Then it'll be big.
[JYP's "Even After 10 Years"]
[A ballad about a sad
love for the other!]
I'm going to sing
without my guitar.
I never imagined that.
Jina without her guitar?
That'll be new.
That will happen if she
becomes a pro musician.
I would like to see it.
I never sang without my guitar.
I'm going to show something different
since I've been showing the same thing.
I'm going head on
by just singing.
[No. 1 Kwon Jina]
[Even After 10 Years - JYP]
[Music director - Kwon Tae-eun
Bandmaster - Seo Young-do]
This stage was by
No. 1 Kwon Jina.
She sang for the first time without her
guitar to be judged solely on singing.
We will now listen to the
commentary and score.
I recommended JYP to wear a mask
to build up tension for this show.
The score is written all over his face.
Why don't we hear what it is?
She signed up last season but didn't
make the regional preliminaries.
She doesn't sing relying
on her innate talents.
She gives much thought,
studies, and practices.
She's improved every week.
She understood what I meant when I told
her to watch Shanice's performance.
She knew what I wanted and
opened her voice that much.
And that strong, sharp
voice did come out.
That's what's frightening.
Her performance was flawless.
I see.
JYP's score...
He said it was flawless.
What will be her score?
It's 99!
It's the highest ever!
99! A point short of 100.
But YG and You Hee-yeol have a
blank face. I wonder what they think.
Who will go first?
YG?
Out of JYP's many hit songs,
I don't really know this one.
Are you still sulking?
The most important thing for a
singer is not just singing well.
It's to convey the emotion and the lyrics...
the most important thing is to move us.
I felt that this song is too good
after watching your performance.
This would be a hit song if
it was sung by Kwon Jina.
- So it's an advantage for her.
- Let go of it already!
The song didn't meet its owner.
If Kwon Jina released this song now,
it would take No. 1 on the music charts.
YG's score...
What is YG's score after
giving such a commentary?
It's 95!
That's a high score,
and You Hee-yeol?
I was really worried that she was
singing this song because...
She sang JYP's songs several times.
Wouldn't this be overlapping?
Even I was concerned that maybe the viewers
might think she's only singing JYP's songs.
And second, this is a ballad.
I wondered if she could sing a ballad
since she sang songs with groove.
Many things will be revealed if she
goes head on with just singing.
But...
There are various singing styles
of many different singers.
Jina has a different color from the
current female ballad singers.
She has a new singing style, not old,
that this generation prefers.
She could become the greatest female
ballad singer. I thought, "Who is she?"
Antenna Music's score...
That was more of a compliment.
I'm curious of the score.
It's 98!
That's a very high score!
She finished with 292.
It hasn't been decided whether
you advance or not but...
How do you feel right now?
Did you expect this score?
I was really worried and didn't expect
such compliments. I'm really nervous.
Whose commentary was memorable?
- JYP.
- I see.
That was only 60%. The other
40% is from the viewers' votes.
Those cheering for Kwon Jina can
text "1" or "Kwon Jina" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Kwon Jina!
[No. 2 Sam Kim]
I was born in the US and this is
my first time coming to Korea.
I sang alone and was just
playing around on the guitar.
But now I have people
cheering me in Korea.
Who am I for them to
treat me so well?
I'm thankful but embarrassed.
[What is JYP's advice for Sam
who's making a frightening rise?]
Since Sam sings with his throat,
if I could just change his voice...
He could give off a
more powerful voice.
So I introduced him to R. Kelly
who sings with his body.
[R. Kelly - the textbook
on R&B vocalization]
You have to use your entire body.
Then you need to breathe from here.
JYP said I lack in fundamentals
and abdominal breathing.
I practice to not breathe with my chest
even when I'm not singing.
I'm paying attention
to it and practicing.
[JYP gets Sam's song choice]
He can utilize what he learned from
the private tutor in this song.
I'm getting excited.
[Ben E. King's "Stand by Me"]
It'll be amazing if he does it.
This song is possible for him.
I expect him to arrange this well.
It was hard at first because this
song doesn't have many lyrics.
I wrote some lyrics to show something new
since it repeats and could sound boring.
[Sam is practicing one day]
[But two men approach his room]
[Surprise visit by EQ's Ki-ryun
and his roommate Se-woon]
[Ki-ryun and Se-woon made time
to come and cheer Sam]
- I really missed you guys.
- You were awesome.
- How's practice?
- It's hard.
- It should be hard.
- It really is.
Could you play a little?
- When I first...
- Oh! Dara?
I'm proud of it.
[They want to feel her warmth]
[I envy you]
My face was really red
after she signed it.
[Last week after getting an
autograph from 2NE1's Dara]
[His face is about to explode]
[Ki-ryun naturally plays
on the keyboard]
[It's been a while since we
last heard them play together]
This is great!
[He plays on the spot for
their surprise visit]
It's good to see you.
Thank you for coming.
I can't sing this well
since I'm bad in Korean.
I hand the guitar to you
so please continue.
Sam, bathe frequently.
And stop eating.
Stop waking me up at 2 AM
to eat cereal with you.
[Are they cheering
or exposing him?]
Become the winner...
And Bernard is runner-up.
It was great. I was happy
to see them again.
I was tired but they
energized me to do better.
[And eating his favorite makchang]
Eat all of this and win.
- You have to win.
- Win?
Honestly, who do you think
will win from the TOP4?
Well...
Actually...
I've been watching Kwon Jina.
- I'm sorry.
- I see...
Should I wrap some
garlics for you?
Thank you for cheering me
and that means a lot.
I'll show a more fun and
better performance.
Go Sam Kim!
[No. 2 Sam Kim]
This stage was by
No. 2 Sam Kim.
We could feel the soul from this
performance by the guitar genius.
Sam is feeling and
enjoying the mood here.
He even made gestures he doesn't
usually make. That was impressive.
Let's hear the commentaries.
I remember when we just
started this season.
Sam Kim was pointed out
the most by me.
He had groove but bad beats.
But he improved so much in
the past several months.
The frightening thing about today
and last week's performance is...
He's now relaxed.
I'm not relaxed because this is a
live show and I could've judged better.
It was great to see
Sam having fun.
But there's one thing and that's
the falsetto in the middle.
It's usually hard for people with
a husky voice to sing in falsetto.
I wanted to give a high score
but you get a deduction for that.
YG's score...
Everything was great except for
the falsetto. What's his score?
It's 95!
95 is still high. Let's hear
the next commentary.
It's true that he improved the most
out of all the contestants this season.
He couldn't sing the high notes
before but he did today.
He improved in singing.
And the falsetto...
I thought the same as YG.
The singing wasn't that great but you
wrote the music and words for this part.
He even has the ability
to compose.
Another thing. Everyone's nervous
but Sam is having a concert here.
I know, right? He made
a lot of gestures.
You were acting coquettishly with
the audience, showing your talents.
That was cute.
Antenna Music's score...
Cute Sam Kim really hit those
high notes. What's his score?
It's 95!
- JYP's left.
- Thank you.
I was interested in whether he was
breathing with his chest or belly.
When he sang the first line,
his breathing was down here.
He gave a really nice sound.
He corrected that in a week.
I was thankful and it was great.
We can't talk only about singing
because there's a musician side to him.
He sang this in the blues scale
but the music is in major.
I think he did it without
knowing music theory.
He was singing and playing a blues
scale on top of a music in major.
It's frightening what he'll
become if he studies music.
But the falsetto the two judges
pointed out and one more thing...
You don't know how to control the speed
and show everything in the beginning.
These two things can be corrected
but you get a slight deduction.
JYP's score...
He showed his weakness in falsetto
and speed control. What's his score?
It's 94!
His total is 284!
You just heard the commentaries.
How do you feel right now?
I did my best but it's a pity
I couldn't sing the falsetto.
I made many mistakes in the
solo part but I had fun.
And I'm grateful for the
unexpected compliments.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
You have a lot of fans here.
How about a wink?
I like pink.
He's gaining more
fans every week.
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "2" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Sam Kim!
[No. 3 The Shorties]
They tried to make their voices heavy
and wide after making it to the TOP10.
I gave them bad commentaries.
I recommended them to a singer
that sings as if speaking.
JYP introduced us to The Supremes.
He always stresses on
singing as if speaking.
After watching the clip, we knew
what singing as if speaking was.
[What song did they choose
taking JYP's advice?]
I never expected this.
This will be very good.
They can't sing this in a
wide voice even on purpose.
They have no choice but to
sing in their voice for this.
This week is...
[What song is it that
surprised him?]
[Toy's "Passionate Goodbye"
written by You Hee-yeol]
[A bold choice that's rare
to hear in auditions!]
We're from Daegu and have been
in Seoul for almost 3 months.
We couldn't attend our graduation.
It wasn't elementary or middle school.
It was our high school graduation.
We have graduated from being teens.
It's sad that we couldn't
be a part of it.
I miss my friends.
I miss my teachers that took
care of me the past 3 years.
- We didn't even get our diploma.
- That's right. We didn't.
[This sadness hangs heavily
in one part of their heart]
[The next morning]
Where are we going?
We're paying a visit to the teacher
that made you into The Shorties.
We're going to Daegu?
[A small present for them by
the production crew!]
I have to fix my makeup.
[Visiting their hometown
makes them excited!]
[A nice car prepared by
the production crew!]
[They're going back after 3 months!]
- This is awesome!
- We're finally here!
It's Daegu! We're here!
[They arrive at their old school!]
We're here.
It's been a while.
[They're overwhelmed with
the school right before them!]
[It's the legendary seniors!]
[What is all this?]
[The juniors greeting them
seem like they'll pop out]
[Even female students in the
middle of hair curling!]
[Everyone welcomes them
in their glorious return!]
[Hi]
[A single hand gesture
makes them go wild!]
[You look like a celebrity!]
Did you hear that?
We're not celebrities.
[They're popular like idols!]
The teacher is in class so you're
told to go to the auditorium.
[They head for the auditorium]
[Unni!]
[You're pretty!]
[They can't believe
their popularity]
[They enter the auditorium]
We congratulate The Shorties
seniors on your graduation!
[300 juniors gathered
in the auditorium]
[Handmade banners and
even an orchestra!]
[Everything is prepared for them!]
[They enter amidst wild cheers!]
[They hug those they missed!]
[An intense expression
of their happiness!]
Since you couldn't attend your graduation
due to your time on KPOP STAR.
Your juniors from GAHS prepared
a surprise graduation ceremony.
We will now hold Yeo In-hye, Park Na-jin, and
Ryu Tae-kyung's graduation ceremony.
[Diploma conferral]
[Close to tears]
This is unbelievable...
[Graduation song]
[They never expected...]
[This big present
from their juniors]
[Can't hear their cries
since they're choked]
I'm really thankful...
I really missed everyone as
I was away from school...
[These school grounds are
filled with their memories]
[Don't cry! Don't cry!]
I really missed all my teachers.
- We love you teachers!
- We really love you!
It was like a dream.
It was meaningful because it
was our very own graduation.
It's our turn to repay them for
the special graduation ceremony.
I believe in them!
I expect it be the best version they
will give me as a gift in my lifetime.
[No. 3 The Shorties]
[Passionate Goodbye - Toy]
This stage was by
No. 3 The Shorties.
This was like the story of
their sentimental graduation.
Let's hear the commentaries.
I also got emotional when I saw
you meeting your teachers.
It's because I can see that
your teachers taught you well.
You're well-trained in
music theory.
And I think you should be
thankful to your teachers.
Our hearts already sank
when you started singing.
It was great that you didn't widen
your voices which I always pointed out.
But you weren't able to
explode with emotion.
I was hoping that your emotions would
lead the song but you weren't able to.
That was a pity.
JYP's score...
Let's see the score.
JYP's score is 92!
YG?
I was getting tired of hearing JYP's
songs all this time on KPOP STAR.
I was happy to hear You Hee-yeol's
"Passionate Goodbye."
Are you still...
I thought it was going to be big since
it's the first time his song was sung.
And the video clip I saw was the
most touching of all on KPOP STAR.
- I was moved to tears.
- The producer is clapping.
So that's why they sang
"Passionate Goodbye."
I agree with JYP on...
I'll talk about what
was unfortunate.
They can sing much better than this but
because they set the concept first...
It overshadowed their singing and that
also happens to pro musicians at times.
I would have applauded if it wasn't
sung in an important round as today.
It was a pity since it didn't
fully show your skills.
YG's score...
Let's see the score. He said
they weren't able to explode...
It's 92!
Congratulations You Hee-yeol. Your song
was finally sung on KPOP STAR.
Please give him a hand!
Let me first talk about
music briefly.
This song is not for an audition
since it's very hard to sing.
But they reminded me of
something that I had forgotten.
This song is a sad song. And
when I first wrote this song...
If it's like ABBA, because there is
no song like ABBA in Korea.
When you three sang, "That's right! I was
thinking about ABBA when I wrote this!"
You made me realize, "This is
how it's supposed to be."
There was that moment but
there's one more thing.
Tens of thousands applied for KPOP STAR
but the reason you made it to TOP4 is...
Park Na-jin, Yeo In-hye, and
Ryu Tae-kyung stood together as one.
So the three of you should
continue in music, okay?
Last of all...
With your graduation coming up,
you knew this song was difficult yet...
You sang this song and
I thank you for that.
Congratulations on
your graduation.
Antenna Music's score...
He gave them advice on continuing music
and that's more than a compliment.
It's 96!
They have 280!
Those cheering for The Shorties can
text "3" or "The Shorties" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
You just heard the commentaries.
How do you feel, Na-jin?
We're thankful for the good score
despite our shortcomings.
We don't know the result but
we will continue to do our best.
Alright. They're very lovely
and energetic girls.
We have finished 3 performances now.
Looking at the current judges' score...
Kwon Jina is first with 292.
Since the viewers' votes haven't been
factored in yet, please hurry and vote.
Text the singer's name in Korean
or their number to #0606.
It's now the last performance.
It's No. 4 Bernard Park!
[No. 4 Bernard Park]
[You Hee-yeol receives
Bernard's song choice]
We'll see his strong hook
with this song.
Richard Marx's "Right Here Waiting."
[A ballad with a warm melody
he wrote longing for his wife]
Our hearts will be stolen by
his solid voice again...
This song goes well with Bernard in
this round where we choose the TOP3.
I look forward to it.
[Then who is Bernard's
private tutor?]
When you sing "I wanna go home,"
it feels like you want to go home.
But when you sang
"Yeah, that's how it was"...
It didn't have that sad feeling.
You were just singing and it
wasn't as if you were speaking.
[So who is his private tutor?]
The one who can teach him how to
sing as if speaking in Korean is...
Yoo Jae-ha.
I didn't know who he was.
His style is completely different from
mine, but as I kept on listening...
I practiced to sing in my style
as if I was speaking.
[After last week's show...]
[The others are happy
meeting with their family]
[On the other hand,
Bernard is alone]
When you are happy,
others are happier.
When something is good, it's better
when you have others with you.
It was hard because I didn't
have such people in Korea.
I miss my parents and friends...
I was really lonely before going to bed
or when I'm in the practice room.
[Bernard is alone in his room
unlike the other finalists...]
[But...]
[His parents made a surprise visit
from the US to root for their son]
[They closed their store and came
in a heartbeat to see their son...]
[They head to the accomodation
where Bernard is alone!]
What do you think it'll be
like when you see him?
- I'll be speechless.
- Me too.
I'll be just staring at him.
[They're filled with emotion
thinking of seeing their son...]
[Bernard is filming an
interview at the same time]
[His parents just arrived]
[Thinking of their son made them forget
the fatigue of flying over 10 hours...]
[They approach him quietly since
he's having an interview...]
[It's been 6 months!]
- When did you come?
- Just right now.
[The comfort of his parents
that he longed for...]
- What about the store?
- We closed it to see you.
[He feels uncomfortable that
they closed their store...]
I'm proud of you! Let me
give you another hug.
I never imagined it.
I didn't recognize them at first
but I was really surprised.
[They brought his favorite chips]
[Really?]
[One bag full of chips!]
[Must have missed them...]
[It's been a while since they were
together and spend a happy time]
You said you're not the best son
in one of your interviews.
[His parents watched every
show he appeared in]
You saw us fail in our business...
But you didn't show any
signs of hardship.
You're the best son to have
grown up like that.
I'm grateful you have
grown into a fine man.
It meant a lot to me that
my parents came here.
Since it's my first time
singing before them...
I'll do my best to show
a great performance.
[No. 4 Bernard Park]
This stage was by
No. 4 Bernard Park.
He's KPOP STAR's official sentimentalist.
You just heard him sing "Right Here Waiting."
Let's hear the commentaries.
You Hee-yeol, I think you
were moved to tears.
It's the first time my eyes welled
up with tears looking at a man.
Bernard, are you happy
that your parents came?
- I'm very happy.
- He's very happy.
Did you eat a lot of chips?
I think I put on some weight.
I saw you eat six bags.
I'll make this short.
Antenna Music's score...
It's the first time giving a
score without commentary...
It's 100!
It's the first 100 ever!
What is going on here?
This changes everything.
100? You Hee-yeol is known
to be objective but gave 100.
JYP?
I can't forget this day to
hear him sing like this.
Once he gets into the emotion...
His voice and resonance are
on a different level.
It's a voice and resonance that
can't come from an Asian.
The difference is whether he's
connected to his emotions or not.
But I think the lyrics got him
into the emotion today.
I already know when
he sings the first line.
I was already groggy for
the remaining 3 minutes.
JYP's score...
I'm curious of the score.
He has 100 right now...
It's 99!
He has 199. He's frightening.
His parents from the US
are very happy right now.
Let's hear from YG.
In the video clip, the first thing Bernard
worried about when he saw his parents...
What about the store?
My family ran an appliance repair store.
So it touched me and I was emotional.
I think I gave him the lowest score
and said the most bad things.
I compared Bernard to a
heavyweight many times.
I said that his opponents easily
avoid his punches because he's slow.
When he started off with
"ocean's apart"...
Compared to boxing, he made me groggy with
just one punch as soon as the bell rang.
It was one punch with
the first line.
The opponent is unconscious
and can't get back up.
I thought Richard Marx couldn't
move us like him if he sang.
That's a compliment.
You were highly complimented for
"Home" and now "Right Here Waiting"...
It was very dramatic as you sang
with your parents here today.
YG's score...
Were his ardent feelings reflected
in the song? What is the score?
It's 100!
It's 299! The highest ever!
Bernard Park takes the lead
with the judges' score alone.
Bernard?
Because of the mood right now,
I think I'll ask in English.
I feel great and it's the first time
I'm singing before my parents so...
Your parents came from the US.
Anything you would like to say?
Thank you.
It's getting awkward.
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "4" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 4 Bernard Park!
I think it was all because his
parents were rooting for him.
Bernard Park is first at 299,
the highest score ever.
But this wouldn't be KPOP STAR
if it ended like this, right?
The order can change with your votes.
Please hurry if you haven't voted.
As stated earlier, we now have
the special stage by the TOP4.
We already have many fans
for the first performance.
It's Kwon Jina and Sam Kim.
Please give them a big hand!
[Call You Mine - Jeff Bernat]
[Nobody - Wonder Girls]
That was a masterpiece collaboration
that can only be seen on KPOP STAR.
The TOP4 performances for KPOP STAR
Season 3 is being televised live.
Voting will soon end and the
semifinalists will be announced.
Stay tuned to find out who
makes it to the TOP3.
We'll be showing a highlight clip
for those that haven't voted yet.
Watch carefully and
send in your votes.
All voting will end in 1 minute!
[No. 1 Kwon Jina]
[No. 2 Sam Kim]
[No. 3 The Shorties]
[No. 4 Bernard Park]
[Voting is over]
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
Voting is now over.
Let's meet some welcomed guests
as we wait for the result.
We have senior JYP artists
as this was JYP week.
We have Sunmi, Jia, the cute
Kal So-won, and GOT7.
Thank you for coming.
- Hello.
- A pleasure.
Sunmi, is there anyone you're
cheering for in particular?
I'm cheering everyone but especially
Bernard Park and Kwon Jina.
It was caught on camera how you
were mesmerized when Bernard sang.
I saw that and was taken aback.
Send them a cheer.
Bernard Park, The Shorties, Kwon Jina, and
Sam Kim, your performances were great.
We look forward to more
great performances.
What can people do
to cheer them?
By texting votes to #0606.
Thank you.
I know your cheers mean a lot
so please cheer them to the end.
- Thank you, Kal So-won.
- Thank you.
They finished tallying
while we were talking.
Who will advance to the semifinal?
Even I'm curious who it will be.
The semifinalists will be announced.
I hand it over to Jun Hyun-moo.
Thank you, Yoo Hye-young.
We are awaiting the announcement on who will
advance to next week's TOP3 live show.
As I said earlier, the total is calculated from
judges' score 60% and viewers' votes 40%.
You will see only three with the highest
score next week in the semifinal.
And one of them will depart
from KPOP STAR today.
The judges were given one envelope
and I was given two envelopes.
We don't know whose name is in it
since we have not opened them.
The three whose names are here will
advance and one will be eliminated.
I'll interview them one by one.
We don't know the result yet.
Kwon Jina, how do you feel?
I'm very nervous but I won't have
regrets even if I'm eliminated.
No regrets even if you're eliminated.
Do you honestly think you'll advance
or do you feel uneasy about it?
It's fifty-fifty.
- Fifty-fifty?
- Yes.
It was good when you heard
the commentaries but...
Are you feeling uneasy because
the viewers' votes take 40%?
- Yes.
- I see.
Sam Kim?
I was scared and nervous at first
performing before an audience on stage.
But it's my playground now
and I'm having fun.
Even though I'm eliminated,
I can leave without regrets.
I felt that you were enjoying it.
You made many gestures you didn't
make during the rehearsal.
What did this mean when you were
playing the guitar? Were you excited?
I don't know. It just came out.
It just came out? So those
gestures just came out. I see.
The Shorties? The result isn't out
but I saw Tae-kyung crying.
Weren't you crying? I saw
tears welled up in your eyes.
- You didn't cry?
- I thought it was our last...
I felt sad that I won't see
those that I got close to.
Does that mean you think
you'll be eliminated?
Why? Does everyone think so too?
It's not decided with just
the judges' score.
We still have the viewers' votes.
What do you think, Na-jin?
We don't know the result but I would like
to say we did our best and have no regrets.
I see.
And how do you feel,
Yeo In-hye?
We're thankful that we even made it this far,
and our singing will improve with practice.
So we'll try harder and practice.
Alright. Thank you.
And Bernard Park?
We're waiting for the announcement.
How do you feel right now?
We have a lot of fans and I don't know
how the viewers' votes will turn out.
I place my trust in my fans.
He doesn't know about the votes
but will place his trust in them.
He's already a star. I think
he's a K-pop star already.
The announcement begins
once I open the envelope.
YG... YG?
We don't know who'll be eliminated
but any last words for them?
I'll say one thing.
Honestly, we don't want
to send anyone away.
It was predictable in
Seasons 1 and 2.
But the TOP4 this season are
skilled and it's hard to predict.
We don't know the result but
we don't want to send anyone away.
Alright. The judges don't want to send
anyone away but one has to be sent.
I will now announce the
first semifinalist!
[Who is the first semifinalist?]
I will open one of the
two envelopes in my hand.
I saw it and only
I know the result.
The first semifinalist for the TOP3
show of KPOP STAR Season 3 is...
Who do you think it is?
Who?
That's right! Please congratulate!
It's Bernard Park!
He put on a great performance
before his parents.
He had the highest judges' score
and it looks like nothing changed.
Bernard, I'll ask you
a second time.
I think everyone understood.
I think his parents are the happiest.
Could you move to the winners seat?
Alright. The first is Bernard Park with
the highest judges' score at 299.
It think he got a good score
from the viewers' votes as well.
I'll now announce the
second semifinalist.
I will open the last of the
two envelopes in my hand.
I don't know the result yet
but I will open it now.
The second semifinalist for the TOP3
show of KPOP STAR Season 3 is...
I opened the one I just opened.
I'm sorry. Bernard's
name was on it again.
This is the one.
It's this envelope.
[Who is the second semifinalist?]
I saw it. I saw who it is.
Who do you think is the
second after Bernard?
Will your guess be right?
Will it go according to the
judges' score or is there a twist?
The result reflecting 40%
of the viewers' votes...
The second semifinalist is...
Please congratulate!
It's Kwon Jina!
Congratulations. Kwon Jina with the
next highest judges' score is second.
Your thoughts?
I thank you and will do
my best. Love you!
You said fifty-fifty. What
were you uneasy about?
Why did you think you
would be eliminated?
The viewers' votes...
The mood here was great but
it was the viewers' votes.
Alright. Congratulations and
please move to the winners seat.
Please give her a hand!
The last envelope remains.
It's not in my hands
but in the judges' hands.
The name of either Sam Kim
or The Shorties is written.
Who is the last seminfinalist?
I'm undertaking an
important assignment.
I didn't open it yet.
Please open it.
There's a four point difference
between Sam Kim and The Shorties.
But what is the result after
calculating the viewers' votes?
- I'll look at it.
- Alright.
Both You Hee-yeol
and JYP saw it.
- Alright!
- Yes?
The last semifinalist is...
Is it Sam Kim or The Shorties?
We won't be seeing one
of them next week.
I'll announce it now.
The last semifinalist is...
It's Sam Kim!
Congratulations Sam Kim!
Please join them.
The semifinalists are Bernard Park,
Kwon Jina, and Sam Kim.
Unfortunately, The Shorties will
be leaving KPOP STAR today.
- Na-jin?
- Yes?
You look quite calm
but how do you feel?
I first thank God that
we made it this far.
I want to show our gratitude to
the judges although we lacked.
I thank the production crew, music director,
and the band members that helped us.
I also thank our teachers, juniors,
and fans that cheered for us.
We will continue to do our best, and the
reason we came this far is because of...
Tae-kyung and...
In-hye...
Please give her a hand.
She's overwhelmed and crying.
I wasn't able to say thanks...
But I would like to take this chance
and say thanks to my two friends.
I love you and
let's try harder.
Good luck to The Shorties.
The Shorties have been eliminated.
Bernard Park, Sam Kim, and Kwon Jina
will be in next week's semifinal.
We had YG and JYP weeks and next
week will be Antenna Music week.
Let's look forward to how
You Hee-yeol will influence them.
This was KPOP STAR Season 3, a real
audition where dreams turn into reality.
We'll impress you more
next week. Goodbye!