Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
The battle audition is like a fierce battle
in Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
Our competitiveness is our group of
experts with 15 years of experience.
I go to check on them
and give advice.
I want them to go a
level higher.
I made a few of them to take
on a bold challenge.
They'll proudly advance to
the TOP10 if they succeed.
If not, I hope it becomes an opportunity
for them to realize what they lack.
We're confident of our
group of musicians.
Korea's best guitarist, Ham Chun-ho,
is gladly helping them out.
My long-time colleague, Kim Yeon-woo,
and ALi are giving them lessons.
I'm confident regarding that.
I venture to predict that
many from YG will make it.
I feel like a mother eagle dropping
her eaglets off a cliff.
The battle audition is the death round
with each agency head's honor on the line.
It begins now!
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[The battle audition goes on]
[Tension hangs in the air!]
[Who will take the
remaining 8 seats?]
Let's start the next battle.
Yao Weitao from JYP.
Sam Kim from Antenna Music.
The Shorties from YG.
[When opponents were
announced that day]
Before the battle audition,
I was afraid of the Shorties.
They're strong opponents.
Sam Kim from Antenna Music.
I was surprised and
wanted to cry.
[These two are even more nervous
for facing the extreme Shorties!]
[Who will win this battle?]
Please enter the stage!
[They enter determined!]
[One chance for victory!]
[1st enters the TOP10!]
[2nd prepares for rematch!]
[3rd is eliminated on the spot!]
[Who will enter the TOP10?]
[The Shorties look beautiful
with the help of YG]
They're cute!
[Two have made it into
the TOP10 so far!]
[Who is the third?]
We have outstanding people
in this group as well.
Many mentioned the Shorties as an
opponent they don't want to face.
Sam, how did you feel when you heard
you were in the same group as them?
I wanted to cry.
They're frightening.
It was Christmas-themed clothes before
and now it's post-impressionist.
First is JYP's Yao Weitao.
The rest will wait on the side.
[Now the battle begins!]
[He looks a little thin]
We talked about many things during
practice and also gave much thought.
But today... as we already said,
forget about everything...
Just think about your
father as you sing.
[Does the song have anything
to do with his father?]
[The day his song was
examined by JYP]
["Dance with My Father"
was chosen for him]
Does he know what
the song is about?
He wants to be a child again
and dance with his father.
He has to convey that feeling...
Is his father still living?
No, he passed away
when I was young.
[He's in the same position as
the singer of this song!]
12 years old...
When you were 12.
[He was 12 years old when
his father passed away]
["Dance with My Father" was sung
in memory of his father]
My father got sick and
it was cancer.
He died 3 months later.
I grieved back then
when I was at home.
My mother had a hard time.
It was hard at the time, but now
it's okay after some years passed.
[Calling his mother in Shanghai]
I miss you.
I saw you on television
singing with this girl.
I liked your high notes and the
judges were complimenting you.
I love you, mom.
I love you too.
My mom is dearer than
the world to me.
I called her some time ago and
found out she was very sick.
I had to be there to help her but
couldn't so it broke my heart.
My goal for now is to
make it into the TOP10.
I don't care if I'm eliminated...
But I have this desire
to win at least this time.
I'll do my best today.
[This song is dedicated to his father
but will it touch everyone's heart?]
[Dance with My Father - Luther Vandross]
[It's really good]
Thank you.
[What did the judges think of
his heartfelt singing?]
[There's a heavy silence]
When I see Yao Weitao...
When I first saw him, he was
good-looking and a chef...
Compared to that, he didn't sing well.
His high notes weren't open.
In the past few months,
his singing improved.
One unfortunate thing...
His high notes are open, but
I hope it had more strength.
Maybe I'm asking for too much...
He made remarkable progress, but it would
move us more if he had strong high notes.
I enjoyed it.
[He didn't get a good commentary
regarding the high notes]
[And You Hee-yeol's commentary?]
JYP gave you a lot of training
and you made great strides.
But...
You're in the process.
Just a little more will
make you complete.
The chorus part of the song
is where people are moved.
But it's always unsatisfactory
compared to the first part.
That's a problem you
need to resolve.
[He gets their commentaries
through interpretation]
[The two judges' commentaries
left much to be desired]
[What is JYP's commentary since
he spent a lot of time with him?]
Changing one's vocalization
at the age of 26 is...
The same as learning a
foreign language at that age.
It's like a challenge in how fast
you can sound like a native speaker.
But as you are now,
you came very far.
I felt how you tried to
empathize. You did well.
[JYP finished his commentary with
warm words of encouragement]
[Will he get the honor of
advancing to the TOP10?]
The next contestant is
Antenna Music's Sam Kim.
[Antenna Music's Sam Kim (16)]
[With the Shorties going last]
[You Hee-yeol is concerned]
His guitar teacher was
Ham Chun-ho...
Really?
And his vocal teachers were
Kim Yeon-woo and ALi.
Wow. Being taught the guitar by
Chun-ho that itself is an honor.
We look forward to a
great performance.
[Will Sam show the fruits
of his training?]
How did you feel when you heard you're
battling Yao Weitao and the Shorties?
[He sighs and sighs]
[Why is Sam so tense?]
1/2 were slightly better.
Congratulations.
[Sam was a part of E.Q that lost
to the Shorties in Round 3]
And I have a problem with the beats
and my sense of rhythm.
[Being evaluated by Ham Chun-ho,
maestro of acoustic guitar]
[Satisfied]
Play on mine.
- I'm afraid.
- You are? Me too.
[It sounds different!]
[In awe]
[As if he's proud of
16-year-old Sam's talents]
I'll lend you my guitar
if you get into the finals.
[He'll gladly lend his
guitar that is his life]
- I don't think I'm worthy...
- I think you are.
He can if he gets into
the finals, right?
[What performance will Sam give as
he received You Hee-yeol's teachings?]
[I'm in Love - Ra.D]
[Can't believe a 16-year-old
has such soul vocals]
[Sam's guitar ad-lib
knocks them off their feet]
[Look at the judges]
[First attempt in rapping]
[The studio breaks into applause]
Going to Antenna Music...
That was luck.
You made remarkable progress in both your
guitar playing and singing in the past 3 weeks.
Antenna Music taught you well and you
practiced hard. Both were combined.
You made the most amazing progress
out of all in this battle audition.
I suddenly had this thought.
Interludes disappeared from all music
starting from the late 1990s.
You're right.
Since everyone is in such
a hurry in life...
They change the radio station
when the interlude comes in.
Verse 2 comes right after verse 1.
Interlude is gone from all gayo.
I want to listen to the
interlude when Sam plays.
I want to listen to his guitar
between verses 1 and 2.
And...
Before he started rapping,
I used to say this to Bernard...
Doing a minor ad-lib
in a major song...
It's amazing, but the contestants this time...
Did you make him? Did you teach him that?
[It's our little secret]
I was surprised and
you also rapped well.
It was a fresh jolt.
I enjoyed it.
I think the same as JYP.
This was your best
solo performance.
That was some good planning.
I didn't expect him to rap.
He rapped well since he has
an excellent sense of groove.
He met You Hee-yeol, a great teacher,
and learned the guitar from Ham Chun-ho.
He made great strides in his sense of
rhythm that I have nothing to point out.
Good job.
[What is You Hee-yeol's commentary
since he trained Sam himself?]
You did well.
Your beats are better.
You're not in a hurry
and now composed.
We fixed one thing
we wanted to fix.
You sound hoarse.
I practiced especially hard...
I'm saying this because there were
two fantastic high parts.
But he couldn't sing them.
You two would have loved it more
but he couldn't because of his voice.
But I want to compliment him for hiding
that naturally with techniques.
That was a relief.
And your dieting is
showing results.
He used to look like this
but he's dieting right now.
Continue to not eat (joke).
Today was good.
The next contestant is...
I'm worried because the
previous contestant did well.
They are without a rival and received
compliments one after another.
No contestant received more
compliments than them.
They kept on shocking
the judges.
[Everyone wants to
avoid the Shorties]
[Recognized as YG's main players]
[But they are more burdened
because Sam was complimented]
Any difficulties or inconveniences
during your stay at YGE?
Our song changed 3 days ago.
It was hard but thanks to YG who
helped us until late last night...
We kept our spirits up
and did our best.
JYP gave his opinion to do a different
song during the warm-up match...
- "I Know"?
- Yes, it was that song.
I wanted them to go with it, but I didn't
think it was the one 3 days ago.
I asked, "I'm really sorry, but
can you change the song?"
They're in a crisis.
They used to sing songs that
they practiced on for weeks.
But today, they have to present
what they prepared for 3 days.
I'm saying this so the viewers and
judges can take that into account.
[But...]
[They can't hear anything because
they're memorizing the lyrics...]
Since JYP told us to
supplement the song...
We thought of making this song
complete and stuck to it...
[Battle audition
T-minus 3 days]
[YG's final inspection]
[They're singing passionately
on what they have practiced]
[He feels it isn't enough]
It doesn't sound good.
This is a big problem.
[They're struggling with the song
itself with only 3 days left]
It's a difficult task to
work out this song.
I think we have to change our plans
instead of sticking to this song.
I think it's better to change into something
you're good at. What do you think?
We've been struggling with
this for several weeks.
But it isn't working out.
It may be hard...
But change the song and
stop thinking about this.
Throw away what's bad and
don't even hang on to it.
Based on my experiences.
Understand?
You'll do well. You've been
doing great until now.
[But...]
We were speechless. What song
can we prepare in 3 days?
[They competed with longer hours
of practice than other teams...]
[They don't even have
the time to worry]
Thinking about the composition
and harmony drove us crazy.
We stayed in the practice room
very late into the night.
We put all our concentration into
creating the harmonies.
It's a pity that we couldn't change
some parts due to the lack of time.
[Why are the judges surprised?]
I'm surprised by George Michael's "Faith"
as much as "I Know." How will this be...
This song is even harder
than "I Know."
[The exciting guitar accompaniment
stands out in George Michael's "Faith"]
- It's a repetition of 3 chords...
- I know. How will they do this?
I'm afraid and excited.
We'll listen with a
joyful heart. Good luck.
Thank you.
[Will they overcome this hardship
and advance to the TOP10?]
[Faith - George Michael]
[They sing the intro in harmony
without the accompaniment]
[The judges watch them more
sharply than before]
[Changes into an exciting
and bright mood]
[With only 3 days of practice]
[What is their commentary?]
Do you think I'm going to say
something good or bad?
You used very complex chords when
you had only 3 days to practice.
[They're pointed out
for the first time!]
You went down 4 semitones
from the first degree.
That's really...
It becomes a dissonance
if it isn't exactly right.
So...
To get to the point,
it was a lack of practice.
[What they feared came true]
You could have used simple and rhythmical
chords but you're not content with that.
You had to get all of those
complex chords in 3 days.
It was unstable throughout the song.
[What is You Hee-yeol's commentary
since he always complimented them?]
It was unstable, right?
[Another objective observation]
Because you went off slightly...
I started to incline my ears,
"What is that chord?"
So, at first... what
was the first key?
E-flat.
Then it was a D-flat, C, and B.
Since you didn't sing it correctly,
a semitone became a whole tone.
I knew after hearing the piano.
Second, there were too
many key changes.
You kept on changing the key
to try to change the melody.
That made it sound unstable.
The composition this time
was a bit discursive.
[They're being pointed out
for the first time]
[What is YG's commentary
since he trained them?]
I casted them because I like them but
I feel sorry for not giving much help.
They would have had more time
if I told them to change early on.
I wanted to trust you
all the way.
JYP said it should be changed
and we changed it a week later.
It was a pity so
I feel sorry.
I would like to compliment that it was
good for something prepared in 3 days.
Will all three teams come to the stage?
We'll discuss to make the decision.
[Who will be the 3rd finalist?]
[The discussion is over]
We'll make the announcement.
1st place to enter the TOP10...
[Who takes 1st place
in the third group?]
[The Shorties' harmony wasn't good
enough due to the short practice time]
[Yao Weitao's high notes
weren't good enough]
[Sam Kim's sense of rhythm
improved and he was full of soul]
[Who will enter the TOP10?]
As expected, It's Sam Kim.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
[It's extraordinary that he beat
the Shorties, the likely winners!]
I'm happy and feel great because
the judges said I did well.
[Time to announce
2nd and 3rd place]
Since both of you...
Practiced with me...
It breaks my heart that
one of you has to be eliminated.
We thank you for taking our advice
to heart and doing your best.
I hope you will continue to do so
regardless of the results.
I hope we can meet again
in the future.
[2nd place gets a chance
for a rematch]
3rd place is...
[Both teams left much
to be desired]
[Who will take 3rd place?]
Yao Weitao.
[Yao Weitao is eliminated]
[YG's the Shorties take 2nd]
[JYP is unable to speak]
You improved a lot.
Your sincerity and enthusiasm
moved us greatly.
I hope to see a better you
in the future.
[I'm happy to have even
made it this far]
[JYP can't bring himself to
see Yao one last time]
[He has no family to
comfort him here]
[But we believe his
dreams are here]
His sincere attitude
and humble heart...
Such things moved us.
I really want to work
with Yao again.
Let's start the next battle.
Complete Chae from JYP.
Something from Antenna Music.
Jang Hanna from YG.
[It's hard to predict the outcome!]
Please enter the stage.
[The fourth group enters!]
We went against Something
once during Round 3.
We were surprised and worried
that we're battling them again.
[A fated rematch where they meet
again at the battle audition!]
We're battling them again...
It was a big shock...
I want to laugh and
not cry this time.
I thought it would be
against female vocalists.
Since I'm alone...
I'm worried.
[An unprecedented battle
will now unfold!]
[Completely different
colors and genres!]
[An unpredictable battle
between teams!]
[Who will take the honor of
advancing as the 4th finalist?]
Hanna, who are you?
[The elegant black dress makes her
beauty to stand out even more]
You transformed beautifully.
What do you think
of your image?
[She's suddenly
brimming with tears...]
Did you cry?
Oh, it's because they
were eliminated.
I forced 2Minute to split...
She had to see them off...
[The moment when her
friends were eliminated]
[She wiped away her
tears in silence...]
Hanna?
You might feel sad
right now but...
The greatest gift you can give them is
doing well and taking 1st place, right?
Just as JYP said, I thought you
were a model when you walked out.
- I was surprised.
- Your clothes look great.
YGE is very good at styling.
Black mesh!
I wore that a lot in 1994.
[She regained her laughter
thanks to the judges' joke]
One interesting thing about this battle is
All Chae and Something battled before.
And Se-woon was eliminated.
Complete Chae won before so
are you more confident?
It's a bit different than before...
[When opponents were
announced a few hours ago]
No way!
The moment it was announced...
it was really shocking.
[After the announcement]
[Chae-yeon cries due to the
burden of having a rematch]
- Are you crying because of me?
- Yes, it's because of you.
I don't know what to do.
[It's a heartless rematch where
they can only comfort each other]
[But they have another difficulty...]
[Song choice! What song
are they singing?]
[JYP's special recommendation!]
[The powerful dance stands out
in Rain's "It's Raining"]
"It's Raining" is hard
even for male singers.
The moves are large, but it has
to be precise with power.
Until now, they did light
dances out of enjoyment.
Doing a dance they never did before and
singing while doing an intense dance...
I wanted them to gain
something from that.
[Training by JYP the day
after the casting audition]
After watching the music video,
do you think you can do it?
We made up some moves
according to our feeling.
You made your own moves?
That's admirable.
[They show the moves they made
according to their feeling]
[JYP suddenly stops the music]
Learn the original moves first.
It'll be a shock if you
do the original dance.
This isn't an easy dance for you.
The dance is a powerful dance.
I'm worried if women can do this
since it was made for men.
There are a lot of moves. I'm worried if
we can sing and dance at the same time...
This is hard!
The song is fast, the lyrics are long,
and there are no parts to breathe.
We practiced thinking,
"Can we do this?"
[Practice to make the
impossible possible!]
[Practice... again... and again...]
[Even during the interview for
the Lunar New Year Special]
[They don't rest and are
absorbed in practicing!]
[They practiced regardless
of time and place]
After getting casted, we rested
only twice during the past 3 weeks.
We are truly something.
[They commend themselves]
It was the best when JYP
trained us personally.
He gave us good advices on
how to put in feeling.
Please watch how we'll dance the
powerful dance made for men.
[They're more tense than before]
Chae-yeon and Chae-ryeong?
Yes?
It's okay even though you
two are eliminated, right?
Yes.
You're still young and
have many things to do.
Just enjoy yourselves
whether you pass or not.
Good luck!
[Their mother cheers them
with an earnest heart]
[It's Raining - Rain]
[A strenuous performance with no
time to breathe, let alone sing]
[Automatically applaud
out of admiration]
Thank you.
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
I think You Hee-yeol should go first
since he knows the least about dancing.
[How did he see them?]
Now I know just this much how the dance
differs from before as I keep on seeing you.
You used to sing and
dance separately.
But today you had to sing
while doing intense moves.
Despite the difficulty, there's
now power in your dance...
And it went smoothly without
running out of breath while singing.
Before, I mainly watched the unstable elements,
how you were young and without habits.
I think you overcame those
weaknesses in this performance.
Thank you.
[The ones waiting are
getting nervous...]
[What is YG's commentary
who is a dancing legend?]
Do you think I'll say
something good or bad?
I'm asking JYP.
[Please say something good]
Just looking at the dance...
I think you have skills to be
Rain's background dancers.
Another thing is that I have
complaints about this show.
Even for pros, harmony is added in the
background music for dance music.
They're not singing solo. There's harmony
in this song but even that was removed.
There are recording techniques
such as doubling and stacking...
But it's hard for their singing to sound
nice after removing that from the song.
I'm worried since I have
affection for them...
[Worried?]
They made it this far with potential but
now we're choosing the TOP10 finalists.
If they do become finalists, the other
nine are very strong opponents.
More emphasis will be placed on
singing and not on dancing.
I'm worried that they are at a
disadvantage in singing.
Putting aside whether they're good or not,
it's my wish that they can go far.
I said this so the viewers can keep in mind
that it's hard to sing while dancing.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[What is JYP's commentary?]
As a producer who was with you
during practice, you did very well.
You were better than expected.
Thank you.
Singing is difficult when
the lower body is moving.
Singing while moving the
upper body is easy...
It's really hard when the lower body is moving
because the center of balance is off, but...
It's amazing that they
could sing like that.
You sang very well.
Thank you.
That was as a producer.
But now as a judge...
You were singing hard like
"I have to sing well."
That's from a realistic standpoint
without taking your age into account.
But what you did was
amazing for your age.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[What is their fate as they
received mixed commentaries?]
[Antenna Music's Something]
What we expect the most
from Something is...
Their own songs. That's what
I personally think as well.
Since both of you have a
strong tendency as artists...
How good or bad your song is will
determine if you pass or not.
[What did they prepare?]
The one that makes me
really anxious is...
Something.
Something has to write
their own song.
The others can go straight to
practice when the song is decided.
But they have to write their song
and it can't be done in a day.
And they both need to write it.
I'm really worried about them.
[Were they able to
write a good song?]
[They present their song
they worked on until now]
Play the beginning part.
Now sing the chorus part.
One, two, three, four!
[There's no difference...]
Do you get it now?
The beginning and the
chorus are the same.
We received commentaries that our songs
are boring so we focused mainly on that.
We had to give much thought and
were stressed in writing the song.
We used to write it quickly but
it took longer this time.
[A few days later]
[They present their
somewhat completed song]
[What did Kim Yeon-woo,
the god of vocals, think?]
They wrote this?
It's very good.
[Unexpected compliments from
Kim Yeon-woo and ALi!]
[Feels proud]
We were exhausted from
thinking about the melody.
It strengthened us when they said it was
good and the rest was smooth sailing.
If their song is bad,
the results will be bad...
Fortunately, I think this can be
the title track of their album.
[Will they receive favorable
comments as he hopes?]
[What is their song?]
[You Hee-yeol feels like
he's being judged too]
[Excuse Me - own song]
[The guitar riff
makes them smile]
Where am I?
I fell asleep because it was warm
And it's already the last stop
Where should I go?
I know that you're busy but
Can I ask for directions?
People are passing by
Color of an unfamiliar city
I'm placed in the middle
Standing absently
Please repeat it to me again
I'm not good with directions
Could you tell me kindly?
You speak a little fast
Where am I?
I'm in love for the first time
I need directions
Where should I go?
I know that you're busy but
Can I ask for directions?
Oh, wait a minute please
I think that I'm lost
Since that day, I've been
Lingering around you
Please repeat it to me again
I don't know much about love
Could you tell me kindly?
It's hard to understand you
[They seem pleased]
[But...]
[The judges don't look satisfied]
[What are their commentaries?]
[YG grabs the mike first]
I personally like JYP.
And I personally like You Hee-yeol
as we got to know each other.
But I'm putting personal feelings aside
because I need to judge precisely.
I'll say what I saw and felt.
[What is he going to say?]
Before you began, I said that
I had high hopes for you as artists.
I watched your performance
as I read the lyrics.
Writing your own song is great but
it's simple without being unique.
[Harsh criticism that went
against expectations!]
The lyrics are about losing
direction and wandering.
But the words I expected
are listed here.
As the round advances,
our expectations grow.
This is not the preliminaries anymore.
The TOP10 finalists are being decided.
There has to be unexpected lyrics
that catch us off guard.
I was being frank.
[The commentaries are merciless
since this is the TOP10 prematch!]
[Next is JYP]
A good song and a hit song
are two different things.
[What does he mean?]
All the songs you sang
until now were good songs.
They had a unique sentiment.
And the ideas were novel.
The subject and materials
are great but...
It doesn't taste good
when you start cooking.
[It doesn't taste good?]
The idea of comparing how you're lost
to being lost in love is great.
But your ability to
work that out...
Compared to an hour-long drama...
It could be explained in 20 minutes
but you used up the entire hour.
We're immersed in verse 1
then it goes...
That's the common thing
in all the past rounds.
But I wrote worse than you at that age.
I wanted to tell you that at least.
[It hurts but it was a
heartfelt commentary]
[Their second harsh criticism!]
[The contestants are
getting more tense...]
The two judges severely
pointed things out.
They told you that as senior artists
so please take that to heart.
Since they said such things,
I will compliment you.
First...
The previous songs
were very unique.
I like this song because
it has universality.
And among the commentaries you
received for the lyrics was...
The lyrics are too personal.
You were reproved because they
couldn't understand what you're saying.
You tried to tell your
story this time...
But you also tried to consider
the hearts of the listeners.
That's one of the things
I would like to compliment.
What they said is that you shouldn't
lose your color in your musical career.
Do you understand?
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[What is their fate after getting
unexpected harsh criticisms?]
Next is Jang Hanna.
[YG's Jang Hanna]
[She looks a little tense]
This song is...
[Is it unexpected?]
I never expected this.
I love this song.
But it's not from my generation.
It was when I was young.
I recall I was in the 8th grade.
I used to record it on cassette.
["As Like the Smiling Face on Parting"
Lee Eun-ha's classic song from 1986]
One of the reasons why
I like Jang Hanna's voice...
She has a very soulful voice.
Aren't you looking forward
to hear her sing gayo?
[The song was chosen out of
YG's ambitious expectations...]
[She was separated from the team
and it was especially hard on her]
[Her 2Minute members]
We did things together
and now I'm alone so...
I feel sad.
[YG prepared a surprise gift
since she's having a hard time...]
[Lee Hi!]
I was practicing but
someone suddenly came in.
I was taken aback because it was
Lee Hi and my face became red.
Expression! You know
that feeling.
We're the same age so
we talked comfortably.
She taught me how to do the beginning
part since she did this a lot.
That became a great support
so I think I'll do well.
[And on the day of the audition...]
Good luck. Looks like you're
taking two exams, huh?
[Unfortunately, the written exam for
college overlapped with the audition]
I'm taking my entrance exam today
and also going to the audition.
I'm really nervous
and burdened.
[2014 practical exam placement]
[She finishes the written exam
and heads for the audition!]
[She arrived 3 hours late
than the other contestants]
[She found out who her
opponents are]
It's going to be Something
and Complete Chae.
[She was unmistakably startled
by the unexpected opponents]
I've been enjoying
it until now.
I couldn't understand when
they said that it was hard.
But now I understand
as I came this far.
[She became close with the 2Minute members
but at the news of their elimination...]
[She wiped away her tears backstage
when she heard the news]
[Her day was especially
long and tiring]
[She tried to hold back the tears
before entering the stage]
[How will her long day end?]
[Her mother in the waiting room]
[As Like the Smiling Face
on Parting - Lee Eun-ha]
[She gets into the rhythm
naturally with the tempo change]
[It was a long day, but she tries to
stay true to the emotions of the song]
[She gave the song some change
according to her feeling]
Thank you.
[She does her best and finishes]
[What will be her commentary?]
[The mood is serious]
[You Hee-yeol grabs
the mike first]
[Did her long day have an adverse
effect on her performance?]
First, the arrangement
was done very well.
It's not easy to sing this
song with just the piano.
You interpreted the song well
apart from your singing skills.
There's one thing...
You're not a jazz vocalist.
It felt like you were imitating one in
your vibration and breathing in the end.
You had the feel but was a
singer for a different genre.
You did well.
[An unexpected objective
commentary]
I...
Agree with the second part
of what You Hee-yeol said.
I don't know who you are
all of a sudden.
When you started doing that,
I thought, "Who is this?"
The thing about you is...
You sang honestly and correctly,
but still had that feeling.
There's no need to
adorn yourself.
But as you adorned your
pronunciation and voice...
The impression that came from your
innocence, honesty, and talent is gone.
Only the talent remained.
I would like to say
that's my fault.
[What happened?]
I saw her singing
during practice...
She was singing honestly.
I said she needed her color
and to be more unique.
She just expressed it
in a wrong way.
That came out first because
she was thinking on what I said.
And her honesty hid behind that.
I think that was the case.
Every time I see her I think,
"She can do better than that."
But Jang Hanna...
When will she unleash it?
I'm losing my temper.
[She did her best but her commentary
leaves much to be desired]
[Who will take first place
and who will be eliminated?]
Will the others join
her on stage?
[Their paths will separate when
the judges finish their discussion!]
[It's hard for them to
reach a conclusion...]
Production crew!
[They suddenly call the
production crew]
[Why is the discussion
getting longer?]
[They're talking about
something seriously!]
[The serious discussion is over]
[YG sits down with
a long face]
[What is the result of
the discussion?]
The discussion ran long.
We three judges had
conflicting opinions.
In Season 3...
It's no exaggeration to say that
this is an unprecedented situation.
We have a shocking result.
Unfortunately...
Today's 1st place is...
No one.
[Does that mean that
they're all eliminated?]
That means none of you met or
went beyond our expectations.
We had another concern.
Who should take 3rd place?
Who should be eliminated?
It was hard to decide on 3rd place
because you were all similar.
Today's 3rd place is...
No one.
[There's no 3rd place?]
[What does this mean?]
We decided that all of you
should have a rematch.
[An unprecedented situation
with no 1st or 3rd place!]
I can't congratulate you
or say that I'm upset.
As you leave the stage,
give this a lot of thought.
You can't do it
like this again.
Just think that
you're eliminated.
Think that you're eliminated
and just enjoy yourselves.
Think that you're going to
show something and go home.
You need this mindset, "Elimination is
fine, but I'm going to show something."
Go and get ready.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[They're shocked as
they leave the stage]
It would have been okay if I did it
like how I did during the rehearsal.
[It doesn't look like her
long day is over yet!]
We kept in mind on the things
pointed out and made this song.
But it was pointed out even more.
I'm at a loss.
It's complicated.
[All three teams enter the
2nd place waiting room!]
[The rematch will be
something to watch!]
[What will be the final outcome
of the battle audition?]
Let's start the 5th battle.
Heejun Han from YG.
I'm burdened with all of them.
Feels like my head will explode.
Brody B from JYP.
Peter Han from Antenna Music.
Heejun's really good. He's a
singer but I'm an amateur.
I don't know...
Please enter the stage.
[Brody's extreme makeover!]
They're different
as night and day.
This is just...
[Battle between the best
looking from the 3 agencies]
You look cool and pretty.
[Who will advance
to the TOP10?]
[Awkward]
The peculiar thing about this
group is that they're from abroad.
Heejun is a former
American Idol finalist.
Brody came from the US
and stole our hearts.
And Peter Han is from Austria.
Their music genre is also completely
different. I can't imagine what...
Especially Brody. I can't even
guess what she's going to do.
I see that it's a secret.
[It's a secret!]
I think it's best for us to talk
after watching their performance.
Antenna Music's Peter Han
will be going first.
- He's good-looking.
- He sure is.
- Don't girls like that face?
- Absolutely!
Wow... a Fender amp and guitar...
[A setting rousing anticipation!]
Peter could become a jazz singer like
Michael Buble which is rare in Korea.
So we focused on that.
He was always complimented on that
but never did such a performance.
I'm singing John Park's
"This Ain't It."
You Hee-yeol told me to sing
the jazz I always wanted to.
So I'm doing a jazz standard.
[Battle audition
T-minus 12 days]
[One-on-one training with
Kim Yeon-woo and ALi]
This is how you sing.
[He sings so it'll be easier
for him to understand]
[Diligently]
[Serious]
- This is how you're singing.
- This is not speaking...
[He's motivated before
the gods of vocals!]
Do it like this or
do it like that.
- Wow! You improved.
- Ain't I something?
[The next day]
[Even planning every minute
detail of stage directing!]
You'll put on a black suit
with a skinny tie.
- Oh! A suit!
- He's loving it!
I love it.
It'll be like Frank Sinatra.
You Hee-yeol said I'm always clean-cut
so I have to show my talents.
I'm finally able to show off
jazz sentiments.
There are high notes and
even a guitar solo.
I will show off my talents.
This is a Peter Han concert.
Melt us audience thinking that
you will throw a strong blow.
We'll give you a warm hand
before you begin.
[Peter is on the rise with
compliments one after another!]
[Will he be praised for jazz,
an unfamiliar genre?]
[This Ain't It - John Park]
[His mid-lows carry weight
yet they are subtle]
[His unique timbre stands
out in the high notes]
[Overflowing with groove
during the guitar solo]
[A traditional jazz performance
for the first time on KPOP STAR]
[What are the judges'
commentaries?]
Your high notes are open now.
You gained a lot with that alone.
As JYP said, you were able to sing the
high notes after coming on this show.
It's completely open.
[He has now mastered
the high notes]
It's completely open but all
the high notes sound the same.
I thought it would be better
if there were some dynamics.
It's like this.
You have to be a seasoned
jazz singer to sing this well.
You have to keep on
singing such songs.
And when it's fully ripened, only
then can you sing this genre.
You just learned vocalization
for the first time here.
It's impossible for you to sing
such a song with dynamics.
You were nervous, right?
I could feel it from here.
I like it when you sing but
also when you play the guitar.
Me too.
Maybe it's influence from your
parents that you can play like this...
Musical nourishment is overflowing
both within your body and soul.
That point alone shows you have
potential to be a great musician.
I applaud you.
[He received both harsh
advice and compliments]
[The next contestant has
a lot on his shoulders]
Next is YG's Heejun Han.
[He's nervous and gulps
down the water]
Kim Bum-soo's "Passing"?
Yes, I personally like this song.
I'm more excited than them because
I wrote this for Kim Bum-soo.
- Really?
- You wrote it?
Yes.
Then I shouldn't have
let him sing this.
I told him to do it without
knowing it was JYP's song.
It's time for us to check
how good this song is.
You heard this a lot
from us that...
You're good like a professional
but we don't know your true color.
Did you find it at YGE?
Let's get into the real problem.
[This was pointed out
since Round 1!]
[He's singing without knowing
what his emotions are?]
Despite the fact that you sing well,
I would like to ask, "Who are you?"
[During YG's mid-evaluation]
You're not thinking about the lyrics
and just singing. There's no heart.
We all know that you're good.
You have to convey your heart now.
[He was asked to put
sincerity into singing]
It's really hard...
Sincerity...
I didn't know it was this hard.
Singing well is not enough.
I have to touch the heart
but that is...
The hardest thing was that
people misunderstood me.
I did my best on every stage
but people say I calculated it.
For example, my lips are quivering
and I'm really nervous but...
I couldn't understand when they said,
"Why are you pretending to be nervous?"
It was hard that there was
no rock to hide under.
To answer YG's question
of "Who are you?"...
I went to where I was born.
I was born in Anyang.
It was Seoksu-dong, Anyang.
The house isn't there anymore.
I went around and visited
the video store I frequented.
I called my mom to confirm if
the places I went to were correct.
I was touched, I don't know why,
and I felt warm inside.
I felt freedom from all my exhaustion
in a city I haven't visited in decades.
It seems I did exaggerate because
I tried to sing what I didn't experience.
So I thought about what song
would fit my circumstances.
There was a song called "Passing"
and I listened to the lyrics.
It really came to me.
"This pain will pass. How much more
do I need to cry for that bright day."
It fit my circumstances.
Since it perfectly explains my situation,
I think my sincerity will exude from it.
[He's more nervous than ever]
[Can his sincerity move
the judges' heart?]
[Passing - Kim Bum-soo]
[How hard must it be and]
[How much do I need to cry]
[For me to smile again]
[It'll pass]
[This pain will end]
[He put all his energy
and sang passionately]
[They lavish him with applause]
[But JYP is unable to speak]
The first thought I had
when I listened is...
I want to give him a song.
[The best compliment a
producer can give!]
I never had that thought until now.
I just thought you were good
and a pro in auditions.
Since you have experience from the
more competitive American Idol...
I'm sorry to say this,
but I was biased.
But for the first time today,
when you sang the first measure...
You have a tone that is
suitable for ballads.
So I thought how well you'll
act if a song is given.
Actors act with expression whereas
singers act with their voice.
You act very well.
I know what these lyrics
are trying to say.
It was good.
[He's slowly realizing how
to sing with his heart]
I...
I can't hide my expression
when I like something.
When you sang the first measure...
I wasn't unresponsive
because it was bad.
I suddenly had the chills and
couldn't move until it was over.
It was as if you were speaking.
I was really sick and had a bad
fever when I wrote this song.
I was in the US and
it was snowing outside.
You know how you feel sad
when you're really sick...
I endured with that one thought,
"I will get better from this cold."
That's when I wrote this.
I started thinking about that time
when I was sick and writing this.
I was immersed and couldn't move
as if I went back to that time.
It was an amazing performance
since I couldn't judge properly.
For the first time, you didn't
sing to try to look good.
It was as if you were telling
your story. You spat it out.
I really enjoyed it
and it was moving.
Thank you.
[And YG's commentary?]
Now I know who you are.
I thought you shined the most in
this performance than any other.
I feel proud as a producer
and judge. Good job.
[His compliment was short but
it was much more meaningful]
["Sincerity" is what he
wanted to hear the most]
[He feels as if all those times
were being compensated]
Next up is Brody.
[JYP's Brody (11)]
I look forward to
what she'll do.
She'll either sink or swim.
JYP must have given
much thought.
[A smile of satisfaction?]
[What is their fate in this
intense battle audition?]
Subtitles by SBS International