We're afraid since we don't
know when we'll be eliminated.
The women's accomodation
started out with 10 people.
Everyone left and only
Ji-hoon and I are left.
As we see the
people leaving...
We feel sad...
I could get eliminated
next week...
Only outstanding contestants
remain in the TOP6.
Now they can't make even
the smallest mistake.
We, the judges, are
even more nervous.
This is the final round
for the 1:1 battle.
You will choose a ball and the
opponent's name will be on it.
[Akdong Musician goes first.
Who will be their opponent?]
What do we do, huh?
[A strong opponent - voice that
moves the heart, Shin Ji-hoon]
- It's Shin Ji-hoon...
- Can we choose again?
Shin Ji-hoon?
Let's go tell her
the sad news.
[It's hard for them to go
to the room where she is]
You've got to be
kidding! No way!
Tell me it isn't
so! This can't be!
We're the only girls left
and we have to compete?
[All they have is a deep sigh
Akdong Musician vs Shin Ji-hoon]
[Meanwhile in
2,000 won's room]
- I hope it isn't Ye-dam.
- We have to go home if it's him.
[3 balls remain - Raccoon Boys,
Bang Ye-dam, and Andrew Choi]
[Please not Bang Ye-dam]
- Can we try again?
- Yes, you can.
- Again. This is Ye-dam.
- It's Ye-dam?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
[Please let it not
be Bang Ye-dam...]
It's him, right?
It's Bang Ye-dam?
[Kim Il-do checks it]
You're no help at all!
I said to just
go with that!
What is this?
[They're up against him again
after the first live broadcast]
[What are they doing?]
[Please save us]
We love you,
Ye-dam.
- What? Why are you here?
- Ye-dam...
[They're like brothers to him,
but he's battling them again]
It's over for me.
[Raccoon Boys are
battling who?]
Andrew!
[Raccoon Boys vs Andrew Choi]
We won't let him
beat us easily.
We're going to give
him a hard time.
[Raccoon Boys came
to tease 2,000 won]
What's with the mood here?
Win, Ye-dam.
Go easy on them.
[Andrew Choi vs Raccoon Boys]
[Shin Ji-hoon vs Akdong Musician]
[2,000 won vs Bang Ye-dam]
[Who will be the victor
from the TOP6?]
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2!
This is the TOP6 battle
and the last 1:1 round!
I will announce
the opponents!
First is Andrew Choi
and Raccoon Boys!
It's a battle between the best
voice and best harmony.
Next is 2,000 won
and Bang Ye-dam!
They are the only teams
having a rematch.
We look forward to it.
Next is Shin Ji-hoon
and Akdong Musician!
A voice that moves the heart, and
own songs that move the heart.
This battle won't be easy.
Another round of applause for
our finalists that will battle!
Hi, I'm the MC, Yoon Do-hyun,
for KPOP STAR Season 2.
The TOP6 finalists were decided
last week after a fierce battle.
The TOP6 finalists will have
another 1:1 battle today.
The winners will go to TOP5 and the
losers are in danger of elimination.
After the battles are over,
one will get eliminated.
Of the three teams that are
candidates for elimination...
One with the viewers' votes and one
with the judges' wildcard will pass.
It's hard to predict who
will be in the TOP5.
We look forward
to their battles.
Other than their battles, we have
a very special performance today.
There will be a comeback stage
by Lee Hi, last year's runner-up.
Don't miss that!
I'll introduce the judges that
will determine the TOP6's fate.
BoA of SM!
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
They're looking sharp.
- JYP?
- Yes?
This is the last 1:1 battle.
Which team do you
anticipate the most?
I think the most fun
will be the rematch.
2,000 won and Bang Ye-dam.
Since they know each other's strong
and weak points, I look forward to it.
I anticipate 2,000 won to
play a great return match.
I see. We request a fair
and careful judgment.
I will announce the order
and the finalists' number.
1st battle is sweet voice
No. 1 Andrew Choi...
And beautiful harmony
No. 2 Raccoon Boys!
2nd battle is voice that moves
the heart, No. 3 Shin Ji-hoon...
And charming sibling duo,
No. 4 Akdong Musician!
Last battle is the talented best
friend duo, No. 5 2,000 won...
And the youngest TOP6 finalist,
12-year-old No. 6 Bang Ye-dam!
Unpredictable battles
are waiting for us.
As much as their skills, your
votes are very important.
Boom will explain the
voting system in detail.
Hi everyone, I'm Boom!
Give me a shout!
Glad to see you!
I'm KPOP STAR
Season 2's MC, Boom!
Your votes are
very important.
TOP5 finalists are
decided by your votes.
To make it fair, voting is
possible only during battles.
I'll explain the
voting system.
Turn on your cellphone and text #0606
with their Korean name or number.
Understand?
It's easy, but keep
one thing in mind.
You can place your votes
for more than one person.
But you can't place multiple
votes for one person.
Going beyond being KPOP
STAR's TOP5 finalist...
You, the viewers, will make
them into a great singer.
We'll start the first battle.
Do you want to see it?
Actually, this is the finals. An
amazing stage is waiting for us.
First, it's charming guy
Andrew Choi...
And three cute boys that are
challenging him, Raccoon Boys!
Are you curious?
Are you?
No need to wait.
Let's meet them now!
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan
[Andrew Choi vs Raccoon Boys]
This will be worth watching.
I think it will be the
most tense battle.
[Raccoon Boys vs Andrew Choi]
I was surprised because
they're a strong team.
We're afraid of consistent
contestants that are good.
We're worried that
we're up against him.
He always shows
something new.
He's a good dancer.
- He also proposed.
- I know...
[Last week's broadcast]
[Andrew's moving proposal]
- Hurry and get married!
- I'm only 23!
I have to get
discharged first.
[TOP6 Battle - D-4]
[Andrew's absorbed
in practicing]
[Who is that peeking?]
He doesn't know
I'm here, right?
I packed lunch to
surprise him.
[Surprised]
I was surprised. I felt
great and was happy.
[Lunch prepared
by his girlfriend!]
[Into his mouth]
I like you most
when you eat.
Many women, when they are proposed
to, want to capture it on film or photo.
It gives me strength
since I can see you.
To show my love for her, I'm
singing 10 cm's "I'm Dying".
[I'm Dying - 10 cm]
No. 1 Andrew Choi expressed
it more sweetly as an R&B.
After we became a team, we
only heard good things...
[But]
[Last week,first
shocking defeat!]
We were faltering, but...
It's not because we lost.
I was disappointed in myself.
We're in a crisis...
I'm worried that maybe
they fell into a slump.
They have to show that they
are taking that leap again.
During the 1st and 2nd round
of the live broadcast...
We didn't really arrange
much in our own style.
We changed the
melody a lot.
We're confident
this time.
[Wonder Girls - "So Hot"]
I have an idea.
We're inside this
box... a toy box.
The men fall for beautiful
women in the original.
But we changed the
order around...
[Shy]
Our concept is girls going
crazy over us pretty boys.
Your mother sent this.
Really? My mom?
Wow! What's this?
"Seasoned raw blue crabs.
Min-suk's favorite."
Wow! I love this!
I spent the past
six months in Korea.
I really miss my mom's
home cooking.
[Chan-hyuk gets a bite]
This is good!
We'll eat this
and do well.
Love you, mom!
We'll show you how much we
improved and our hot charms.
Raccoon Boys!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
[So Hot - Wonder Girls]
I'm open-minded
All the girls swim
I'm always a cool guy
I'm their support
Whatever I wear becomes a pictorial
Everyone blocks my way
I'm sick of this!
Why was I born like this?
Every time I walk outside
Fans follow around
Girls' reaction when they see me
Hot Hottie Hot Hottie Hot
I might shine too much when I walk
So I purposely cover myself
I might become a thief if I don't
Stealing my glance every night
No. 2 Raccoon Boys really
showed off their colors.
We just watched Andrew Choi
and Raccoon Boys battle.
I really enjoyed
them both.
I'm really curious what
the judges thought of it.
Let's hear the commentary.
I'll start with Andrew Choi.
Are you really the Andrew
I know? Today...
High notes were open, groove
was great, even the gestures.
You were always stiff, but...
You were comfortable and was
like the happiest man on Earth.
I want a boyfriend
who sings like you.
Since the live broadcast began,
Raccoon Boys started slowing down.
Today, you seemed
a little comfortable.
Your teamwork is always good.
But choreography was good today.
But you always lack 2%.
I don't know what that is.
I wanted to get excited, and the
moves and looks were exciting.
I felt your voices
couldn't keep up.
But Brian and McKay's high
notes were stable than last week.
I enjoyed it.
That was BoA's
commentary.
Let's hear the next.
I'm not a fortune-teller, but I
never anticipated Andrew Choi.
To be honest, I never knew
you'd make it this far.
BoA said it well. You can't
ignore age and experience.
I could see you
steadily rising.
You proposed last week, and
I told you to write to her.
"I love you to death just seeing
you." It's the main lyric.
I really envy you.
But they only pack
lunch before marriage.
It's over when you're married.
What are you getting at? You
should be giving a commentary.
Anyways... Raccoon Boys.
Last week, I said it seemed you
only hit to 1st or 2nd base.
This team has a good combination
since each member is different.
But the problem is that your
individuality doesn't stand out.
Combination should be good and
your individuality should stand out.
You started to lose that,
and just as BoA said...
It seems something more would
come out with those skills.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
That was YG's
commentary.
Next is JYP.
I was distressed as I
left home because...
I have to say the same
thing after Andrew sings.
"It's a pity. You sing well,
but press your throat."
It's a burden when I leave home
since I say this every week.
But for the first time, he was
open and sang with his body.
What just happened?
When we practiced, the
only thing you did was...
To be relaxed and move
your body while singing.
You were relaxed and was moving
when you started today.
I thought, "Is he?" You were
open and sang in a soulful voice.
I wish for nothing more since
I heard it. I really enjoyed it.
But Raccoon Boys, I feel
the same as the two judges.
I was just talking about
the body. You were stiff.
You wore suits and had a
hard look from the start.
Your body has to assimilate with the
music when it starts, but it was stiff.
Maybe that had some
relation. I enjoyed it.
Last year, JYP talked about
half breath and half sound.
Second was his
shoulder theory.
When the viewers
saw them today...
Andrew was the most comfortable
and his shoulders were limp.
As JYP pointed out, Raccoon Boys
were stiff. You were trying to do well.
This is advice for
the next stage.
Thank you very much.
That was a generous
commentary.
Andrew got some good
commentaries.
Raccoon Boys as well,
but they lacked 2%.
Please announce
who the victor is.
- I'll go first...
- It's JYP.
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
Andrew Choi who unclogged
what was stuck in here.
Congratulations!
JYP chose him.
He did sing comfortably.
Let's hear the next.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
- Andrew Choi who I envy.
- Congratulations!
He's now in the TOP5!
This is unexpected.
Unfortunately, Raccoon Boys
lost, but it's not over.
We need to hear
BoA's choice too.
I'll make the
announcement.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
Everyone already knows.
It's Andrew Choi.
He makes it to
TOP5 unanimously!
Congratulations!
Raccoon Boys put on a great
stage but unfortunately lost.
But it's not over. Your votes
are even more important.
Those that are cheering for
them, please send in your votes.
They're No. 2 Raccoon Boys.
Now we have the 2nd battle.
It'll be worth watching.
I think it will be
today's big match.
I'll tell you
who they are.
The battle between Shin Ji-hoon
and Akdong Musician starts now!
[Shin Ji-hoon vs Akdong Musician]
[Following morning
after live broadcast]
[It's time for the
defeated to leave]
Do well. Don't
leave like us.
Everyone's packing their
bags. Now it's real.
It's so empty.
The women's accomodation
started out with ten people.
Eight dropped out within three
weeks, and ten became two.
We'll stay together.
Together, we'll make
it to the end.
We wanted to stay together
since we feel lonely.
We wrote our
diaries together.
We do our nails
when we're bored.
Now the men's accomodation
should be wiped out.
That's what we said...
Soo-hyun, how can
you pick me?
I hate this!
[They only sigh...]
How did this happen?
[Akdong Musician vs Shin Ji-hoon]
A battle of geniuses.
Shin Ji-hoon is in
another crisis.
Akdong Musician are like pros,
sing well, and are popular.
It's like they are emitting
this terrifying aura.
I'm afraid and worried.
The look the judges had when
we sang our very first two songs...
They had that look for
Ji-hoon this round.
Even I get the chills when she
goes that high without a hitch.
We're going to
be compared.
Shin Ji-hoon returned.
Now it's time to
show their skills.
I'm singing Secret Garden's
"You Raise Me Up".
This is a famous song and I'm
worried of getting compared.
Soo-hyun is cute, pretty,
bubbly and lively.
I'm singing a song where I
have to convey sensibility.
I might have a chance of winning
if I'm true to my feelings.
[You Raise Me Up - Secret Garden]
Thank you.
No. 3 Shin Ji-hoon, her faint
voice touched our hearts.
What do we do, huh?
- Shin Ji-hoon... her?
- Can we pick again?
Shin Ji-hoon!
We wanted to avoid
Ye-dam and Ji-hoon.
We had a hard time
when that happened.
We were frustrated after
we came to our senses.
[Frustration]
[Special time to go out
for our frustrated lambs]
What do I do?
- Wow!
- It's huge!
[She's excited like
a fish in water]
I now realize that
she's a figure skater.
I think I could
do it too.
[He takes the
challenge]
[His rhythm is somewhat
perfect on ice]
- OMG!
- Oh, no!
[He doesn't give up
and even jumps!]
[Ta-da]
Wow! Thank you!
I forgot how
ramen tasted.
[No time to talk!]
It's really good!
[Snacks were prohibited for
2 months to stay in condition]
[Seems like she's going
to eat the pot too!]
Let's both make it to prevent
our room from being empty.
Let's do it!
We're going to sing
our song, "Crescendo".
When my brother was
going through puberty...
When he fought or had a hard time,
he was timid and didn't speak.
He always kept
it to himself.
This song has a message
for the youth that...
They can overcome and
speak their mind.
[Why did you choose
your song?]
They wanted us to do
it, so we chose it.
That is our only
advantage.
My dream is to make
all kinds of music.
Our concept this time
is to be like an idol.
This stage would be closest
to what KPOP STAR is.
Every good response they got
was for their own songs.
I hope they release their
potential with their song.
Crescendo is a musical term
meaning a gradual increase.
I hope our confidence and voice
increase gradually on stage.
Akdong, let's go
to TOP5! Yeah!
[Crescendo - own song]
My voice is getting lost
My breathing gets louder
No one listens to my words
It's rising in crescendo
Raise your voice. High
Notice me. Hi
Catch my voice
Catch it tightly, Oh hey
Squeeze through that gap
That pain that made you small
Shout toward the sky
That shines on you
For everyone to notice me
Crescendo
To understand me
My voice reaches the skies
Until the clouds hear and understand
My wish at sunset and early morning
Or about my love that dragged on
Start talking, that's what we're hoping
Don't give up without starting
The dream deep down in your heart
Thanks, today's weather is joy
Whether there or not, pull up your chin
Play like kids, la-ti-do-re-mi-fa
Melody rises, follow the fast tempo
Laugh aloud, hahahahaha, hahahahaha
For everyone to notice me
Crescendo
To understand me
For everyone to notice me
Crescendo
To understand me
No. 4 Akdong Musician showed
a new charm with their song.
It was a battle between teams
with different personalities.
What did the judges think?
Let's hear the commentary.
There's a good song
and a hit song.
Some songs are popular, but fall
short on individuality and quality.
While others are not, but have
individuality and quality.
But Akdong Musician's
"Crescendo" got both.
The chord progression you
used is a very popular form.
But the melody and lyrics had
character. The melody was great.
It was a perfect song.
The difference between this and
your other songs? This is popular.
Even the stage and choreography
were great. It was perfect.
That was a good
commentary.
Ji-hoon, you sang well, but
why didn't it touch me?
Who was the "you" in the song?
Who did you think about?
Religion or friend? Who is this
"you"? Did you think about it?
- My mom...
- Your mom?
Was it Kim Soo-hwan last year
who sang "It's Fortunate"?
I knew he had a girlfriend when he
sang the first two lines, so I asked him.
But when you sang, it didn't seem
like you were thinking about "you".
Maybe you weren't focused because
you were trying to sing well.
Thank you very much.
Next is BoA.
Park Ji-min sang this
song last year.
I believe she was 16
as well last year.
The difference between
her and you is skill.
You have a clear, ringing
voice and singing is clean.
But you need skill to push
and pull people's hearts...
Be expressive and sing a
wider genre of songs.
But today, you concentrated
too much on the high notes.
If that high note was a single
strong punch, it would move us.
But there were too many
of those high notes.
I once thought why Akdong
Musician's songs are popular.
So I listened to all
of your songs again.
The emotions people
your age feel were...
Expressed cleverly and from
a different perspective.
That's why many people
can relate to the songs.
"Crescendo" has a very
hopeful message.
You're small but want to be big.
It was expressed in a fun way.
The melody and choreography
were great like what JYP said.
I personally think Chan-hyuk
is cute and cool when rapping.
Chan-hyuk's rapping voice and
Soo-hyun's beautiful voice...
The combination of your voices
was great. I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, we have YG.
Shin Ji-hoon failed in her choice
of song and plan because...
Park Ji-min left a great
impression for this song.
It's true you lack in technique
and voice to catch up to her.
As a KPOP STAR judge, I have to
evaluate the contestant's skills.
But JYP and I are also producers.
In the case of you and Bang Ye-dam...
It's a problem that we think about you
in a year or two and not just now.
You sang well, but I had expectations
since you sang really well last week.
I want to be honest
with Akdong Musician.
When I first saw you,
I liked Lee Soo-hyun.
Your voice has character like a
French girl singing "chanson".
Although they're siblings, I thought
of debuting only Lee Soo-hyun.
- To be honest...
- You're really honest.
Chan-hyuk looked dark, depressed,
and couldn't adjust to society.
Chan-hyuk, I like you.
For real. I really do.
The amazing thing is that I could
see him rise with the times.
He looks depressed, but
did you see him today?
That talent... I'm always amazed
when I see him. He's great.
In the history of gayo, were
there any sibling singers?
Was it Hyun-yi and...
- Hyun-yi and Deok-yi.
- That was in the 70s.
Ryang-hyun and Ryang-ha
were brothers, right? Right.
I'm complimenting Akdong Musician.
There aren't characters like them.
Their songs are unique,
and like what JYP said...
They danced and sang well today.
It was impressive. Good job.
Thank you very much.
The commentary was very long.
It means they had a lot to say.
Please announce
the results.
I'll go first.
The victor chosen by SM,
I'll say it right away.
- It's Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
Please announce
the next victor.
The victor chosen by
YG is Akdong Musician.
Congratulations! They
advance to TOP5!
It's not over.
Let's hear JYP.
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
I said Akdong Musician's
stage was perfect today.
But I remembered one. The tune
for "ti-do-re-mi-fa" was wrong.
Other than that,
it was perfect.
- We also chose Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
They advance to TOP5.
Just because Shin Ji-hoon
lost, it's not over yet.
Please wait since she
has the viewers' votes.
Next battle is the rematch. It's
Bang Ye-dam and 2,000 won.
They'll start now!
[2,000 won vs Bang Ye-dam]
Who is your opponent?
It's KPOP STAR's
Grim Reaper.
He's Mr. Bang.
[They want to forget the
time they picked the ball]
You're no help!
It's 2,000 won and
Bang Ye-dam again.
[A cruel trick by Fate?]
The one with potential and
the ones that help that.
God gives us as much
pain as we can handle.
That pain is starting.
We're on a cliff
every round.
But we don't know how it'll turn out.
Our expectations for Ye-dam is rising.
We didn't expect much, but 2,000 won
continues putting on a great stage.
If they put on a really
exciting, splendid stage...
I believe they
have a chance.
Despite the good comments, we want
to show an enjoyable, playful stage.
We chose this song.
[Legendary rock group, Sanullim,
released this children song in 1978]
We received many harsh
criticisms until now.
We turned that into a
"committed a crime" concept.
That concept came out from getting
out of the harsh criticisms quickly.
Since we passed by receiving
the most viewers' votes...
We want to repay that
love given to us.
We want to show that your
votes weren't in vain.
What if we're candidates
for elimination again?
We're in trouble.
Hope it won't.
[No. 5 2,000 won]
I wanted to do well
Didn't know how to enjoy
I was tenacious
So our crime is this
Growth plates closed
[Rascal - Sanullim]
Arrows of elimination aimed at me
Most likely to be eliminated
That mark follows me
It's not gone like a zit
Bounce back up like a roly poly
Rap and play and it's already 12
I'm excited on stage like a child
I shine because I enjoy
It's not the stage lights
What's the problem? Feel it
I'm old but still a rascal
My dream is XL. Keep on running
I'm a rascal who runs nonstop.
I just enjoy. I don't care
Switch all eyes on manner mode
Play hard before it gets late
Light up the passion and fire
Ladies and Gentlemen
Why don't we have fun?
Why don't we play?
Forget studying
No. 5 2,000 won really had a
fun time with the audience.
[Two consecutive wins!]
[Bang Ye-dam - youngest contestant
and the strongest opponent!]
How does he do that when
he's usually goofing off?
He's always in someone else's
practice room and not his.
But he's good on stage.
We get surprised.
That's his plan.
[He forgot what to say due to
the ridiculous assumption]
Most of the time, I usually
write something by myself, but...
But I am practicing!
[He's enjoying the music, but
others think he's goofing off]
I'm going to sing
Rain's "I Do".
[Rain's ad-lib and romantic
voice stands out in this song]
He'll do this well.
Whatever song he sings,
he does it flawlessly.
I'm excited as a composer how
he's going to change my songs.
I want to think much
about the performance.
[Performance by Ye-dam]
I want to challenge
myself in rapping
[Rap by Ye-dam]
I'll practice hard
on the harmonica.
[Harmonica by Ye-dam]
I want to do well.
I video chatted with
my dad for advice.
- Hi.
- Hi, dad.
What are you singing?
Rain's "I Do".
This song is in a
medium tempo.
It's really hard.
You might sing faster.
You have to think.
Don't get fast.
Never. Okay?
- You can do it!
- Bye, dad.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- You can do it!
- I'll try hard.
I don't know if I could
sing well like Rain.
I'll practice hard on the
harmonica, rap, and dance...
I'll try hard to
show you my style.
[No. 6 Bang Ye-dam]
[I Do - Rain]
Don't tease me. Even a kid like me
Can protect you even though I'm young
Age doesn't matter. I'm a man
I do. My heart is beating, oh my
Baby, baby, baby, oh like
I'm wild but still a child
But compared to others
I'm very, very kind to you
Multi-talented Bang Ye-dam
became little Rain today.
That stage was by
No. 6 Bang Ye-dam.
The results of their
match are unpredictable.
What did the judges think?
Let's hear the commentary.
I'll make this short because the
previous commentary was long.
2,000 won's stage
was very good.
You called yourselves "potential
helpers" and faced Ye-dam again.
I saw you giving your all.
In Bang Ye-dam's case...
I'll do both at the same time.
I can see 2,000 won
trying very hard.
Bang Ye-dam doesn't try,
but I see him enjoying.
There's a well-known saying.
"The one who tries can't win
against the one who enjoys."
Bang Ye-dam is much
younger than 2,000 won.
2,000 won's stage was great
today and last week.
Compared to 2,000 won, I think
Ye-dam is the one who truly enjoys.
- Good job.
- Thank you very much.
Next is JYP.
For the first time I thought
Ye-dam won't meet expectations.
He was tense, tempo
was getting fast...
And he squeezed his voice. I
thought, "What's wrong with him?"
But after rapping,
he was relaxed.
Then he was his usual self - singing,
dancing, and everything. It was good.
Did someone make that harmonica
line or did you just play it?
I made it together with
the music director.
I don't know if you did
it yourself or not, but...
The highest I think was a seventh.
It's uncomfortable to play that.
I don't know how you do that.
You don't have music education.
It's frightening
when I see that.
2,000 won's stage was
exciting and splendid.
One thing worries me. Does Il-do
have something other rappers don't?
Whether it be flow or voice.
You were great, but...
Do you have a different voice or
color compared to exisiting singers?
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Next is BoA.
I personally didn't like
both performances.
I expected a lot from 2,000 won
since they are rising right now.
Ye-dam always did well so maybe
my expectations were too high.
For Ye-dam, it was great
up to the harmonica playing.
But when you started singing,
the tunes were all wrong.
I felt uneasy. Only the
rap part was good.
Rhyming "I do, I know, oh my" was
great, but overall it was unstable.
For 2,000 won, Hyo-bin was unstable.
Although you were stable later on.
How should I put it? Both of
you were ahead of yourselves.
But that didn't reach us.
I'll make my decision on
who did better. I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
It's unpredictable.
Bang Ye-dam won in
the previous rematch.
Please announce who
is the victor today.
I'll start with the
announcement.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
- 2,000 won.
- Congratulations!
They are victors
chosen by SM.
Please announce
the next victor.
It's hard to decide maybe
because it's the last round.
But I just made my
decision a while ago.
I chose the one who
knows how to enjoy.
- It's Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
It's neck and neck.
I'm getting nervous.
I think it's because
it's a rematch.
JYP's choice will
decide everything.
It wasn't hard to choose
because they were good.
But they didn't meet our
expectations as BoA said.
My standard was whether
they had their own color.
- JYP chooses Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He advances to TOP5!
It was a tense moment.
It's not over for 2,000 won.
They have the viewers' votes.
Please vote in the
remaining one minute.
All the battles are finished, and
we're waiting for the final result.
Before we hear the result,
there's a special performance.
There will be a comeback stage
by last year's runner-up, Lee Hi.
Such a big hand.
Those who cheered for her last
year will be filled with emotion.
Let's hear her new song that is
first revealed here on KPOP STAR!
[Lee Hi has a huge potential
to be a great singer - YG]
[It's Over - Lee Hi]
I enjoyed her performance.
I'm with the judges right now.
I'm really nervous because this
is where they give commentaries.
First, YG watched her
with a fatherly smile.
Can you tell us
how it was?
Since I saw the choreography
many times during practice...
It was awkward seeing
that here in a while.
Lee Hi lost a
lot of weight.
You might misunderstand me, but
I never told her to lose weight.
I thought she's very good
at taking care of herself.
Your looks told us
that it was perfect.
BoA, she's a junior singer
now because she debuted.
How was it, as a senior?
She was a contestant last year, but
she's like a singer on TV today.
It was amazing. She also
lost a lot of weight...
- She's pretty, right?
- Yes, she's pretty.
- You're also pretty.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
JYP, I'm curious.
Give a commentary
like last year.
Singing, visual, half
sound and half breath...
She was completely relaxed
and producing was great.
She's pretty and sings well. She
was a bit unnatural in her last song.
But now she's like
a real singer.
- Was she perfect?
- Flawless.
YG, I love your
commentaries.
You talked about kimchi stew
and it became a hot topic.
If you compare me, Boom, to
a stew, what would it be?
- Mixed stew?
- Thank you.
That was simple.
This is how you can debut as
soon as you win on KPOP STAR.
The results are in.
Are you curious?
Why don't we see
the final result?
[TOP6 Final Result]
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
After a fierce battle...
Andrew Choi, Akdong Musician, and
Bang Ye-dam advanced to TOP5.
Unfortunately, next to me are
Raccoon Boys, Shin Ji-hoon...
And 2,000 won. They are
candidates for elimination.
Of the three, one with viewers' votes
and one with judges' wildcard will pass.
Who among the three
will advance to TOP5?
I have the voting results and
will announce the highest.
I will now announce the TOP5
finalist chosen by the viewers.
The TOP5 finalist chosen
by the viewers is...
2,000 won!
Congratulations!
It's so hard
to say it.
They got the highest
votes from the viewers.
2,000 won dramatically survived.
How do you feel right now?
Since this is our second time
passing with the votes...
We feel sorry, and we made it
to TOP5 without beating anyone.
We should win at least once.
We love you and thank you.
Another round of applause, and
please join the others over there.
Only Raccoon Boys and
Shin Ji-hoon remain.
Please move here...
Only one will pass with
the judges' wildcard.
And the other will say
farewell to KPOP STAR.
The judges are troubled since
this is an important moment.
They are discussing who will pass.
Seems like they haven't decided yet.
How do you feel?
Did you get it? He's nervous
and Shin Ji-hoon did well.
Still deciding?
Shin Ji-hoon?
You must be nervous...
Seems like they decided.
- We're done deciding.
- Now the announcement.
It was hard since we never
expected them to be here.
Raccoon Boys pleased our eyes
and ears starting with "Thriller".
Shin Ji-hoon always put on a
good stage starting with "Ben".
Shin Ji-hoon actually
applied for dancing.
But I believe many were pleased
to see you improve each stage.
I believe many also liked Raccoon
Boys' witty lyrics and stage.
We chose the one we
want to see again.
Please make the
announcement.
The last TOP5
finalist is...
- Raccoon Boys.
- Congratulations!
They dramatically passed!
Unfortunately, Shin Ji-hoon
was eliminated; didn't make it.
Her friends are encouraging her
and she can't stop the tears.
Shin Ji-hoon?
A big hand for Shin Ji-hoon
who made it this far.
Unfortunately, she will say
farewell with this stage.
If you have any last
words, please say them.
I thank the judges for picking
me after I was eliminated.
I'm crying again.
This stage is over, but you
will have plenty in the future.
Another big hand for her.
Any advice for her
from the judges?
JYP?
She applied for dancing. In
other words, she never sang.
With that wonderful voice, an
open voice you're born with...
Take this chance to get singing
lessons, and practice...
Then you will be
a great singer.
- That's right.
- You can do it!
Cheer up.
Shin Ji-hoon is eliminated, and
the TOP5 will battle next week.
They will battle to be casted
by the three agencies.
Please look forward to the exciting
stages to get casted by the agencies.
The fierce competition to be a
K-pop star continues next week!
See you next week!
Goodbye!