Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
Next up is Brody.
[JYP's Brody (11)]
I look forward to
what she'll do.
She'll either sink or swim.
[Heejun Han was just
complimented]
[It's apparent that she's nervous
as if more burden was placed]
JYP must have given
much thought.
[Every moment must have been a
challenge for JYP with Brody]
[What performance was prepared?]
[They automatically have fatherly
smiles just looking at her]
Hello.
I'm Brody the disco girl.
Please look forward to it.
[No one can keep up
with her cute charm]
[The judges fell for
her charms]
[What did Brody the
disco girl prepare?]
[JYPE Training Center]
[Off stage, Brody's a
naive 11-year-old]
[She's pretty good in Korean!]
[Diet?]
[Has no problem playing alone]
[She's always filled
with bright energy]
Brody definitely has
that star quality but...
It won't be easy for her to
compete in the TOP10 yet.
So I just want her to enjoy
while singing and dancing.
She might have a chance if her star qualities
are shown through her natural expressions.
[What is she singing?]
[Boney M's "Sunny" started
a disco craze in the 1970s]
[This song became well-known in
Korea due to a movie soundtrack]
[She has to sing and
dance this time]
No, that's wrong.
[The Lee sisters help Brody
since she's having a hard time]
[Thanks to them, she's
having fun practicing]
[Will her bright energy become
a dynamic force for the TOP10?]
[Her mother feels proud and
cheers her in her heart]
[Sunny - Boney M]
[She's composed and does
the moves flawlessly]
[She's getting into the
rhythm and enjoying it]
[She mesmerizes the judges with
her adorable expressions]
[She finishes with a cute move]
[How did the judges see it?]
[You Hee-yeol grabs
the mike first]
You were beautiful
and like an actress.
You were like a prodigy
who acts very well.
But it's time to be objective.
[The judging standards
are more strict]
You made remarkable progress...
But I couldn't hear
your singing.
I couldn't check your singing
skills with this performance.
[The commentaries are more objective
since they're choosing TOP10 finalists]
But the fact of your remarkable
progress during this time...
I, especially, learned a lot
from the contestants.
Brody, you did well.
I think I have more affection
for Brody than anyone else.
She was supposed
to be eliminated...
But I saved her
with a wildcard.
Her performance today
was a bit lacking.
Since she's young... I mean, it's
incredible she made it this far.
The song I was expecting
was different from this.
[This song wasn't enough?]
It would've been better if we were able to
hear her singing skills or her sincerity.
Today's performance
was just cute.
It didn't go beyond that
so it was a pity.
[What is JYP's commentary
since he trained her?]
I wanted her to experience a lot
and take on difficult challenges.
I wanted that to be a help when
she later becomes a star or singer.
The clothes, choreography,
singing, and everything...
I thought it would be better to
have these precious experiences.
I think I was able to see
a glimpse of her future self.
I gave you a difficult task...
But I was happy that you did well
with a joyful heart. Good job.
Will all three come
to the stage?
[Who will be the fourth
TOP10 finalist?]
I'll make the announcement.
I believe even the viewers already
anticipated who got 1st place.
It's the one all the judges
complimented on...
1st place is Heejun Han.
Congratulations.
You made it to the TOP10.
I really congratulate you.
You made it on American Idol and
you started over and made it again.
You're really something.
I applaud you.
[Announcing who's eliminated]
Unfortunately, the one we
won't be seeing again is...
I have to send off someone I liked
the most and had affection for...
[Brody made remarkable
progress in every round]
[Peter Han showed his potential
through plenty of hard work]
[Who will be eliminated?]
[Brody B is eliminated]
Say something in English.
She's about to cry.
[She tries to accept it calmly
like the coy princess she is]
[Congratulations on
a new beginning]
It's sad...
- YG can't speak.
- I can't.
Send her off now...
[We hope to see her again since this
is not the end but the beginning...]
[She gets emotional as soon
as she sees her mother...]
[After calming down...]
Alright, this is the last battle.
Our ace, Bernard Park from JYP.
Lee Chae-young from YG.
Heo Eun-yul from
Antenna Music.
Please enter the stage.
[The final seat for the TOP10!]
I was afraid of Bernard the most.
I'm having a mental breakdown
because I'm going against him.
I feel uneasy right now.
Bernard and Chae-young were
talked of as likely winners...
So I really wanted
to go home.
[A close match where
each fears the other]
I really wanted Bernard
to try on a suit.
- He looks good.
- Doesn't he?
And it's the first time
he raised his hair.
You look great.
What about you,
Eun-yul?
[Pfft]
You're Eun-yul?
[She completely transformed
that no one recognized]
First up is Lee Chae-young.
Would the two wait by the side?
She practiced the
longest at YGE.
She was with our choreographers
even until last night...
It must have been hard for her since
the moves changed last night, right?
Yes.
She'll be going against strong
contestants in the TOP10.
So I went the extra mile for her
and gave the most attention.
I tried so she can show
something better.
But that may have been a burden
to her since she's young.
The moves and everything changed
so I have to practice more...
[She arrives first and practices
until very late at night!]
I don't have a lot of energy compared
to others because I'm young.
But I think to myself that I have
to practice so that was hard.
[No matter how tough, she was
as determined as anyone!]
[Battle audition
T-minus 4 days]
[She arrives first again
and practices!]
[Who came to visit her?]
[Season 2 runner-up
YG trainee, Bang Ye-dam]
Hello.
[Startled]
[Blank]
[She's exhausted so
he came to cheer her!]
- I came to cheer you.
- Oh... thank you.
[Dumbfounded]
How old are you?
- I'm thirteen.
- Same here.
- Hi.
[They're 13-year-olds.
Boy meets girl?]
[Awkward]
What are you singing?
[Already asked...]
How old are you?
[Already answered...]
I'm thirteen.
So we're the same age.
[Why is Yedam more nervous?]
[He's just sipping his milk]
[They watch the clip when Yedam was
complimented for "I Want You Back"]
I'm in a good mood because
Bang Yedam came to cheer me.
I need to turn it
up a notch.
I felt grateful because YG personally
pointed out each and every move.
I would be practicing at home
if it wasn't for this show.
My dream will become clear
if I make it to the TOP10.
So I hope I make it in.
[Her parents cheer her ardently]
[I Want You Back - The Jackson 5]
[Will her dreams that she prepared
for the past 2 years come true?]
[She adeptly sings the
rhythmical high notes]
[She has a small frame but
moves freely on stage]
[She sang the difficult
high notes part]
Thank you.
[The others are in awe
at her performance]
[The judges watched her proudly]
[What is her commentary?]
Since your moves got changed
yesterday, that explains a lot.
You were thinking, "Where do I
move my foot and hand?"
You're just singing powerfully.
Your voice was at max volume.
You have to sing comfortably and
that was what made you look great.
You were perturbed. You faltered
and just sang powerfully.
I thought the key
was a bit high.
It was high for her.
In the middle where you sang
the high notes, it sounded flat.
[It would have been much better
if her high notes were stable]
But...
When we first saw you...
We focused on your dancing but
we see your singing improving.
If you can sing like that
in such a short period...
How will you sound
in a year or two?
Everyone must have thought of this,
"What was I doing when I was 13?"
I had a runny nose and was
playing marbles and pogs.
I didn't listen to music
or even understood it.
But she has an open voice
and can sing powerfully.
Technique and experience
are all she needs now.
We saw a lot of good things.
You did very well.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[She's still lacking but
also has potential]
[The next contestant is nervous
at the objective commentaries]
The second contestant makes
us to compare them...
It's Bernard Park from JYP.
The number one person the contestants
don't want to face is Bernard Park.
Second is Almeng and
third are the Shorties.
So it's Al, Ber, Shor.
[Bernard Park is a likely
winner and it's his turn]
[Those in the same group
are even more nervous!]
I asked those that came to Antenna Music
and the majority didn't want to face you.
I think you'll do really well so I said that to
get you conceited and make mistakes.
He's like the ace or goal getter
on the other team in soccer.
He has to be in a bad condition
for my team to win and move up.
Did you eat something bad
and have a stomachache?
I think I caught the cold.
Oh no... I was joking.
[You Hee-yeol was playing around
to make him feel relaxed]
But this song...
I really didn't expect this.
[What is it?]
Other songs would catch us off guard,
but this song goes beyond that...
I can't imagine this... Park Seung-hwa
is a member of Yurisangja.
It's Park Seung-hwa's
"I Love You."
I can't understand why
JYP chose this song.
When I trained Bernard,
TOP10 wasn't the goal.
He has to move the people
of Korea someday.
I wanted him to sing gayo
with gayo sentiments.
So I thought of the
most gayo song.
But...
I never heard of this song.
How am I supposed
to sing this?
R&B and pop songs don't have
the four steps. They just flow.
But gayo has the four steps and a
melody that explodes in the chorus.
Bernard will feel like
a fish out of water.
But this is a mountain
he needs to climb.
[He attempts a style
different from R&B!]
[He spent a lot of time in
understanding the lyrics...]
[Will his efforts show?]
[I Love You - Park Seung-hwa]
[He puts emotion into
each and every word...]
[He sings without using
any techniques]
[Unfamiliar style and sentiment]
[He overcomes another
hurdle today...]
[He finishes without mistakes]
[What are the judges'
commentaries?]
Should I go first?
[You Hee-yeol doesn't
look satisfied]
I...
I don't know if this is good or bad
but I see someone's strengths first.
[What is he trying to say?]
Then I see the weaknesses.
That's my style.
We all know your strengths and
complimented you a lot.
But I felt this for
the first time...
I was disappointed.
[That was unexpected
from You Hee-yeol!]
It felt like you were
like any other singer.
Until now, you sang clean
with standard tactics...
Then the techniques later on
were revealed through the song.
I'm not so sure when
I listened to this song.
I thought something would
happen later on.
I wasn't so sure since you
kept singing like that.
I thought, "What's going on? The
Bernard I know shines more than this."
I think it's better if you choose
a song with more emotion.
[Unexpected harsh criticism
from You Hee-yeol!]
[What about YG?]
He sang songs in English alone
in the first 3 rounds.
I think this is the first time
that he's singing gayo alone.
I think JYP wanted him to sing
gayo and chose this song.
I understand JYP's intentions and
also agree with You Hee-yeol.
He showed many great skills and
voices in the previous rounds.
You just had a good voice today.
I just heard the good voice
we have known until now.
It's a pity that it was a bit boring
compared to previous rounds.
But you still sing well.
You did well.
[Bernard isn't used to
hearing such things]
[Harsh criticisms from two judges...]
[What is JYP's commentary
since he trained him?]
I think I have some problems as a
producer for the casting audition.
I didn't think of what he can do well
to advance to the next round...
I thought of what more he could learn,
realize his problems, and improve.
A song where he can't use
R&B techniques...
That's right. He can't
with this song.
A very Korean song that
he can sing honestly...
I wanted him to get that feeling
when he sings in Korean.
But...
The Korean sentiment and language
isn't easy as expected.
And the gayo melody isn't easy.
It was as gayo as it can be.
But I believe it was a good
attempt and you learned a lot.
You did well.
[Sadly, JYP finishes with
warm words of encouragement]
[What is Bernard's fate as he got
unexpected harsh criticisms?]
Finally, we have Heo Eun-yul
from Antenna Music.
It's another YG song.
[You Hee-yeol and Heo Eun-yul
have a meaningful smile]
I'm curious how she'll sing
this. I can't imagine it.
We're doing a dance for the first
time in Antenna Music's history.
I was eliminated once
and barely came back.
I thought of doing well
for this round...
[Pitted in the worst pool!]
They're all strong...
I think I'll be last.
[Moreover...]
[Practicing Taeyang's
"Only Look at Me"]
This is hard...
I thought of giving up because
it was mentally taxing.
- How long does she...
- About 10 days left.
This song didn't fit her...
She has to do really well since
the finalist is being chosen.
That's when she said something.
I used to dance...
Really? What dance?
Popping...
[Popping Eun-yul?]
Could you turn on a
popping music?
[First time seeing this
from Eun-yul!]
Eun-yul's weakness is that
she's predictable.
We need a winning card and
I thought of adding dancing.
Let's go with this.
I'm not joking.
I'm more burdened because
I'm trying something new.
As long as I've come to this,
I should show everything I got.
[Antenna Music invites
its first choreographer!]
[A dance song changes with
an acoustic arrangement!]
[They took care in their clothes
for their new transformation!]
I had this thought, "If I just
get past this hurdle..."
But that desire is slowly fading
because of my opponents.
No, I can do well!
[She gives her all because
this could be her last!]
I'm curious. Let's talk
after hearing you sing.
[Boldy threw her winning card!]
[The guitar is getting ready]
[She turns around
and gets ready]
[What will be the result
of her winning card?]
[Only Look at Me - Taeyang]
[Tries to put the emotions of
the lyrics at her fingertips]
[Her desperate heart
is in each move]
[She's not used to the moves
yet her breathing is stable]
[Attempted a new transformation
to get into the TOP10!]
[What is her commentary?]
You went to Antenna Music...
I don't know what happened but
your singing has greatly improved.
How can she sing like that
while doing such a dance?
Singing is most difficult when
moving the lower body.
She was continually moving her
lower body but her singing...
It was stable.
It was completely stable.
But...
I couldn't focus on your singing
because you were dancing.
I would've been absorbed if you
sang how you usually sing.
I'm sorry Eun-yul.
It was my mistake of wanting to make
you stand out with a performance.
But there's an image
you had until now.
Breaking out of that
itself is a success.
That's what I meant.
When I asked if you wanted to
dance, what did you say?
Advancing is important but...
I want to show various sides
and experience many things.
That attempt itself was good.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
Will all three come
to the stage?
[Time to announce 1st place!]
[All three were simultaneously
complimented and pointed out]
[It's not easy to tell
who will be 1st place]
Alright!
For you three in this battle...
We considered today's performance
and previous performances.
We took all of that into
account and ranked you.
The 1st place that will
advance to the TOP10 is...
Bernard Park from JYP.
Congratulations.
[Time to announce the eliminated!]
Unfortunately, 3rd place will
have to depart and that is...
[Who will be eliminated?]
Heo Eun-yul from
Antenna Music.
[Heo Eun-yul is eliminated]
It's now time to
say goodbye.
Any last words?
It was like a dream.
I just threw myself to
experience some things.
I experienced many good things...
My dream for music
has become clear.
I was able to sing before great
teachers and you judges.
And last of all, being taught by
You Hee-yeol were precious moments.
Thank you.
Now it's the beginning for you.
I really look forward to it.
- Cheer up.
- Thank you.
Come and visit.
I'll buy you kimbap.
Chae-young, get ready
for the next round.
I hope to see Eun-yul again.
Both of you did well.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[Leaves the stage energetically]
[As soon as Chae-young enters
the 2nd place waiting room]
[Shock]
[Looks bleak...]
It's not an exaggeration to say that
the expected 1st place became 2nd.
I think it's going to be the most
competitive and fun round this season.
We'll see you soon
at the rematch.
[Who will take the
remaining 5 seats?]
Practice for the rematch
will now begin.
[Practice room prepared
for the 2nd place!]
[They begin practicing
for the rematch!]
[Everyone's busy]
[But Jang Hanna isn't able to
concentrate as if she's worried]
[They receive a message from
the production crew!]
Rematch in 30 minutes.
It's going to be
30 minutes from now.
- Let's go!
- Let's begin!
30 minutes!
Only 30 minutes left!
What do I do?
[30 minutes left!]
[As the time draws near,
they become anxious...]
[Tae-kyung of the Shorties
burst into tears!]
[Even Na-jin!]
[The Shorties are extremely tense
and facing the most critical time!]
[Tremendous pressure!]
[Who will make it
to the TOP10?]
[Practice time is over!]
We will now start the rematch.
Please enter the stage.
[They're tense as they enter!]
[Seeing such strong contestants
entering one after another...]
[They exclaim automatically!]
Wow! They're all outstanding!
[Only 5 out of the
8 teams will survive!]
Seeing all of you here, there are many
that should have went into the TOP10.
Please show us an impressive
performance without regrets.
5 already made it to the TOP10
and 5 more need to make it in.
This could be your last
on KPOP STAR.
We ask that you do your best
and put on a great performance.
Everyone, including the production
crew, will give you a big hand.
[Wishing them a good fight!]
First is Something.
[The first contestant for
the rematch is Something]
I told You Hee-yeol over a meal that
I wanted Something to do well.
We kept in mind on the things
pointed out and made this song.
But it was pointed out even more.
I'm at a loss.
[They barely wrote a song
in every round]
[They are at a disadvantage and
feel more burdened than anyone]
[They just start practicing]
We're going to show everything
since we're given another chance.
[Can they overcome this crisis?]
[Why are the judges surprised?]
They couldn't write a song.
But looking at this title...
It's "Come Back Home" by
Seo Taiji and Boys.
[They chose "Come Back Home"
by Seo Taiji and Boys]
It's the first time they're doing
another singer's song and not theirs.
We look forward to how you'll sing
Seo Taiji and Boys' "Come Back Home."
[How will they sing
"Come Back Home"?]
[Come Back Home - Seo Taiji and Boys]
[They give a new feeling
and draw attention]
[Something's new arrangement
of "Come Back Home"]
[What are their commentaries?]
[Their first attempt at arranging
and not writing their own song]
[What is YG's commentary?]
I thought, "Do they have to write
their own song every round?"
They can do a singer's song one
round and their song another round.
It was new and I liked it.
It was completely new.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
I agree with YG in singing
another singer's song.
This song goes on with a bass riff
but you interpreted in your style.
There weren't any tension
or substitution chords...
But I like how you interpreted it.
I want to compliment you for that.
It was energetic compared
to your other songs.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
The next contestant is...
Bae Min-ah from YG.
[Bae Min-ah is the
second contestant]
[The rest are nervous because
the first contestant did well]
You sang Keyshia Cole's song
better than I expected.
It's important that you sang well
but this is more important.
Don't be cautious and show your
capabilities to the fullest.
[But she looks more
nervous than before...]
[A few hours ago...]
[She was sadder than anyone
at Jung-hee's elimination]
I'll cheer you on!
You must be cold. Go in.
I honestly think that
Jung-hee did better.
I feel sorry because we were
a team the previous round.
I really feel sorry... and worried
because I need to pass again.
I don't know if I'll enjoy it
or force myself to sing.
[Can she get over this crisis
and amaze them again?]
[I Wanna Dance with Somebody
- Whitney Houston]
[Clean high notes and
amazing ad-lib]
[She's completely immersed
and enjoying herself]
Thank you.
[She amazed them again]
Today must be her day.
[She's complimented in
every performance]
[The other contestants are
getting more nervous]
I really enjoyed it. I think this
will raise Season 3's standards.
This is a very critical round and
could be a consolation match.
It's hard to get into such groove
under these circumstances.
I compliment you for that.
- Thank you.
- One more thing...
When you sang that ad-lib,
the notes were accurate.
That's really hard.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[Will she advance
to the TOP10?]
Next is Complete Chae.
[The third contestant
is Complete Chae]
- Girls?
- Yes?
Just enjoy it whether
you pass or not, okay?
Yes.
We thought we would
definitely be 3rd place.
We will think of this as our last
and do our best and enjoy it.
[Swagger Jagger - Cher Lloyd]
[They look relaxed and
confident in dancing]
[Complete Chae's performance
puts a smile on their face]
[They used to prepare singing
and dancing separately]
[Now they look natural in
singing while dancing!]
- That's cool!
- How do you do that?
Thank you.
[What are their commentaries?]
The rematch is fun.
- They're better here.
- I know.
Sometimes the agency's
casting is bad.
[That's how natural and good
their performance was]
I honestly think it was better than
Rain's song because they were natural.
They didn't have much practice but
did something that fits their age.
They looked natural with
expressions fitting their age.
You did well. Your dancing, singing,
and expressions were great.
Thank you.
[The contestants are putting
on a good performance]
[The remaining contestants
are greatly burdened]
[Who will take the
remaining 5 seats?]
The next contestant
is Nam Young-joo.
[The fourth contestant
is Nam Young-joo]
This round is too important
to be taking risks.
I'm really upset right now.
I'm upset that I did bad
because I was nervous.
[She blames herself for
performing bad and is upset...]
[Can she overcome this crisis when
she's in her worst condition?]
[Ordinary Woman - Lyn]
[She puts all her energy
and sings passionately]
[What is her commentary on
her passionate singing?]
It was as expected.
[Does he mean it was
good or bad?]
You didn't have much time and
your throat is in a bad condition.
You played it safe and
chose this song.
You should have done such a song
in the previous round...
And I think you should have
taken a risk in this round.
You did well but
it wasn't new.
[She couldn't show anything
beyond the usual]
But I'm glad to see
the usual you.
Your best weapon is that
solid tone of yours.
I like that tone and
you're born with that.
If you do advance, we would like
to see a different image.
I enjoyed it.
[Will she advance
to the TOP10?]
They need much practice and
came to YGE. Next is the Shorties.
[But]
[Something's strange...]
Relax! Don't be nervous.
[They're very nervous
unlike other times]
[What happened to them?]
[During the battle audition]
[They unexpectedly took
2nd because of Sam]
[Since the Shorties were
complimented every round]
[They must have been especially
shocked for taking 2nd place...]
[But]
[There isn't enough time
to get the harmony!]
[At a loss]
[Everyone is busy practicing
the songs they decided]
[They're just getting
more nervous...]
[They finally pull themselves
together and start practicing]
[Tae-kyung suddenly
stops practicing!]
[The production crew is worried
and initiates a conversation]
[She's extremely nervous!]
I'm doing the highest part...
I might make mistakes since I'm discouraged.
[She's extremely nervous]
[She eventually burst into tears!]
[There's not enough time to
practice but the tears won't stop]
We don't have much time
so stop crying.
[She barely stopped crying...]
[And now Na-jin cries!]
Stop crying!
[They're extremely nervous]
Stop crying already!
[Their worst crisis!]
[Can they finish
without a hitch?]
[Stand Up for Love - Destiny's Child]
[The song is about not
losing hope in despair]
[Tae-kyung's high part that
she was nervous about!]
Go on! Go on!
It's okay! You don't need
to sing the last part.
Do something about JYP!
He kept on doing this.
- Stop doing that!
- I'm sorry!
I ruined it. I'm sorry.
He was making pterodactyl
sounds in the middle.
I shouldn't be doing that.
It's the first time
I screamed like that.
[Tears of anxiety turned
into tears of relief...]
All your performances
were great but...
Remember how I said all
of you can go solo?
You can go solo.
All the great singers on this show
are right here in this group.
The three of you were here
with different timbres.
That's why this team is good.
We weren't able to see your individual
skills because of the harmony.
Since you were each given a part,
there are 3 main vocalists.
We were able to confirm that.
You three are really good.
It was unthinkable for me to shout
as a judge and I apologize.
I'm sorry because I can't hide
it when I like something.
What YG said was true because there
was no lead vocalist in this team.
At a certain point, I started to see
Tae-kyung as the lead vocalist.
Then In-hye started singing
like a diva in Round 3.
I thought, "What's going on?"
Na-jin is very good at
singing the A and B parts...
But not the chorus because
she only has the upper range.
But when I saw her upfront
during the warm-up match...
I saw her breathing was wrong.
I pointed that out and she
corrected it within a week.
I could see how she's
single-minded...
In a good way.
They could do team battles
and have individual skills.
I think they could become the
heroines of this season's show.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[What is YG's commentary
since he trained them?]
I would've been complimented
as well if you did this song.
Fortunately, you did it.
I said, "You call yourselves a harmony
group?" That could've hurt your pride.
You took out a lot of the harmony
because you didn't have much time.
And that revealed each of your
capabilities and presence.
I apologize and take back
what I said that time.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[They overcame this crisis!]
[They smile in relief]
[Will the Shorties take
one of the seats?]
Lee Chae-young,
please get ready.
[She steps up with a
determined look...]
I expected to take
2nd or 3rd place.
I'm going to do my best
for the rematch.
I've shown only dancing but I want
to show that I can also sing.
I want to show that I can make it to
the live show with my singing skills.
[How will it be since she's going
to compete with singing?]
[Happy - Mocca]
[She sings a song of hope for
her 2nd attempt in 2 years]
Thank you.
[They break into applause]
[But]
[What does his look mean?]
The melody in the beginning and middle
are in semitones except for the last part.
She sang the semitones accurately
when it's not easy at that age.
But there's one thing...
You sing too powerfully.
You should be singing comfortably
with powerful singing occasionally.
You're like a radio
on max volume.
Your skills will show even when
you sing naturally and comfortably.
It's because you were
trying too hard.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
I don't have such experience...
But if my agency picked someone
and were training that person...
I would hug, compliment, and pinch
the cheeks of a trainee like her.
But looking at her as a judge...
This is your second attempt.
Maybe that's why...
I can feel that you're
trying too hard.
[Same thing that JYP said...]
I thought it would be better
if you were a little relaxed.
It's true that she
wanted to do well.
You were complimented the most
in the previous round.
It's because you were the
most relaxed at that time.
Because you're only 13 and
you have to survive...
You tried to win with strength because
those before you were complimented.
I felt both proud and
pity for you.
But I applaud you for this fresh
performance and challenge.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[It's hard to predict who
will make it to the TOP10]
[Will Lee Chae-young
make it to the TOP10?]
Next contestant is...
It's Jang Hanna who
made my blood boil.
[She was always pointed
out for the same thing!]
[Why can't she unleash
it on stage?]
[It was tougher for her than
anyone after she took 2nd]
It's true that I was burdened
due to the high expectations...
But I feel sorry that I couldn't
meet their expectations.
[This is her hardest round...]
[Her long day started at dawn since
it overlapped with her entrance exam]
[There were many ups and downs
before she got up on stage]
[How will her long day end?]
During the remaining time...
I have to practice a song that
I'm good at and shows my color.
[It was hard but how will her
performance turn out?]
[Give It to Me Right - Melanie Fiona]
Thank you.
[It was a short but
intense performance]
[What is her commentary?]
That note is very high.
It was the "I don't want it" part.
What was the note?
I think it's E.
I can't sing it so
I think it is E.
But...
We've seen you get into the rhythm
naturally but for the first time...
It was a short period, but you can sing
the high notes and passionately.
I think you can do it.
YG especially said how you
made him lose his temper.
If you sing a different song
with such high notes...
I think you can unleash it.
[The compliment she
had waited for!]
When she sang the high notes,
I thought, "That was good."
I think the judges will fall for you
if you can sing with such freshness.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[She received a positive commentary
for exploding at the high notes]
[What is her fate?]
[The last contestant
for the rematch!]
Peter Han from Antenna Music
is the next contestant.
[He was always with a guitar
but where is it today?]
[Keyboard!]
[He always played the guitar
but it's a keyboard...]
Peter always played the guitar but
it's the first time seeing a keyboard.
I'm not that good but
I wrote a song...
I wrote this a long time ago
and really wanted to sing it.
This is a song I treasure.
I only thought of doing well
while on this show.
But I want to show a music I like
and enjoy without regrets.
[He plays the keyboard
for the first time!]
[How will his song on
the keyboard sound?]
[Help from Above - own song]
[The song is about asking for help
from above for those in pain]
[A voice and piano melody
that soothes the heart]
[He's given a big hand]
[But can his song take
him to the TOP10?]
It wasn't new since we heard such lyrics,
melody, and chord progression before.
But...
When you play the guitar
and the keyboard...
You have amazing musicality.
I heard something like
this before but...
I thought it would be great if
drums and strings were added.
Basically, you have great
musical talents.
Your starting point is to draw
that out and create your own.
There's tremendous musical nourishment
stored up in you. I feel that every time.
[His talents were recognized but
will he make it to the TOP10?]
All of you did well. We'll now call out
5 teams from among you that will advance.
[The judges begin the discussion
that will determine their fate!]
[The discussion is more
serious than ever...]
[Who will be the 5 finalists?]
[The discussion is over!]
[The judges have a long face]
[What was the outcome
of the discussion?]
We have the results.
We'll announce the five that
will advance to the TOP10.
We'll announce the first
TOP10 finalist.
They moved us like a
nuclear bomb.
Congratulations to
the Shorties!
Please move to the seats.
[They boldly move to the seats
while being congratulated!]
We've participated in many
song festivals but...
I think it's KPOP STAR that clearly
engraved the title "The Shorties."
[7 teams remain on stage!]
The second TOP10 finalist...
We have waited all this time
for this person to unleash it.
It's Jang Hanna.
Congratulations.
[YG smiles more than anyone]
Today was a long day.
I thought I was going to be
eliminated when I took 2nd.
[Her long day finished
with a happy ending...]
[The hot tears fall
feeling relieved]
[Only 3 out of the
6 teams will survive!]
The third TOP10 finalist...
Although you took 2nd place,
you were always complimented.
[They already have
an idea who it is]
You also received many
compliments in the rematch.
Congratulations
Bae Min-ah!
I tried out this audition
because I like singing.
Now it's the beginning. I would like to
think of KPOP STAR as my beginning.
[Only 2 seats remain!]
Man...
[3 teams are destined to be
eliminated from the 5!]
[It hurts them more since
they know the results]
Only 2 teams remain.
[Only 2 out of the
5 teams can survive!]
We'll announce the
fourth TOP10 finalist.
Actually...
The judges' opinions differed
a little starting from here.
In other words...
There wasn't a big difference between
those advancing and those eliminated.
The next TOP10 finalist is...
We chose the one that can give a stable
performance before a large audience.
[A contestant that can give a
stable performance would be...]
Congratulations
Nam Young-joo!
[Her best friend, Choi Rin,
is the happiest]
[Maybe because she wasn't satisfied with
her performance, she doesn't look bright]
[But later on...]
[She cries like a baby]
[9 finalists have been decided]
[Now only one can survive!]
The last TOP10 finalist...
There's no big difference whether
you advance or are eliminated.
The last TOP10 finalist is...
I'm more desperate than anyone
because I practiced for 2 years.
I really want to make
it to the TOP10.
I want to smile and
not cry today.
My mom can come to Korea
if I make it to the TOP10.
I would like to make it
for my mom.
I hope I can just enjoy myself
while singing and dancing.
[Just one team will survive!]
The last TOP10 finalist is...
Something. Congratulations.
[They give them a big hand
and congratulate them]
We're sorry for the
lacking performance.
We'll try harder to put on
a better performance.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations. Please
move to the seats.
[Lee Chae-young, Complete Chae,
and Peter Han are eliminated!]
We don't think you four
are eliminated.
You are winners in our eyes.
[Peter Han was able to sing the
high notes with hard work]
[Lee Chae-young made remarkable
progress compared to 2 years ago]
[The Lee sisters were able to
sing confidently on stage]
You did great to even
have made it this far.
I think the staff here has
to give them a big hand.
[These four receive a big hand
more than those that passed]
[Chae-ryeong got emotional
and burst into tears]
We promised not to cry.
[They'll soon leave the stage
they got attached to]
[The Shorties bursts into tears
at the thought of Peter leaving]
[Chae-young tries to
look spirited]
[The four leave the stage
with a warm applause]
[Their families are waiting
for them at the exit]
Chae-young, you did great!
You're the best! Now
it's the beginning.
Cheer up! It's okay.
You did well in the last performance.
You will always be the best in my heart.