The road to being a
K-pop star isn't easy.
[Almeng receives a man-to-man
consulting for their makeover]
- Let's lose those guts.
- Alright.
You should go on a diet.
[Starts training to lose weight!]
- 15 more of these?
- Yes, 15 more.
[Why are you doing this to me?]
[At the same time, Nam Youngjoo
goes to see an ENT doctor]
[Lee Soo-young - ENT doctor]
[Taking care of one's throat is
basic for a more perfect stage!]
Your vocal cords are hard.
If you get tired, you
can lose your voice.
They maintain their best condition
after seeing a doctor.
Now it's the day that
they take profile pictures.
[T-minus 7 days
jenny house]
You look prettier when
you have volume!
[She is the beautician in
charge of the TOP10 finalists!]
[Kim Hyun-sook - visual director]
[What is Jang Hanna's
hairstyle feature?]
I want her to look mysterious!
[Mysterious girl Jang Hanna]
[What is Kim Ah-hyun's
makeup feature?]
Don't put on any lashes.
It'll make her look older.
[Her innocence stands out]
You look like a doll!
[TOP10 finalists' makeover!]
[We reveal their amazing
transformation!]
[They start on their profile shots!]
[He draws out their best pose!]
[Kama Zo - photographer and
head of KAMA Studio]
I'll give you tips on what
to do in front of a camera.
The first most important
thing is confidence.
- What is it?
- Confidence.
Today I look what?
Great! The best!
[Practicing their looks
in front of a mirror!]
[I look the best today!]
[There's another expert!]
[Kang Hyun-seung
KAMA Studio photographer]
That's a great smile!
They are being reborn
with help from experts!
They look more like a
celebrity than me.
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[Last week!]
[After Group A the death group
finished their competition!]
[Bernard Park and Sam Kim became
candidates for elimination!]
[Now their fate rests...]
[On the audience judging panel!]
[Group B will soon begin!]
Group A is good but
even Group B is good.
I hope we at least
get 3rd place.
Even Group B is the death group.
[And!]
Heejun...
Heejun is...
I'm next after Heejun...
[Everyone is wary of Heejun Han!]
What do I do?
They're all strong...
They didn't get into
TOP10 for nothing.
[They head to the stage
feeling tense!]
[Only 3 can get into the TOP8!]
[What is their fate?]
[Group B begins!]
Group B will now begin.
We had a shocking result
for Group A where...
Sam Kim and Bernard Park became
candidates for elimination.
[Group B hears it for the first time]
[It's a big shock and
they feel more nervous...]
YG, how do you predict
Group B's competition?
This show is fun because, as in the
group drawing, it's unpredictable.
Everyone expected Group A
to be strong but...
The three of us talked
how Group B will explode.
So we look forward to
a bomb-like stage.
So you predict a twist.
What about You Hee-yeol?
The 4 best vocalists
are in Group B.
This is a chance for us to
differentiate their skills.
Something will be revealing
their new song today.
It's exciting because the results
can change depending on their song.
What twists will there
be in Group B?
The first contestant for
Group B is Heejun Han!
[Heejun Han's stage]
[Wild cheers by the
female audience]
Heejun already has
3 female fans.
[Good luck Heejun!]
That was a tremendous cheer.
How are you feeling?
Are you nervous?
Very.
You received your greatest
compliment last time.
You could be at a disadvantage
because of higher expectations.
Do you have anything
up your sleeves?
I learned to sing with my heart
and that'll be my weapon.
Have you ever regretted
applying for KPOP STAR?
I regret it every time
before I go to sleep.
"Why am I having a hard time in this
place without friends or family?"
When unexpected things happened and
unexpected tasks were given to me...
I think I had regrets
because it was hard.
But I felt proud of myself as
I did my best little by little...
And those regrets went away.
American Idol was a
cutthroat competition.
KPOP STAR is a survival
but it was like school.
I didn't know I could improve in
singing since I stuck to a certain style.
I thought, "What more can
I learn or do here?"
The judges gave me advice on singing
from the heart and finding my color.
I never received such advice.
I think I was able to find
my color as a singer.
[And the day of the
TOP10 match...]
TOP9, the number 9 followed
me around like a label.
I could get rid of it
if I pass today...
I'm really nervous because
I'm facing my max limit.
[B-1, Heejun Han]
We look forward to how
you'll please us.
Let's give him a hand
before he begins.
[Everyone in Group B
thinks he'll get 1st place]
[What performance
will he present?]
[Regret - Kim Gun-mo]
This stage was by Heejun Han!
He sang "Regret" by Kim Gun-mo.
Let's hear the commentaries.
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
Heejun is a completely different style
from Bernard who just sang in Group A.
I expressed Bernard as a heavyweight.
He's heavy without minor skills.
But Heejun is light and...
He's good at throwing jabs...
He's detailed and good
at sidestepping.
But he doesn't have
that decisive blow.
We now see your sincerity and
we all know you sing well.
You need to arm yourself with another
weapon and that is that final punch.
Good job.
I first got into you when
you sang "I Love You."
I wrote that for Kim Jo Han
as a wedding present.
It's a very meaningful song
since I'm friends with him.
Despite the fact that it's
a meaningful song to me...
But when you sang it...
It didn't remind me of
Kim Jo Han who sings well.
[His rendition was excellent
than the original artist]
But this song reminded
me of Kim Gun-mo.
As if I missed him.
[What's the difference?]
You were complimented by us
when you sang "Passing."
It's as if you brought that over
and substituted for this song.
I'm worried if such compliments
might have confused you.
You sang very carefully.
You're pushing out on each note
because you're being careful.
You don't know how it'll come out
but just sing as it comes out.
I thought, "What if
he sang like that?"
You might have had the toughest fight
on this show out of all the contestants.
You had to fight against
our prejudice.
All the songs you sang
since Round 1 were...
Gayo... even this song
by Kim Gun-mo.
As time goes by, I see that
you are optimized for gayo.
This song by Kim Gun-mo is
very hard because...
The notes are all up here
and none are down here.
It's hard to be dynamic.
The more I see you, I can see
how good you are at acting.
You can sing various genres.
You can sing pop, R&B, soul...
Now you have armed yourself
with gayo and ballads.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
This stage was by Heejun Han!
[Heejun is testing his limits]
[Can he take that one step from
American Idol's TOP9 to TOP8?]
Next is Group B's second
contestant, Bae Mina!
[Bae Mina's stage]
Mina showed her strengths
mainly in pop music.
She prepared a song by
As One. How was it?
I chose this song because I think my
ad-libs and R&B style can stand out.
I don't know what you'll think
but I'll do my best.
[She's complimented every round]
[Bae Mina's sudden prominence
as a powerful dark horse]
I can't believe it!
This is like a dream!
[One day at her lodging]
[She's writing a letter
to someone]
I got a letter before I came here to
live with the other contestants.
One of my brothers wrote telling me
to do well and not worry since I worry.
But...
Since I'm young...
[She's young... and it's a
tough journey for her dream]
I haven't lived away
from my family.
Why am I crying?
[She almost forgot her "family"
due to her desperate dream]
I was touched after reading
that letter because...
I thought how much my brothers
are thinking about me.
I'm burdended, "What if I do bad?
What if I disappoint them?"
My dad's coming and he hasn't
seen my performances before.
That's my biggest burden.
I won't worry and think
I can do well.
I'll do my best for
my family today.
[B-2, Bae Mina]
[Day by Day - As One]
Thank you.
This stage was by Bae Mina.
She sang "Day by Day" by As One.
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
I want to compliment you
on your ad-libs.
It's hard even for R&B singers
to draw out the tension note.
It was impressive how you
drew out the tension notes.
But...
I think those that played around have
an advantage in being a singer.
Those that have dated and
even broken up...
When you hear a certain lyric,
you know that feeling and use it.
I don't know you but if you were
just a nice girl who only studied...
And never had a crush, it's hard
to sing with that emotion.
But such things will
get better with age.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[Exceptional singing skills but
lacking in emotinal expression]
I'm going to say something
different from JYP.
Bae Mina and Sam Kim are the
youngest of the TOP10 finalists.
They're 16.
It could be impossible for a 16-year-old
to describe experiences on love.
Who's the top R&B
artist in Korea?
Female would be Lena Park and
male would be Kim Jo Han.
It's at the tip of
You Hee-yeol's tongue.
Even the audience judging panel
would give the same answer.
The number of R&B singers
we know is very small.
So I want 16-year-old Bae Mina
to develop her voices and...
I hope she could be one of Korea's
top R&B singers in a year or two.
You're a diamond in
the rough. You did well.
You have a nice timbre.
It's a timbre Koreans like.
It's when people say, "She has such
a pretty voice." It's that timbre.
Second, you have great
pronunciation.
Pronunciation isn't something
that can be taught.
It's just like when JYP says
that bending can't be taught.
Same goes for pronunciation
but yours is pretty.
It's because your speaking is also pretty.
Your pronunciation is pretty when you sing.
When you sing such songs or an R&B,
you have the power to sound lovely.
But your singing in gayo sounds
weaker than in pop because...
There can be only one syllable
for each note in gayo.
It's like this.
But pop is like this.
When you sing something like "sky,"
you can draw out the "E" sound.
But you have to do all that
with one word in Korean.
So it feels like you're playing
around with the song in pop.
But you don't have that
technique in gayo.
Once you can do that, we can feel
that you're playing with the song.
It was a lovely performance.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
This stage was by Bae Mina!
Please remember that.
[Will Bae Mina make it to
the TOP8 live show?]
The third contestant for
Group B is Nam Youngjoo!
[Nam Youngjoo's stage!]
[Nam Youngjoo's mother and sister]
I think she's going to be big.
She's good at getting into the emotion
on stage and adept like a pro.
She's like a pro and left
a big impression.
[They think of her on a professional
level but how will it be?]
Hello, I'm Nam Youngjoo.
[A beautiful white dress]
It's like a Disney...
Elsa?
You're like the heroine
from "Frozen."
What is your concept?
A wedding.
A wedding?
I'm singing JYP's "Behind You."
This is a sad ballad and I wore this
to try to feel more like a goddess.
I don't really sing and I rarely sing
when I go to the karaoke with friends.
But this is the only JYP song
that I am able to sing.
I'm saying this because
I really like this song.
You might get a good commentary
if you sing this one well.
I said it to keep your spirits up.
Don't sing along.
I was in darkness before I went on
last season's KPOP STAR.
[What pain did she go through?]
My dream was to be a singer
ever since I was young.
I had many opportunities
when I was younger.
I had a short two-year contract
with a small record label and...
I released four digital singles...
[She used to be a singer
under the stage name RAM]
I thought, "Am I singing on stage?
Am I singing before an audience?"
Singing on stage wasn't
as easy as I thought.
It just ended without a chance of
singing on stage as a singer.
Afterwards, I had fewer opportunities.
I even thought of quitting...
I never thought that but...
Since my parents were
having a hard time...
[It hurts her even more to see
her parents having a hard time]
I was worn out...
Since I can't see my future...
I didn't see any hope that
I'll be doing something soon.
I couldn't see anything.
[Jamsil preliminaries last August]
My sister is in the 10th grade...
She said, "I'm applying
for KPOP STAR 3."
"What about you?" I replied, "I'm not.
Why should I apply for that?"
I kept it a secret
from her and applied.
On the day of the booth audition,
someone was calling me, "Unni!"
I went "Huh?" and saw
that it was my sister.
[Nam Youngjoo's sister
Nam Sohyun, 16 at the time]
I was worried. It's good if she makes it,
but what if I don't make the preliminaries?
What is she makes it
and I don't?
[She was a singer at one time and
takes her first step for her dream again]
I was really worried but fortunately,
I feel sorry for her, but she didn't make it.
She cheered me on.
My parents and sister...
My parents always say,
"I live because of you."
My parents have been very
disappointed with me.
You made it and I didn't.
So you have to do my share
and keep on advancing, okay?
When Season 4 begins, go on
and make it to the TOP10.
[Round 1 after the preliminaries...]
I liked the fact that
I was on stage.
It was a shining stage that I couldn't
even stand on when I used to be a singer.
I was able to sing before people...
Now I felt like I really
became a singer.
Now I want to be a real singer.
When I'm asked, "Are you a singer?"
I want to be a singer that can say, "Yes."
[One more step and she can stand on the
impressive stage of the live show!]
I'm most worried about running away
and hiding like a coward on stage.
I hope I won't hide this time...
[B-3, Nam Youngjoo]
[Nam Youngjoo's mother and sister]
[Behind You - JYP]
[Her mother was nervous
throughout the song]
[Her sister is also
trying to calm down]
This stage was by Nam Youngjoo.
Let's hear the commentaries.
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
[They're hesistant in
picking up the mike!]
[Were they not satisfied?]
[JYP picks it up first]
I expected it to be something
like this when you sang this song.
You did it exactly as expected
but nevertheless it was great.
It's like you know that person's specialty in
judo is shoulder throws and you get thrown.
That's how intense the
beginning part was.
But...
You backed out the moment
you sang the high notes.
You threw away your emotions
somewhere at the high notes.
You were like, "I'm going to show
my high notes! Here I go!"
I was getting into it but...
That was a real pity.
But...
It's an amazing change that you
were able to sing those high notes.
I saw that potential in you
for the first time today.
Now put some feeling
into the high notes.
Don't expand your voice when
you sing the high notes.
Sing the high notes with the voice
you sing in the mid-lows.
I saw that your skills can
improve another level.
I enjoyed it.
[The compliment was meaningful since
she didn't run away at the high notes!]
[What about YG?]
I said earlier how I like
this song and often sing it.
I think you made a wrong choice in
choosing JYP's "Behind You."
I was looking at how you would
sing this song differently.
But it didn't go beyond my expectations.
Maybe it's due to your throat condition.
JYP says this a lot, you sang
like established singers.
It's because you feel
like a professional.
We've been doing music for years.
We couldn't find anything new.
When we see new contestants, we think,
"Oh? They can sing it like that?"
We try to look for that. I think the
viewers will also think the same.
You're not optimized for a live stage
but you'll shine in a studio recording.
You're someone who fits the mike.
Just sing songs in that genre
without a lot of high notes.
The trend today in music is that
there are many songs catering to feel.
If you change that direction, there's a high chance
for you to be a singer people like nowadays.
I enjoyed it.
[Will she be able to advance to
the live show she desired?]
Group B is almost done.
[Group B's fourth contestant!]
[Jang Hanna's stage!]
[Jang Hanna's father,
sister, and mother]
She looks like Yuna Kim.
She looks like a figure skater.
[She's pretty]
How are you feeling?
- I'm a bit hungry.
- Hungry?
This is the TOP10 stage.
A pro shines on such a stage.
They do better the bigger it is.
Please do your best.
How do you feel after
becoming a TOP10 finalist?
I'm really nervous...
Now it hit me that the
real battle begins.
I'm really nervous...
I applied to make memories
and gain experience...
I never dreamt I would
make it this far.
It's very different from a year ago.
It's like I'm in another world.
I made a lot of progress.
You must be the pride
of Yangpyeong.
That's what everyone says.
The pride of Yangpyeong.
Since I grew up in
a rural area...
The county governor and
township chief would call...
And people say that they're
watching me on television.
Everyone says hi to my mom
when she goes to the market.
She said she can't leave home.
My parents are very proud of me.
I think I'm being a
good daughter.
My sister really likes it
and she's young...
She likes it because her
sister is on television.
[Her family is her reliable support]
I'm thankful to the judges for all the
compliments since Round 1 but...
I think their expectations are really high
and I have to unleash my potential.
Every time they talk about potential,
I know what they're saying but...
I get nervous on the stage and
I always regretted my performance.
During practice I would think,
"What am I supposed to do?"
But I'm going to enjoy it
this time and show them.
I want it to be a performance
without any regrets.
[B-4, Jang Hanna]
[Will she be able to push aside her
regrets with today's performance?]
[Warning - Tashannie]
Thank you.
[She finished her intense performance]
[How did the judges see it?]
[JYP picks up the mike first]
We always said the same thing
to you in every round.
We wanted you to explode
somewhere in the middle.
And you exploded for the first time during
the rematch in choosing the TOP10 finalists.
You exploded again today.
But...
You exploded in sound
but not in emotion.
[Her emotions didn't explode?]
What I mean is that it felt like
you were in your right mind.
[She wasn't into the song!]
Some singers falter in their singing
because they are into their feeling.
You need those little changes
in your daily life to do that.
Those that are reserved, don't express
their feelings, and aren't moody...
It's not easy for such people to
get into that emotion in singing.
[She was pointed out for her lack
of emotional expressions...]
[What about YG?]
I saw her a little when
I casted her to YGE.
But she's a tomboy.
She's talkative, jokes around,
and screams with laughter.
Like that.
But why can't she explode?
JYP said that he wanted her to be someone
that plays around at least on stage.
But she's a nice girl.
JYP always say to just
sing half-heartedly.
She's a bad example of that.
What he meant by that
is to sing naturally.
- But she really...
- Sang half-heartedly?
But I want to compliment
you on one thing.
But you looked confident compared
to your previous performances.
It looked like you had
swagger and confidence.
I hope you can also sing with
confidence and sincerity.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[There were sharp observations but
it ended with a positive commentary]
[And You Hee-yeol?]
Your clothes make you look
like a figure skater.
You look like Yuna Kim.
I have to talk about beauty since
I became a judge in BoA's place.
I'll say just one thing
about your singing.
Putting everything aside...
JYP mainly talks about one's
attitude on the live stage.
I, on the other hand, imagine
you in a recording studio.
How would you sound during
recording when you're a pro?
Do you know why? It's because
you're not a live stage singer.
- It's because you only record.
- You're on my side for the first time!
You always teamed up with
You Hee-yeol and made fun of me.
[Anyways]
Your strength when I think
about the recording studio...
You're the best in
the chorus part.
You have the power
to pull us in.
Mixing engineers increase it, double it,
and do various things to get that.
It's like instinct for you.
You were born with that talent.
Seeing you sing that chorus part,
I see that you truly are a singer.
I enjoyed it.
[She finishes with the
best compliment]
[It's hard to predict
Group B's ranking!]
[Group A's Bernard Park and Sam Kim
are candidates for elimination!]
[2 teams from Group B will be
candidates for elimination!]
[Who will those two be?]
[And later!]
[The audience judging panel
will start their voting!]
[Who will be eliminated?]
Now we have today's final
TOP10 performance.
Please welcome Something!
You are the last in Group B
among the TOP10 finalists.
The others just need to
prepare a song...
But it's hard for Something since
you need to write a song.
We always asked beforehand
what your song is about.
But we won't ask because we want to
listen today without knowing it.
We'll just look at the title
and wonder what it's about.
[Previously for the TOP10 match]
[Something barely made it to
the TOP10 after the rematch]
[After the TOP10 prematch]
[Everyone is bright and sharing the
joy of making it to the TOP10]
[Only Something looks down]
I felt more burdened
instead of being happy.
[They were choked with emotion since
it was harder for them to make it]
Many things happened and we didn't
really smile on stage until now.
And we never smiled
when we left the stage.
We always felt bad.
It was hard as if 10 years
had passed like that.
We met each other for the first time
on this show. It's been 3-4 months.
We never learned composition.
- For every round...
- We had to write a song.
It was overwhelming and hard.
We want to be complimented by the judges
and do a performance we won't regret.
Our song is called
"21st Century Chameleon."
A chameleon changes color depending
on its environment to survive.
It's about adjusting to the color of reality
and making our dreams come true.
We have to be cute and sing like
kids in the beginning part.
It's a bit awkward and
hard for me to do that.
We will show how much we improved
to be complimented by the judges.
[B-5, Something]
[21st Century Chameleon - own song]
We don't know anything
What should I be
When I grow up?
All I need is
My mom and dad
That's all I need
Under "My dream" in my
Elementary school yearbook
My dream was to be president
That dark 13-year-old boy
Was like the color of the sky
But became an adult
In the gray world
My dream is to be a civil servant
My dream is to be an office worker
I'm gradually losing my color
I like green
But the world is gray
I hide myself again today
I'm a chameleon
I hid my longtime dream
Kept it a secret
I want to shout it out
I'm going to stop crying
Tonight is black
I sing in the darkness
Chameleon
After I wake up from that long dream
I won't see you again in the morning
The starlight clears, the sun shines
Should I go to sleep by singing?
Although I became an adult
In this gray world
My dream here
I sing of my dream
I want to find my color
I like green
But the world is gray
I hide myself again today
I adjust my color to reality
And I hide myself
I live today
Even tomorrow
And maybe even the day after
I'm a chameleon
Thank you.
[They wrote a song with a new
color with an earnest heart]
This last stage was by Something.
[Will they get complimented?]
I could somewhat expect what the
lyrics would be just by the title.
Jung Se-woon is 18 and
Kim Ah-hyun is 23.
Those in their 20s and 30s, including
teens, should relate to your songs.
I'm in my 40s...
But the lyrics were childlike.
That was a pity, otherwise
it would have been a good song.
[The lyrics need more depth]
The lyrics were a pity and
not your performance.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
I like Something.
I truly do.
Lyrics such as "It's funny the clock is round"
are so good that they pierce the heart.
And I know what kind of
people you two are.
Both of you are good-hearted
with exceptional artistry.
But the problem is...
You need the ability to change
that into a 4-minute hit song.
But we have never been pulled
into the song for 4 minutes.
It was the same for this song.
If the two of you can
develop that...
If you can express that artistry into a
popular song or a song that moves people...
Then you can become
great composers and artists.
Thank you.
[They were pointed out for
the same thing again...]
I know because I trained
them for 3 weeks.
They're wandering right now
to find their way.
We know how you're searching.
You two met on this show and did
your best in collaborating.
I would like to applaud you but
some things were unfortunate.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[A warm applause of
encouragement]
Would all 5 teams come
up to the stage?
The Top 3 will now be chosen.
[The judges discuss to
choose who passes!]
[The 5 teams from Group B
go up the stage feeling tense]
The 5 teams from Group B
are now on the stage.
They're discussing carefully to choose
the 3 that will go to the TOP8 live show.
The 2 teams that aren't called will
be candidates for elimination.
Together with the two from Group A,
the audience judging panel will vote.
1st from Group B was Heejun Han,
2nd was Bae Mina, 3rd was Nam Youngjoo...
4th was Jang Hanna and
5th was Something.
They are very nervous right now.
Are the judges finished?
[They're finished!]
Please announce which 3 teams from Group B
will advance to the TOP8 live show.
We expected it...
But it was harder than Group A.
We had conflicting opinions.
Our standard for choosing the Top 3 is
based only on today's performance.
The one that was pointed out the
most out of all the contestants...
That means we had a lot
of interest in you.
1st place is...
[Who is 1st place in Group B?]
Heejun Han!
Heejun is 1st place from Group B
and advances to the live show.
Congratulations. You take
1st place in Group B.
How do you feel?
Thank you.
I'll try to do a performance
worthy of being 1st place.
Speak to them in a loud voice
like a 1st place winner.
You're 1st place.
Next time I'll... could
you raise the mike...
[Such wits to liven up the mood!]
[Hold it yourself]
Thank you for picking me.
I'll put much thought into giving a
performance worthy of being 1st place.
Thank you.
Congratulations. To your right...
He's very conscientious...
Heejun Han takes 1st place.
Now I'm starting.
Now I'm getting ready to run.
When were you TOP9?
It was exactly a year ago.
It took a year to subtract
just one number from 9.
You're right. To subtract
a number from 9...
It took a year...
It went by in a flash.
[He overcame his limits once
more as a TOP8 finalist]
[2nd place announcement!]
It was hard since there
were 3 female vocalists.
It's not easy to pick from
similar contestants.
2nd place is...
[Who takes 2nd place?]
Jang Hanna!
Jang Hanna takes 2nd place
from Group B and advances.
Hold the mike and tell
us how you feel.
Thank you.
[She burst out crying]
Are you crying because you didn't
expect it or you feel sorry?
I was always a disappointment
and even today...
[She had regrets and thought
she was eliminated]
I'll try harder and show you that
I can enjoy it. Thank you.
Jang Hanna is 2nd place.
Congratulations!
[She's resolved to enjoy it
on the bigger live stage]
Now we have the last one
from Group B.
Who is the last to advance?
What Jang Hanna said last played
a big role in choosing 3rd place.
She said she'll enjoy it next time.
This is obvious but...
A hard worker is better than
a gifted person and...
Someone who enjoys is
better than a hard worker.
Among the remaining 3 teams...
It's not about who sang
or composed better.
It's about who wasn't nervous
and enjoyed this stage.
3rd place is...
[Who is the last to advance?]
Bae Mina!
3rd place for Group B is
Bae Mina. Congratulations!
How do you feel?
I thought I would be
4th or 5th place.
Thank you. I'll do better and
give my best. Thank you.
Heejun Han is lst, Jang Hanna is 2nd,
and Bae Mina is 3rd from Group B.
They advance to the TOP8
live show. Congratulations!
Nam Youngjoo and Something are
candidates for elimination.
Se-woon, you aren't eliminated yet.
We don't know. We still have the votes.
[She keeps crying
for some reason]
She's out of it...
It was hard for them...
[They desperately wanted
to be in the TOP8...]
Something is great!
[They cheer them by applauding]
Was it hard?
I felt frustrated for getting
the same commentary...
[They try and try to reach that
place but are in the same spot...]
Something! Ah-hyun!
Don't keep your chin down.
Your eyes puff up when you cry.
Your nose gets bigger.
She might cry more.
Say that to yourself.
Thank you JYP.
At least she doesn't wail.
- He can't say anything.
- She doesn't cover her eyes.
That's right. She doesn't
press on her eyes.
Let's have Group B's Top 3 step down
the stage. Please give them a hand.
Please go down the stage.
Now we'll have the two elimination
candidates from Group A on the stage.
Let's have Sam Kim and
Bernard Park on stage.
[As soon as these two appeared]
[OMG!]
[I can't believe this!]
[These two were mentioned as being
TOP3 candidates at one point!]
[Which two will make it?]
We have now finished watching them
perform the past two weeks.
Only 2 from these 4 teams will
advance to the TOP8 live show.
Those 2 will be chosen by votes
from the audience judging panel.
The 3 judges are no
longer responsible.
Their fate now rests in the hands
of the audience judging panel.
Voting will now begin!
[The panel starts voting!]
[The remaining two are
placed on the ballots!]
[Who will the panel pick?]
[The 4 teams move to
the waiting room!]
[Their steps are heavier
than before!]
[They start voting as
soon as they exit!]
[They cast their vote by putting
their number into the ballots!]
I'm sad... really sad...
I want to say that I have no regrets
but my performance was pitiful.
[Bernard Park received a lot of
votes from the female members]
We won't get discouraged even
though we get eliminated...
We'll remain steadfast and
continue with our music.
My eyes met with my mom.
I keep thinking of
the look on her face.
[Voting is almost over]
[Who received the most votes?]
[The last panelist voted...]
[Voting is over!]
[Ballot tally begins!]
We'll start with Sam Kim.
[Each vote is stuck on
the wall and confirmed!]
Next is Bernard Park.
[Does he have a similar
number of votes as Sam?]
Next is Nam Youngjoo.
Seven! Eight...
[Last is Something!]
Twenty! Twenty-one! Twenty-two...
[The final number of votes will
be revealed on stage!]
[Ballot tally is finished!]
[They leave the waiting room
and head for the stage!]
[Who will make it and
who will leave?]
[The audience judging panel
is gone after voting...]
[The elimination candidates' family
members silently take their seats]
[The 6 teams that passed are
on one side of the stage!]
We will now have the candidates
for elimination on stage.
Please enter!
[The 4 candidates enter!]
[Bernard Park, Sam Kim from Group A]
[Nam Youngjoo, Something from Group B]
[Just seeing them
makes them sigh...]
This is more painful than
choosing the winners.
It was a close match.
It'll be a pity whoever
gets eliminated.
How do you feel JYP?
I think it's fortunate that
we didn't need to decide.
Even though we put our heads together,
we can't choose who to pass or eliminate.
It's fortunate that the panel bore that burden
since we might not have been able to.
What about you YG?
The saddest moment for me
when I was in school...
It would be graduation.
This feels like a graduation.
[Sadness in letting go of friends
they became familiar with...]
I already feel sad.
It will be a graduation filled with tears
whoever passes or gets eliminated.
I will now announce the last two finalists
that will advance to the live show.
[Announcement time!]
I have two sealed envelopes.
One of them is 1st place and
the other is 2nd place.
3rd and 4th place not in this
envelope are eliminated.
[Tremendous pressure!]
I'll now announce it.
[Announcement for 1st place!]
[The MC opens the envelope]
[Who is 1st place?]
I'll announce it!
The first additional finalist that will advance
to the TOP8 live show next week is...
42 votes from a total of 107!
The first additional finalist to
advance to next week's live show...
That is...
Congratulations!
Bernard Park!
[Bernard Park's older cousin]
[The others truly congratulate him]
[Even the judges]
The 7th finalist will move to the
winners seat. Please give him a hand.
[He was in danger of getting eliminated
and miraculously sprung back to life!]
[It's as if he's worn out]
[He quietly holds back the tears]
We now have only one team left to
advance to the TOP8 live show.
The last ticket is in my hands.
I haven't opened it yet.
No one knows.
[Whose name is in the envelope?]
Only one from the remaining 3 teams
will advance to the live show.
I'll announce 2nd place!
[Whose name is written?]
Alright...
[Whose name is in the
last envelope?]
I saw the name.
I don't know who the judges expect
but the results are already out.
31 votes from a total of 107!
That's a lot...
That is also a lot of votes.
The last finalist to advance
to the TOP8 live show is...
[The ones not called
are eliminated!]
The last finalist to advance
to the TOP8 live show is...
[The ones not called
are eliminated!]
Congratulations!
Sam Kim!
[Nam Youngjoo is eliminated!]
[Something is eliminated!]
[Nam Youngjoo's mother]
[The family members of the
eliminated are sadder than anyone]
[He didn't expect it]
[He cries feeling sorry...]
Let's have the finalists on stage.
Including Sam Kim, we now
have all the finalists.
[The eliminated pat each
other for the good run...]
[His tears don't stop]
He's crying...
For the first time.
He was always smiling.
[He feels sad and sorry
since they shared a room]
[The live show is right around the
corner but they have to leave...]
[Leaving KPOP STAR...]
I was always busy
running away...
I ran away from the high notes
and played it safe on stage.
But I didn't run away today.
I truly did my best...
I'm grateful that you recognized
that I didn't run away...
I'm grateful to have learned
not to run away when I'm on stage.
I'm truly thankful since it was an
opportunity and time I didn't deserve.
I did music alone but I thank everyone
that made me look great on stage.
Tune in next week for
KPOP STAR 3's live show!
Good-bye!
Subtitles by SBS International