Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
[After the TOP10 finalists
were decided last week...]
[Nam Young-joo held back
her tears but finally cries]
[Even the Shorties
shed tears of joy!]
How many times are
we crying now?
Thank you mom and dad.
I made it this far!
[I love you]
[A few days later...]
[Mok-dong SBS Broadcasting Center]
[The TOP10 finalists arrive
one by one with their bags]
[Today is the TOP10
admission ceremony!]
[Meanwhile...]
[7 cars await the contestants]
[The production crew explains
how rooms will be assigned]
[They give their utmost concentration
since they're picking roommates]
[The male contestants
choose their roommates!]
[Contestants that get in the
same car are roommates!]
[Lee Hae-yong is already in]
[Jung Se-woon is in
a different car...]
[Who will be their roommate?]
[Which car is Bernard running to?]
[He's rooming with Lee Hae-yong!]
[We're sharing a room?]
[Kwon Jin-ah and Kim Ah-hyun!]
This is like a twist of fate!
[Bernard is excited and proposes
that they take a commercial!]
Should we?
You take a drink and
then bat your eyes.
[They're all assigned rooms!]
[They head to their accomodations!]
[They arrived!]
[They're beside themselves]
[These accomodations were specially
prepared for Season 3's TOP10 finalists!]
[What scene awaits them?]
It's spacious! This is great!
It also echoes!
[A spacious, cozy living room
for 5 men to rest in]
[He's happy as if he
gained the world]
What is that?
Don't we look the same? No?
The doll looks better.
That hurt my feelings.
[Soft]
I'm going to lie down.
This is nice.
[Accomodation for the
female contestants]
[Wow! OMG!]
[The female contestants roughly
had a similar response]
Can we drink all of these?
Can I drink this?
[A keyboard was provided so
they can practice at any time!]
I'm getting spirited!
[They finished unpacking...]
Even the calendar's pretty.
[Their schedule is up on
the living room wall]
[A tight schedule!]
[Battle to advance
to the live show]
The schedule's brutal!
[That night...]
[It's time to write their resolution]
[Bernard Park's resolution]
[Use more Korean, improve in singing,
look more natural before the camera]
[What about the youngest?]
[Sam Kim's resolution
"Do your best"]
[Park Na-jin's resolution]
[Day one after getting admitted! Promise
to do my best every day while praying!]
[What did the eldest write?]
[Choi Rin's resolution]
[Be happy, have fun, and be an
Almeng like in the beginning!]
[This is how their first night
comes to an end...]
Lights out, Nam Young-joo!
[Sweet dreams to the TOP10 finalists]
[The joy of passing was
only for a moment!]
[They start practicing for
the TOP10 match!]
It's the TOP10! Of course,
we're more burdened.
I'm really nervous since I have
to act like a TOP10 finalist.
Since I was eliminated at
TOP9 in American Idol...
My biggest challenge is
to make it to TOP9.
My fear is whether
I can make it.
[2 teams will be eliminated
from this TOP10 match!]
[Who will advance to TOP8?]
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 3 will be awarded...
A cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a powerful
mid-size diesel vehicle...
And a compact diesel vehicle.
[The day of the TOP10 match!]
[An awesome set is being built!]
[The contestants arrive with
tension-filled looks!]
[They're getting ready
for recording!]
[They'll perform with a live band!]
[Kwon Tae-eun - KPOP STAR's
music executive]
[The judges arrive 2 hours
before the recording!]
What are you anticipating today?
Season 3 was fun because
it's unpredictable.
There will be several performances
that will go beyond our expectations.
I want to enjoy the competition
between strong contestants.
[Preparations are going smoothly...]
[Now it's the TOP10!]
[The biggest difference!]
[It's performing together
with a professional band!]
[They are a step closer to
being on a professional level!]
[Their first rehearsal with a band!]
I'm nervous because the
stage is big and pretty.
[Now the real battle begins!]
[Within extreme tension...]
[Who will be able to
draw out their skills?]
This is the final hurdle
to the live show!
We, the judges, and the audience
judging panel will be choosing.
[The audience judging panel on
KPOP STAR for the first time!]
The application for the audience
judging panel was done via internet.
[107 were selected carefully after
considering age, gender, and region!]
I'm excited!
I want to watch now.
I flew here from Jeollanam-do.
I believe they will put on their
best performance today.
We'll catch what the 3 judges miss
and judge them objectively.
Good luck!
I'm more curious at who the audience
judging panel will choose and not us.
[10 minutes to the TOP10 battle!]
[The audience judging panel enters!]
[Seeing the grand stage right in
front of them for the first time!]
[They are all seated!]
[The TOP10 finalists leave the waiting
room and head for the backstage]
[Extreme tension!]
My heart feels like
it's going to explode.
[The Shorties relax by
matching their harmony]
[Sam Kim has a hard look]
I'm really nervous and
I'm still trembling.
[Can they overcome this
tremendous tension?]
[The judges head
towards their seats!]
[Overwhelming expectation at the
new means of competition!]
[Cheers and applause like thunder!]
[KPOP STAR judges' and the audience
judging panel's first encounter!]
[They see what's happening
from the backstage!]
I'm afraid...
[They move behind the entrance!]
[The atmosphere is quite
different than usual!]
[MC Jun Hyun-moo enters the stage
to make the opening remarks]
[Wow, it's Jun Hyun-moo!]
Jun Hyun-moo looks great!
[Jun Hyun-moo's first official
recording for KPOP STAR!]
Let's begin!
[The TOP10 battle will begin soon!]
[Different environment!
Extreme tension!]
[The eagerly-anticipated
TOP10 battle begins!]
Hello, I'm Jun Hyun-moo, the emcee
for the third season of KPOP STAR!
Happy to be here.
Season 3 ran for 7 long months starting
with the overseas preliminaries in August.
And the finale is right
around the corner.
This season especially had many outstanding
contestants just like past seasons.
It will be a close match where
the results will be unpredictable.
I will now introduce those that went
through the fierce competition...
And a number of processes
to make it all the way here.
I now introduce the TOP10 finalists
for the third season of KPOP STAR!
[Season 3's TOP10 finalists]
[Gaping at their makeover!]
They are the TOP10 finalists,
the leading roles of Season 3!
- YG?
- Yes?
You must be filled with emotions since
you saw them from Round 1. How is it?
I'm more worried at how nervous
the contestants might be.
I think You Hee-yeol would be
nervous since it's his first time.
- Are you nervous?
- Yes, I'm always nervous.
And amazed... I don't know who's who.
They're very pretty and good-looking.
They're very pretty in person and
they look like celebrities.
I look the least like a celebrity.
They're very glamorous and great.
And JYP, how do you feel?
I'm very nervous because it used to
be just us three judges but...
We have the audience judging panel
together with us today...
[The audience judging panel were
gathered from across the nation!]
I think I have to do
better in judging.
I'll tell you the differences
for this season.
Only 8 out of the 10 here will
advance to the TOP8 live show.
And 2 teams will be eliminated today.
The role of the audience judging panel is
crucial in choosing who is eliminated.
Please watch their performances
carefully and be prudent.
[What judgment will the audience judging
panel make in the TOP10 performances?]
I'll announce the rules
before we begin.
The 10 teams will be divided into
Groups A and B with 5 teams each.
1st, 2nd, and 3rd place will advance
after Group A's battle ends.
And the remaining 2 will become
candidates for elimination.
The same goes for Group B.
Only those that make it to 1st,
2nd, and 3rd place will advance.
[Then what about the 4 teams that
are candidates for elimination?]
[The audience judging panel will
vote for the elimination candidates]
[The 2 teams with the highest votes
will advance to the live show!]
[And the 2 with the lowest votes
will be eliminated!]
[The TOP8 for the live show
will be selected today!]
[Being in a favorable pool and battle
order is as important as their skills!]
[The TOP10 finalists will be choosing
their group and battle order!]
There are various red balls here.
Who would like to go first?
I'll give you that chance.
You're choosing your own fate...
Lee Hae-yong is going to...
He looks the same as
on television.
I thought he would be nervous
but he came out right away.
It's random so you have
to choose carefully.
[Almeng has nerves of steel
but what is their fate?]
It's A-5.
They're going last in Group A.
Almeng will be fifth in Group A.
Please take this with you.
Alright. They're fifth in Group A.
Would that be an advantage?
Who's going next? You're choosing
your own fate anyways...
Okay...
[Second is Something's
Jung Se-woon and Kim Ah-hyun]
You two are a lovely couple.
Will Ah-hyun choose?
Even though you stare at it,
it's not written on the outside.
[Likely winner Almeng is A-5]
[What is Something's fate?]
[Is it a shocking result?]
They're the very last.
The fifth in Group B.
Something is fifth in Group B.
Alright. Group B go up here.
This is like the World Cup
group drawing!
Who's next? As long as we're at it,
let's finish this already.
Should I pick someone?
Should I? Jang Hanna...
[Third is Bernard Park]
[He's getting a lot of
cheers today]
He's going to choose the ball.
What order do you want?
I want to go late... like
I want to go last.
Like you want to go last.
Do you want to be in A or B?
Group B.
I see, Group B. I think he wants to
be fourth since he wants to go last.
A-4! He's fourth in Group A.
Alright, congratulations.
Move to Group A.
It's important whether
you're in Group A or B.
It's important who you battle.
It'll be fun if the Shorties
get into Group A.
[Likely winners Almeng and
Bernard are in Group A!]
[What other teams will
go to Group A?]
- Who's next?
- I'll go.
[Fourth is Jang Hanna]
Going first in Group A is
the most burdening.
She's fourth in Group B.
It seems that those that went first
are at an advantage in the order.
All that's left is 1, 2, and 3
for both Groups A and B.
Next is the Shorties.
[The Shorties are likely winners]
Please choose carefully.
If they're also in Group A,
this is going to be something.
[Currently Almeng and
Bernard are in Group A]
[Will Al, Ber, Shor be
in the same group?]
They're second in Group A.
I was happy when we got fifth
but they're all coming here.
[Likely winners Almeng, Bernard,
and the Shorties in Group A!]
I should've waited.
[Will this be the death group?]
[Group A's battle of likely winners
Almeng, Bernard, and the Shorties!]
All that's left is A-1 and A-3.
A-1 is the most burdening.
There's also B-1, B-2, and B-3.
Everyone's in Group A.
[Who will get eliminated from among
Almeng, Bernard, and the Shorties?]
Next is Kwon Jin-ah.
[A dark horse with
a mighty force]
What order do you want?
I just don't want to
be in that group.
You don't want to be in Group A?
Then Group B is an easy mark?
You just don't want to
be in Group A.
She must be really nervous.
She's third in Group A.
[Shock]
[Alright]
Kwon Jin-ah, it's this way.
You have to go where you chose.
This is Group A. Come to your senses.
Kwon Jin-ah is third in Group A.
I thought Almeng, Bernard, and
the Shorties were in Group B.
I thought, "I'm safe," but they weren't.
I felt that I'm done for now.
Next is Nam Young-joo.
She gave a sigh of relief.
She's third in Group B.
Congratulations.
Next is Bae Min-ah.
She's second in Group B.
Whoever goes to Group A
will have a hard time.
A-1 is left and this death group
will be quite the burden.
Coincidentally, first for
both groups remain.
We have Heejun Han and Sam Kim...
Sam Kim is going first.
What group do you want?
I got A-1.
It's A-1.
[OMG!]
Sam Kim is in the death group.
It's not just Group A but
I'm also going first.
This is it for me. I have to
pack my bags and go home.
That makes Heejun Han
first in Group B.
Heejun Han is in the same
group as Jang Hanna.
I'll announce the groups again.
Group A is Sam Kim, the Shorties,
Kwon Jin-ah, Bernard Park, and Almeng.
Group B is Heejun Han, Bae Min-ah,
Nam Young-joo, Jang Hanna, and Something.
Please give them a big hand!
[Group A prepares for battle
in one part of the stage]
I wasn't nervous until a while ago
but my heart is pounding right now.
Al, Ber, Shor are here.
I'm done for now...
I can't imagine who'll win.
I'm afraid.
They must be very burdened.
We'll begin Group A's battle.
First is Sam Kim!
[A-1, Sam Kim]
It's been 4 months since you
came to Korea. How was it?
[He thought for a long time...]
There wasn't anything hard
but I felt lonely at times.
I'll go to my friends or family
whenever I felt lonely.
I can't do that because
I'm here far away.
It's amazing that I came here.
[One day at his lodging]
Hello?
Mom?
Mom, dad!
Did you watch the broadcast?
- It's a big deal.
- Really?
- They watch when you're not on...
- And ask, "Why isn't he on?"
When you were trembling on stage,
I was also trembling here.
You were a baby when you first went
and now you're all grown up.
You really are something.
[Sam is strengthened by
his family's support]
The TOP8 is decided today.
So I'm nervous and afraid.
It's awkward for me to be in front of people
and I can't really start a conversation.
I'm so nervous because
they're all very good.
There's Bernard, Kwon Jin-ah, Almeng,
and the Shorties in Group A.
They're all strong and
I'm going first in that group.
I thought I have to pack my
bags and get ready to go home.
[First time performing
before an audience]
[Water, please]
[Sam is extremely tense
and is looking for water]
[Good luck!]
[They root for Sam who's
nervous right now...]
[That XX - G-Dragon]
[The studio breaks into applause]
That was by Sam Kim,
first in Group A.
He must have been very nervous for
going first. Let's hear the commentaries.
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
You asked me in the beginning
if I was nervous or not.
I said I wasn't nervous...
But strangely I'm
getting nervous now.
[The judges and audience are all as
nervous as the first contestant]
We've seen many of
Sam's performances.
I think you were the most nervous
today out of all your performances.
[Burden and tension of performing
before an audience for the first time]
But I understand because Sam is 16 and
performing before an audience for the first time.
You arranged it differently from
G-Dragon and sang in a different voice.
It's not an exaggeration to call it
your song since you sang in your style.
I felt uneasy but it was a good
performance. Good job.
[Sam is complimented by YG,
the producer of this song]
The TOP10 battle is like the playoffs.
The regular season is over now.
The good teams in the playoffs
have solid fundamentals.
The one thing I'm worried about you
and feel pity is the fundamentals.
[Sam lacks the fundamentals!]
It didn't drag you down that much but
I'm worried that it'll start to drag you.
It's because you're young and
weren't properly educated.
You exhale too much.
Singing becomes hard for you since
you need to inhale a lot inbetween.
You'll injure yourself because
you strain at the high notes.
If you strengthen your fundamentals,
you'll become a great musician and singer.
You have the talents for it.
I enjoyed it.
[The standards are higher and the
commentaries more objective]
[What is You Hee-yeol's
commentary?]
I'm pleased because we talked a lot
about your rhythm and beats.
The best way to correct that
is to perform with a band.
The experience itself in performing with a
full band is a gift to you by KPOP STAR.
You're only 16.
You're just a year older than
the girl in All Chae.
We were expecting a lot from you
because of your mature looks.
I always think how you can play the guitar
like that and have such musical talents.
I can already imagine how well
you'll do later in your 20s.
You wore like GD but didn't
look anything like him.
- Anyways, you were first...
- He looks like GE, no?
I'm sorry.
Lucky for you that this
isn't the live show.
[No use crying over spilt milk...]
Anyways, you did well for going first.
We give you a big hand.
Thank you.
[Sam was complimented and
pointed out for his performance]
Since you just performed, anything
you would like to say to the judges?
Thank you. I really thank you.
Honestly, I know I'm eliminated.
I truly thank you.
While on KPOP STAR...
- I really learned a lot...
- That isn't true. We don't know.
Nobody knows, right?
- Nobody knows yet.
- We really don't know.
This stage was by Sam Kim!
[He finished his performance
which could be his last]
[But there are people that
cheer him with a big hand]
[Will Sam be able to continue?]
Second is the Shorties!
[The Shorties' stage!]
[The Shorties' family came
from Daegu by train]
[They look more nervous than usual...]
Did you expect to make it to
the TOP10 when you applied?
- Nope!
- Never!
We didn't expect it.
We went to many different auditions
separately but we never made the cut.
This is the first time that
we came out together.
[During the Busan preliminaries]
[They had already shown
their exceptional talents]
We thought we would get
eliminated at Round 1.
It's because we were ordinary...
It's amazing that we're here
and we're still bewildered.
[The Shorties are training hard
for the TOP10 performance!]
[But!]
[Maybe it's due to too much practice but
their body condition became worse!]
[They finally went to the hospital...]
It's H1N1.
[Shock]
You'll recover around Wednesday
or Thursday of next week.
[But the performance is on Monday!]
[Moreover!]
I went to see an ENT doctor...
there was a cyst in my vocal cords.
The doctor said something shocking.
It looks like Reinke's edema...
these are pseudocysts.
- You're the most serious.
- Excuse me?
You might need an operation if that
goes on or becomes severe.
[A desperately dangerous situation
where she can't overuse her voice!]
I'm someone who'll
continue singing...
But that could become difficult
if this continues on...
So I have a lot of worries.
And we felt sorry to each other
to say, "Let's continue practicing."
That was uncomfortable
so it was really hard.
But we went through a lot
to make it this far...
So we'll hang in there and
make a great performance.
I haven't really done anything
to make my mom proud.
But I think I made her proud
by performing on this stage.
It was worth it and
I'm thankful.
My dad participated in the
International Topless Marathon.
We wrote "SBS K-pop The Shorties"
on his chest and ran like that.
He showed me on his cell phone,
"Tae-kyung, look at this."
I was surprised, "Dad!
You ran like that?"
After making it to the TOP10, it's the
first time our family will be watching.
We don't want to disappoint them.
We'll make it a performance where even the
judges and audience won't be disappointed.
[A-2, The Shorties]
[Ryu Tae-kyung's aunt]
[Yeo In-hye's mother]
[Na-jin's mother is already
moist with tears...]
[Brown City - Browneyed Soul]
[Park Na-jin's father]
[Park Na-jin's mother]
[Wild cheers!]
The Shorties were second and just sang
"Brown City" by Browneyed Soul.
Let's hear the commentaries.
[You Hee-yeol goes first!]
Your previous performances were sung
to the piano accompaniment.
The compositions were charming
and like a musical.
But this time, you
went head-to-head.
It's not easy for your voices to be heard
above a full band especially with the brass.
But your voices were above it.
The sound reached us here.
You truly are something.
You feel like pros now.
Another thing is that I didn't know it was
the Shorties because of the clothes.
Especially Na-jin.
It feels like I'm seeing someone else.
It's as if you're out for blood.
Your performance drilled it in deeply
that this is actually the TOP10 match.
It feels like part 2 of
the Shorties is starting.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[This performance showed another
development of the Shorties!]
I agree with You Hee-yeol.
The contents are the same but
the thoughts are opposite.
[What does he mean?]
Your skills improved. That's true.
Your voices were above the
accompaniment. That's true.
But I'm worried about that.
Since you sang throughout trying
to sing loud and powerful...
Your natural voices disappeared.
Singers have this mike.
Try to rely on the mike and sing
as if you're singing in your voice.
If you do pass, place trust in the mike
and sing comfortably and naturally...
If you return to the voices when
you had fun, I think it'll be better.
That was a pity.
[What is YG's commentary?]
I was taking notes while
you were singing.
And I was thinking of giving
a good commentary.
But it's the first time that the
judges had the same commentary.
Just as You Hee-yeol articulated...
Despite the loud sounds of the drums
and brass, their voices were above them.
I would like to compliment
you on that point.
Compared to soccer, the goalie
and players on defense...
Since this is an important round,
they ran to the front and made a goal.
This performance was new
compared to previous ones.
"Wow, they could do
something like this?"
[Their new strength stood out
in this performance!]
I wanted to compliment first
because I felt that.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[Their family are now at ease...]
This stage was by the Shorties.
Please remember it.
They'll return to their seats.
The Shorties are very
beautiful today.
Very beautiful.
[They're innocent for
their makeover!]
You've been hiding your beauty.
Securely!
[No one can stop him]
[What is their fate as they
showed a new potential?]
Third is Kwon Jin-ah!
[Kwon Jin-ah's stage!]
- Jin-ah?
- Yes?
- Were you well?
- Yes.
I saw you waving
from over there...
Who were you waving at?
My parents and sister came...
[Her family came from
Busan to cheer her]
- Aren't you nervous?
- Completely.
Your clothes look nice.
Thank you.
You may begin.
[He tries to make her feel
relaxed before starting]
No one in my family is into music
so they were adamantly against it.
They thought I would continue in my studies
and didn't think I would become a singer.
But my sister supported me saying,
"She needs to go on this path."
When I was discouraged for
not making it last season...
She said, "Other singers went to hundreds
of auditions. How many times did you go?"
Her support and the courage she gave
allowed me to come this far.
You applied last year?
Yes, but I didn't make the
regional preliminaries.
My dad boasted to his friends showing a
clip of me saying, "That's my daughter."
And my mom became a star
among her students.
It's been a while since I saw
my friends because I'm from Busan.
I really miss them...
I want to chat with them
when I see them.
[So we came to Busan!]
[She wore her school uniform and
now she's in the 11th grade]
[She came to school to be assigned
to her classes and get her books]
[She visited her old classroom
when she was in the 10th grade]
I used to goof off and lie down on
these lockers and get in trouble.
We used to gather
around this mirror.
What's wrong with my hair?
Oh! The bell's ringing!
[It's bringing back old memories]
[She misses her friends even more
being in the empty classroom]
[But?]
[Who's that hanging around
outside the classroom?]
[Surprise visit by her friends!]
[This is how girls react
when they're happy]
[They greet each other
after calming down]
- Did you dye your hair?
- Yup.
[Her friends are amazed at
how beautiful she became]
Seeing you makes me feel like
I returned to the past...
[Seeing her friends fills
her with emotion]
You sound like a Seoulite.
[Is she more comfortable
speaking in a Seoul accent?]
You're already a star.
I came to get my books and
get classes assigned but...
I'm thankful that they were
happy to see me...
They told me to do well and that
they were cheering and watching me.
It really moved me.
I'll try hard and do my best since
a lot of people are cheering for me.
I'm singing Primary's "See Through."
[An exciting song in the soul, punk
genres but based on hip-hop]
When I sang "I Need a Girl"...
JYP said that I sing sad songs well
but can't sing exciting songs.
I'm going to show that
I can sing an exciting song.
The original song is in a hip-hop style
but I arranged it in an acoustic style.
You'll feel something different.
[A-3, Kwon Jin-ah]
[What will her performance be like?]
[See Through (ft. Gaeko, Zion.T) - Primary]
[Breaks into applause]
[JYP grabs the mike right away]
I said earlier that teams with solid
fundamentals win the playoffs.
You really have solid fundamentals.
And you improved each round during
this season of KPOP STAR.
I said there were contestants with
too much air in their voice...
And there were contestants that
strain their throat to sing powerfully.
Sometimes you have air and no air.
Your voice is solid then soft...
Being able to play around with the tone
is fact of your solid fundamentals.
I was mesmerized when you sang
the high notes in the middle.
I personally think that you made the most
improvement in singing this season.
Your performance was flawless.
I really enjoyed it
and you did well.
[She received the best
compliment ever!]
[The next contestant is
getting more nervous...]
Being with JYP for 3 years made me
to see distinct features in his evaluation.
His voice is raised an octave
when he really likes something.
[JYP can't hide what he likes]
The viewers might have
felt this as well.
Singing well and high in auditions,
and the many things JYP pointed out...
Relaxing the shoulders, keeping the chin in,
and singing as if speaking are all important.
But the most important thing is
how well one can lead the song.
Kwon Jin-ah led this song well.
She didn't stand out for me
among the TOP10 finalists.
But I'm seeing her a little
and able to see her charms.
I would like to compliment her.
It was exciting and she wasn't nervous.
That's how well she steered the song.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[And You Hee-yeol?]
Your strength is...
No matter what song you sing,
it becomes your song.
This was Primary's "See Through"
but the original is completely different.
It's as if she has a filter and it comes
out saying, "This is my song."
It's delicious when you sing.
The first measure, B part, and
chorus are all different.
Compared to a drama,
it has all the four steps.
Above all, you look natural
when you sing.
You don't look unnatural or
look as if you're trying.
Kwon Jin-ah looks mature but
she's now in the 11th grade.
Now I'm convinced that she
has unlimited potential.
- I enjoyed it.
- Thank you.
[She was lavished with
compliments by the judges]
She's getting better
by the day.
What more is there to say?
It was the best!
It's game over!
[Will she make it to TOP8?]
Now it's our fourth contestant.
Next is Bernard Park!
We changed him into a suit from
his cardigans at JYPE but...
Now he wears it under the suit...
[He sure loves his cardigans]
It was a good compromise.
You may begin.
How do you feel after
making it to the TOP10?
I feel great.
My goal was to make it
to the TOP10.
What if you didn't make it?
Then...
I give up on music.
This was my final attempt...
[Is there something
we don't know?]
[At the Atlanta audition
six months ago]
[Many experienced
the joy of passing!]
[Bernard passed with flying colors]
[But he doesn't look happy]
[Interview in Atlanta]
[This considerate young man couldn't
be happy even though he passed]
[And finally!]
[He decided to go to Korea
for his dreams!]
Do you think you made the
right choice in coming?
[He takes another step
towards his dream!]
[A-4, Bernard Park]
[Words I Want to Say - Kim Tae-woo]
[Wild cheers from the female members
of the audience judging panel!]
[Do the judges feel the same?]
In Bernard's case, we always
expected him to make it to TOP3.
The voice that he has is...
In the heavyweight class and
the others are lightweight.
We heard many of your
good points today...
I would like to give you a tip
in making it to the TOP3.
You're a heavyweight
but you look heavy.
I want your steps to be light
even though you're a heavyweight.
Your rich, full voice and high notes are
great but your tone is a little heavy.
Your weakness is that your
singing sounds monotonous.
Your punches should be of heavyweight
but your steps need to be light.
If you correct that,
TOP3 will be possible.
This is an important round so I wanted
to give advice than compliments.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
[He heard harsh advice first]
[Next is You Hee-yeol]
This must have been your
most difficult song.
This is a very dramatic song.
It goes up from the bridge and
you go all out in falsetto later.
And this is gayo. You sang
a traditional ballad.
I watched with interest.
I had my doubts thinking all
you can sing are R&Bs.
But in this song...
It wasn't enough but you know
how they say class is forever.
Since you basically have
power in your voice...
You do have potential.
You did well.
[He received a positive commentary]
The reason I fell for Bernard is
when he sang "End of the Road."
You simplified a song with
8 chords into 4 chords.
When you sang a
detailed song like that...
I thought, "Where did he
get such confidence?"
And I was moved by
that simplicity.
But...
You have this great power to
simplify detailed things.
But I'm thinking maybe you're
not able to do the opposite.
It has to be more detailed,
especially so with gayo.
That's what I'm worried about.
[Objective commentaries due to
the high judging standards]
[Outside the studio!]
[Voting ballots are being placed
for the 4 elimination candidates!]
[2 teams among them will be
candidates for elimination!]
[The death group,
Group A's battle!]
[Which 2 teams will be
candidates for elimination?]
[Ilsan Bitmaru Broadcasting Support Center]
This stage was by Bernard Park.
Please remember it.
Now we have our final battle.
Next is Almeng!
[Feels it wasn't good enough...]
[Almeng is getting ready
within the heavy mood]
[Choi Rin's mother]
[Lee Hae-yong's mother]
Before you begin...
Your throat was in a bad condition
during the battle audition.
Is it better?
Yes, I can do well.
Really? That's a relief.
But this song is unexpected.
It's Song Chang-sik's
"Cigarette Store Girl."
I can't imagine how
they'll sing this.
Many made remakes of this song but
I don't think a mixed duet ever did it.
He's playing a show off
that's trying to hit on me.
I'm stuck-up saying,
"I don't like you."
We chose this song because it can
show our power and excitement.
Did you expect to make it to
TOP10 when you applied?
No.
We thought we couldn't even
make the booth preliminaries.
We were supposed to sing but danced,
wait, was it an impersonation?
I can impersonate Park Hyo-shin's
"A loud shout to the front!"
Can I dance?
[6 months ago, they wanted to
pass the preliminaries at least]
You know how we draw a picture
of our future when we're young.
I always drew myself
singing with a mike.
I guess this was my dream
since I was young.
I was part of a band in middle and
high school and continued music.
I was a trainee at a
small agency a year ago.
After I stopped being a trainee,
I didn't think of being a singer.
It was hard and I thought,
"Maybe I can't be a singer."
People around me say that I'm good
but I had nothing to prove that.
I put it aside and thought
this would be my last try.
And that is KPOP STAR.
Suddenly I'm in the TOP10
and I'm really thankful.
[Her miraculous final opportunity when
she was about to give up on her dream]
[During the TOP10 prematch]
[The mucuous membrane in her vocal cords
ruptured but she sang in that condition!]
I wasn't able to show as much as I prepared
last time but my voice is much better now.
So I'll do my best this time.
We'll perform with confidence
and make it to TOP8.
We'll make it.
[A-5, Almeng]
[Cigarette Store Girl - Song Chang-sik]
This mustached man hits on me
At our cigarette store
That blonde I have my eyes on
Her smooth looks are attractive
If a hunk like me approaches her
She'll take off the mask in her heart
Even American Heejun was
Turned down by her
Even "Resonance" Bernard was
I'm on a roll in this town
And I'm the only one left
Look forward to it
It's coming soon
If I end my sentences with "oppa"
He might start talking big
The pads in his shoulders are
As big as Lady Gaga's
I laugh because I'm dumbfounded
But he laughs because he likes it
It's him again
He's coming
How much will be enough?
You see these car keys?
Are those your dad's?
Just because I'm in this store
Doesn't mean I'm dumb
I can't believe I'm treated like this
By someone as ridiculous as you
"How much can you give me?"
Don't even think about it
Being a grouch and naughty
Doesn't make you a bad boy
You make a pass in every city
But you can't hit on me
Early next morning
I go to buy cigarettes
I secretly take out
A designer bag I brought
I'll wink at her
When she's startled
She's a bit stuck-up
Even though it has no fragrance
An artificial flower's fine
If your sincere heart won't fade
I don't care what I do
That girl in our neighborhood
Desires a sincere heart
I'll add some fragrance to that
Beautiful artificial flower
Since you have an innocent heart
You look more attractive
Am I really attractive?
Are you nuts about me?
I'm going to buy cigarettes again
[A tremendous applause]
[The mothers are moist with tears
seeing them perform for the first time]
[What are the judges' commentaries?]
Choi Rin's voice is
almost back to normal.
How did you recover so quickly?
I took extreme care.
I wore a mask, drank 3-4 L of water
every day, and took my medication.
I asked because your throat wasn't in
a condition to recover that quickly.
You kept your throat warm, took water and
medication, and followed the doctor's orders...
I felt that's how you recovered.
[Every day after the
battle audition...]
[She tried very hard to
recover her voice]
You shouldn't be scolded for hurting
your throat or catching the cold.
Since that can happen no matter
how well you take care of yourself.
But the judges will scold you if you
talk loud with others and on the phone.
Taking care of yourself means to
not get sick before you do get sick.
And being careful to recover
when you do get sick.
That's taking care of yourself.
It doesn't mean not getting sick.
Such attitude is necessary if you're
going to do music all your life.
I was surprised by that.
Choi Rin's singing, rapping, conveying
the lyrics, performance, and talents...
You get a perfect for
today's performance.
Almeng will be a frightening team.
You sang well and it was great.
[A warm encouragement for Almeng
that showed their earnest efforts]
I saw the lyrics as
you were singing.
"I'm fine even though it's an artificial
flower without fragrance." It rhymed here.
[Even though it has no fragrance]
[An artificial flower's fine]
"I'll add some fragrance to that
beautiful artificial flower."
Such lyrics... maybe it's
because I'm sensitive...
How did they write such lyrics?
That's how good it was.
I congratulate you on
recovering your voice.
I look forward to a better performance
since your voice will be much better.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[Two judges encouraged
and complimented them]
I want to say two things.
When Choi Rin rapped, this
part was really impressive.
"You make a pass in every city
but you can't hit on me."
It made a big impact.
I see you're very good at that
and would like to compliment you.
And the second thing is...
If you do get good results,
what can you do next time?
I can predict it now.
We complimented you last time despite
your throat condition because...
It was different.
Today was your trademark performance.
It was humorous with cute acting.
I think your task will be
to go beyond that.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
[High standards and a
fierce competition]
[Who will make it to the TOP8?]
All the contestants in
Group A have finished.
Let's have all 5 teams on the stage.
Please give them a round of applause.
[Now it's the fated moment!]
[The judges begin their discussion
to choose who passes!]
We don't know the results so we did our
best every day thinking we might pass.
I realized that this is the right path
for me after making it to TOP10.
TOP10 was our goal during
the battle audition.
But now we want to go
more and more.
[The Shorties' Yeo In-hye's mother]
[Almeng's Choi Rin's mother]
[Discussion is over!]
[Which three teams did
the judges choose?]
Please announce
the top 3 teams.
We'll announce the 3 teams
that made it to the TOP8.
[Which 3 did the judges choose?]
1st place is...
[The Shorties' Yeo In-hye's mother]
[Kwon Jin-ah's mother]
You must have expected it...
It's Kwon Jin-ah!
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Kwon Jin-ah is the first to
advance to TOP8 from Group A.
Kwon Jin-ah, how do you feel?
Did you expect this?
I trembled a lot and don't know
how I finished but thank you.
Let's give her another
round of applause.
I can't believe it!
[She beat Al, Ber, Shor and
confidently took 1st place!]
[She's overwhelmed
and can't speak]
She's rising as the dark horse!
Please announce 2nd place.
The remaining 4 teams were
lacking in some areas.
Sam Kim trembled for going first and
lacking fundamentals due to age.
Bernard lacks in rendering
the song with detail.
The Shorties did well but sounded like
established singers for the first time.
Almeng was predictable.
It wasn't easy to choose
2 from the 4 teams.
We choose two after a
long discussion...
But the two that passed need to be
on their toes and give more effort.
And we hope the two that are
eliminated won't be discouraged.
2nd place for TOP8 is...
[All 4 teams received not that
good of a commentary!]
[Who did the judges
pick for 2nd place?]
It's the Shorties.
Congratulations.
The Shorties are second to advance.
Please tell us how you feel?
Thank you.
We didn't know if
we would pass.
We were surprised.
Thank you for choosing us.
We'll do our best.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
[The Shorties' Ryu Tae-kyung's aunt]
[They can't believe that
they're 2nd place]
Please announce the last team that will
advance to the TOP8 from Group A.
First...
I would like to say that the two that
didn't pass gave a great performance.
All 3 teams did well but
were also lacking.
Please don't lose courage.
The final judgment will be made
by the audience judging panel.
This was very hard...
3rd place for TOP8 is...
[The best were gathered in
Group A the death group!]
[Bernard Park has a voice
that resonates in the heart]
[Sam Kim is a guitar
genius with soul]
[Almeng is a witty ideas bank]
[Those not called will become
candidates for elimination!]
[Who will be 3rd place?]
3rd place for TOP8 is...
[The best were gathered in
Group A the death group!]
[Bernard Park has a voice
that resonates in the heart]
[Sam Kim is a guitar
genius with soul]
[Almeng is a witty ideas bank]
[Those not called will become
candidates for elimination!]
[Who will be 3rd place?]
It's Almeng!
Congratulations. Almeng is
the third to advance.
[Almeng's Lee Hae-yong's mother]
[They calmly accept the results]
[Bernard Park and Sam Kim from Group A
are candidates for elimination!]
[Lee Hae-yong passed
but he doesn't smile]
[Even JYP doesn't feel good]
Hae-yong doesn't look happy.
What's wrong?
Shouldn't you be happy for
advancing to the TOP8?
Bernard was my roommate
and I also had fun with Sam.
- I don't feel that great.
- I see. You feel sorry?
- Yes.
- I see.
Anyways, the judges were discreet.
Kwon Jin-ah is 1st, the Shorties are 2nd,
and Almeng is 3rd from Group A.
They advance to the TOP8 live show.
Please give them a big hand.
Sam Kim and Bernard Park aren't eliminated.
They are just candidates for elimination.
I wonder how they feel.
Let's ask Sam first.
How do you feel?
It's a pity.
Let's give him a hand.
Why don't we hear what
Bernard has to say?
Let's give him a hand.
Please remember that the elimination candidates
from Group A are Sam Kim and Bernard Park.
With the elimination candidates from
Group B after they are done...
The last two teams for the
TOP8 will be decided by votes.
Please give them a big hand!
[They feel relieved after
coming down the stage]
- It's over now!
- Look at this sweat.
[They let out a sigh of relief]
[Bernard is in shock!]
[First time seeing this
side of Bernard!]
[Their names are placed on the ballots
for the candidates for elimination!]
[How many votes will they receive
from the audience judging panel?]
[They enter the waiting room for the
candidates for elimination weakly]
Subtitles by SBS International