Survival Audition KPOP Star S3
It's the season finale
of KPOP STAR!
[From 11 cities around the world such as
the US, Europe, China and Japan]
[A big run of 8 months to find
the next K-pop star!]
The contestants improved more
than we imagined in Season 3.
We didn't drag them along. This is
a path that we will walk together.
So we were very happy to
meet each and every one.
There were times when
I learned from the contestants.
There were times when I became
passionate after seeing their passion.
[And!]
[First time ever on an audition! The winner
chooses the desired agency on the spot!]
The contestants were nervous on the stage,
but now the 3 agencies are nervous.
I was cold and pointed things out.
I think I'm at a disadvantage.
I think Antenna Music has the best
group of musicians in Korea.
I'd be happy to get
such an opportunity.
Whether you're the winner or runner-up,
this will be your final performance.
I hope the two of you will do
your best. Good luck!
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 3!
I introduce you to the TOP2
for the season finale!
The first candidate is...
Bernard Park who touches all
with just his voice!
The second candidate is...
Sam Kim, a soul genius who
shines the most on stage!
Give them another round of applause
for making it to the final round!
Glad that you're with us live.
I'm MC Jun Hyun-moo.
It's finally the day!
This show had many twists and
it was the talk of the town.
It is now the season finale.
You will be able to meet the
3rd K-pop star today.
Please stay tuned to find out which of
these two young men will be the winner.
I introduce you to the three judges
that will judge impartially today.
First is JYPE's Park Jin-young!
YGE's Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Music's You Hee-yeol!
- YG?
- Yes?
Today is the last day and I think the
judges are as nervous as these two.
How are you feeling?
I would like to say that it's the first time that
two men are battling in the final this season.
This is the moment I have anticipated
and waited for since the show started.
The winner gets to choose the desired
agency on the spot in this season.
Those two are nervous but we
judges are nervous as well.
You three don't look
so good today.
It's the first time ever on an audition
for the winner to choose on the spot.
JYP, please say something so that
the winner can choose carefully.
Choosing an agency is
very important, so...
Forget all of my bad commentaries and
how I coldly pointed things out.
- Please see me in a good light.
- He's suddenly maintaining a right image.
You Hee-yeol, please say something since
they're young and might be nervous.
Bernard and Sam are truly something to
have made it past hundreds of thousands.
Don't be nervous and put everything
aside since you two are the best.
Put on the best performance. Why don't
the audience give them a big hand?
Please give them a hand.
Many came to cheer reminding us of
the Korea-Japan soccer match.
I have something to ask
before we start.
I heard that the two of you are
the closest out of all the contestants.
Sam, have you ever thought of
facing each other in the final?
- I never expected it.
- You never expected it.
I still can't believe
that I'm actually here.
I'm grateful to the judges and fans
that allowed me to make it this far.
I'm happy to be here
with Bernard as well.
Alright. And you, Bernard?
I never knew I'd make it this far.
I'm happy to be in the final
with my closest friend.
Bernard, who do you
think will win?
I'm not sure but
I'll do my best.
What do you think, Sam?
Speak into the mike.
I don't know either
but I'll do my best.
That's different from what
you said in the waiting room.
The winner gets $300,000 and a midsize vehicle,
and the runner-up gets a compact vehicle.
Please look forward to
who will be the winner.
I'll explain today's rules.
There will be two rounds.
The judges give a mission in Round 1 and
the contestants pick freely in Round 2.
The judges' score is 60% and the
real-time viewers' vote is 40%.
The one with the highest total
will be Season 3's winner.
Please stay tuned to find out
who will be the new K-pop star.
I will now announce their
number and order.
No. 1 Sam Kim is a musical
genius to be reckoned with.
No. 2 Bernard Park has a voice
that touches the sentiments.
Those are some cheers.
Since the final is neck and neck,
your votes are very important.
Yoo Hye-young will explain
how you can participate.
- Yoo Hye-young?
- Yes, that's me.
You are watching the season finale.
I'll explain how you can vote.
Text "1" or "Sam Kim" to #0606 or
"2" or "Bernard Park" on your phone.
As you know, you can vote for Sam or
Bernard but no multiple votes.
You can also vote via KakaoTalk
so I hope many can participate.
We will begin soon.
Are you ready?
Text voting starts now!
[Text voting begins]
[Text the contestant's name in Korean or
number to #0606 (10 cents data charge)]
Your participation is crucial
since the winner is decided.
There are special performances prepared
other than the two contestants.
Please look forward to the performances
by this season's contestants and judges.
Season 1's winner and member of 15&,
Park Ji-min, will reveal a new song.
Please look forward
to that as well.
Let's begin the performances
for the season finale.
First is Round 1 the mission stage.
This stage is by No. 1 Sam Kim!
[Right after last week's show...]
[The judges gather to
choose a song]
Sam is completely different now
compared to six months ago...
I want him to trust his voice
and fully convey it to us.
[They have decided!]
- What is this?
- This week's mission.
[What mission did the
judges give Sam?]
"Show us a performance where
you focus more on your voice."
[The judges want him to combine
his voice and amazing guitar skills]
I feel uneasy.
I arranged it to show my guitar skills but
they want me to show more of my voice.
I feel uneasy.
[What song did Sam choose?]
[What song made him laugh?]
Huh?
[Is it hard to predict?]
I'm burdened.
It's BIGBANG's "Lies."
BIGBANG held many concerts
and did many arrangements.
But the most difficult was "Lies."
It's hard to arrange it.
It'll be great if he does a
lyrical rendition but...
It won't be easy.
You have a video message.
From who?
[He plays it right away]
Oh! It's mom.
Even I'm nervous.
I anticipate, cry, and get excited
every time I watch your performance.
I really love you and
miss you. Bye.
It's grandma!
Do I start?
I'm so proud of you, Sam.
Everyone talks about you.
Bye, until we meet again.
This is great.
I've been having a hard time but
it was great to hear their voices.
I arranged it to fit my style and
to focus more on my voice.
I hope my voice will be pleasing
since I put everything into it.
[Lies - BIGBANG]
[Music director - Kwon Tae-eun
Bandmaster - Seo Young-do]
This stage was by No. 1 Sam Kim
who played his rendition of "Lies."
What did the judges think?
Let's hear the commentaries.
Who will grab the mike first?
JYP?
We gave him a mission to
focus more on his voice.
Sam has proven how great of a
performance he can give.
As a composer and producer...
We're curious of how his voice
will sound in a recording studio.
I don't think this was an appropriate
performance to focus on his voice.
We weren't able to fully
hear his voice, but...
We were curious of the arrangement
and it was satisfyingly amazing.
JYP's score...
His arrangement was amazing
but not his voice...
It's 91!
Next is You Hee-yeol.
One good thing as I was
listening to the song...
All of your weaknesses are gone.
Even your fundamentals are solid.
But there is one thing.
This is the final.
I don't think this song choice
was geared to you.
Antenna Music's score...
The song choice was a pity.
What is the score?
It's 93!
Let's hear YG's commentary.
Since BIGBANG is under YGE,
I saw it in a good light.
BIGBANG held many concerts
and did many arrangements.
I said in the clip that this is going
to be hard since it was attempted.
It's crucial how close or off the
arrangement is to the original.
But it was an appropriate arrangement
that was beyond my expectations.
JYP said it would be better if he did a
song that showed more of his voice.
Since he already said it,
I'll say something else.
Vocalization and techniques
don't need to be by the book.
Every artist has a different personality.
It's important to sing well, but...
In terms of personality, I do believe
that Sam possesses his own voice.
YG's score...
He complimented on the
arrangement. The score is...
It's 94!
He has 278!
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "1" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Sam Kim!
[What do the judges want
to see from Bernard?]
I want him to sing
an actual gayo.
Some viewers thirst for Bernard.
I absolutely want to see him
overcome that, at least in the final.
Me too.
[What is Bernard's fate?]
[He gets the judges' mission
the following day...]
"Sing with a gayo sentiment
naturally as if speaking."
[Deep in thought...]
[What will he choose?]
[He gets Bernard's choice]
He'll win if he does well.
These two...
They're pros at choosing now
since this is the final.
[What song did he choose?]
It's Yoo Jae-ha's
"Because I Love You."
Bernard can put his emotions
into this gayo at least.
But it's really difficult.
He's going head on.
If I'm to sing as if speaking, I heard
Yoo Jae-ha was the best in Korea.
I liked it as I kept
listening to his songs.
I wanted to sing this in the final
even before I got my mission.
Even though I practice...
I have to try to understand
the lyrics of the song.
I listened to it all day.
I read the lyrics as I listened and
thought about it to make it mine.
I'm trying to make it as
close as the original.
[Because I Love You - Yoo Jae-ha]
Bernard went head on
by singing a gayo.
He sang "Because I Love You"
as the song for his mission.
What commentaries will the
judges make for him?
You Hee-yeol?
Bernard can sing gayo now.
But...
The final is interesting
and amazing.
I thought it was game over
when he started singing.
But?
He made a mistake in the
lyrics towards the end.
Then he missed his breathing.
The outcome became questionable.
But you sang gayo very well.
Antenna Music's score...
He sang gayo well but made
mistakes. What is the score?
It's 95!
Next is JYP.
It's hard to hide how much a person
practiced or put effort into it.
As I saw him sing...
I could see how much thought
he put into it and practiced.
That was great but...
Now I have assurance that
you can sing gayo well.
But just as You Hee-yeol said...
But you broke down quickly
after making a mistake.
That lowered your score.
JYP's score...
The final is making him nervous.
He made mistakes but...
It's 95!
That mistake was a pity. YG?
This is an important round,
but he can make mistakes.
He could get the lyrics
wrong because...
That can happen if he's
really into the feeling...
And also because he's not
good in Korean yet.
When he sang the first measure...
I always compared him to a heavyweight.
Sam is sitting there but I thought,
"Sam needs to be careful today."
This heavyweight removed his gloves.
There's a chance for Sam to get
KO'd if he gets hit by that.
I thought Sam should avoid well in
Round 2 since this is Round 1.
It's a pity due to the mistake
since you could have gotten 100.
YG's score...
Both Sam and Bernard's
flushed faces are memorable.
It's 96!
He has 286 and taking the lead!
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "2" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Bernard Park!
I can see that they're enjoying it
as they appreciate the music.
But there's still Round 2 even though
Bernard is in the lead with 286 points.
Please stay tuned since there
could be a twist in Round 2.
I'll introduce the first
special stage.
Last week was Akdong Musician but today,
Park Ji-min prepared a special comeback.
Let's watch 15&'s comeback stage!
[Can't Hide It - 15&]
That was a great performance.
Park Ji-min used to be a contestant but
she's back on stage as a JYP artist.
Seems like there will be a storm
on the music charts again.
You are watching the season finale
live and now it's Round 2.
They choose their own songs.
The winner is decided after
two performances in Round 2.
A warm round of applause for
the tense two contestants!
[Sam gets into the car
and goes somewhere]
Where are we going?
Ham Chun-ho said...
Remember he'll lend you his guitar
if you make it to the final?
Yes.
[When Sam learned the guitar from
Ham Chun-ho at Antenna Music]
I'll lend you my guitar
if you make it to the final.
[That promise was made
around 2 months ago...]
There's this huge banner reading...
"Go to the final with
Ham Chun-ho's guitar!"
I believe I'm giving my soul
by lending him my guitar.
[Sam Kim is going to
Ham Chun-ho's house]
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
When did we last meet?
- 2 or 3 months?
- 2 months, right?
Your guitar skills improved
a lot during that time.
You're really enjoying the stage.
This guitar is different because
it has a richer sounding lows.
[He plays right away]
- I like the feel.
- I know, right?
[Ham Chun-ho's guitar will be
with him at the final stage]
You have to be the winner
when you return this.
Do your best and enjoy it.
Looking forward to a good result.
I have the strength to practice
since he lent me a great guitar.
This is HIS guitar...
So I have this responsibility
to do well with his guitar.
[What is Sam's final song?]
How does Sam know this song?
This was unexpected.
This is an important song that
could determine his victory.
It's Sting's "Englishman in New York."
It's a risk.
It's definitely a risk.
Sam has to be more detailed
unlike his energetic style.
I've been complimented
until now for fast songs.
I wanted to be recognized for
a different style of song.
I've been playing fast but
this one will be soft.
I've practiced hard and I'm going on
stage with Ham Chun-ho's guitar.
I want it to be great.
Thank you, Ham Chun-ho!
Sam Kim's groove is back!
Sam Kim was somewhat
tense and flushed but...
He showed his talented groove
and sprang back to life.
JYP can't seem to close his mouth.
I'm saying this a second time
but Sam was crazy in this song.
The three of us made eye contact
when he started playing the guitar.
How did he even think of starting
with such a playing style?
It was an unexpected style.
The other thing is the lyrics.
Sting is an Englishman.
"It was awkward being in the US
but 'be yourself.' I'll act myself."
"I'm an Englishman in New York but I'll be
myself." He was just like the lyrics.
"I'm a stranger in Korea but I'll
be myself." And he did just that.
It was hard to take off
points. JYP's score...
Sam Kim gets the highest score
when he's recognized for who he is.
It's 99!
It's the highest score so far.
I think he found his pace.
Who's going next?
YG?
Sam Kim made a difficult choice in
Round 1 by doing BIGBANG's "Lies."
I was really worried in this round
because he chose Sting's song.
Since he sang a style
he never sang before.
I've danced for years.
It's hard to do a slow dance than a fast one,
and the same thing goes for rapping.
There's nothing more to expect
from Sam's performance now.
Nothing more?
It was such an amazing performance that
I'd like to give more points if I could.
I think Sting would be pleased
if he happens to watch this.
YG's score...
He said he wanted to give more.
What is the score?
It's 100!
Ain't that something?
He was a little tense in Round 1
but he regained his smile.
The outcome is unpredictable.
You Hee-yeol is next.
I remembered when I first met
Sam as I listened to this.
He was playing the guitar and
we, the judges, were amazed.
Then 6-7 months passed...
But such an arrangement can't
be done by a 16 or 17-year-old.
Even pro musicians can't do this.
His voice and all that doesn't matter
because Sam is really really good.
Compliments one after another.
It seems my commentaries for this
performance are just additions.
Sam, it was the best ever!
Antenna Music's score...
What is the score after
all those compliments?
It's 100!
He has 299 and finished Round 2
by springing back to life!
Those cheering for Sam Kim can
text "1" or "Sam Kim" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 1 Sam Kim!
[One day, with the final ahead]
Is there somewhere you wanted
to go when you came to Korea?
I wanted to go to the beach.
[A short trip for Bernard
before the final]
I went to the beach a lot with my family
as a kid when I first came to Korea.
I swam a lot and we gathered
clams that we ate at home.
That's why I wanted to go to
the beach again when I came.
[The beach holds many memories
and he's back as an adult]
I came to Korea for my dreams but
didn't have time due to practice.
I felt great to be out
of the practice room.
[It was a significant time
even though it was short]
[What is his final song?]
This song...
He knew he would make it to the final
and intentionally saved this, right?
[R. Kelly's "I Believe I Can Fly"]
It feels like he brought this out
to deliver his sunday punch.
Just a graze from this
punch will kill you.
This song is saying that your dreams
will come true if you believe in yourself.
All of us are on this show
because of our dreams.
It fits my situation...
I have to believe in myself to make it
come true so I chose this song.
- What does it mean?
- I'm going to be first.
How do you feel as this is
your last interview?
My last interview...
I feel sad that this show
is going to end now.
I like being on stage.
I just wanted to be in the TOP10
when I came to Korea.
I'm thankful to those
cheering for me.
I want to stand on such stages if
I'm going to be a singer in Korea.
This stage was by Bernard the angel
as if he was going to ascend.
This was his second song, but it's
hard to tell what the judges thought.
What are their commentaries?
You Hee-yeol is first.
I was curious of how
he would sing this...
Since I thought it was
the perfect song for him.
Your voice is hoarse
from practice, right?
He said it is.
Your greatest charm is what JYP said
and that's half air, half sound.
The substance is enveloped with air
as if your voice is coated.
You start to strain because
your voice is hoarse.
It's as if that coated air
became volatile.
It's a pity that you couldn't
fully show this song's charm.
But...
- Bernard is still the best.
- He's still the best.
Antenna Music's score...
He didn't fully show his
skills but he's the best...
It's 97! That's a high score.
Next is JYP.
It was like a scam when I heard
that he's singing this song.
I thought he would put on his best
performance since it's like a foul.
But when he started singing,
it wasn't his voice.
Half of his voice was gone.
I was thinking, "What's going on?"
He couldn't focus on the feeling
because he couldn't control his voice.
No matter how well he sings...
He can't throw that sunday punch
if he's not connected to the feeling.
I don't know what happened to his voice
but this wasn't his best performance.
It's a pity but just as
You Hee-yeol said...
Your voice is still there.
JYP's score...
His voice was great but the feeling
was a pity. What is the score?
It's 95!
Next is YG.
I thought it would've been better
if the order was switched.
I think he wouldn't have made mistakes
if he had sung this song first.
I didn't say it in the clip but I was
worried when you chose this song.
You have an R&B tone to your voice but
your singing is different from black artists.
That's why you exploded when
you sang Richard Marx's song.
The distinct nasal bending of
black artists is important in this song.
I was worried about how
you will sing this.
Since you gave many moving performances,
this one didn't meet my expectations.
YG's score...
Let's see the score.
What is it?
It's 95!
He has 287!
Those cheering for Bernard Park can
text "2" or "Bernard Park" to #0606.
Voting can also be
done via KakaoTalk.
This stage was by
No. 2 Bernard Park!
All the performances are over
but voting is still going on.
Please hurry if you
haven't done so.
It's time for the second
special stage.
JYP and You Hee-yeol were always
judging but they left their seats.
They prepared a special stage.
Let me ask YG. What is it?
JYP and You Hee-yeol are doing a
collaboration with the contestants.
I don't know what
they are doing but...
Since JYP pointed out many
things for the contestants...
I'll be objective and observe
what to point out for JYP.
He was always judging but
now he's on the stage.
Let's watch the performances.
[Kim Ki-ryun]
[The Shorties]
[Kwon Jina]
[Peter Han]
If the contestants I met on this show
still have the same love for music...
We will definitely meet someday.
Is there someone you would
especially like to perform with?
Yes.
It's the one who's in
my heart this season.
[During the battle audition when
he saw Hong Jung-hee off]
As we practiced, we will meet someday
playing the piano and singing.
I'll be playing the piano then.
Promise to meet again.
Thank you.
[He keeps that promise today]
[Parting - Patti Kim]
[Hong Jung-hee]
That was a joint performance
between teacher and student.
It was a great performance between
the judges and the contestants.
Many must have wanted to see
that last performance.
You Hee-yeol kept his promise with
Hong Jung-hee. It was moving.
The collaboration between JYP and
the main contestants was memorable.
It must have been emotional since
you sang songs that they sang.
It was an honor since they sang well and
it was more exciting singing together.
I see. Many sang JYP's songs.
YG, you were watching with pleasure.
Could you give an impartial commentary?
You Hee-yeol's performance...
Shows how much affection a
producer has for the singer.
In other words...
I dare say that his ability drew out the
best performance from Hong Jung-hee.
I see.
I'm going to criticize
JYP's performance.
He didn't sing from the start.
I thought he was avoiding it but
suddenly let out an eerie shriek.
- Don't you mean falsetto?
- No, it was an eerie shriek.
It was an eerie shriek?
Then he said, "Break it down."
And the last was, "Hey."
So I can't comment
on his singing.
Okay, so you're not
giving a commentary.
The production crew prepared a
special stage unknown to the judges.
Someone will surprise us on this stage
and even the judges don't know.
Let's watch who it is!
[Three high school girls
loved to sing together]
[They became the
best vocal group]
[Chae-young was just a
young girl 2 years ago]
[Her dream of being a singer
is just around the corner]
[Se-woon and Ah-hyun
enjoyed music alone]
[They became a fantastic duet
complementing each other]
[Lee Chae-yeon (4),
Lee Chae-ryeong (3)]
[These sisters have
the same dream]
[Bae Mina (5)]
[The applause of the world
was unfamiliar to Mina]
[They go for the same dream]
[All of them are]
[Future K-pop stars]
Hi, I'm Brody.
[One Dream - KPOP STAR Theme Song]
[TOP6 Almeng]
[TOP10 Something]
[TOP18 Lee sisters, Lee Chae-young]
[TOP8 Jang Hanna]
[TOP8 Bae Mina]
[TOP10 Nam Youngjoo]
[TOP3 Kwon Jina]
[BoA]
[TOP4 The Shorties]
BoA, last season's judge, graced the
performance with her appearance.
The main contestants also
performed together.
The winner is decided today
but it's also a graduation.
That was a performance
befitting a graduation.
Voting will end soon and the
winner will be announced.
Looking at the judges' score...
Sam Kim has 577 and
Bernard Park has 573.
Sam is in the lead by 4.
We'll be showing
the highlight clip.
Watch it carefully and vote
if you haven't done so yet.
Voting will end in a minute!
[Voting is over]
[Live from Bucheon Gym]
You are watching this live.
Voting is now over.
As we wait for the result,
let's meet with 15&.
- Hello.
You were enjoying it.
How was it?
Things are upgraded every season
such as the stage and directing.
I was moved since both
sang very well.
Is there anyone
you're rooting for?
I'm a Beraholic and
a fan of Bernard.
But I fell for Sam Kim after
watching the performances.
So it changed. Any words of support
as they are watching right now?
They sing well so don't be nervous
and hope they get a good result.
I think they'll be waiting energetically
after receiving energy from a past winner.
The result has been tallied
while we were talking.
The announcement for the
3rd K-pop star will be made.
I hand it over to
Jun Hyun-moo.
You are watching this live.
All that remains is the
announcement of the winner.
Judges' score is 60% and
viewers' vote is 40%.
The one with the highest score
will be Season 3's winner.
The winner gets $300,000
and a midsize diesel vehicle.
The runner-up gets a
compact diesel vehicle.
I have an envelope and either Sam
or Bernard's name is written inside.
Who will be the 3rd K-pop star?
I'll make the announcement soon.
But it doesn't end with that.
The winner will choose his desired
agency and sign the contract.
Who will be the 3rd K-pop star
between Sam and Bernard?
Let me ask them before
I make the announcement.
Sam, how do you feel?
I'm grateful to have
made it this far.
I had a hard time but it
was great to be with him.
It's an honor even
if I lose to him.
I love him.
Sam Kim is such a nice boy.
And you, Bernard?
It was a pity but
it's been great.
I had fun and met many great
people because of this show.
I also made great friends
so I have no regrets.
The result of the final score
is inside this envelope.
Whose name do you think is inside.
Everything is finished now.
Sam, what do you think?
- It's definitely Bernard.
- Definitely Bernard?
But you were complimented
and got 299 in Round 2.
We don't know the outcome.
Huh?
No one knows the result but
you did well in Round 2.
Then you could be the winner.
But I think he's more qualified
since he did both rounds well.
You think he did better.
What do you think, Bernard?
How can I beat 299?
Is he telling the truth
or making a fuss?
According to the judges' score,
Sam is in the lead by 4.
But we don't know
the final result.
- YG?
- Yes?
Any words for them before
the announcement?
This is the last time
I'm holding this mike.
I wrote some things down
to wish them well.
I think about the happiest moments
since I'm in my mid-40s now.
What's important is who was I with
rather than what did I do.
The contestants met the 3 judges
who are difficult to meet.
They also became close to one
another as they lodged.
They're waiting for the
announcement but...
I think they're all winners with
great memories made in their youth.
I congratulate the winner and hope
they gladly accept the outcome.
Alright.
Any words from JYP as well
since this is the last?
Both are winners since
they stood to the end.
You did well. We were happy
to watch the two of you.
Thank you. He said
both are winners.
Any words from You Hee-yeol?
They had hard times
lodging together.
Now you can eat
whatever you want.
Both said they had to lose weight but
now you can do whatever you want.
You did well.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
I will open it now.
Season 3's winner is...
Whose name do you think
is in this envelope?
I saw the name.
I'll say that it was a close match,
and there wasn't a definite difference.
Season 3's winner is...
Everyone!
The name is...
In English!
Season 3's winner is...
Please congratulate...
Bernard Park! Congratulations!
Bernard Park is the winner
of KPOP STAR Season 3!
He's being congratulated by Sam
but he looks bewildered.
His knees are feeling weak.
Would both Bernard and Sam
step forward please?
Congratulations and say whatever
you want to your heart's content.
Thank you very much.
This show is over but
now it's the beginning.
Please watch how I do.
Thank you.
Say something to your parents
who were also watching.
I love you mom, dad, and sis in the US.
Thank you for always cheering me on.
Thank you.
Sam, you were complimented in
Round 2 that it was the best.
Wasn't it a pity?
How do you feel?
It would have been better
if I did better in Round 1.
But it's good and it's
great that he won.
Weren't you really nervous when
you sang "Lies" in Round 1?
I was really nervous.
Slow songs aren't my style
and I was really nervous.
It was a pity but it was great.
I had fun and it was an honor.
Alright.
Bernard is the winner
but it isn't over.
Now the 3 judges have to
wait for Bernard's choice.
Who did Bernard choose between
JYP, YG, and You Hee-yeol?
Did you already decide?
Yes. It was hard but
I already decided.
It was hard but he
already chose. Alright.
Between YGE, JYPE, and Antenna Music,
we will announce which one he picked.
The winner will choose from the
3 agencies on live broadcast.
Who will the winner choose?
The contestants were
nervous on stage.
But this is the moment when
the 3 agencies are nervous.
I'm scared and afraid
but I have the desire.
There are contestants we like but
we'll have our eyes on the winner.
[Which agency will the
winner choose?]
[The winner's final choice]
Bernard is weak in the knees
and is tottering right now.
He's still overwhelmed
but I think he's decided.
I'll give each agency
some time to appeal to him.
What is JYPE like? Please
say something briefly.
The owner of JYPE
is a Beraholic.
The owner is a Beraholic.
- That's all I have to say.
- That's too much. YG?
Akdong Musician debuted and
are taking first right now.
You have to choose your
career path wisely.
YG, you...
I'll use every means possible to
make you first if you choose YGE.
You'll make him into the lord of cheers.
That was an obvious sign of affection.
You Hee-yeol?
Have you heard of the
tyranny of major companies?
You are thrown out if
you are not first.
But we are like a family that
will walk together to the end.
- Come to Antenna Music.
- Antenna Music, alright.
The judges were just appealing to him.
Bernard will choose carefully.
Is it YGE, JYPE, or Antenna Music?
In which agency is his
heart bound? Please tell us!
He's beating around the bush.
That's good. They should also
experience how this feels.
He's still beating around the bush.
That's it Bernard! Keep at it!
Bernard's choice is...
I choose...
Congratulations JYP!
The original Beraholic was
choosen by Bernard.
JYP is the head of the agency that
will make a contract with the winner.
Congratulations!
JYP is really happy.
Your thoughts, JYP?
It's an honor and I'll do my
best to be a good supporter.
Bernard wasn't always first.
He was a candidate for elimination
many times but overcame them.
I'm proud that he made it.
We'll do well together.
Thank you.
The other two judges might be sulking
but come down and let's wrap this up.
Why did you choose JYP?
I still have many
things to learn.
I think JYP is the one who
will teach me the best.
I pray that you made
the best choice.
Do the other judges have anything
to say? YG? You look bitter.
I'll say one thing.
You'll regret it.
Bernard?
You're going to suffer.
But you found the
best teacher.
I'm looking forward to it.
Season 3's winner is Bernard Park
and he chose JYP as his agency.
This ends KPOP STAR
Season 3's long run.
We congratulate Bernard on taking his
first step as a pro singer with JYP.
Please watch how he'll grow.
Thank you everyone for watching and
we'll be back stronger in Season 4.
Bernard might return then
with his debut song.
Goodbye everyone!