A harsh and tough journey
to become a K-pop star.
Currently, 8 teams
have survived.
The stage for the TOP8
is bigger and enormous.
The 1:1 battle system
is used again.
Don't blame me
for picking.
Ye-dam, don't pick blue.
I don't want
to face him.
[Who is their opponent?]
They are shocked at the
opponent they chose.
No one can let their guard
down in this fierce battle.
The TOP8 battle is
filled with tension.
It starts now!
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
This is Survival Audition
KPOP STAR Season 2!
The TOP8 battle will
proceed as 1:1 battle.
I introduce to you
the contestants.
First is 2,000 won and
Akdong Musician!
They have unique personalities.
Looking forward to their match.
Next is Choi Ye-geun
and Andrew Choi!
It's a battle between professional
composer and genius arranger.
Next battle is...
Raccoon Boys
and Bang Ye-dam!
Both get over 2 million views.
We look forward to them as well.
Last of all is...
YouU and Shin Ji-hoon!
I think we will be
glued to this match.
A round of applause
to our TOP8 finalists!
Hi, I'm Yoon Do-hyun,
MC for KPOP STAR.
TOP8 finalists were decided
after last week's fierce battle.
Two will be eliminated
this week for TOP6.
This week's battle will
be 1:1 battle again.
The winner goes to TOP6 and the
loser is in danger of elimination.
Among the 4 teams in
danger of elimination...
1 with viewers' votes and 1
with judges' wildcard will pass.
I look forward
to the battle.
I will first introduce those who
are always the talk of the town.
I introduce the three judges!
BoA of SM!
Yang Hyun-suk of YG!
Park Jin-young of JYP!
The crowd's going wild.
It seems BoA is getting
prettier on KPOP STAR.
Thank you. I'm wearing bright
colors since it's almost spring.
You look gorgeous.
We request a sharp
and fair judgment.
I'll reveal the battle order
and the finalists' number.
1st is No. 1 Choi Ye-geun
and No. 2 Andrew Choi.
2nd is No. 3 YouU and
No. 4 Shin Ji-hoon.
3rd is No. 5 Raccoon Boys
and No. 6 Bang Ye-dam.
Last is No. 7 2,000 won and
No. 8 Akdong Musician.
It won't be an easy battle.
I anticipate it to be exciting.
Boom will explain the voting
system and how it's totaled.
Hi, I'm MC Boom here live
at KPOP STAR's battle!
Give me a shout!
Things are really
heating up here.
The most important thing here
at KPOP STAR is your votes.
You can start voting when
your favorite is battling.
You can't vote for them
when their battle is over.
Keep that in mind. I'll
explain how to vote.
On your cellphone, text #0606 with
the finalist's Korean name or number.
One important thing. You can
vote for more than one person.
But you can't make multiple votes
for one person. Remember that.
As the weeks go by, it's
getting hotter here.
Your votes are
very important.
Your votes allowed Akdong Musician
and Shin Ji-hoon to pass last week.
We request your
participation.
We will now begin
our 1st battle.
It's Choi Ye-geun and
Andrew Choi. Excited?
Voting for them will
also begin now!
[Choi Ye-geun vs Andrew Choi]
[Hard to predict this one!]
These two...
Their chance of
winning is 50%.
Both have superior musicality;
the ability to interpret the song.
The problem is the song.
Who will transform from
a musician to a singer?
This is a battle of
two musicians.
She plays chords I didn't
expect. She's a genius.
He helps me a lot music-wise
and we are on friendly terms.
It's complicated since
we have to battle.
The song I'm singing is
Jessie J's "Price Tag".
[It contains a social message
criticizing mammonism]
I arranged on the piano and showed
my colors through voice until now.
Since the stage
is bigger...
I wanted to express my colors
through stage production.
[It contains mostly her
thoughts and message]
To describe the disparity
between the rich and poor...
Only people with money
are on this side.
And poor people without
money are on this side.
That's how I
made the stage.
To show people getting
run over by money...
People move to the right
then left on stage.
I want to sing this to those
who are rich but not happy.
I'll be satisfied with the stage
if my message gets across.
[Price Tag - Jessie J]
No. 1 Choi Ye-geun made the
stage flashy with her colors.
I think this week's stage
will be the hardest.
Because I'll be showing a
side I never showed before.
I'm going to dance
while singing.
Andrew's dancing?
What do I do?
It's Usher's "DJ Got
Us Fallin' in Love".
I danced when I was
in high school.
It's been a while
since I danced.
I forgot a lot.
She's smart, nice,
and pretty.
She always thinks
about me.
I'm thankful to meet such
a person... and happy.
Since I have to sing
while dancing...
I'm worried my voice
will be unstable.
But I'll dance well
for my girlfriend.
[DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love - Usher]
I didn't know he
had such a side.
No. 2 Andrew Choi gave
an amazing performance.
His battle with Choi
Ye-geun is unpredictable.
I'm curious what
the judges think.
Let's hear the
commentary.
It's hard to tell who's better
since it was appealing.
Choi Ye-geun did almost
everything, even staging.
It was fun to see the stage
you made using the lyrics.
The scales you sang in the
middle were hard, but you got it.
You arranged it differently and
sang it in your style. It was good.
Andrew, I never expected
to see you dance.
But you gave a good performance
with exciting music. It was good.
I never dreamt you would
propose before you began.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Next please.
Every time I see Choi Ye-geun, she
is like a uniquely designed sofa.
She's a very expensive sofa
because she's one-of-a-kind.
It's a sofa that looks good
but uncomfortable to sit on.
You have great skills and techniques,
but I feel burdened to listen to it.
I want to ask Andrew a
question. How old are you?
- Mike's not working.
- Oh, okay.
I remember you to be in
your mid-30s, correct?
What's your definition
of success?
It's not working?
I'm sorry.
The mike works.
He didn't understand.
He didn't understand?
I'm sorry.
- He can't speak Korean...
- Thank you, JYP.
- Can I answer in English?
- Sure.
What did he say?
Success is doing
what I love.
I admire you. That's the
answer I was waiting for.
Most people would
answer it as money.
How much do you have
to make to be happy?
You just gave the
correct answer.
I think the greatest success
in life is to be happy.
You officially proposed to
your girlfriend today...
And you're enjoying music
even in your mid-30s.
That tells me that you
are already successful.
Today's stage was very
moving. Good job.
Thank you very much.
And JYP?
In regards to Choi Ye-geun, it's
very similar to what YG said.
I was thinking what advice
to give as I was listening.
Listen to music of singers that
sing as if they are speaking.
Without showy techniques. For
example, Yoo Jae-ha in Korea.
Or The Beatles in the West.
It will touch our heart if
you sing as if speaking.
Many singers that sang as
if speaking succeeded...
Even though they didn't
have a powerful voice.
But those that didn't
sing as if speaking...
Although voice is powerful,
rarely succeeded.
I want to give
you that advice.
Andrew sings very well since
you know the feel of the song.
But I want to say something.
Since you sang Usher's song...
This is what I think, but...
How Usher sang in his 3rd
album changed from before.
His vocalization was open from 3rd
album on and became a great singer.
Singing is the same, but breathing
and vocalization were unstable before.
It was as if the sound was pressed.
Of course, this is my opinion.
If you listen to his songs with
that in mind, it'll be a great example.
Your interpretation of
the music is excellent.
But just as YG said, I envy you
for proposing to your girlfriend.
Thank you very much.
He gave an unexpected performance
and his proposal left an impression.
She showed her talents through
staging and heard many things.
Please announce the
victor of this battle.
I had a hard time.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
Both showed amazing techniques, new
challenges, and were unperturbed.
It was hard to choose.
The victor is Andrew Choi.
It's Andrew Choi!
Congratulations!
He was chosen by BoA.
Please announce
the next victor.
Both have pros and cons.
But what we see is...
Who has a higher chance in getting
their shortcomings fixed quickly?
From that point of view, one
of them has a higher chance.
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
- Choi Ye-geun.
- Congratulations!
It's neck and neck!
The score is 1:1. YG's choice
will determine the outcome.
This battle is the most
difficult because...
It's 1:1 and both have
outstanding skills.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
I chose the comfortable
and happy side.
- It's Andrew Choi.
- Congratulations!
The first TOP6 finalist is
Andrew. Congratulations!
Choi Ye-geun put on a good
stage and lost, but it's not over.
The final decision is
made with your votes.
Those who are cheering
for her, please vote.
The next teams have
different charms.
The battle between YouU
and Shin Ji-hoon begins!
[YouU vs Shin Ji-hoon]
Wow, this...
I really don't know. It
doesn't lean to one side.
How did this happen?
[But]
[They're laughing hard]
[Seems like they
were working out]
- You're so funny.
- Why don't I go up?
[Laughing their
heads off]
[Shin Ji-hoon wins
in sit-ups!]
Ji-hoon was the first to
speak on KPOP STAR.
We were close like sisters
but are now opponents.
I was taken aback, but
this is a survival.
We have to compete.
What do I do?
The times when they are good
and bad fluctuates greatly.
Which YouU or Shin Ji-hoon will
appear? That will determine it.
What are you singing?
I already have a man...
- Really?
- Yes.
It's going to be new.
It's hard to imagine.
2,000 won already sang
"I Have a Girl".
[2,000 won showed
their witty raps]
Choi Ye-geun also sang it.
[Highly complimented for
extraordinary arrangement]
When the girl group sings this,
I believe it will be different.
It's going to be different
from the group dance we did.
It's going to be a fantastic
performance with a story.
Let's go, YouU!
[I Have a Girl - JYP]
No. 3 YouU reinterpreted
JYP's "I Have a Girl".
She never had lessons
and just sings.
It's terrifying that she
could sing like that.
I'm going to sing
Kim Kwang-jin's "Letter".
The lyrics touched
my heart.
"I want you to be happy.
Take this heart of mine."
I felt sad.
In the 16 years I lived,
I never had a boyfriend.
I feel sad when I sing,
and I start to sniffle.
Shin Ji-hoon has a faint and
dreamlike sadness in her voice.
I think she'll sing well! She
has that sensibility! She's just...
[But]
I was told I need techniques.
I think I'm really bad at it.
There are composers and those that
arrange the song in their style.
But singing wasn't
the goal for me.
I always feel
that I'm behind.
I don't know why
I'm starting to cry.
[Tears fall as she
speaks her heart]
I'm not like this.
- Guess it's puberty.
- I think so.
Putting aside whether I'm
better or worse than others...
As long as I'm on stage,
my goal is to do better.
[Letter - Kim Kwang-jin]
Thank you.
No. 4 Shin Ji-hoon calmly
finished her stage.
Both teams battled with
contrasting charms.
What did the judges think?
JYP's expression was memorable.
Please step forward and we'll
listen to the commentary.
I believe every human being is a
beautiful instrument made by God.
Only your special and beautiful sound
will come out if you make it.
When humans are tense and squeeze
their throat, that sound isn't made.
Especially in the high notes,
that sound doesn't come out.
But Shin Ji-hoon makes that sound
in the low, mid, and high range.
It's hard even for me, and I
learn a lot just by watching.
It made me think that a human being
was made to produce beautiful sounds.
That was Shin Ji-hoon's
commentary.
The previous commentary I made was
the singing wasn't as if speaking.
When YouU sang, it was as
if they were speaking.
All five of you have a great
talent for singing and dancing.
But Min-joo has both.
You started off
with a waltz.
The dance for popular music
is 4/4, but a waltz is 3/4.
It's awkward when
you dance that.
It's amazing how beautifully
you expressed the waltz.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
That was his commentary.
Let's listen to the next.
Son Yoo-ji of YouU,
do you live in Bucheon?
When I came here, I saw
a banner cheering her.
I believe Lee Hi is
also from Bucheon.
So I enjoyed it.
Son Yoo-ji, I would
like to make a request.
Can you do the choreography
for that part please?
- That part...
- Do you remember?
Yes. It's that move.
It's strange. She's the youngest
and the shortest in the group.
I was surprised how perfectly
she did those moves.
- You were entranced by that?
- Yes, I was.
- The smaller, the shrewder.
- I see.
I thank you for putting in less
moves as I said before, but...
One unfortunate thing is that you
didn't show anything with the dance.
Shin Ji-hoon...
You were much better today.
I don't know where you
went, but you were good.
Techniques, high and low notes are
useless. What's terrifying is that...
Just like confessing one's love,
She moves the heart with music.
I don't know if she sang well,
but she moved us and the viewers.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
BoA?
Since they were long,
I will make it short.
It must have been hard for the
five of you to prepare in a week.
I enjoyed it, and I also had an
eye on Son Yoo-ji's moves.
I never imagined that Shin Ji-hoon
would improve in a short period.
Especially the ending
notes and vibrato.
But you changed the
mood with a little vibrato.
Shin Ji-hoon returned.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
YouU was complimented for
improving in dancing and singing.
Shin Ji-hoon received a favorable
comment for moving our hearts.
But we need the results.
Please announce the victor.
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
Rather than who's worse,
both did very well.
I had to choose who was
a little more better.
- Shin Ji-hoon.
- Congratulations!
She was chosen by JYP.
Please announce
the next victor.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
The one who moved the
heart... it's Shin Ji-hoon.
Congratulations! She's
now in the TOP6!
YouU unfortunately lost, but
let's hear what was SM's choice.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
Shin Ji-hoon, the beautiful
voice that moves the heart.
A round of applause for making
to TOP6 unanimously!
Congratulations.
It's not over for YouU
so don't be disappointed.
They have the viewers' votes.
Please look forward to that.
Two teams are preparing for
the next unpredictable battle.
It's between Raccoon
Boys and Bang Ye-dam!
[Raccoon Boys vs Bang Ye-dam]
We're very afraid.
He has less stage
fright than us.
He's a baby.
He likes to be carried and
be in someone's bosom.
He never watches TV alone.
He's always next to someone.
He's cute, but when
he's on stage...
He does a 180. He doesn't speak
right before he goes on stage.
I don't know if he's
trying to stay focused...
Bang Ye-dam is moving
up right now.
But Raccoon Boys have
the potential to win.
The problem is choice of song
and how it'll be interpreted.
[What did they choose?]
We never sang jazz.
We're singing
Fin.K.L's "Now".
[90s legendary hit song
Fin.K.L's "Now"]
I grew up in the States,
but I listened to gayo.
I knew Lee Hyori,
but not Fin.K.L.
She's in Fin.K.L, right?
It's a pity we couldn't show
our arrangements last round.
To receive the commentary, "Just
as expected from Raccoon Boys"...
We prepared a lot.
[Ye-dam watches them practicing]
Why did they deceive
me that they're bad?
I'm afraid of 2,000 won, but
more so with Raccoon Boys.
[They make him feel small]
Ye-dam is a strong contestant, but
we'll show a great stage in our style.
Let's go, Raccoon Boys!
[Now - Fin.K.L]
OK, you look stunning
Your entrance is different
For all the men waiting
This is the highlight
That fine bodyline's my type
It's a style everyone wants
Wolves will definitely come
Girl tell me, when you got time?
I approach carefully
And speak
I say a few words
Throw your heart with a splash
Your love isn't interested
It's like a deserted island
I get seasick, but I want to get
On your dream boat
They sing any song
in their style.
No. 5 Raccoon Boys'
teamwork stood out.
I don't know about this.
Raccoon Boys are in a fix.
- Ye-dam...
- It's Bang Ye-dam.
What do we do?
We're very afraid.
When we use the word
"frightening", we don't know.
Bang Ye-dam is frightening since we
don't know what's going to come out.
Are you dancing again?
- Well, I...
- Don't dance.
Please don't.
[How does he feel
about their fear?]
I guess I'm unlucky.
I went against 2,000
won last week.
This week I'm up against
Raccoon Boys.
I don't know why
I picked them.
On top of that, I
have a bad cold.
I'm worried because
my condition is bad.
But I'm going to
practice hard.
I'm singing Stevie
Wonder's "Sir Duke".
I'm familiar with it and think
I can arrange it well.
I discussed with the music director
and thought how to dance in this song.
I don't know
what to do.
I'm afraid of Raccoon Boys,
but I'll try hard. Let's go!
[Sir Duke - Stevie Wonder]
An amazing stage by
a 12-year-old boy!
No. 6 Bang Ye-dam gives
a surprise every stage.
Both Raccoon Boys and
Bang Ye-dam did well.
It truly was a
fierce battle.
What did the judges think?
Let's hear the commentary.
Am I first again?
I'm not calm yet.
It's written all
over your face.
The one who came out as
Ye-dam's girl, can I be her?
I'll start first with
Raccoon Boys.
Since the live broadcast began,
you are hesitant to show.
"Now" started calmly and there's
something big in the middle.
I don't know if it was high,
but Brian couldn't go through.
I thought you should lower
the key in the next round.
Bang Ye-dam is the most
frightening and strongest.
He does get extra points
for being young.
How could someone
young do that? But...
Compared to existing singers,
he plays with the rhythm...
It wasn't choreography, but he had
gestures here and there in the song.
It doesn't just come out.
That's hard even for me.
I was amazed, and that role
as his girl is tempting.
- Didn't give up on it?
- I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Next please.
I said in the interview that
Raccoon Boys were perfect.
But it seems you only hit to
1st or 2nd base every stage.
You don't surprise us anymore
and are just playing it safe.
Kim Min-suk leaves a
lingering impression.
We are in dire need of rappers
here and in the underground.
The other two are good too, but I
think Min-suk's discovery is big.
Why are the judges surprised
and praise that 12-year-old?
The viewers might not
understand at times.
Bang Ye-dam first sang
Justin Bieber's "Baby".
Second was Michael Jackson.
Today was Stevie Wonder.
These three seem similar,
but they are different.
Reinterpreting and singing
them on stage is...
As BoA said, it's hard for existing
singers because of their color.
It's amazing that he does the motion,
style, and rhythm befitting the song.
It really touched me.
You did a good job.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, let's hear
JYP's commentary.
Mine overlaps with YG's. I'm
going to talk about Min-suk too.
In the lyrics, "Looks and
entrance are different."
"Highlight for the men."
"Different" and "highlight"
actually don't rhyme.
Both words are different.
He makes us to hear
as if they rhyme.
It's called slant
rhyme in hip-hop.
Making us hear as if it rhymes.
Rappers like T.I. are good at it.
I'm amazed at that ability.
I want to compliment you.
Brian's high notes aren't open like
the rest, but it's in the right direction.
Just practice as
usual, even McKay.
I believe you're on
the right direction.
I don't know what to
say about Bang Ye-dam.
Among the TOP8, Shin Ji-hoon
and Bang Ye-dam are...
Showing the existing singers a
demonstration of vocalization.
It's perfectly open in the high
notes and also when they hit it.
It's amazing. Viewers might
think why we are excited.
Rhythm is more important
than singing.
Bang Ye-dam sings while
perfectly being in rhythm.
It's hard to sing while
having that groove first.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
Now it's time to
announce the victor.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
The one who hit a homer.
- Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He was chosen by YG.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
- Bang Ye-dam.
- Congratulations!
He's now in TOP6!
Let's hear JYP's choice.
The victor chosen by
JYP is also Bang Ye-dam.
Congratulations for making
it to TOP6 unanimously.
It's not over for Raccoon Boys.
There is the viewers' votes.
Now the battle between 2,000 won
and Akdong Musician begins!
[2,000 won vs Akdong Musician]
We're the same
whoever we face.
We are in trouble.
Always those four words:
[Blue!]
No one's happy to go up
against Akdong Musician.
Why did Soo-hyun
pick that?
Chan-hyuk also had
a hard time, but...
He saw us with
the blue ball.
He was the happiest that
day out of the entire month.
Contestants release their potential
when they battle against us.
Bang Ye-dam, Choi Ye-geun,
and Akdong Musician...
We help them with
their potential.
[They feel bitter and
give a hollow smile]
This is our goal.
This time we won't help
you with your potential.
Many will be surprised when
they hear our choice.
We're going to sing
SISTAR's "Alone".
[Unexpected choice! Two guys
sing a girl group's song]
We want to show them that we
are always taking new challenges.
We split one situation
into two standpoints.
I'm having a hard
time being alone.
I'm the opposite from him,
"Who cares if I'm alone?"
How much are they going to
show their ideas and sense?
If we were potential
helpers until now...
We will now release
our potential.
2,000 won. I want to
win at least once.
Me too.
You dimwit. Couldn't forget her?
Fool! How can you be so stupid?
Love changes. It comes and goes
Everyone breaks up as if dying
Don't do anything
Everyone goes through it
[Alone - SISTAR]
Crying while listening to ballads
Isn't cool like UV
Where's your attitude?
You got nothing
I'll fix you with a pretty model
Go see some flowers this spring
What's with that look? Tell me
What the heck is your problem?
I'll tell you what you can do
Let's say you're at the movies
A seat in the front amongst couples
There's one left and it's yours
You can sing at the karaoke
No need for reservations
Don't be discouraged. Breakups come
In roughly like waves and go away
Look at me. Single from birth
Why can't you be single?
It's not hard to do things alone
Throw that bias away
Know how to handle breakups
Then it'll hurt less
Not enough time to spend it alone
There's too many things to enjoy
You're a fool to drown in sorrow
In life, you come and leave alone
No. 7 2,000 won's witty
ideas and staging stood out.
If we showed only our
songs until now...
We want to show you
a different taste.
We arranged a song.
[Compete with an arrangement
and not their own song?]
We arranged SHINee's
"Ring Ding Dong".
[How did they reinterpret this song
with an intense electronic sound?]
We thought if we should
go as rock or something.
Then we chose to go
acoustic since that fits us.
Guitar will just
get the point.
We set the mood with guitar,
jembe, and the conga.
You'll get to see the best
of acoustic instruments.
[Akdong Musician is
confident but...]
Hyo-bin sings well
and Il-do raps well.
They do everything.
They're entertainers.
We're nervous.
Does Akdong Musician have
a weapon to fight with?
A cuteness they
don't have...
[This is their cuteness]
Please discover another
side to us and be happy.
Let's go, Akdong Cross!
[Ring Ding Dong - SHINee]
Miss, oh young lady
I'm pure Chan-hyuk
I may look like I'm in grade school
You're the girl I'm dreaming about
Come to me
I paved the road that leads to me
The way you eat and sleep looks cute
That's how deep my heart is for you
That was SHINee's "Ring Ding Dong"
and SHINee is with the audience.
No. 8 Akdong Musician gave
off their acoustic charm.
Both teams put on a
stage full of character.
It seems the judges were enjoying
it, but let's hear the commentary.
It was fitting as
the last battle.
I think this is the most
difficult for the three of us.
This was the best out of all
of 2,000 won's performances.
It was good to see you enjoy
and you had some good taste.
Akdong Musician are unique.
The lyrics and everything
are highly praised.
2,000 won, as I said earlier, even
though you go to the next round...
I enjoyed it because
I saw you enjoying it.
I always wanted to feel that
and I thank you for that today.
I don't know if I should say this. If I
compare Akdong Musician to a painting...
It's like a painting drawn by a kid
who digs out sweet potatoes.
- That's hard to understand.
- Right? What I mean is...
Compared to artists with a degree, studied
abroad, and influenced by many works...
Akdong Musician has one thing
those artists do not have.
That's why I believe many
like Akdong Musician.
They arranged "Ring Ding Dong".
I personally think it's better for
them to sing their own songs.
They arranged it well, but
just as I said earlier...
Many will identify with a
painting by an unknown artist.
I enjoyed both.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
Let's hear the next.
2,000 won did the best
today. I enjoyed it.
I think today is
a day for rappers.
Il-do's rap was
the best today.
One of the lyrics was, "A seat
in the front amongst couples."
It's not easy to rap
from 4/4 to triplet.
I was amazed, and Hyo-bin
also sang well, but...
It was a pity you sounded old
even though you sing well.
Bang Ye-dam and Shin Ji-hoon
sing without any habits.
It was a pity that you
sounded relatively old.
What was great about
Akdong Musician is...
Soo-hyun sang clearly and both
of you had a lot of energy.
I always try to catch anything
musical from your performance.
And you always taught me something.
But I had nothing to learn today.
Chord progression was normal... You
said it was the best of acoustic instruments.
But all the instruments played
how they are supposed to play.
It was a pity that I didn't
learn anything music-wise.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, let's listen to
BoA's commentary.
I'll start with 2,000 won.
Staging and your skills
on stage were great.
I liked how Il-do expressed
the rap with the dancers.
Both of you did
SISTAR's key move.
It was comical and good.
You had good energy.
But why are you always
in an unfavorable pool?
Akdong Musician arranged
SHINee's "Ring Ding Dong".
JYP said he had
nothing to learn, but I...
It was good to hear how you
changed the melody to your style.
It should have made me
remember the original...
But I didn't remember it since
you arranged it in your style.
I really enjoyed
Chan-hyuk's rap.
I liked how you used the
words "ring ding dong".
Don't you run out of
breath when you sing that?
- Yes.
- Right?
It was really long.
Soo-hyun's voice was very
beautiful. I enjoyed it.
Thank you very much.
2,000 won enjoyed the stage and
Akdong Musician got mixed comments.
Please announce the
victor of this battle.
I'll go first.
The victor chosen
by YG is...
This round was
very hard.
- It was 51:49.
- It's neck and neck.
- I chose Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
They were chosen
first by YG.
Next is JYP.
The victor chosen
by JYP is...
I considered every stage
they did until now.
What can I look forward
to in the next round?
But today, I chose the
team that amazed me.
- It's 2,000 won.
- Congratulations!
This is a really
tight match.
BoA's choice will
decide everything.
The victor chosen
by SM is...
It was a fierce battle. 2,000 won is
continually showing improvement.
- 2,000 won...
- No, I'm explaining.
You startled me. I thought
it was 2,000 won.
Akdong Musician slowed down
but released their potential today.
It was hard since both teams
put on a great performance.
- I'll make the announcement.
- Is it real this time?
- Yes. The victor is...
- The victor is...
- Akdong Musician.
- Congratulations!
They are the last
finalist for TOP6!
2,000 won lost but don't worry.
They still have the viewers' votes.
The voting will end soon.
The final decision for TOP8
will be announced soon!
The winner of KPOP STAR
Season 2 will be...
Awarded a cash prize of $300,000
Make their first debut
And receive a mid-size and
compact premium sedan.
[Broadcast live from
Bucheon Gymnasium]
The voting is over.
We are waiting for the
results. Before that...
A great star came
to visit all of you.
Beyond Asia and to the world.
A round of applause for SHINee!
The greatest girl
group, SISTAR19!
They're great! But
first of all, SHINee...
This is how your song
changed. How was it?
I feel great because they
sang our song very well.
They have good taste,
and I learned a lot.
And Jonghyun?
I enjoyed it and that
chord gave me the chills.
Show me that expression.
That's how it was.
And SISTAR19, they put
on an appealing stage.
How was it?
First, I thank them for
doing our song on stage.
If we expressed the pain of
breaking up with sorrow...
They were cool and showed a
different charm. I enjoyed it.
I look forward to better
performances. Thank you.
Many of them are
nervous right now.
Bora, as a senior singer,
could you cheer them up?
It's not over yet, so
give your all! Yeah!
Go, go, go!
They are finished totaling the
votes. Who made it to TOP6?
When will you
reveal it, Minho?
Please show it
to us now!
[Final results of TOP8]
All the TOP8 battles
are finally over.
After the fierce battle, Andrew Choi,
Shin Ji-hoon, Bang Ye-dam...
And Akdong Musician
advanced to TOP6.
Unfortunately, Choi Ye-geun, YouU,
Raccoon Boys, and 2,000 won are...
Candidates for elimination.
Of the 4 teams, 1 will pass with viewers'
votes and 1 with judges' wildcard.
Of the 4 teams, which team
will advance to TOP6?
The voting results are
inside this red envelope.
I will announce
the finalist.
I will now announce the TOP6
finalist chosen by the viewers.
The team with the highest votes
will advance to the next round.
It's written here.
Of the 4 teams, which
team will advance?
The TOP6 finalist
chosen by the viewers...
Is it Choi Ye-geun who
sang in her own style?
Or YouU that put
on a new stage?
Or Raccoon Boys that arranged
"Now" in a new way?
Or 2,000 won that
enjoyed the stage?
Your choice is this team.
The TOP6 finalist is...
2,000 won! Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations!
I think they got good results
because they enjoyed the stage.
That means the viewers
also enjoyed their stage.
How do you feel
right now?
- This doesn't make sense.
- It does make sense.
I love you!
I love all of you!
Can you describe your
feeling in one word?
I'm taken aback.
We'll be a 2,000 won that
challenges. Thank you!
I think you got the highest votes
because the viewers were entranced.
Congratulations and join
the rest over there.
Only three teams remain.
The joy of congratulating
is only for a moment.
The viewers' votes
are now over.
Now one team will pass
with the judges' wildcard.
The three judges... I think they
are having conflicting opinions.
It's been some time, but I don't
think they reached a decision.
These three teams must be
nervous and trembling.
Which team will pass?
Choi Ye-geun has a hard look.
How do you feel?
I don't think I can
describe it in words.
You must be very nervous.
YouU did very well and
made many improvements.
Raccoon Boys also
put on a great stage.
Please choose the one that will
pass with the judges' wildcard!
After our discussion, the team
that will advance to TOP6 is...
All three teams did well that we
don't want to send them away.
I'm sure they will be talented
people in the gayo world.
But we had to choose one.
We based it on who has a
higher chance for growth.
- The last TOP6 finalist is...
- The last finalist is...
- Raccoon Boys.
- Congratulations!
Unfortunately, Choi Ye-geun and
YouU will say their farewells today.
Raccoon Boys, let's
have an interview.
- I'm nervous right now.
- It's fine. How do you feel?
I feel great and thankful.
But it was unfortunate.
We will do better
next time.
I think their determination will
be great. How do you feel?
I don't know. Min-suk,
help me out here.
He can't continue
because he's nervous.
You must look forward to the
next round. How will you prepare?
Personally, today's stage
was a little lacking.
We will put more of our colors
and improve more. Thank you.
Okay. Another round
of applause!
Choi Ye-geun and YouU.
Choi Ye-geun, where are you?
Choi Ye-geun?
You should say goodbye
to the viewers.
You showed such
individuality until now.
A word for your family and the
viewers that cheered for you.
I thank you that I was
able to make it this far.
I thank the judges for saying
good things about my arrangements.
I thank my family and
those that cheered for me.
Mom, dad, and big bro,
I love you guys.
Thank you. I think KPOP STAR
was a worthwhile chance.
Think of this as a beginning.
A round of applause for her.
And YouU... you
did very well.
You were injured along the
way, and now it's over.
Any last words?
We tried hard without regrets
and showed many things.
We feel great and thankful.
We learned a lot. Thank you.
A round of applause
for YouU as well.
The TOP6 will have a
fiercer battle next week.
What stage awaits
us next week?
KPOP STAR Season 2 will see
you next week! Thank you!