This place is on lock-down!
What's the containment level?
Containment?
There is no containment!
- What about the barracks?
- Breached!
- The armory?
What about my lab?
Lab? That's how this whole cluster
started! You and your experiments!
Damn it, I have to get to the lab!
Now, Captain!
Yes, sir!
Security protocol. Aidan Wexler.
We need a new evacuation plan.
We're not leaving this place.
We're fixing it.
This facility was entrusted to me.
Everything I have built is here.
I am not going to run away.
You can go down with the ship
if you want to, Colonel.
I didn't sign up to be
one of your guinea pigs.
Neither did my men.
As far as I'm concerned, you can rot
here with the rest of your pets.
But if you ask me nicely, maybe I'll
do you a favor, and end you here.
You're pathetic.
If you were any kind of leader,
you and your men
would have held this facility.
That was your job. You failed.
Help me!
Air's clean. We're good.
All right, ladies and
gentlemen, we're in the green.
LZ is clear.
Just over that ridge,
it turns into jungle fast.
Sat imagery didn't pick up
any heat signatures,
that doesn't mean
the trees aren't crawling
with those skin puppet bastards.
Eyes open all the time.
Understood?
Sir! Yes, sir!
Remember mission objectives.
One, find and locate
any Alpha Team survivors.
Two, get the hell out alive.
Yeah. And three, kill a ton of deadies.
You think this is a video game, Pugh?
Whatever's on this island took Alpha
Team offline in less than an hour.
They were a hell of
a lot tougher than you!
Our single advantage is, we have some
idea of what we're walking into.
This may be the one day in your life
you get to be
smarter than someone, Pugh.
Try not to screw it up.
Understood?
Sir. Yes, sir.
That thing working?
100%.
Good. Set it for 10 hours on my mark.
Ready? Mark.
What's that?
Safety net.
GPS beacon.
Five hundred miles east of here,
there's an Ohio-class sub
listening to that box.
We don't hit the snooze on
that sucker within 10 hours,
our friends under the sea will surmise
this island is beyond reclamation
and nuke the almighty crap out of it.
So, assuming we get
out of here as planned,
one of us needs to remember to
turn the lights out before we go.
You hear that, Gibson?
Loud and clear, sir.
This island holds significant
scientific importance.
You don't get to just destroy it.
All due respect, mademoiselle,
I don't know how
the French government works,
but the US government made this island.
They want to unmake it,
that's their call.
We're on this godforsaken
island for exactly 10 hours.
When that chopper comes back, I
expect every one of you to be on it.
You read me?
Sir! Yes, sir!
Make sure your personal beacons are on.
Don't want anyone getting lost.
Good.
- Duggan, you're on point.
- Copy that.
Doc, you're with me and Gibson.
Pugh, try not to trip over your own
dick. Jerome, you got rear.
Sir, do you hear that?
I don't hear anything.
Exactly.
We've been to 100 of these places.
They always sound like a freaking zoo.
I don't like it.
You and me, both.
Meant what I said, Gibson. We're
all getting off this island.
- The facility is that way.
- Much obliged.
Sir. Right there. One bogey.
Just as advertised.
Wonder how many more are around.
That thing moves half an
inch towards us, it's toast.
There's more of them!
To the left!
Fall in! Fall in! Fall in!
I got the six. Fall in! Fall in!
- Move! Move! Move!
- Fall in!
- Fall in! Fall in!
- Go! Go! Go!
To the west! To the west!
Did overall just do that?
Pugh, take care of Duggan.
I think that's the last of them for now.
Gibson! Med kit!
What happened?
The whole island's swarming with them!
It's going to be okay.
Sir, you know what you have to do.
Not now, Doc.
She's one of my own.
You fix her up best you can.
Yes, sir.
We gotta keep moving. Eyes on the prize.
"Eyes on the prize"?
I don't know what just happened,
or what these things are,
but we are not prepared!
You are a Navy SEAL, son. You are
prepared for anything and everything.
You hear me?
Good.
Captain!
Jerome. Gibson. Take the west flank.
I got the east.
Sir!
I got you, all right? I got you.
You know she's dead, right?
Captain!
Gibson, over here!
I fixed her up the best I could.
Captain!
Where is he, Pugh?
Where is he?
Uh...
That way.
We gotta move.
Let's move! Let's move! Come on!
Let's go!
Yes.
Listen, if you're going
to insist on bringing her,
you might want to shut her up.
She's gonna draw attention.
Let her rest.
Here.
Sit her down.
There you go. There you go.
Bite on this for me, okay?
You're going to be okay.
It's going to be okay, all right?
It's going to be okay.
You know what you have to do, right?
You're going to be okay.
Got any morphine?
No.
It's gonna be okay, all right?
It's gonna be okay.
The facility is that way,
probably a mile or so.
You're okay.
We're going to have to keep moving.
And you cannot bring her with us.
You know that.
Jerome and Pugh can go with you.
I need to stay here and handle this.
What are you doing?
I'm going to stay here
and position the GPS,
so I can light a fuse in this dump.
We have to find that research facility.
"We"?
You're not a member
of this team, Doctor.
You're a piece of carry-on luggage.
Listen, our primary mission
hasn't changed.
Yes, it has. The minute that that freak
took our Captain into the jungle,
my mission became keeping my men alive.
No, your mission is to find
whatever's left of the Alpha Team.
That mission doesn't get tossed aside
just because you saw something
that scared you.
So, what's it gonna be, Lieutenant?
Are you gonna do what you came here
to do? Or are you going to run away?
Jerome! Pugh!
Are you ready to finish this?
Sir. Yes, sir.
Lieutenant!
Come on, come on!
It's all right! It's all right!
Just look at me.
It's gonna be all right.
Look at me! Look at me!
Duggan!
She's turning! She's turning.
Come on. Come on.
Look at me. Look at me!
You'll be fine, Duggan.
- She's turning!
- It's going to be all right.
Look at me! Look at me!
Look at my eyes.
It's all right.
Keep fighting, Duggan.
Keep fighting! Keep fighting, Duggan.
It's gonna be all right, Duggan.
What the...
You killed her!
What was that?
Dispatching the problem
before it gets worse.
She was dead the moment that thing
bit her. You all know that.
If anything, you should be thanking me.
That was not your call! You are
not the leader of this team!
Neither are you!
Or else, you'd act like it.
You know as well as I do,
what was happening to her,
what she was becoming.
You should have done what I
did the moment you saw it,
but instead, you put all
of our lives in danger.
You raise your gun at
one of my men again,
and the next bullet's going to go
right there.
Are you done?
Hey, uh, sir? I think you're
gonna wanna see this.
What?
Who's Murphy?
The leader of Alpha Team.
There's more over here.
This must be as far as they got.
Dug in and emptied the whole thing out.
It doesn't make any sense.
Search the area.
Sir, listen. We're wasting time.
We have to get to that facility.
In this situation, anything we
can find right now matters.
Whatever Alpha Team had in
that box did not help them.
What makes you think
it's going to help us?
I'm an optimist.
Davy Crockett?
Hey, Gibson!
Davy Crockett!
What is that?
Nuke-enabled RPG.
Sounds like an HK416.
Yep.
I think it's the facility. All right.
We gotta move. We gotta move, now!
Where is everything?
I mean, I just
thought there'd be more, uh...
What? Remains?
Yeah.
Well, it was protocol to keep everything
as barren as possible
around the facility.
You know, less chance of
getting something contaminated
moving around the island.
Or even worse,
off of it.
So much good that did.
What the hell was that?
Let's keep moving.
Jerome!
It's locked!
Well, how do you get in?
The main entrance is to the north.
You sure know a lot for being a doc.
Hey, guys, I see something.
We got incoming, boys!
We got incoming!
Sir! Help me!
Get inside! Henderson! Kurtis! Inside!
Everybody inside! Go!
Get in! Get in! Come on. Come on in!
Come on! Come on!
Thought you guys could use a hand.
I'm Henderson, Alpha Team.
That's Kurtis.
Gibson. Bravo Team.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
That hole is the only way in
or out of this whole facility.
We've done a full recon.
Welcome to the freak show!
We need to get to the lab.
All right, Henderson, Kurtis,
you guys cover us, all right?
Pugh, Jerome. Take the six!
Go! Let's go! Let's go!
Who the hell put him in charge?
Go!
Everyone all right? Anyone get bit?
All good.
How long do we have before
the chopper comes back?
A little over eight hours.
Pugh, ping HQ.
At least we let them
know we're still here.
Yes, sir.
We're good.
Let's keep moving.
Who are you, exactly?
Dr. Mikaela Usylvich.
First Lieutenant
Phillip Henderson. And your rank is?
CIA, Special Agent.
I deal mostly with
virus and bio-weapons.
CIA?
Yeah, I figured as much.
I didn't think a doctor could fight
like that without a little training.
Hey Gibson, you're, what, second louie?
First.
Ah! Rescue and retrieval, huh?
That's right.
After HQ lost you guys,
they sent us in here
to see what the hell happened.
What they failed to tell you, this
is basically a suicide mission.
With you guys
disappearing, it became clear
that the island was still a hot zone.
So, that's when I came into play.
Well, now you found us.
So, do you think
you can get us off this rock?
Negative.
All we can do is ping HQ. We're on
our own for the next eight hours.
And we're gonna get nice and comfy.
What the hell happened?
You're looking at it.
Murphy got too cocky,
sent us in unprepared.
We're ready.
Guys, I think
we're going to have a problem.
Yeah? What's that?
The GPS tracker.
Look, I think I might have lost it
when that undead bastard tackled me.
I'm pretty sure it's still active.
So, what are you saying?
It means, in eight hours, instead
of a rescue chopper, we get...
Nukes.
Can't we ping HQ, let them
know we're still here?
Zero tolerance.
If we don't disengage that GPS,
command is going to think
we've been compromised.
Government thinks the best way to
handle a problem is to incinerate it.
If it's ash, problem solved.
See anything?
Two.
On three.
One, two, three!
Drop the gun!
Drop the weapon right now!
Down! Get down!
I'm Colonel Aidan Wexler!
This is my facility!
You are not in a secure location.
You need to come with me, now.
My God.
You look just like her.
Doc, what the hell is going on?
He's my dad.
Come with me, now!
Please, sit, sit.
Please. I haven't had
visitors in over a decade. Sit.
No, don't... Don't worry.
They are all securely locked up.
There's nothing to worry about.
What are they?
My patients.
I found a cure.
Cure?
Cure. Cure. Yeah,
that's what I said, "cure".
You should be eating.
Why are you not eating?
Here. Here. You must be hungry.
Here.
She was a brilliant
researcher, you know?
Your mother.
The work that we did together
at the NIH, it was just...
It was really groundbreaking.
Did she ever talk about me?
Yes.
Yes, at the end.
You know, by then, she assumed that...
Right. Yeah, of course.
I want you to know that I did ask her
to come with me to this facility. I did.
But she said... She just...
If I had had her help...
The sequencing...
But that... No... That's...
I mean, this is speculation.
Water under the bridge.
You know, bridges burn,
and then they fall down and
then you can't build them...
Can't put 'em back together.
You're here!
Ha!
You're here! This, uh...
This isn't a coincidence, is it?
It's not.
I thought this might be my only
chance to get to know your work.
I've never considered the possibility...
I know. That I was alive.
Mikaela, I'm sorry.
Colonel, why didn't
you try to contact HQ?
Let them know you're still alive?
What's the point? I mean...
The estimated mortality rate was total.
I was considered collateral damage
the minute the pathogen escaped the lab.
They weren't coming for me.
They weren't coming for any of us.
But that is the point
of a 10-year quarantine.
Isn't it, huh?
Yeah.
You let the epidemic run its course,
and kill any possible host,
and just starve it to death.
That's why we picked
this island, in fact.
There's a natural limit
to how far it can spread.
Yeah, but what about, like, birds and
fish? I don't know, other stuff?
Has there been a case of an
outbreak on the mainland?
No.
Then I guess that birds fish
and stuff, are not a problem.
What exactly went wrong, Colonel?
The order was to create a weaponized
strain of the Ebola virus.
And, you know, when the army
embarks on such an endeavor,
we split the work into
two tracks, all right?
Refining the pathogen
to make a bio-weapon,
and synthesizing
an anti-serum to defeat it.
Why?
Why do you have the safety
on your gun, soldier?
So, you don't kill yourself
with it accidentally.
What we saw out there in that
jungle, that wasn't Ebola.
No.
No. Not anymore.
The head of my bio-weapons team
is also my second in-command,
Captain Marshall.
Marshall, he...
He created some
mutated strains of the vir...
See, he was sloppy. Sloppy.
And you know what?
He didn't follow protocols.
Why have protocols if you're
not going to follow them?
So, one of his strains
was very aggressive,
its effects were beyond something
that we could control.
And so, when you're infected, it became
what you saw out there in the jungle.
Those dead and
rotting, and flesh-hungry animals,
devoid of any human characteristics.
What Marshall created
just wiped the soul
out of everyone it infected.
I was overseeing the anti-serum teams,
and we were progressing on a cure.
A virus that would keep it
at bay, but it was too slow.
You see, this is why
if I had your mother,
this is why it would have been
okay because this was her forte.
And the minute it left the lab,
we were all caught flat-footed.
I was lucky to have survived.
Too bad we can't say
the same for your men.
How did the pathogen escape?
What are you implying, soldier?
I have been running this
facility by myself for 10 years.
I have protocols.
I don't need your questions.
Okay. You don't have to
answer my questions,
but I don't think HQ is going
to be quite so patient.
Oh, you think that...
What's so funny?
I'm not going anywhere.
The work that I've been doing here
is far too important to abandon.
Your work ended 10 years ago.
My initial research, yes.
But what I have been working on
since the incident, Mikaela,
it is very interesting.
So, you've been
continuing your research?
We're scientists.
Wouldn't you?
I said I discovered a cure.
For what?
For death.
Do you want to see?
This is patient 9166.
She had been infected nearly seven
years by the time I had found her.
With the pathogen having infected
nearly every organism on the island,
coupled with a mortality rate
of nearly 100%,
finding a cure for
the virus was challenging.
I had to find a way to reverse
the effects of the virus,
at least to slow its progression.
And it was during my
"lab myopia," I call it.
I discovered it had an amazing
effect on human death.
You can see, the effects
are just fascinating.
You're experimenting on your own people.
No, no, no. Not people, Lieutenant.
They are cadavers.
They're just a little more animated.
So, after all
the tests and all the death,
your research hasn't
yielded any progress.
There are many ways
to gauge progress, Lieutenant.
And, uh, my theory here says
that I have made remarkable
strides in modern medicine.
And fortunately, I don't have a
shortage of raw material to work with,
sans, of course, healthy subjects.
How do you get away
with them not attacking you?
Time.
Lots of time.
I have lived with them,
I have worked with them.
And, I understand them.
You can almost say
that I've domesticated them.
Oh, my God!
Do not touch it!
They are not toys.
See? This one is nearly healed.
How can you call this
medicine? All I see is a horror show.
That's because you're looking
at it through laymen's eyes.
What good does this do?
Well, aside from
the myriad of gene therapies,
each one of these individuals...
Cadavers.
"Victims," would have
suffered an agonizing death,
only to rise up again.
I saved them from that.
I gave them... I gave them a gift.
And what's that?
What we all want. A second chance.
I'd rather be dead
than some mindless pet.
They're not mindless.
What?
See? They're interacting.
That's correct.
You're as perceptive as your mother.
They have formed a rudimentary
social structure.
They're actually highly trainable.
I realized that if I focused
on the cortex thickness,
that I could actually alter...
Would you like to meet a miracle?
Cheryl.
Come here.
Wexler?
Cheryl.
How's my favorite patient today?
Feeling great.
When can I leave?
I want to go home to my family.
I know, I know, and you will.
You need to rest first,
but your day will come soon.
Visitors.
Welcome. Good evening.
Good evening. How are you?
Feeling a lot better than yesterday.
Doctor Wexler is a genius.
Yes. Yes, he is.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Okay, okay, Cheryl? Thank you.
Then why is the jungle full of monsters?
Why not just do that for everybody?
Because you can't cure it.
You can only suppress it.
That's it, isn't it?
That's exactly it.
There is no true way to reverse
the effects of the virus,
but you can keep it in check.
If you catch it in time,
there's an 86.5% chance
of arresting the virus spread.
Of the 13.5% left, most
will succumb to the virus,
and then you just dispose of them
by destroying the hypothalamus.
"Most"?
What?
You just said most of the 13
and whatever percent remaining
can be destroyed by ripping
out the hypothalamus.
I'm not a scientist, but if most can
be killed that way, what's left?
I mean... Irrelevant...
Any population exposed to a virus,
a certain percentage is going to
display an anomalous reaction.
This is why some people get the flu
even though they've had their flu shots.
It's very simple.
But this isn't the flu, is it, Colonel?
This is a super-mutated
weaponized strain of Ebola,
so forgive me if I'm a little curious
as to what that "anomalous
reaction" might look like.
The anomalies.
It's much more than I could possibly...
But it doesn't... It really...
Um, there are accommodations
on the level below,
if you'd like to spend the night.
Uh, the building is 100% secure.
So, you would be safe...
Sure. Right, yeah.
Thank you, Colonel.
We have a slight problem.
We lost our GPS beacon
in the melee outside.
Unless we can relocate
that beacon and check in,
they're going to be lighting this whole
island up like the Fourth of July.
Okay. What's the time frame?
About five hours.
Okay. Uh...
I will help you locate the beacon,
but then I think
it's best you all leave.
I will guide you to the beach through
a path in the jungle that I use
that is generally clear.
Thank you, Colonel.
In the meantime, Jerome, Pugh,
will pack up your things.
No. Uh, as I said,
I'm not going anywhere.
Colonel.
You're coming with us.
No, I was very clear about this.
I am not going to leave my research.
We went over this.
My orders from HQ...
I don't care what your orders are!
Dad, please, just don't.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No one is going to steal
my work and pervert it.
Not you, not the government,
especially, not him.
You can either come with us
willingly, Colonel,
or we can take you by force.
Come on. It's like birds and fish...
Contain him! Contain him!
He's turning! Shoot him, Gibson!
I'm taking him out! I'm taking him out!
Shoot him!
No! Shut up! Shut up!
Shoot him! Gibson, shoot him!
Doc!
Talk to me.
What? Come on. What?
Coat...
"Coat? Jacket?" What?
Coat pocket...
Okay, coat pocket. The serum's
in his lab coat, just wait!
You got five seconds, Doc!
Doc, whatever
you're going to do, do it now!
- Got it!
- You got five seconds, Doc!
Five seconds!
Five!
Jesus Christ!
He's turning! Just shoot him!
Four!
Three!
- I'm taking the shot!
- Two!
- Shoot him!
- One!
It's working. It's working.
Well, this is plan 'B'.
Get him up!
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
Let's get out of here, man.
This is the window of
opportunity, I say we take it.
We're leaving. Now.
No, no, no! I'm not going
anywhere without him!
He is a compromise... He's my father!
He is a compromised asset!
We are leaving.
If he so much as twitches, I'm
gonna put a bullet in his brain.
You make one move towards him,
and I'm cutting those off!
Try me.
Calm down.
Doc, we're leaving.
Listen, with this, I was able
to help control it before.
Now that I know what to do,
I can do it again.
We take him on a chopper,
he compromises everyone.
You're the scientist.
You tell me what happens if we
introduce a pathogen like that
to the rest of the civilization.
I just found him.
I'm sorry.
Well, now that that's that,
what are we doing?
We're leaving.
We've got five hours before extraction.
Gibson,
let me get to my father's lab to see
if there's any research I can salvage.
You got one sweep.
One.
Jerome, Pugh, come with us.
See if you can find a radio,
somehow we can contact command.
Kurtis, Henderson.
Keep an eye on that son of a bitch.
Yep! Roger that.
The main lab is one level down.
The stairs should be this way.
Keep your heads down. Watch your six.
We're going to head downstairs.
See if you guys can
find a working radio.
You got it, Lieutenant.
Nothing.
One floor down, huh?
Doesn't look like anyone's
been down here for years.
We've got company.
I got this.
Ready?
Yeah.
Well?
Give it a shot.
Anything?
Dead.
Like everything else in this place.
I got to 10-1.
Now?
Yeah! Now.
Pugh!
What was that?
Get my six.
- Good?
- Yeah.
You think this place
can get any weirder?
Honestly? Yeah.
Yeah. Me, too. Let's find Gibson.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey!
Pst!
Take it easy. Take it easy.
I'll take the main computer.
You take the filing cabinet.
What filing cabinet?
That one.
What the hell am I looking for?
Anything XP 573.
Wait a minute.
Okay. All right, it looks like Wexler
conducted his original research
under the official
military project name,
but at some point, he started
tracking it all under "Katja".
And I can't find any hard copy
of anything after that.
Katja was my mother's name.
Here we go.
After the outbreak, my
father changed his approach.
Instead of working on
the pathogen itself,
he began using the infected to
test and refine the anti-serum.
So, the bastard was
searching for a cure.
No. He was using the anti-serum,
XP 573, to enhance them.
Without the natural limitations
of living tissue to restrict him,
he was actually able to improve
their physical attributes.
Depending on their original
condition, of course.
So, if you're a zombie, then you
kind of get to stay a zombie.
Correct.
But if the infection
hasn't spread too far,
he was actually able to increase
their size and strength
well beyond the human norm.
Beefed-up super-zombies.
What could possibly go wrong?
Well, considering one of the side
effects is increased aggression...
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You just said that
the fresher the victim,
the more effective the serum is, right?
He didn't try to inject this crap
into a living person, did he?
There are references to tests
on uninfected tissue.
Yes, right here.
Patient 1138 was given
the anti-serum first.
Results, near catastrophic
collapse of all systems.
They actually had to use the
pathogen to balance the impact.
One won't work without the other.
What the hell does that mean?
You gotta be freaking kidding me.
What?
Patient 1138...
I am Colonel Aidan Wexler, Patient 1138.
I have been bitten by patient 1136.
I am going to inject myself with XP 573,
which should halt the virus
at its current stage.
And with the increased rate
of DNA synthesis,
should completely rebuild
my cellular structure.
Injecting now.
He infected himself.
What the hell did you just do?
Nothing.
Somebody tripped the alarm!
Uh, we have to move now.
No! Just hold on.
- We have to move now!
- Hold on!
We have to move right now!
I'm going to have to bypass security
- if the alarm is...
- Now.
- Now!
- Wait! Hold on!
- Doc.
- Just give me a second!
- We're moving! Let's go!
- I have to bypass security.
The alarm has kicked in some
kind of lock-down protocol.
We've got to move now.
Come on!
Got it.
Let's go! Come on!
What are you doing? What are you... Hey!
I have to find the pathogen.
You have to find what?
The fridge. Hey!
What are you...
Doc! Hey!
Come on! Wait!
What the hell is that?
It's my dad's serum. XP 573.
So, they sent a virologist.
How serious is that shit?
Very. Give me your kit,
your med kit. I need it.
You'd better keep it safe.
I... Shit.
We have to go.
Oh, shit. What?
I think I just opened up
the whole security system.
Why would you open up
the whole security system?
I don't know! I just opened it!
I just opened it!
Keep your voice down! We gotta go now!
Wait.
- Come on, Doc!
- Got it!
Let's go!
Shit!
Henderson! Kurtis! We gotta move...
Jerome.
Come on. Let's go find them.
Henderson!
Guys?
Kurtis!
Where the hell are we?
Some sort of hellish nightmare, man.
I just wish someone would wake me up.
Let's keep going.
Huh?
Henderson!
Gentlemen. Stand down!
Put 'em down! I said, now!
Tell me, what kind of trouble
did you get yourselves into?
Pugh?
Jerome?
Is that Pugh?
Let's move. Move.
Boys.
No, no, no!
Pugh. Hey! What happened?
Pugh?
Found you.
What's going on here, Colonel?
Just an average day
on the Isle of the Dead.
You're a disgusting
human being, you know that?
Mikaela.
Disgusting.
Mikaela, listen to me.
Do you know why
we even named you "Mikaela"?
It's Dutch. It means "like a God".
That's the work of scientists.
It's what we do. It's what your
mother and I did together.
It's the work that
you and I can do together.
The right to be a god is yours.
If you want to work with me.
Father and daughter.
We're not family. You're not my father.
Not anymore.
No, you need time to think about this.
Time is something
you don't have, Colonel.
That GPS beacon outside,
it's still ticking.
In a little less than two hours,
that's going to become a welcome
mat for enough Trident missiles
to turn this whole island into a warm
spot at the bottom of the ocean.
Unless you let my men go.
So, we can deactivate it and
get to the chopper in time.
So, you can either help us,
or we can all die together.
What's it gonna be, Colonel?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Where are the keys?
The keys are on the desk.
Oh! No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
I wouldn't do that. No.
Why not?
What'd you do?
I'm sorry.
I can't help myself.
You didn't. Please tell me you didn't.
You son of a bitch.
Why?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- The others?
- No. No.
He's turning.
Do you want me to?
No.
Help the others.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry, Pugh.
Sir. Yes, sir.
Now, let's just finish this, all right?
Please?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You let them out?
Oh.
That isn't good.
We got company.
Clear!
What are we looking out for?
My mistakes.
What do you mean?
Experiments with inferior DNA
that went a little too far.
Realistically,
what are we talking about?
Your worst nightmares.
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Move it!
We're surrounded! They're coming!
Go! Go! Up the stairs, and to the left.
I'll hold them off.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
- I said, go!
- Go! Go! Go!
Wexler.
It's been a long time.
Jerome! Come on! Jerome!
Jerome! Come on! Come on! Look at me!
Easy! Easy! Okay! All right!
Come on! Okay, okay.
- Jerome! Don't you do it.
- Just shoot!
I'm already dead!
- Come with us!
- Put it down! Put it down, man!
Don't do it!
Go!
- Jerome, don't you do it, man!
- Don't you do it! No!
Fuck!
Let's go.
Let's go!
Doc, come on! Doc!
Kurtis, find that GPS. Deactivate it.
Yes, sir.
This island deserves to get nuked.
Yeah, but not while we're on it.
Here. Take this.
Henderson, take her to
the rendezvous point.
Yes, sir. Where are you going?
I'm going to find the little party favor
Henderson and his team left here for us.
The chopper's going to
be here in 90 minutes.
I'll see you there!
Stop!
What are you waiting for?
Waiting to kill my master!
Where the hell are you?
There you are.
Keep your eyes open.
Hold.
Henderson?
Do it.
Do it!
Mikaela!
Captain!
It's Gibson.
I'm going to have to kill you, Captain.
I stopped the clock.
No one's coming for you.
Attack!
Marshall!
I'm going to kill you!
Go.
Go!
Doc!
The chopper's here! Doc!
Come on! We gotta go! Hey.
Are you okay?
You know what you have to do. Please.
Maybe if we can get to the chopper
and inject the serum,
it can slow down the process.
Go.
Marshall has activated the GPS. Go!
Come on! We have to go!
Mikaela!
I'm sorry.
Do it!
Please.