Presented by CJ Entertainment
A Myung Film Production
Starring
Yoo-Seok Kim
Jung Suh
Sung-Hee Park
Cameo Appearance by
Hahng-Sun Jang & Jae-Hyun Cho
Director of Photography
Suh-Shik Hwang
Lighting by
Jun-Ha Shin
Art Director
Ki-Duk Kim
Editor
Min-Ho Kyung
Sound Supervisor
Seung-Chul Lee
Music Supervisor
Sang-Yun Jun
Producer in Second
Jae-Woo Hwang
Executive Producer
Dong-Jun Seok
Producer
Eun Lee
Screenplay by & Director
Ki-Duk Kim
Damn...
Give me a pack of 4-inch
love-tailed worms
Ouch! Shit!
Hey, 8 cups of coffee here
Let's see it
Come on up. We're gonna need
something more than just coffee.
You first
- No, you first
- No! You first
Damn, I'm out
Hey you, come on in
- You're out
- Bastard...
Come on, let's have those cards
Hey, you're not gonna do it?
I don't want to
What, you think it's dirty?
Just pay up and let her leave
Oh, really
You won, so you pay
I barely won, you bastard!
Ah, shit, it's only fuck money.
Just pay her.
Cheap assholes...
Hey, say something, then I'll give
you the money, OK?
Come on, you moan.
I know you can talk.
Oh, stop teasing and let her go
Bastard... I'm gonna pay!
Hey, say something.
I can't just give it to you. You
have to say something, come on...
Here, here... Shit!
- Let's have them
- You're such a fucker
- We have to catch something
- I'm starving...
Oh, it's me.
Put Hae-Mi on.
Then wake her up...
Oh, Hae-Mi, it's Dad. What did you
learn at kindergarten today?
Making a kite?
- Help!
- What?
Help!!
- Come here, you dumbass
- Help!!!
Here, here... Grab it
Wait a second...
Hold on!
Hurry up
The light-green float
- This boat is ancient
- It probably leaks, huh?
- Will they pay double?
- They should
- Stop messing around
- What?
What took you so long
Be glad that we even came this far
That's why we pay you double
Thank you
She's so rude
They're the size of your thing
Hey, you saw mine?
I can tell
If it's bigger than this, I'm not
gonna let you go today
- Come here
- What's the rush? Coffee first...
Ah, my shoes, my shoes...
Wait, is there a restroom here?
He's nuts. It's raining like hell, and
he wants a fuck.
Hey, you asshole. It's raining like
this and you want to fuck?
I feel like shit, so let's hurry up
- Hey, put your clothes on
- What??
- One more sugar
- Sugar's bad for you...
Pay up, I have to go.
You have to pay me for the trip.
What, where's the boat, hey!
Bring the boat... Hey you!
Hey!
What are you gonna do?
You have to pay me double the double now.
Do you know how many customers I have?
Fuck, I have to pee...
I can't go here!
Shit, don't look.
You'll pay up, right?
Ooh, that's a relief
What are you making?
Oh, it's a bicycle.
Hey, can you fix this?
It's too loose.
Let me try
Oh, it's looks so real.
Can I have it?
You seem like a nice guy since you
can make a pretty thing like this.
Stop cursing, it doesn't suit you
Oh, you say it, too.
Right, it's not me.
I know she's here. Who the fuck is
holding her for hours?...
Can I hug you?
I'm attracted to men who are quiet.
Fuckers... Come out you fuck,
come out before...
- He didn't do anything wrong!
- Come here, you bitch! Nothing's wrong here??
You sonuvabitch, you know how
much this costs? You asshole!
Hey, did you get paid?
Hurry up, bitch! Fuck, Get on...
Let's go...
Motherfucker! An ugly-ass motherfucker!
I'll be here for a month.
Let's get to know each other.
- What color do you like?
- Me? Green
Take us to the green float
Catch some?
- Got it!
- Wow
- Damn, it's a big one
- Look at it go!
It's strong like you
You know, we should make sushi
out of this right away
- You can do that?
- Why not?
Try it
- It's good, huh?
- Better than I thought
Take a look at this
Wow, that's neat
Oh, it's incredible!
Have some
Now?
I came to see you because it's
my day off
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
I'm not a whore. I came to see you
because I wanted to, not for work.
You're mean
This is for someone else
Don't forget to drink the juice.
I'll be back.
Bye
See you later...
Thank you for helping my friend
Ah, ouch... Shit!
What??
OK, slowly now...
Excuse us, we need to make an
inspection
I'm sorry but could we see some ID?
- Yes...
- Let's see it
But... I don't have one
Then you'll have to come with us
You OK?
Fuck, we lost him
- Look over there
- Is he dead?
- Don't know... Wait
- Right
- OK, OK...
- Grab... Grab him
No, this bastard... this fucker...
Dare stab a police officer? You shit!
What are you doing?
Take me to the yellow float.
Where are we going?
The yellow float is over there.
This is not it...
Hey, where are those fuckers?
Where is that ugly-ass?
Bring the boat
God damn it!
Where is she? Asshole...
What the...?!
Hey, anybody there?
Aren't you open for business?
Go away
Get the fuck away from me!
What are you, crazy?
I'm not your man. I can leave
whenever I want to, you whore!
- What color do you like?
- Me? Uh, purple!
- Purple? That's too far.
- Farther the better. Let's go.
- OK, let's go to the purple one
- Get on...
- Was it good?
- Yeah, of course
- Got it
- Wow
Man, oh Wow
It's so alive
Oh, shit
Do you any idea how much that costs?
Operator, operator! Get me the local
divers.
- What, it's a scooter
- What's it doing here?