damn...
give me a pack of 4-inch
love-tailed worms.
ouch! shit!...
the Isle
hey, 3 cups of coffee here.
come on up. we're gonna need
something more than just coffee.
let's see it.
you first.
- No, you first.
- No! you first.
damn, I'm out.
hey you, come on in.
- you're out
- Bastard...
come on, let's have those cards.
hey, you're not gonna do it?
I don't want to.
what, you think it's dirty?
just pay up and let her leave.
oh, really.
you won, so you pay.
I barely won, you bastard!
ah, shit, it's only fuck money.
just pay her.
cheap assholes...
hey, say something, then I'll give
you the money, ok?
come on, you moan.
I know you can talk.
oh, stop teasing and let her go.
Bastard...
I'm gonna pay! hey, say something.
I can't just give it to you. you
have to say something, come on...
here, here...shit!
let's have them.
you're such a fucker.
oh, it's me. put hae-mi on.
then wake her up...
oh, hai-mi, it's dad.
what did you learn
at kindergarten today?
...making a kite?
help!
what?
come here, you dumb-ass.
help!
here, here...grab it.
wait a second...
hold on!
hurry up.
the light-green float.
- this boat is ancient
- It probably leaks, huh?
- will they pay double?
- they should.
- stop messing around.
- what?
what took you so long?
Be glad that we even came this far.
that's why we pay you double.
thank you.
she's so rude.
they're the size of your thing.
hey, you saw mine?
I can tell.
If it's bigger than this,
I'm not gonna let you go today.
- whatever...
- come here.
what's the rush?
coffee first...
ah, my shoes, my shoes...
wait, is there a restroom here?
he's nuts. It's raining like hell,
and he wants a fuck.
hey, you asshole.
It's raining like this
and you want to fuck?
I feel like shit, so let's hurry up.
hey, put your clothes on.
what?
one more sugar.
sugar's bad for you...
pay up, I have to go.
you have to pay me for the trip.
what, where's the boat, hey!
Bring the boat...hey you!
hey!
come inside, it's raining.
what are you gonna do? you have
to pay me double the double now.
do you know how many
customers I have?...
Fuck, I have to pee...
I gotta go...
I can't go here!
shit, don't look.
you'll pay up, right?
ooh, that's a relief.
what are you making?
oh, it's a bicycle.
hey, can you fix this?
It's too loose.
let me try.
oh, it looks so real.
can I have it?
you seem like a nice guy since you
can make a pretty thing like this.
stop cursing, it doesn't suit you.
oh, you say it, too.
right, it's not me.
I know she's here. who the fuck is
holding her for hours?...
can I hug you?
I'm attracted to men who are quiet.
Fuckers...come out you fuck,
come out before...
he didn't do anything wrong!
come here, you bitch! Nothing's
wrong here? Fuckers...
you sonuvabitch, you know how
much this costs? you asshole!
hey, did you get paid?
hurry up, bitch! Fuck...get on...
let's go...motherfucker!
an ugly-ass motherfucker!
I'll be here for a month.
let's get to know each other.
what color do you like?
me?
green.
take us to the green float.
catch some?
- get it!
- wow.
- damn, it's a big one.
- look at it, go!
It's strong like you.
you know, we should make sashimi
out of this right away.
you can do that?
why not?
try it.
It's good, huh?
Better than I thought.
take a look at this.
wow, that's neat.
oh, it's incredible!
have some.
Now?
I came to see you because it's
my day off.
what are you looking at?
what's wrong?
I'm not a whore.
I came to see you
because I wanted to, not for work.
you're mean.
this is for someone else.
don't forget to drink the juice.
I'll be back.
Bye.
see you later...
thank you for helping my friend.
ah, ouch...shit!
what?
ok, slowly now...
Excuse us, we need to make
an inspection.
I'm sorry but could we see some Id?
yes...
let's see it.
But...I don't have one.
then you'll have to come with us.
Fuck, we lost him.
- look over here.
- Is he dead?
- don't know... wait
- right.
ok, ok...
- grab...
- grab him.
No, this bastard...this fucker...
dare stab a police officer?
...you shit!
what are you doing?
take me to the yellow float.
where are we going?
the yellow float is over there.
this is not it...
hey, where are those fuckers?
where is that ugly-ass?
Bring the boat.
god damn it!
where is she?
asshole...
what the...?!
hey, anybody there?
aren't you open for business?
damn it.
go away.
get the fuck away from me!
what are you, crazy?
I'm not your man.
I can leave whenever I want to,
you whore!
what color do you like?
me?
uh, purple.
purple? that's too far.
Farther the better. let's go.
- ok, let's go to the purple one.
- get on...
was it good?
yeah, of course.
got it.
- wow
- man, oh wow
It's so alive.
oh, shit.
do you any idea how much that costs?
operator, operator!
get me the local divers.
- what, it's a scooter.
- what's it doing here?