Damn! Give me a pack
of 4 inch love-tailed worms.
Ouch! Shit!
THE ISLE
Hey, 3 cups of coffee.
Come on up. We're gonna need
something more than just coffee.
Let's see it.
You first.
- No, you first.
- No! You first.
Damn. I'm out.
Hey you, come on in.
- You're out.
- Bastard.
Come on, let's have those cards.
Hey, you're not going to do it?
I don't want to.
What, you think it's dirty?
Just pay up and let her leave.
Oh, really?
You won, so you pay.
I didn't win much, you bastard!
Shit, it's only fuck money.
Just pay her.
Cheap assholes.
Say something and I'll give you
the money, okay?
Come on. You moan,
I know you can talk.
Stop teasing and let her go.
Bastard.
I'm gonna pay!
Hey, say something.
I can't just give it to you.
You have to say something.
Here. Here.
Shit!
Let's have them.
You're such a fucker.
It's me. Put Hae-Mi on.
Then wake her up.
Hae-Mi, it's Dad. What did you
learn at kindergarten today?
How to make a kite?
Help!
What?
Come here, you dumbass.
Help!
Here, grab it.
Wait a second.
Hold on!
Hurry up!
The light green float.
- This boat is ancient.
- It probably leaks, huh?
- Will they pay double?
- They should.
- Stop messing around.
- What?
What took you so long?
Be glad we even came this far.
That's why we pay you double.
Thank you.
She's so rude.
They're the size of your thing.
Hey, have you seen mine?
I can tell.
If it's bigger than this,
I'm not letting you go today.
- Whatever.
- Come here.
What's the rush.
Coffee first.
My shoes, my shoes.
Wait, is there a restroom here?
He's nuts. It's raining like hell,
and he wants a fuck.
Hey, asshole. It's raining
like this and you want to fuck?
I feel like shit,
so let's hurry up.
Hey, put your clothes on.
What?
One more sugar.
Sugar's bad for you.
Pay up, I have to go.
You have to pay me for the trip.
Where's the boat?
Bring the boat. Hey, you!
Hey!
Come inside.
It's raining.
Hey!
What'll you do? You have to
pay me double the double now.
Know how many clients I have?
Fuck, I have to pee.
I can't go here!
Shit, don't look.
You'll pay up, right?
That's a relief.
What are you making?
Oh, it's a bicycle.
Can you fix this?
It's too loose.
Let me try.
It looks so real.
Can I have it?
You must be nice if you can
make a pretty thing like this.
Stop swearing.
It doesn't suit you.
You too. Right, it's not me.
I know she's here. Who the fuck
is keeping her for hours?
Can I hug you?
I'm attracted to quiet men.
Fuckers! Come out, you fuck!
Come out before...!
He didn't do anything wrong!
Come here, you bitch!
Nothing's wrong here? Fuckers!
Son of a bitch! You know
how much this costs? Asshole!
Did you get paid?
Hurry up, bitch!
Fuck! Get in.
Let's go.
Motherfucker!
Ugly-ass motherfucker!
I'll be here a month. Let's get to
know each other better.
What color do you like?
Me?
Green.
Take us to the green float.
Catch anything?
I got something!
- Damn, it's a big one.
- Look at it go!
It's strong like you.
We should make Sashimi
out of this right away.
You can do that?
Why not?
Try it.
It's good, huh?
Better than I thought.
Take a look at this.
Wow, that's cool!
It's incredible!
Have some.
Now?
I came to see you because
it's my day off.
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
I'm no whore. I came to see you
because I wanted to, not for work.
You're mean.
This is for someone else.
Don't forget to drink the juice.
I'll be back.
Bye.
See you later.
Thank you for helping my friend.
Ouch! Shit!
What?
Okay, slowly now...
Excuse us, we need to
do an inspection.
I'm sorry, but could we
see some ID?
Yes.
Let's see it.
But I don't have any.
Then you'll have to
come with us.
Fuck, we lost him.
Look, over there.
Is he dead?
- I don't know. Wait.
- Alright.
Okay, okay.
- Grab...
- Grab him.
No, the bastard.
This fucker...
What are you doing?
Take me to the yellow float.
Where are we going?
The yellow float is over there.
This isn't it.
Where are those fuckers?
Where is that ugly-ass?
Bring the boat.
God damn it!
Where is she?
Asshole.
What the...?
Hey, anybody there?
Aren't you open for business?
Damn it.
Go away.
Get the fuck away from me!
What are you, crazy?
I'm not your man. I can leave
whenever I want to, you whore!
What color do you like?
Me?
Purple.
Purple?
That's too far.
The farther the better.
Let's go.
- Okay, let's go to the purple one.
- Get in.
Was it good?
Yeah, of course.
Got one!
It's so alive.
Oh, shit.
Do you have any idea
how much that costs?
Operator! Operator!
Get me the local divers.
- What? It's a scooter.
- What's it doing here?
What?