(Hill) West!
You bastard.
You did this to me.
But you'll not escape me.
Not this time!
(Laughs)
(Gunfire in distance)
(Helicopter overhead)
(Man speaking Spanish)
(Airstrike sounds)
(Patients whimpering)
- (West) Take this.
- It'll burst an artery.
If we don't remove this now,
he's going to go into cardiac arrest.
- Just be ready to clamp.
- If it doesn't hold...
We have no choice, Dan!
- (Patient groans)
- Now!
(Agonizing screams)
Jesus Christ! It didn't hold!
But his central nervous system
is still intact.
He might still prove to be useful.
More useful than he'd be otherwise.
(Explosions and gunfire)
(Patients moaning)
We have to retreat!
The front lines have weakened.
(Grunting)
(Gunshot)
(Cain) Goddamn it, Herbert!
What are you doing?
- You know what I'm doing, Dan.
- (Cain) Don't you ever stop?
(West) We may never again have access
to this volume of fresh subjects.
(Cain) Fascinating.
There's somebody...
- (Explosions)
- (Iguana hisses)
- Get away from those!
- What are you doing back here?
- Leave.
- Put that thing away!
This is too dangerous for all of us.
Where are you going?
We've got lots of work to do here.
Come on! Jesus Christ!
- She's right!
- She's wrong. We are close, Dan.
Reticular consciousness
is not just in the brain.
We know that, yes?
We've gone beyond that.
Look at this.
- These reptiles are the key, Dan.
- Yes.
You just still don't understand, do you?
This is no longer about
just reanimating the dead.
We will create new life.
- (Explosion)
- Hang on!
(Men shouting in Spanish)
Francesca?
Get out of here!
- Come on! Let's go!
- (Explosion)
- Let's go.
- My notes.
- Leave them!
- Wait!
- Forget it!
- We'll need this back home.
Come on!
(West) Dan?
(Men speaking Spanish)
Dan?
Well, you're going to be alright.
We've got to get out. Come on.
Come on. Let's go home.
- (Heart rate monitor beeping)
- (Door opens)
(Cain) Morning, Gloria.
- How's the star patient?
- Hello, Doctor.
You look great.
I see you even put on some make-up.
Don't tease me.
It's just that...
My head is about the only part of me
that's not sick.
- Excuse me.
- This is Dr. West.
He'll be coordinating with pathology
about your biopsy.
You're right.
That part of you is quite well.
I'm scared.
Don't worry. The surgery is routine.
I'll be taking real good care of you.
Come on.
(Pen clicking)
She's not an experiment.
- She's terminal.
- She's a patient!
- She could be of use to us, Dan.
- Not us! You.
- I'm a doctor.
- Well, be a scientist!
(Humming)
(Phone ringing in background)
Yes?
Lieutenant Leslie Chapham,
Arkham Police Department.
- Leslie?
- Lieutenant.
Well, how may I help you,
Lieutenant?
I understand you're in charge of the
remains from the night of the massacre?
Yes, but it's my understanding
that the case is closed.
Not to me.
It showed up in a carnival sideshow
just outside of Arkham.
Dr. Hill?
Remarkably well preserved, considering
the massacre was eight months ago.
All the specimens from that night
exhibit the same qualities.
Yes, as you see,
the skull is fractured right there.
Didn't you know it was missing?
You know, I could fix that.
Where do you keep
the rest of the remains?
The specimens from that night
have shown almost
no signs of deterioration.
This not only holds true
for the gross anatomy,
but the individual cells in each specimen
display a lack of decay.
Are you saying that
they're not quite dead?
What's dead is dead, Lieutenant.
I should know. It's my field.
What's this?
That's something
Dr. Hill was working on.
I haven't been able to identify it.
Yet.
I was planning on doing that first thing
in the morning, as a matter of fact.
Is this all of it?
- Except for fragments and debris.
- What happened to that?
Why, we burned them, of course.
(Graves) Suicide.
Would-be ballet dancer
didn't have the stuff,
- cut off her feet and bled to death.
- (Ernest giggles)
- Where are her feet?
- Her feet?
Why... they're missing.
A lot of stuff's been missing
from around here lately, Holmes.
Body parts?
Really, Lieutenant?
Who'd want to steal body parts?
Yes!
Hm-mm...
How did you get back here?
(Chuckles)
Well...
...well, well.
What do you think of the location
of the will in the brain now, Dr. Hill?
I'm sorry, what was that?
Actually, you've been
quite useful to me.
You helped me prove that consciousness
resides in every part of the body.
You had such pretensions of grandeur,
you pompous plagiarist.
But look at you now.
You're nothing but a dead-head.
A no-body.
(Chuckles)
- Did that police officer find you?
- Police?
Yes, he came by
while you were in surgery.
(Coughing)
You're gonna be alright...
...Gloria.
Herbert?
Dan!
(Laughs)
Look at this!
We practically share a wall with
the Avril's crypt in the cemetery.
- Ew!
- Yes, that's a 150 years of decay.
Oh, well.
Dust to dust.
- What happened to our cadaver?
- I was finished with it.
Would you help me with this,
please?
Security.
From what?
- Herbert, I've got something to tell you.
- Really?
I have something to show you.
- (Iguana hisses)
- Shh...
Look at that, Dan.
And no tissue damage.
It simulates a heart attack.
And it leaves virtually no trace.
(Cain) That's real useful
if you want to murder someone.
(West) It is very useful...
...in obtaining...
...the freshest animal specimens.
Right here.
The amniotic fluid
of the Cuzco iguana.
Did you know that this reptile has
not changed significantly in over...
...100 million years.
Herbert, I know this is important.
Now... we extract
the amniotic fluid from the sac.
With that,
we add the muscle proteins
of myosin, actin and...
- Tropomyosin.
- Good.
And then...
(Bubbling sounds)
Our reagent.
Pure potentiality.
The primordial ooze
from which life originates.
Dr. Hill...
Dr. Hill gave me this idea.
(West giggles)
I'm moving out.
What?
Dan...
You can't turn back now.
This... This is the key
to creating life!
- Parts! Reanimated parts!
- We're saving whole people, not parts.
Exactly, and what are people, Dan,
over and above
a collection of living parts?
We can create...
...new life.
This morbid doodling
with human body parts!
Is this what it's all about?
Is this what all our great work has led to?
- Exactly what are you insinuating?
- This is your madness!
It had nothing to do with me. I'm out!
I didn't see you rejecting my work
when Meg was lying there dead!
- Where were your great ideals then?
- Don't you...
Daniel?
What was it about Meg that you loved?
Meg's heart.
Help me... to continue the work.
We can create a new life.
Starting...
...with Meg's heart.
(Echoing heartbeats)
Yes.
Now, Dan...
You're going to have to help.
At the hospital.
- What about the police?
- No, the police will never come here.
(Door buzzer)
- Daniel Cain?
- Yes.
Police?
Come on in.
Is there a problem?
Who are you?
Dr. West.
- Lieutenant Chapham.
- Police.
(West) What do you want?
It's... quite an old place
you got here.
It used to be a mortuary.
After the cemetery filled up,
it was the caretaker's house.
Nobody's been here for twenty years.
- Odd place to live.
- Has its advantages.
Huh...
- Pretty morbid stuff.
- I don't consider science morbid.
It was pretty morbid
the night Dr. Carl Hill died.
And Dean... Dean...
- Halsey.
- Dean Halsey. Yeah.
And Megan Halsey.
Do you mind if I sit down?
Dr. West, what kind of problems
did you have with Dr. Carl Hill?
Dr. Hill and I had
professional differences.
It was nothing personal.
I have been all through this.
It's in the police records,
which I am certain you have access to.
(Chapham) I understand that
you have some radical ideas about...
the reanimation of dead tissue?
When I was in medical school, I might
have had time to discuss the theory.
I don't anymore.
I suppose those poor souls
out at the Sefton Ward... are theory.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
And I suppose you don't know anything
about the missing body parts
at the hospital?
Missing body parts?
No.
(Chapham) I can find my own way out.
(Squawking)
(Screaming)
(Wings flapping)
Get off! Get off!
Get off me!
Ernest?
Dr. Graves wants to see you
right away.
- Pathology?
- Right away.
- What about the...?
- I'll take care of it.
Cool.
(Hill grunts)
More.
Dr. Hill...
- Is that you?
- More!
Dr. Graves.
You... you see?
I recognize you.
You do?
That seminar in Zurich...
Yes.
Your theory of reconciling
creationism...
with the origin of disease...
Yes.
Totally idiotic!
It's you. Come in.
No, no. No lights.
Come over here.
Dr. Hill? Speak to me.
Speak to me, Dr. Hill! Speak.
This is some kind of joke,
right, man?
No, it is not a joke!
He can talk.
He heard my lecture in Zurich.
The head? He heard your lecture?
He can talk, for God's sake!
Listen.
Talk, damn it! Talk!
- Talk!
- The head...
Don't you ever do that again,
you mental midget!
Oh, my God.
My God, I'm losing my mind.
I have some unfinished business.
And you will assist me.
(Cain) Not out the front door?
Just the doctor taking a patient out
for a little air.
(Dog barks)
- (Man) Man!
- (Woman) Oh, my God!
Herbert!
(Muttering)
(Dog whimpers)
Hey, pooch.
Yes! You said "Hi" to him!
Francesca!
Uh...
- Hi, Doctor.
- Hi.
Don't let the little head
rule the big head, Dan.
So, what are you doing in Arkham?
Oh, I'm doing some
interviews in Boston this week.
(Paging System) Dr. Cam, 5436.
Dr. Cain, 5436.
- Oh, God. I've gotta go.
- I know.
Listen...
What about dinner tonight?
Only if you let me cook.
- Real Italian style.
- Okay. Only if you let me help.
Real American style.
- It's a deal.
- See you tonight.
Yeah. Hope you like garlic!
Well, Angel? What do you think?
Hey, pooch.
Where did you come from?
From Peru.
Is that where you met Dr. Cain?
Why do you want to know, Mr...?
Oh, uh... Lee Chapham.
Arkham Police.
Lieutenant.
I'd like to talk to you about him.
(Elevator bell)
Did you ever hear of the "Miskatonic Massacre"?
- No, I haven't.
- It happened here at the hospital.
Eight months ago, the department
got a call about a homicide
at the Miskatonic University hospital.
The whole place was in a panic.
It was down in the morgue.
There was blood all over the walls.
You ever been around dead bodies?
(Gasps)
Then you know that stench
of decaying flesh.
Out of the darkness,
we were attacked by a naked maniac.
He jumped right on my partner
and bit his arm.
Nothing could make him come loose.
Tore the muscle right off the bone
before we pumped enough lead in him
to make him stop.
The dean of the medical school
was down there.
In pieces.
Also a prominent physician,
Dr. Carl Hill.
We found only his head.
The rest of his body was
just part of the muck.
Funny thing, though...
His head, when I found it,
was still...
...twitching.
Twitching?
The doctors had a lot
of highfalutin explanations.
Post-mortem involuntary spasm...
I don't know.
But I've seen my share of the dead.
And I never saw a twitching
like that before.
They blamed it all
on these ones in here.
The funny thing is,
there's a death certificate
at the hospital for each one of these.
A death certificate?
I mean to say these three didn't get
to the morgue on their own two feet.
(Francesca)
The hospital made a mistake?
(Patients groaning)
(Door slams)
The hospital might have made
a mistake about those two.
(Groaning)
Not... But not this one.
I know about this one.
She was my wife.
I'm sorry.
Elizabeth, stop!
Get off me! Get off me!
(Screaming)
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm alright. Thanks.
That's enough.
She's never done
anything like that before.
Just...
What does all this have to do
with Daniel?
Dr. Cain and Dr. West were
the only normal survivors of that night.
Daniel's girlfriend was Meg Halsey,
the dean's daughter.
And Daniel was found
with her dead body in his arms.
Her dead body.
Twitching.
Like that blasted head.
(Chirping)
(Bubbling sounds)
Be careful not to use too much of that,
we don't want premature reanimation.
(Cain) Thank you,
I've never done this before.
Yes.
- (West) Good.
- (Gurgling sounds)
The circulation is going to work.
Goddamn it, Herbert!
What are we doing anyway?
Why don't we just publish our findings?
We could get grant money.
Because they would never
understand our methods.
Besides that,
they would steal the work.
It's never gonna work.
She's gonna be uncontrollably spastic.
Unless we reanimate all the limbs
at the same time, they'll separate.
That's why we inject
directly into the heart.
The circulatory system
should distribute the reagent
to all the various limbs
and effect reanimation concurrently.
- We've never done that before.
- I know that.
No, I don't want to gamble
with Meg's heart.
(Door buzzer)
Oh, God...
- Ciao, dottore. Come va?
- Francesca...
Sorry about the place.
I didn't have any time to...
- Did I come too early?
- No! No, no, no, uh...
God, you look great.
Open this up, will you?
It's a Chianti, 1987.
- Uh... so, where is the kitchen?
- It's right over here.
- Did you have any trouble finding it?
- Oh, no. The cemetery made it real easy.
(Francesca)
This is my special sauce.
Here.
- What do you think? You like it?
- I love it.
So do I.
Come on.
You're so beautiful.
Your skin's so soft.
So warm.
What are you doing here?
What do you want?
The body you took
from the crematorium.
Get out of here. Right now.
What's down here?
That's none of your business.
You are making a big mistake.
Do you believe that dead is dead,
Dr. West?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I am talking about my wife!
No! You can't go in there.
- Move.
- No.
Move!
You...
...butcher!
How dare you judge my work?
"Work"?
Was my wife your "work"?
- Don't lay your guilt on me, Lieutenant!
- What?
Your wife died
of multiple contusions to the head.
- From a blunt instrument.
- No.
- Multiple blows to the head!
- She fell!
She fell, did she?
That was not my fault!
(Heartbeat slows to a stop)
- What happened?
- He attacked me.
No, Dan! Dan!
I can't help it if his heart gave out!
God, Herbert, he's a cop!
You...
- What are we gonna do with him?
- Well...
We could get him
back out on the street.
Walking.
You don't wanna gamble
with Meg's heart.
This is our opportunity for a test.
Do you wanna waste it?
How much do you think he weighs?
230, 240?
So little tissue damage.
Oh, Dan?
Just in case.
Daniel?
It's working.
- (Chapham mumbles)
- (Heartbeat grows louder)
Get away from me with that cloth!
No! Dan!
He's a wife-beater, Dan!
Use the gun!
(Screams)
(Skin sizzles)
(Heartbeat continues)
(Glass clinking)
Dan?
Herbert!
(Chapham whimpers)
Lieutenant Chapham!
What are you doing here?
(Snarling)
Herbert!
No! Stop!
Get away from me! Get out!
Get away!
(Chapham grunts)
- (Cain) What happened?
- (Sobs)
- Is he gone?
- What is going on here?
What did you do to him
to make him that way?
She's hysterical.
What did you do to him? Why?
(Anguished screams)
(Hooting)
(Dog barking)
(Metal clatters)
What are you doing down here?
Your welcome does not extend
to this part of the house.
(Francesca) Angel?
Sweetie...
(Screams)
(Snarling and barking)
Get out of my way!
- You should never have brought her here.
- Get that thing out of here!
- Francesca, wait! Let me explain.
- Is this what you did to Meg?
You're a freak!
God, I hate you!
You're better off without her.
Dan, now listen to me.
All we need is just one last piece.
Dan?
Gloria?
- Hi.
- (Heart rate monitor beeping)
How are you feeling today?
You see... it helps me
to think of you as Meg.
Meg who lived.
(Flatline tone)
Nurse!
Paddles!
I didn't even notice.
God, what's wrong with me?
Let me through!
Give me that!
Clear!
Push the lidocaine!
Forget it, Dan. Let's go in.
- She's never gonna survive this.
- She's already dead, Dan.
No, you're off midline.
Damn it!
- (West) I'm getting nothing.
- I'm sorry.
- Come on!
- (Suction sound)
- Anything?
- Still flat.
- I'm calling it.
- No!
Not again.
Go home.
Go... home.
Yes. Come to room 613, right away.
(Wheezing and grunting)
Damn you, West!
- Wilbur! Get me out of here!
- No.
West took my body,
but he cannot take my mind.
Take me to him!
No. Just don't talk.
Don't say anything.
(Hill snarls)
(Graves screams)
Don't make me get someone else.
(Hill wheezes)
What do you think you're doing?
Stop!
Do as I say, you nincompoop!
Come on, come on.
You're going away now.
Now, now...
(Door opens)
- Yo, Dr. West.
- Let's get this.
No, no. You get the feet.
I'll get the head.
Was she good-looking, Doc?
You take this to the crematorium.
The crematorium?
You mean pathology.
I mean the crematorium.
Well, excuse me!
Excuse me,
have you seen Dr. Cain?
He left.
For the day, I think.
- Is there something wrong?
- He's very upset.
He lost a patient.
I've never known a doctor
that cared so much.
Yeah.
(Night sounds)
Now, Dan, I'm going to need
your help with this. Understand?
This is for you, too.
- Gloria! No...
- Dan, don't quit on me now, please.
It's going to take the two of us
to fuse the brain to the spinal cord.
- No!
- Dan, look!
Look what we've done.
Meg's heart is going to beat again.
Others dare not dream
what we are about to do.
Dan...
The feet of a young ballet dancer,
who ended her life
when she lost her ambition.
These legs...
walked the streets.
You remember the hooker who was
killed in ER by her pimp last week?
Think of all the bodies
these legs have wrapped around.
What was the value of her life?
To end up being picked apart
by the likes of Dr. Graves
and his bumbling students?
And here,
the womb of the virgin.
Struck down before tasting
the pleasures of life.
Remember?
Her skin. So soft.
So warm.
But so cold in death.
The arms of a waitress.
The lawyer's hand.
Case dismissed.
And look at this delicate piece.
What do you think?
A sculptress?
A harpist?
Would you believe...
a murderess?
But they're all equal now.
Nothing but cast-off remnants
of a meaningless existence.
Even her.
How beautiful is this face?
Oh, yes.
She... was special.
Yes.
Just... dead... tissue.
But in our hands...
it's the clay of life.
Within this chest,
Meg's heart will beat again.
Good.
Let's get to work.
Who's there?
(Door slams)
I didn't do anything.
(Laughter)
Oh, no.
You disappoint me,
Dr. Graves.
Please.
On the table!
- No!
- Yes!
Scalpel.
(Phone rings)
(Hill) Left!
Get off me!
Let me go! Get off me!
What's the matter?
Don't you like me?
No! Let me go!
No!
- Cain, West. They did this to me!
- Get the fuck off!
And they'll pay!
(Graves)
Please, let me out!
Let me out, please!
Please let me out! Please!
- (Woman) Oh, my God!
- (Man) Get security!
(Alarm bell ringing)
(Distant thunder rumble)
Well...
If it all had been
as fresh as the head, but...
- I think we're ready, Dan.
- Good.
(Scratching)
Sounds like rats in the wall.
Rats? Yes.
That's what it is.
The little buggers
better stay put or I'll...
(Thunderclap)
We start with the heart.
And God created woman.
Let me.
(Glass shatters)
Time?
- Time?
- 15 seconds.
45 seconds.
(Thunder rumble continues)
Three minutes, 15 seconds.
It's going to take time.
(Door buzzer)
Damn it!
Not now!
(Distant screaming)
(Growling and snarling)
(Laughing)
(Wings flapping)
(Screams)
(Roaring)
Breathe.
Yes.
Breathe, breathe...
Breathe. Breathe.
Stay with me. Yes...
Yes.
You're alive.
Alive...
(Gasps)
(Growling and roaring)
(Wings flapping)
(Groaning)
(Cain) Herbert!
(West) Oh...
I made you.
Daniel!
She's alive.
- They're coming!
- (Chapham) Now!
Dan! Get her out of here!
Freeze! Police!
What...?
Francesca, go!
Dan, help me!
No! This!
Get this!
Yes.
Who is she?
It's Meg.
Meg is dead.
Dan!
(Banging)
My God, they're using tools.
(Grunts)
What have you done in here?
We created her life.
- You made her?
- Yes. Dead pieces of this!
With my hands,
I created what no man's mind
or woman's womb
could ever hope to achieve.
This is blasphemy!
Blasphemy? Before what God?
A God repulsed by the miserable humanity
he created in his own image?
I will not be shackled
by the failures of your God.
The only blasphemy is
to wallow in insignificance.
I have taken refuse
of your God's failures
and I have triumphed!
There!
There is my creation!
He made me.
(Chapham) Open up! Open!
Dan? We've got to fight them off.
Leave him alone!
Listen to me.
(Screams)
Your girlfriend doesn't
stand a chance.
Our girl is superior.
Help!
Leave her alone, you monster!
Forget it, Dan.
She's just an assembly of dead tissue.
You... You made me.
I made you!
Don't! Dan, wait!
Don't you want me?
I don't want your body.
- (Electric current sound)
- (Thunder rumbling)
Then what do you want?
(Bones cracking)
(Loud heartbeat sound)
Is this what you want?
You're not... Meg.
Meg's dead.
(Howling)
- No!
- (Door splinters)
- Out of the way!
- You're next, you little squirt!
(Screaming)
(Manic laughter)
Make a note of it, Dan!
Tissue rejection!
My wife understands, really.
(Grunting)
(Bones snapping)
Francesca!
(Laughter)
West!
You stupid biped!
No.
Get back!
How dare you!
You're under arrest!
(Cackling)
Get off! Get off of me!
No!
Oh, my God, Dan.
- (Manic laughter)
- (Screams)
Are we having fun, yet?
Get off of me, you rejects!
(Loud thud)
(Hill laughing) It's over, West!
(Howling)
(Heartbeat slows down)
(Heartbeat stops)
Please check out
https://katcr.co/show/community/