5
00:00:35,453 --> 00:00:37,422
<i>Doctor!</i>

6
00:00:39,248 --> 00:00:40,416
<i>Mr. West!</i>

7
00:00:44,295 --> 00:00:45,504
<i>Mr. West!</i>

8
00:00:45,544 --> 00:00:46,839
<i>Get out!</i>

10
00:00:48,927 --> 00:00:50,091
<i>Now?</i>

11
00:00:50,102 --> 00:00:51,591
<i>Yes.</i>

12
00:00:51,602 --> 00:00:52,802
<i>Move back.</i>

20
00:01:23,234 --> 00:01:25,336
<i>Dr. Gruber, how are you?</i>

23
00:01:48,025 --> 00:01:49,819
<i>He's dead.</i>
