You know I gotta bring you in.
You're gonna have to kill me first.
Yeah, I know.
Do it.
I can't.
Careful how you look at me, now, stranger
You ain't rolled the trail
that I've been on
Until you taste the dirt
and smell the danger
You don't know the hell
that's made me strong
The devil stole my woman down in Tucson
And a biscuit down in Juarez
became my only friend
Spurred my horse before...
cut the noose off
And rode off in the sunset once again
And I ride high
In the saddle
But my heart has hit me
like the setting sun
I never had to run and hide
with my old friend here by my side
But you can't kill a memory with a gun
Oh, crap!
Oh, wake up, little darling
Open them eyes
All those birds out singin' outside
Get up, little darling
Throw on them shoes
How are you, Edward?
Two S's in Mississippi, Amos.
- Mind your own business.
- I'm just trying to help.
- You're late.
- Oh, yeah.
You're looking fine
as cream gravy, Eleanor.
You're looking spiffy yourself, Jesse.
- Had a long night. Overslept.
- You didn't.
Haddie Randolph. She's a real bear-cat.
Haddie Randolph?
Jesse, how in the hell do you do this?
You know, sometimes I wonder myself.
You know what?
You're gonna have a lot more time
to wonder about that, because chief...
he's in a real mood today.
And when he finds you?
Helms!
- Amos.
- Jesse.
Close the door behind you.
Please. Have a seat.
Sure.
Why are you here?
Well, you... called me in, remember?
- I'm not in the mood for this.
- So I was a little late.
Work starts at 7:00 a.m. sharp.
Do you have any idea what time it is?
- I understand, sir.
- This is a business, son.
A well-oiled machine. If one cog in the wheel
is not working, then it all falls apart.
Do you see what I'm trying to say to you?
That I'm a cog, sir?
I should've fired your ass long ago,
when I had the chance.
Trouble is, you do a bang-up job.
When you're here. Hence my dilemma.
How to let you go
without being the bad guy.
Or how to let you stay
without appearing weak.
- Come again, sir?
- I have this little pet project of mine.
More of a passion, really.
I stumbled on this about five years ago
when I took over the chief's job.
Arizona, 1892.
Bank robbery gone wrong. Six people dead.
They called it the mid-day massacre.
September 23rd, 1892.
Four men, led by an ill-tempered outlaw
named Levi Hardin, walked into a bank.
In the small boom-town
of Young Country, Arizona.
When the smoke cleared, six people
were dead, including a five-year-old girl.
Traveling photographer happened
to be passing through town that day.
- Frank Sheldon.
- Sheldon?
- The one that started the Gazette.
- That's right.
And what was supposed to be
a series of rudimentary shots
to test a camera he'd invented
ended up capturing
one of the only live bank
robberies ever caught on film.
No, men, stand down! Stand down!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Don't you... I'll fucking kill her!
Hey, I'll kill her, Duke!
- Hardin, don't you hurt her!
- I know you don't want that.
No!
Come on!
It gained national attention,
what with the vicious nature
of the crime an the...
high-profiled individuals involved.
One in particular, a well-respected
U.S. marshal named Duke Donovan.
That him?
Some say he was the ringleader.
So the man people were supposed
to trust ended up betraying them.
Doesn't end there.
Donovan and Hardin
escaped free and clear that day.
But a posse caught up to them later.
This one's alive.
So Hardin double-crossed Donovan
and took the money.
On the contrary,
it's all right there with Donovan.
Donovan claimed that he
was trying to stop them,
but Hardin was holding a woman
hostage outside of town.
He said he was gonna kill her
if Donovan didn't aid in the robbery.
So Donovan said he went along with it,
until the last second.
- There was no sign of a mysterious woman.
- And Hardin?
Donovan claimed he shot him
in the head before he blacked out.
Never found the body.
Well, what happened next?
I don't know if it was his 20 years
of service to the law,
or the fact that Donovan claimed he never
fired a shot during the robbery, but...
something put doubts
in the minds of the jury.
That's a hangin' offense,
but they sentenced him to life
in the Yuma territorial prison.
He lasted there six weeks before escaping.
He was killed two days later
by a young deputy.
- Sounds like quite a story.
- Oh, it is.
I had to uncover a lot of rocks
to find this much.
- But what do you think?
- I'm not sure.
But I'm gonna let you
help me form that opinion.
- How's that?
- By getting an interview
with the last man alive
who knows what really happened.
His name is Seymour Redfield.
Some people think his real name
is Tom Sullivan.
The young deputy
that killed Donovan that day.
When Sullivan brought Donovan's body
back to town, he disappeared.
- Was never heard from again.
- Why don't you just talk to this man?
Well...
Let's just say we don't see eye to eye
and leave it at that.
Only interview I never got.
What makes you think
he'll wanna talk to me?
Because you have more motivation
than I do. Your job's on the line.
Get the story.
Or...
Hello?
Hello? Mr. Redfield?
Jeez.
That's a .45 long Colt.
Its many admirers referred to it
as the peacemaker.
- Mr. Redfield?
- Depends on who's asking.
I'm Jesse Helms, from the Gazette.
I was hoping I could talk to you.
I'd've thought you people'd
take the hint by now.
I didn't mean to intrude, sir.
Knocked on the door, and it fell open.
You know, I could've blown
your goddamn head off.
And I'd've been well within my rights.
But, since I just saved your life,
why don't you have a drink with me?
No thank you, sir. I'm on the clock.
Whose clock? Not my clock.
Well, in that case, a small one, sir.
Why don't you rest your butt?
Make yourself comfortable.
Thank you, sir.
You know, my...
Chief said that you didn't
like to talk too much.
Your chief? You mean Morgan Heinz?
Well, pay no attention to Morgan Heinz.
He's nothing but a damned old blowhard.
Only thing he's interested in...
is a good scandal so as he can sell
more sheets of that rag he puts out.
Heinz said that if I didn't talk to you,
then I'd be out of a job.
Well, that's too bad.
However, I hear the pig farm
down the road is hiring.
You know, sir, I don't wanna waste
any more of your time.
I'll see myself out.
I inherited this gun...
from Duke Donovan the day he died.
Marshal Duke Donovan?
The very one.
Was that the gun he used in the robbery?
Is that why Heinz sent you here?
Talk about Duke Donovan?
Well, yes, sir. It is.
Well...
I suppose if you're looking
for the truth...
that's where it all began.
With Donovan.
By 1892,
some say the legend of Duke Donovan
had begun to eclipse the man.
He never had any children.
On account of their getting married
later in life.
Just a wife he loved fiercely.
But their passion for each other
more than made up for it.
Their love was constant.
Through thick and thin, she stood by him.
Has the jury reached their verdict?
We have, your honor.
We, the above entitled jury do hereby
find Duke Donovan guilty on all counts.
Order! Order in the court! Order!
Now, the punishment for such a crime
is to hang by the neck until dead.
However... in light of your many years
of community service,
and your impeccable service record,
the court has decided
to grant you a reprieve.
Therefore, you are hereby sentenced
to life imprisonment
at Yuma territorial prison.
Where you shall do hard labor
for the rest of your life,
without the possibility of parole.
This court's adjourned. Take him away.
Duke came to Yuma prison
in the spring of 1893.
His arrival was the talk of the place.
He had as many enemies in Yuma
as he did admirers.
He'd put half of them in there.
He was a quiet, deliberate man.
And those eyes...
no one ever forgot those eyes.
All hands at attention!
Warden's on the floor!
I'd like to take a moment to...
personally welcome you all to Yuma.
I believe...
you'll find your stay here to be a tough,
but a fair one.
We work a six-day week
and rest on Sundays.
That's reserved for the good Lord.
I don't care who you are or what you did.
But in here, you're mine.
The government of this great territory
has asked us to assist
in the construction
of a new section of prison.
You'll get two squares a day.
But you'll have to work
damn hard for them.
However, in the end,
you'll manage to do something
you failed to do in your previous lives.
Make a positive contribution to society.
I consider myself a fair man.
Should you have a need
that has not been addressed,
my door is always open.
Ace high.
Godspeed in your work.
You ladies heard the warden.
Back to work.
Not you, Donovan. Come with me.
Come on!
You'll be stayin' in here. Warden Logan
thought it might be a good idea
to keep you away
from the rest of the populace.
Get changed. We'll come by
to collect your clothes.
Remember, ladies.
There is no talkin' on the line.
Unless you wanna be eating
your dinner through a straw.
Keep it down! Stay quiet!
Put your backs into it!
Hey!
Are you talkin' to me?
Yeah.
I like that pickaxe you got right there.
Say...
ain't you that law dog
everybody's been talking about?
Yeah.
That's me.
That's right! These rocks
ain't gonna break themselves!
Donovan began to settle in
to his newfound lot at life in Yuma.
Working by day and separated
from the other prisoners at night.
Many began to forget he was there.
As days turned to weeks,
the first month passed.
It looked like Donovan
was gonna be all right.
That is, until the day Will Penny...
and Cage Dalton arrived.
Dalton's ornery disposition
got him thrown in the hole immediately.
Straight to the hole.
As for Will Penny? Well...
He would have more to do
with the fate of Duke Donovan
than anyone could have ever realized.
That's right! Keep diggin'!
You want some?
No messin' around!
Is it true? That if the warden's
in a bad mood,
he makes us prisoners dig
with just the handles?
No?
What're you doing, kid?
Keep workin'!
Hey! Hey!
Get a hold of yourself, goddamn it.
Bunch of criminals.
Kid, kid, look at me.
You want Cane to hear you?
Son of a bitch.
- Sorry about this, kid.
- No, no, no, no, no!
What's going on here?
I don't know.
I think he's scorpion-bit.
That true?
Yes. It's just like he said.
All right, all right.
Get him up on his feet.
Get him up on his feet, take him
to the wagon. Get him a drink of water.
Whole thing's gonna set us back today.
Warden's gonna blow up!
Take a little sip of water.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Donovan.
Warden's on the block!
What happened here?
He got scorpion-bit, sir.
Show me.
- What's that, sir?
- Show me your bite.
Well, you know,
I don't know... You know, I...
Show the bite now, or I'll shoot you dead.
Okay! Please.
There is no bite.
I don't got no bite, sir.
I thought so.
There, now. There, now.
It feels good to tell the truth,
doesn't it, boy?
Yes, it does, sir.
Well, that's still no excuse.
Oh, no! Please! Please!
Throw him in the hole.
I will not tolerate liars.
Get up! Come on!
You got a problem with that?
He's just a kid.
That kid cut a couple in El Paso
from ear to ear with a butcher's knife.
But then, you know all about
murdering women and children, don't you?
- Deputy Sullivan?
- Yes, sir?
Throw him in the hole as well.
Seein' as you're the sympathetic type,
you can spend some time there
with your new friend.
Let's go, Donovan.
Come on.
Next time, it won't be empty.
I'm sorry about this, Donovan.
All right.
Checking the locks.
Stop.
Cut your goddamn tongue out.
Get some sleep.
Still one more week to go.
Cocksucker.
Ladies. Lockdown.
Listen, Donovan.
Yeah, kid?
That... that thing in... Young Country?
Did it really go down
the way they say it did?
You know, in all my years
of working with the law...
- there's one thing I learn.
- And what's that?
Nothing ever went down
the way they say it did.
Yeah.
I guess so.
What about you, kid?
Guessing they got your story wrong, too?
No, sir.
I...
I killed those people...
deader than hell.
After my parents died...
the state took my sister and me.
Put us in an institution.
Then one day, this...
this couple come, and...
they say I was gonna go live with them.
It was all right at first.
Made some new friends and...
had a roof over our head.
Then...
Then, one night...
the wife came into my room.
She wasn't wearin' nothing.
And she said, if I told anyone,
she was gonna send my sister away.
So...
I went along with it for a while.
To protect her.
Then I...
I caught the old man with her.
And I...
I knew I had to do something.
She was just...
just a little girl, you know?
Innocent.
That's a hell of a thing, kid.
That's a hell of a thing.
It's a real touching tale, ain't it?
What about you, Dalton?
What's your story?
Me?
Oh, I've done...
train-jumping and grave-robbing.
Card-playing. Lying, cheating,
stealing pretty much my whole life.
See, I was in... Clementina, New Mexico.
A few weeks ago, in a jail,
waiting on my trial date,
and there was a man in this...
in the jail cell with me.
He's limey, through and through.
Had a real nasty scar on the left side
of his face, result of getting shot.
- What was his name?
- We ain't in no hurry, is we?
- I said, we ain't in no hurry.
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
This fellow claimed that...
the gunshot to the head almost killed him.
Bank robbery gone wrong, says he.
Convinced this lawman...
to go along with him on account
of he had a fine piece of ass
held hostage, and he was gonna kill her.
If the lawman didn't go along with him.
I need your help, Duke.
Put your gun down,
or I'm blowing her head right off!
- He's gonna kill me!
- Put your gun down!
Good. I need your help.
- Keep talking.
- Well...
Anyhow, they pulled off the robbery
and got back to the hideout.
And they thought this lawman
was gonna be easy pickings,
on account of he was
outnumbered and all, but...
They was wrong.
Come on! Let's go!
Dark irony, it was.
Seems that this lawman
and the woman he was trying to help was...
actually the very woman who betrayed him.
She was a painted lady.
Lover of Levi Hardin.
Nursed him back to health.
Was in on it all along.
What happened to him?
- Where is he?
- That's... that's the best part, see?
Hardin was caught stealing cattle
in that part of country.
That's a hangable offense.
Hallelujah...
- Sheriff?
- Levi Perry Hardin...
you have been sentenced by a jury
to hang for your crimes until dead.
Do you have any last words?
Yeah. Y'all can kiss my ass!
It's just funny how...
a man can kill innocent women
and children and...
get life in prison.
But you take a man's cow?
That's a whole 'nother
goddamn deal, ain't it?
Guard!
You tell the warden I'm ready to see him.
Well, prisoner Donovan.
This is a pleasant surprise.
Leave us.
I must commend you.
You and your friend lasted a good while.
Not as long as some, mind you, but...
then, they didn't have the choice you did.
I came here to tell you
that Levi Hardin is still alive.
And I think I know where he's headed next.
Excuse me?
That's what you came to say to me?
Did you hear what I said?
Hardin's still alive.
I think my wife's in danger.
Well, that is a predicament.
But I fail to see what that has to do
with our meeting here today.
Listen, you son of a bitch!
I don't care what you think of me.
My wife's in danger.
Hardin's not gonna stop till
he gets to me any way he knows how!
Now, you gotta do something!
I suggest you take your hands
off my collar.
One call from me, and you won't have
to worry about your precious wife.
Because you'll be dead.
Excellent.
Guard!
- Take him away.
- Back to the hole?
No, put him in with the main population.
I'm sure they'll make room for him.
I don't care what you think of me.
There's an innocent woman in danger.
It's your duty to help her! It's your duty!
I have a witness! Ask Dalton!
Ask Dalton!
They will crucify him, sir.
Do it.
Cy...
you do make the best ribs
this side of the Mississippi.
Look, Sullivan, as far as I can tell,
you're the only guy in here
that has some sense of right and wrong.
Now, if you won't help me, help her.
Unhook him.
She's all alone out there, Sullivan.
You gotta help her.
You gotta do something!
There ain't nothing I can do, goddamn it!
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Go on.
Go!
Go, please.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. Donovan. I got me a nice place
right over here for you.
You know, first thing
I did when I got out...
was make a trade for this.
Hey, Donovan.
What's going on?
You need to get out of here, kid.
No matter what happens, you stay away.
No, sir, I need to stay
right here with you.
Beat it.
Beat it!
What you gonna do?
I'm not sure.
You remember me?
Oh, yeah, I remember you.
Jarvison.
You and your rapist brother.
It ain't proper to insult the dead
since you done the killin'.
Kid, I want you to promise me something.
Yes, sir.
No matter what happens to me,
you hang in there.
You stick with the old-timers.
They know how to survive.
- Yeah.
- You hear me?
But you gonna be okay?
- Just promise me.
- Yes, sir.
Let it be.
Yeah! Go!
Come on, Mr. Donovan!
Watch out!
Come on. Come on.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Take it... take it easy.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Hang in with me, now.
It's all right, kid.
You give him a decent burial.
Ladies! Lockdown. It's night-night time.
Checkin' the locks.
Checking locks.
Donovan.
You don't belong here.
Meet me at the new yard in one hour.
You get caught, you're on your own.
Checkin' locks.
Hey! Hey! Come on.
Get down! Get down. Now, look.
This... this tunnel will take you
into the cemetery,
under the wall, and come out
by the warden's stables.
There's a set of reins there
waiting for you.
The warden had this dug
in case there was ever a mutiny.
- What about you?
- Oh, no. My runnin' days...
they behind me. You just get on.
Rescue your lady.
Hey, Donovan.
I'm real sorry about that kid.
Now, go on, get to getting, 'cause...
them guards'll be starting
a new set of rounds soon.
Cyrus, you could get hung for this.
No, don't worry about me.
I'll be all right.
I thought you said
your running days were over.
I changed my mind.
Well, I was shaken from my sleep
As they dragged me to my feet
I was mistaken by the long arm of the law
And the lesson I have learned
Is the innocent get burned
And the guilty set you up
To take the fall
Nobody's guilty in here
And the truth ain't always how it appears
Our story's all the same
Lord knows we've all been framed
And the evidence is perfectly clear...
Sorry to trouble you, ma'am.
Got a man hurt.
Can we use your well?
Please?
Bring him inside.
You know. We'd better water these horses.
There's ain't no time.
Well, if we don't water them,
we're gonna be walking.
All right.
- Who was it?
- Donovan.
- And Cy, too.
- Cy?
Goddamn nigger.
Bring them back. Dead.
Put him over there.
Get me some towels.
Well...
It's a real pretty place.
Yep.
Thank you.
Not much further, friend.
I'll tell you one thing, Cyrus.
- You sure don't ride like a cook.
- That's 'cause I ain't one.
Well, the warden sure liked your cooking.
Yeah, well, that's 'cause
of my special sauce.
- Oh, special sauce?
- You don't wanna know.
- So what happened, anyway?
- What happened to what?
To get you thrown in that rat-hole prison?
Well, I was in the ninth.
- You're a sure-enough buffalo soldier.
- That's right.
- That's Colonel Hatch, wasn't it?
- Yes, sir.
You know, we had us
this old buck sergeant.
I mean, he wanted to ride me
all the way to Kansas City.
Busting me down to a dog robber...
- Made you a cook, did he?
- Yeah, I don't like being a cook.
Let me ask you something, Donny.
Now, really, do...
now, do I look like a damn cook?
Cook.
How's it look?
He's got a bullet in his stomach.
Gut-shot.
How long ago was he shot?
A few days ago.
Where did it happen?
Just across the border, in New Mexico.
You know, you ask a lot of questions.
Don't mean to.
My husband was also a marshal.
Donovan. You know him?
We're gonna need to get him into town.
I'll get the...
Yeah, I know him. I know him real well.
- What's wrong?
- Something ain't right.
What do you mean?
- Where are the horses?
- Well, they could be turned out.
Maddy!
Maddy! Maddy.
Maddy, Maddy, Madeleine.
Talk to me.
I gotta get help. I gotta get help.
Oh, God...
Cyrus, get the horses.
We gotta get to town.
She's hurt! She's hurt bad.
Don't die on me. You hear me? Don't die.
I... Get the horses!
Don. Don, she's gone.
I'm real sorry, but she's gone.
- Another drink?
- No.
I lost my thirst.
Well, you wanted the truth, didn't you?
I just gave you what you asked for.
- Yeah, I did, didn't I?
- You sure as hell did.
I didn't ask you to come
snooping around here, you know?
Why are you telling me all this?
Why don't you just let me walk out of here?
Maybe I felt sorry for you. Being
in trouble with your chiefy and all.
Or maybe it's just because...
you remind me of myself
when I was your age.
I don't know.
I do know... you didn't come here
to talk about me.
You came here to talk about Donovan.
All right.
Well, then let's see. Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
Hardin and his men continued west.
To them, the events that had transpired
just a few hours earlier
were nothing more than a passing amusement
to be boasted about.
Oh, my darlin' Madeleine
Go on, Charlie, have fun with it.
Come on.
Wake up. I know you're not doing well,
but you're slowing us all up here.
You all right?
They've been here, all right.
That's their hoofprints in the watering hole.
All right, then.
We'll set up camp here for the night.
You know I'm real sorry, Donovan.
Something like this, I...
I just don't got no words.
This ain't your fight, Cyrus.
Yeah, well.
It seems to me... I've been fighting
other people's wars my whole life.
And I expect this ain't no different, but...
sometimes there's wars
a man just got to fight.
Mind telling me what the plan is?
I'm gonna track him down.
All the way to the gates
of hell, if I have to.
All right.
Yeah.
I'll tell you what.
That is a fine fire right there.
Think we gonna catch 'em tomorrow?
If they're headed
where I expect they're headed.
- Where's that?
- Backside of the whetstones.
- Donovan's ranch.
- How far?
Oh, I don't know.
Another day, or most of it, at least.
Damn.
You think he did it?
Did what?
Robbed that bank? Killed those people?
Hell yeah, he done it.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
You'd better get to knowin'.
She done this for you, didn't she?
She did a lot of things for me.
Thunder rolls up from the ground
Birds fly away from the sound
A lone hero stands in the eye of the storm
And demons dance in the fire
Chasing desire like devil's companions
But one will stand when there's none
When black horses run
Through the dark canyon
That's not gonna do any good now.
I don't reckon it's gonna
do no harm, neither.
Ready?
Go ahead, I'll catch up with you.
- All right.
- I'll be willing to go down
Where I've never been before
If you will hold the door
I will run through the valley
Where the sun will never shine
If you will be my light
And hard as I try
There's just no place to hide
Until this journey ends
And there's no tears left to cry
And I'll keep you with me
Safe in my memory
And I will see you on the other side
Of the ride
And I am bound to find the man
That I used to be back then
And before we meet again
When I put this anger down
Six feet in the ground
I will never kill again
And hard as I try
There's just no place to hide
Until this journey ends
And there's no tears left to cry
And I'll keep you with me
Safe in my memory
And I will see you on the other side
Of the ride
Take the reins.
What in the hell is this?
That's sage.
That's an Indian sign.
Indian sign? The hell you talkin' about?
Cy must still be with him.
Let's get down to the barn,
see if we can't find some grain.
Figure if they're going after Hardin
they'll be in Rio Verdes.
Indian sign, my ass.
Hey. Hey!
Show some goddamn respect!
I don't care who you are. If I catch you doing
something like that again, so help me God,
when we leave here, I'll bury you here.
That goes for both of you.
Bitch.
Yeah, you think the word's out
on our escape yet?
There ain't no railroad.
Probably no telegraph.
Shouldn't be no problem, then.
Yeah, unless Hurley's
still the marshal here.
He knows you?
He's an old acquaintance.
Hell, Donovan, everybody
in this country knows you.
Let's go.
Get me a bloody bottle of whiskey! Now!
- Maybe.
It's a little early
in the morning, ain't it, boys?
Drink it up, boys!
We don't see too many...
We don't see...
- too many...
- What?
Strangers.
Around these parts.
So, what'll it be?
Whiskey. Two glasses.
Leave the bottle.
What're you looking at?
I said, what the hell...
are you looking at?
You got any coffee?
Coffee?
Yeah. Sure. Of course, I'll...
- I'll be right back.
- That'd be a good idea.
I know you... I know you heard me.
What're you looking at?
Oh, and you, too?
That is a mighty nice bandanna
you got there.
You like this? Thank you.
I know you, don't I?
Maybe.
- Been around here before?
- No.
I'm from Sonora. They call me Chale.
Well, that is quite a name.
You're my friend, right?
But you gotta tell me something, friend.
Why the hell...
do you come in here with your
mulo slave who stares at people?
It's rude, no?
No, he's not rude.
He just doesn't like scumbags.
No, that ain't it.
I just don't like you.
Come on, let's go.
I'll be needing that horse, governor.
I do know... who you are.
- Was he here? Was he here?
- Who?
Tell me what he looked like.
Tell me what he looked like!
He was a rough-lookin' man.
He had a bad scar
that run across his face.
We didn't mean no trouble.
We're just trying to make a living is all.
You didn't mean any trouble?
You didn't mean no trouble?
If you're gonna kill me, start shooting.
Easy, Duke.
Just need to talk.
There ain't no time.
They took off that way.
Best I can tell, on one horse.
Good. We can catch them then.
Can't lie, if they come looking for you.
I wouldn't expect you to.
Come on. Let's go.
Greetings.
I'm Deputy Tom Sullivan. Yuma.
Marshal Hurley. What can I do for you?
- We're looking for a couple of men.
- One of them's a nigger...
Duke Donovan. The other one's name is
Cyrus Parker, and he is a buffalo soldier.
They broke out of Yuma.
Yeah, they came through town
a couple of hours ago.
Killed two men.
- I ain't surprised.
- Me either.
Those were a couple men who needed
killing. Rolled with Levi Hardin's gang.
We caught wind that Hardin's men
killed Donovan's wife.
- That they did.
- Son of a bitch.
- Any idea where they're headed?
- Oh, my guess would be the border.
- The border?
- Yeah. They're hot on his trail.
- Whose?
- Hardin's.
Obliged.
- Let's go.
- Thanks for the whiskey.
Freedom is your prison
when you curse to keep on running
Hard to tell the difference
From the hunter and the hunted
Looking for redemption
down the barrel of a gun
Your finger on the trigger
Your back against the sun going down
Going down
Going down to the place
where no mercy can be found
And you pay for what you've done
with your soul
Going down where the darkest
of the angels circle round
He's just waiting 'cause he knows
Yes, he knows
It's going down
Going down
Come on, Walker! Go!
Easy.
- He ain't been dead long.
- Yeah.
Come on. Come on. Get up, Cy.
How bad is it?
Well... didn't catch any bone,
but it's a good one.
What's going on over there?
That's three of the warden's deputies.
They're gonna be sitting ducks for Hardin.
Foster, check it out.
What're you doing?
I can't let innocent men get killed.
Even if they are trying to kill me.
- Think they lost us?
- Listen.
- What is it?
- It's too quiet.
Sullivan, get down!
Goddamn it! Jesus!
- Do something! Do something!
- Goddamn it!
Son of a bitch!
He's already dead! Already dead!
Got one!
We gotta get back to Cyrus.
Ready? Let's go.
Damn, my leg!
How you doing, Cy?
How the hell's it look like I'm doing?
Donovan, trying to get yourself shot?
Yeah, it appears so.
Come on.
We are dead men down here.
Sullivan, we gotta get to higher ground.
Now you're making sense.
Cy, I'm gonna need that mare's leg.
Yep.
When I give the signal...
- you give it all you got, all right?
- All right.
All right, Tom. You break when I do.
Let's go!
Shit!
Come on, Walker, let's go!
Fuck!
How many bullets you got left?
Four. Five, maybe.
So I guess we're finally gonna
get to finish what we started.
Finish what you started.
It doesn't matter.
The way I see it, we both lose.
You took my money. And I took your life.
You know what,
I'm gonna let God sort that out.
Fuck you!
So this is it.
This is the best you can do.
The great...
Duke Donovan!
Get up. Get up, Duke. Get up.
Fucking...
Duke! Duke!
She cried out for you, you know!
For you to save her.
Oh, she was a live one!
She wiggled like a little fish, she did!
She was all wet and slimy.
I slid right up, right in.
You know I gotta bring you in.
You're gonna have to kill me first.
Yeah, I know.
I ain't got no choice.
We all got choices.
I made mine a long time ago.
Do it.
I can't.
You're getting pretty good
on that thing, Cy.
Hey, Donovan.
You ever wonder why
I helped you escape out that prison?
It's 'cause you help me remember...
how I used to walk.
And I'm mighty beholden to you.
Here. This'll keep you company
on your travels.
You know, you might even learn
how to play the damn thing.
Thanks.
Donovan never told Sullivan
where he was going.
Both men wanted it that way
so as not to put the other at risk.
Cyrus rode east. Some say to Louisiana.
Where it was rumored
he'd prospered in dry goods.
Sullivan returned to Yuma with a bounty.
Of course, it was so charred,
no one could really tell who it was.
So the warden had to take
Sullivan's word that it was Donovan.
That day, Sullivan left Yuma for good.
Changed his name to Duncan.
And a month later became
the sheriff of Wickenburg.
Where he lives to this day.
So Sullivan never up and disappeared
like everyone thought.
He just changed his name.
Now you're catching on.
Wait, if... if you aren't Sullivan...
and only those three survived that day...
then you're...
- That makes you...
- 82 years old.
I thought you said you got that gun
the day Duke Donovan died.
I did.
I inherited this gun from Duke Donovan
the day he became Seymour Redfield.
He didn't need it anymore.
He was a dead man.
There's no statute
of limitations on murder.
Is there?
No, son, I'm afraid not.
Just got one more question.
- What is it?
- The robbery.
Were you tricked into it?
- Or behind it?
- What do you think?
I think I need another drink.
Can I ask you one more thing?
Why'd you tell me everything?
Well, I figure the sand in my hourglass
is running a little low,
and somebody ought to know the truth
about what really happened.
Just keep it under your sombrero,
will you? Until after I'm gone?
Thank you.
Thunder rolls up from the ground
Birds fly away from the sound
A lone hero stands in the eye of the storm
Lightning cracks open the sky
Mothers take their children and hide
Evil rides and the day of darkness is born
When fear blocks out the light
And the day turns to night
And hope is abandoned
And demons dance in the fire
Chasing desire like devil's companions
But one will stand when there's none
When black horses run
Through the dark canyon
Gunshots tear open the air
Trembling hearts send up a prayer
Hoping someone will come
To earn their salvation
When rocks of faith crumble to dust
You search your heart for someone to trust
Sometimes it's you
You've always been chasing
When fear blocks out the light
And day turns to night
And hope is abandoned
And demons dance in the fire
Chasing desire like devil's companions
But one will stand when there's none
When black horses run
Through the dark canyon