What are you stopping for?
I'm stopping for a rest.
Really Philip, you
can't stop here.
For pity's sake rather go on
or go back.
You can't expect me to spend the night
like a half-drowned rat on a mountainside.
Better to stop than drive the car
gently over a cliff, isn't it?
Well, it won't help things
losing your temper.
I've never been in a better temper
in my life.
I love driving a hundred miles through
the dark practically without headlights.
I love the trickle of ice cold water
pouring down my neck.
This is one
of the happiest moments of my life.
- Would you like me to drive for a bit?
- Yes, I was expecting that.
Oh, I shall be glad
if we get to Shrewsbury.
If we get to Shrewsbury.
- You happen to have any idea where we are?
- I haven't the least idea in the world.
That's very comforting.
You all right, Penderel?
Fine. Where are we?
We don't know. We've lost our way.
We're somewhere in the Welsh mountains.
It's half past nine,
and I'm very sorry.
Don't mention it!
- Ten to one we don't see Shrewsbury tonight.
- Oh well, never mind.
Oh, Mister Waverton, what shall I do?
I wanted to go to Shrewsbury
but they took me on to [Crew?]
As a matter of fact,
taking one thing with another,
I'm not particularly sure
that I want to go to Shrewsbury.
Far as that goes, I don't particularly
want to go anywhere.
Something might happen here,
but nothing ever happens in Shrewsbury.
Something certainly might happen here.
I'll tell you something that might happen.
- I don't want to frighten Mrs. Waverton.
- Go on, Mr. Penderel, I'm not easily frightened.
- Aren't you? I am. Well, I was just going to say,
we'll have to be a bit careful...
Don't stop!
How can I help stopping?
You think we're in a motorboat?
Stuck for the night!
Stuck for the night! Stuck...
- Sr. Penderel, please!
- Sorry.
- Do you think we'll do it?
- I really don't know.
Bon Voyage.
Well, now, for heaven's sakes, stop!
Let's look at a map or something.
My own view is we're not on a map.
Oh, you look, Philip, I can't see anything.
It's all a stupid puddle.
Seems to represent this country very well.
Everything here is underwater.
Oh, just drive on.
We'll arrive somewhere, sometime.
I suppose that's all we can do.
Singin' in the bathtub,
singin' in the rain....
Oh, look, Phil! Lights! Lights!
Pull in there.
- Probably wiser to push on.
- Well, I'm for staying here.
There you are.
The whole hilltop has probably fallen off.
'Is there anybody there?,
said the Traveller.'
Knock again, louder.
I suppose that was loud enough
to wake the dead.
- That's an idea.
- What is?
Wouldn't it be dramatic?
Supposing the people inside were dead,
all stretched out with the lights
quietly burning about them.
I'm sure it would be very amusing.
I'm sure I could do with a drink.
If people have to be soaked,
they should be soaked inside, not out.
- Listen.
- What is it?
I thought I heard something.
Good evening, we've come to ask
for shelter, we've lost our way.
We're absolutely cut off.
Don't you understand? We can't go
forward and we can't go back.
The road's blocked on both sides,
landslide
Even Welsh ought not sound like that.
My name is Femm. Horace Femm.
How do you do?
I'm very sorry to break in
on you like this.
My name is Waverton.
May I introduce my wife?
How do you do?
Penderel!
- Charmed, I'm sure.
- How do you do?
Won't you sit down?
Thank you.
My sister was on the point
of arranging these flowers.
I don't know if your man
explained the situation to you.
He did his best but I'm afraid
I couldn't understand him.
You see, Morgan is dumb.
Oh, I see. Of course,
I didn't realize.
We saw your lights and wondered
if you'd be kind enough
to give us shelter for the night.
You see it's
quite impossible to go on.
I see. How awkward.
How very awkward.
What is it?
What do they want?
Allow me to introduce my sister,
Rebecca Femm.
How do you do?
What are they doing here?
What do they want?
How are you?
How do you do?
What do they say?
What do they want?
What are they doing here?
What's all the fuss about? What?
You must excuse my sister.
She's a little deaf.
In fact, sometimes quite deaf.
They want to know if they
can stay here for the night.
Shelter. They've been caught
in the storm.
Of course they can't stay!
We can't have them here!
...
Go on...
You see, there's a landslide.
Half the mountain seems to be crumbling.
It only just missed us.
The road's blocked behind us and I'm
pretty sure it's blocked in front as well.
We hate to intrude but what else can we do?
You see there isn't anywhere else
we can go.
And even the road below is underwater
and, for that matter,
this place itself may be underwater
pretty soon or even buried.
What's the matter?
Did you hear what he said?
There's a landslide and floods.
The lake has burst its banks.
We're trapped. We're trapped.
We've got to go. Do you hear?
We've got to go.
Hmmph. You're afraid, Horace.
You're afraid, aren't you?
You don't believe in God
and yet you're afraid to die.
You've seen His anger in the sky
and you've heard Him in the night.
And you're afraid. Afraid. Afraid.
Where's your mocking now?
You might well be afraid.
Your time will come.
But it hasn't come yet. This house is safe.
I know it better than you. Morgan!
You remember the great storm years ago
when we were cut off?
And there was a landslide. And floods.
And the roads were washed away?
Morgan remembers. He means this house
is safe. Because it's built on rock.
You will have to stay here.
The misfortune is yours, not ours.
No beds!
They cann't have beds!
As my sister hints, there are,
I'm afraid, no beds.
That's quite all right. If we can just sit
around the fire that will be fine.
By all means. I'm not very sure
that I want to go to bed myself tonight.
Morgan will tend to the fire.
Is there any place I can put
the car out of the rain?
There are some stables 'round the corner,
to the right.
- Morgan will show you.
- Thanks very much.
- I'll come along and get the bags.
- Right.
No beds! You can't have beds!
- Quite a storm!
- We're well out of it.
I hope you're right, though
this house gives me the creeps,
not to mention its inmates.
Well, it's better than driving along roads
that aren't there.
At least there's a roof and a fire here.
Now, Mister Penderel, do you think
that you could join me in a drink?
Mister Femm, I honestly believe
I could join you in a drink.
It's only gin, you know. Only gin.
I like gin.
Mrs. Waverton?
Thanks very much.
Mister Penderel, I'll give you a toast
that you will not appreciate, being young.
I give you... illusion!
Illusion? Huh! I'm precisely the right age
for that toast, Mister Femm.
Oh. I presume you
are one of the gentlemen slightly,
shall we say,
battered by the war?
Correct, Mister Femm. War generation,
slightly soiled, a study in the bittersweet,
the man with the twisted smile, and this,
Mr. Femm, is exceedingly good gin.
Dreadful night.
Seems to be getting worse.
Yes, it is pretty bad.
But evidently there's no danger here.
Your sister was quite definite about that.
But supposing we're cut off,
shut up in here?
Well, it would be rather a nuisance for you
having us billeted on you like this
But it's awful. How can you be so calm?
You don't seem to understand.
We may be cut off.
Shut up in this house!
I'm afraid I'm rather nervous.
I am rather a nervous man.
The fact is... Morgan is an uncivilized brute.
Sometimes he drinks heavily.
A night like this would set him going
and once he's drunk, he's rather dangerous.
I don't wish to alarm you, Mrs. Waverton,
but I don't quite know what we should do.
Well, I know what I'm going to do.
That is, if Miss Femm will let me.
What?
I'm dreadfully wet and I would be so glad
if I could go and change my clothes.
What?
I wondered if I might change my things?
You look wet. You'd better go
and change your things.
Oh, thank you. A good idea.
Is there a bedroom or something?
- It's a dreadful night.
- What?
I say, it's a dreadful night.
Yes, it's a very old house.
Very old.
- Very kind of you to let us stay.
- What?
I say, you're very kind!
Yes, it's a dreadful night.
I'm a little deaf.
I understand.
Yes. No beds!
I'll have none of this electric light.
I won't have it.
Thanks very much.
I can manage quite well now.
My sister Rachel had this room once.
She died when she was twenty-one.
She was a wicked one.
Handsome and wild as a hawk.
All the young men
used to follow her about.
With her red lips and her big eyes
and her white neck. But that didn't save her.
She fell off her horse, hunting.
Hurt her spine.
On this bed she lay,
month after month.
Many the time I sat here
listening to her screaming.
How dreadful.
She used to cry out to me...
to kill her.
But I'd tell her to turn to the Lord.
But she didn't. She was godless to the last.
Well, I'd better change my wet things.
They were all godless here.
They used to bring their women here.
Brazen, lolling creatures
in silks and satins.
They filled the house with
laughter and sin, laughter and sin.
If I ever went down among them...
my own father and brothers...
They would tell me
to go away and pray.
They wouldn't tell Rachel to go away
and pray. Ha ha ha ha ha! And I prayed!
I left them with their lustful red
and white women. My father's still alive.
He's upstairs. He's very old.
Oh, is he?
He's a hundred and two.
That's very old, isn't it?
He's a wicked, blasphemous old man.
You're wicked, too. Young
and handsome. Silly. And wicked.
You think of nothing but your long,
straight legs and your white body
and how to please your man.
You revel in the joys of fleshly love,
don't you?
That's fine stuff, but it'll rot.
That's finer stuff, still.
But it'll rot, too, in time.
Don't! How dare you?
...brazen, lolling creatures
in silks and satins...
laughter and sin... laughter and sin...
lustful red and white women...
Philip! Aaah!
Good for you, Mrs. Waverton.
You make it look like a party.
Thank you.
You must have thought I was a long time.
Matter of fact, I thought
you were quicker than usual.
Oh. I just thought I'd been rather long.
Supper!
Philip.
Horace! What are you doing?
We aren't all heathens.
Oh, I had forgotten
my sister's strange tribal habits.
The beef will seem less tough
when she has invoked a blessing upon it.
Horace Femm. If I can't hear, I can see.
You're blaspheming.
On the contrary, my dear Rebecca.
I was merely telling your wondering guests
that you were about to thank
your gods for their bounty....
That'll do. I know your mocking,
lying tongue.
... to thank them for the health and prosperity
and happiness granted to this family.
For its years of peace and plenty. To thank
them for having created Rebecca Femm.
And Roderick Femm. And Saul...
Stop!
Bless O Lord this... mankind. Amen.
Have a potato.
Thank you.
Well, this is a storm and a half.
Yes, isn't it?
Have a potato.
Thank you. I should love a potato.
Vinegar, Miss Femm?
It's simply coming down
in bucketfuls outside.
Thank you, Mrs. Waverton. That's the phrase
I've been searching for all evening.
No, no pickled onions, thank you.
Those lights. They gave me quite a start.
I suppose it's the storm.
On the contrary. We make
our own electric light here
and we're not really good at it.
Pray don't be alarmed if they go out altogether.
There's someone outside.
They can't come in!
But surely they must come in.
It's probably dangerous out there now.
They're probably half drowned. You know,
really, we oughtn't keep them waiting.
No, I'm afraid we shall have to let them in.
Morgan, open the door.
Come on then, Morgan.
Let them in.
Whoooo! What a night!
I thought you were never going
to open that door.
Why... hoo huh hah!... there must've been
a reservoir burst or something.
Ha ha ha! Anyhow, before
we knew where we were,
something had fallen down
and smashed the car in.
Ha ha ha! It's a wonder
it didn't smash us. Hah!
Incidentally, this house will probably
be washed away any minute.
Hey, whoa, ha!
Look at that! Ha!
Ohhh. That's a grand fire.
I'm sorry to barge in on you like this,
but... ha!...
needs must when the devil drives. Ha ha ha!
Well? Who's the owner here?
My sister is the owner. Miss Femm.
How do you do, Miss Femm?
My name is Porterhouse.
Sir William Porterhouse
And this lady is Miss Gladys DuCane,
a friend of mine.
Glad to know you.
Nice weather for ducks.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Mrs. Waverton.
How do you do?
- Mister Penderel.
- How do you do, Sir William?
- And, uh, Mister Waverton.
- How do you do?
Sir William Porterhouse.
Howdyedo?
I've never seen such a night
in all my born natural.
I tell you, it's coming down in bucketfuls.
Pretty well soaked we were,
I don't mind telling you. I shouldn't
be surprised if we caught our death.
Here, you'd better not put
those wet shoes on again,
or, as Sir William points out,
you'll probably catch your death.
Here you are. These may not be exactly your size
but at least they're dry.
Thanks. That'll do fine.
Whee! Ha ha!
Are you fond of opera, Monsieur?
Come and have something to eat.
Oh! Now, you're talkin'.
Morgan, bring out some chairs.
Oh ho! Roast beef! Hah! There's nothing
like roast beef when a man's hungry.
Oh, the roast beef of old England...
How does that go? Do you remember that,
Mister Waverton, or was that before your time?
- Penderel's our song expert.
- Oh, so you're musical, are you?
Well, I've got a bit of an ear myself...
Have a potato.
Morgan, bring a
glass of water for Sir William.
Ah, thanks very much.
... take ourselves, for instance.
Here we are, six people,
sitting around,
and we've been talking now
nearly two hours,
and what do we know about each other?
Not a thing.
How reassuring.
I agree with Sir William.
At best, we only make guesses.
If you were a woman,
you wouldn't talk about only guesses.
Ah! The famous old feminine intuition.
Does it ever tell you which horse
is going to win the Derby?
No. But it tells me
quite a lot about you.
I wonder, Mrs. Waverton,
whether it happens to tell you
that I am wanted by the police?
Why, no, Mister Femm,
it tells me nothing so romantic.
After all, can you conceive of anybody
living in a house like this if they didn't have to?
Well, there's no accounting for tastes,
you know.
No.
- Miss DuCane?
- Yes?
What does your intuition tell you about me?
Quite a lot.
Hmm... that frightens me a good deal.
What does it tell you?
It tells me...
Well, it's not very interesting anyway.
Oh, yes, it is. Let's have it.
Well... heh heh, it sounds silly but...
I think he doesn't quite fit into these times.
You know, factories and cheap advertising
and money grubbing and...
well, what I mean is, Bill here's all right
with these things.
But they make Mister Penderel
a kind of fish out of water.
You should be flattered, Mister Penderel.
No, I'm not flattered.
You see, I've not much sympathy with fish
out of water although I happen to be one myself.
My trouble is, I don't think
enough things are worthwhile.
Now, Sir William here would put tremendous energy
into anything to make even a few pounds.
I don't think it's worth it.
No doubt you'll think I'm very fat-headed,
my young friend.
But maybe I can see through things
a bit further than you suppose.
That was a very fine speech of yours
but I know as well as everybody else here
that you're really
only getting at me.
But, honestly, I wasn't doing
anything of the kind.
I envy you. I admire you.
Oh, yes, you envy me, all right.
But you don't admire me.
Heh! Well, I... I don't admire myself so much.
I know that money-making isn't everything.
But let me tell you something.
I'm a young man, see?
Married to a Manchester girl,
pretty as paint,
the only thing in the world I care about.
Well... she dies.
It's this way. My directors give a party.
They ask us. Red letter day for us, I can tell you.
Heh! I buy my first dress suit.
And Lucy had a new frock. A cotton frock.
It seems that Lucy didn't go too well
at that party. Especially with the women.
They snubbed her.
Nothing definite, you know.
Just didn't think the cotton frock
was good enough.
Well, Lucy worries about it.
Gets into her head that she's gonna hold me back.
Well, you may not believe it,
but I know that's what killed her.
That's what started me making money.
I swore I'd smash those fellows and their wives
who wouldn't give my Lucy a kind word.
Ha! And I have smashed 'em.
At least, most of 'em.
Once you've started making money,
it's hard to stop.
Especially if you're like me,
there isn't much else you're good at.
Ha! But what Gladys here
has to be superior about, I don't know.
Miss DuCane.
Why don't you tell 'em your real name?
My real name... is Perkins.
And a very nice name, too.
I may not be this
and I may not be that
but you don't catch me
pretending to be what I'm not.
I think I'm finding you
a little bit offensive.
That's all right, Mister Penderel.
I can take care of myself.
Least, if I can't by now,
I never will be able to.
I wasn't trying to put
anything across you, Bill.
I don't pretend to be what I'm not either.
I'm not as dumb as that.
These people here know a chorus girl
when they see one.
And, incidentally,
not a very good chorus girl at that.
If I were better at my job,
I probably wouldn't be weekending with you.
No. I take that back. I probably would.
You're nice enough. We get on, but...
Morgan's at the bottle again.
I knew he'd begin tonight.
Where did he get it from?
He didn't get it from me.
Can't you stop him?
He's in the kitchen now, drunk.
Quite drunk.
Who's Morgan? Is he the fellow
who waited on us at table?
Yes. Morgan is the...
the butler.
Looks to me as if he could do with a shave.
Ha ha!
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Well? Have you come over to help me
gaze upon the wrath of God?
No. I came to say thank you for trying
to take my part just now.
Charmed, I'm sure, Miss DuCane.
Perkins to you.
Thanks, Perkins.
I say, I'd mortgage
the old homestead for a drink.
Hmm... so would I.
And we'll have one!
I've got some whiskey in the car.
I'd forgotten all about it.
You stay here and I'll go and get it.
No, I'll come with you.
Wheeee!
You'd better stay here under cover.
The car's in the stables
and you'll get soaked.
All right. But don't be long.
Mister Penderel?
Hello. What are you doing here?
I was just coming.
I thought I'd come
and fetch you.
Hey, hey. What's the matter?
What's happened?
Nothing. Nothing, really.
I'm a bit scared, that's all.
Somebody slammed
the door in my face.
- Probably the wind.
- No, it wasn't.
I know wind when I see it.
It doesn't sound much, but,
you know, it gave
me a bit of a turn.
Yes, I bet it did.
Here, what you want is a drink of this.
Thanks.
I feel a bit more human now.
This certainly is a benighted household.
You're right. It is.
Look at those.
Come on, take 'em off.
I seem to've spent most of the evening
changing your shoes.
You ought to be a nursery maid.
Yes, except that the best nursery maids
don't drink whiskey out of the bottle.
The storm's just as bad as ever,
isn't it?
Worse.
That's done it. The light's gone out.
I suppose they'll stay out this time.
Now, we shall be miserable all the evening.
That's all right. Surely, there's
some candles somewhere, aren't there?
Can I do anything about the lights,
Miss Femm?
No. Nobody understands
our lights except Morgan.
And, as an electrician,
Morgan is temporary disqualified.
You haven't got a lamp by any chance,
have you?
No. No. We haven't got a lamp.
- What did they say?
- Nothing. Nothing important.
Oh? Not important? Ha!
It happens I heard that time.
They want a lamp. Give them the large one.
There's oil in it.
We used it the last time the lights went
wrong. Go on, Horace. You know the one.
I don't remember where it is.
Suppose you get it, Rebecca?
It's too big for me. If you don't know
where it is, I'll tell you.
Now, you know as well as I do.
It's on the top landing on the little table.
You know where the top landing is, Horace?
At least you might believe there is a top landing.
Oh, but you do believe in so little.
It's up there, Horace.
Up there. Next to the roof.
Yes, of course. I remember.
But I think it's a little too heavy for me.
I don't think I could carry it down
all those stairs.
Why don't you say
what you mean, Horace? Ha!
You mean that you're afraid
to go up there alone.
You go with him. Here take this.
I don't know why I bother myself.
Do you all good to sit in the dark.
- We'd better go up, hadn't we?
- Yes. I suppose we had.
We won't be long.
That's all right. Mrs. Waverton will see
that I don't get nervy.
You'd better lead the way.
This is my room.
Oh?
There are one or two things
that I should very much like for you to see.
I should like to very much.
But you must show me some other time.
We've got to get that lamp.
Yes.
Listen, why should we bother
about the lamp?
Let us wait here for a few minutes
and then go back
and say that we couldn't find it.
Or that it's broken.
I can't see the point.
Yes, but why should we trouble
about the lamp if we don't want to?
But we said we'd get it,
so why shouldn't we get it?
Yes, but why should we if we don't want to?
And I don't want to.
But this is absurd...
Did you hear that?
I did hear something.
What was it?
It must have been Morgan.
He's drunk, you know.
He's probably making a disturbance
downstairs in the kitchen.
I thought that noise came from upstairs.
Anyway, what about this lamp?
I wonder whether you would excuse me
from coming with you?
I'm not very strong.
There are rather a lot of stairs.
I really should have told you before
but the, the vanity of age, you know...
You'll find it on the little table
at the end of the landing, two floors above.
I suppose it's not too heavy
for me to carry.
Oh, no, not at all.
It's quite light really.
I see.
Thank you, thank you very much.
You opened it, didn't you?
Well, now you can go and shut it.
Go on, shut it. I can't.
Go and shut what?
The rain's pouring in.
The flood's rising.
We all'll be drenched
if you don't come quickly.
She means the window in her room.
I'm afraid I opened it.
Go on. You opened it.
You can shut it.
That's all right, Miss Femm.
I'll come and shut it.
Mister Penderel! Miss DuCane!
It's Morgan. He's there at the bottom
of the stairs.
Take the candle.
Get back there.
Get back!
Go on, get back!
- Is he dead?
- No, you can see him breathing from here.
He's only stunned.
He'll be conscious in a minute but he'll probably
fall asleep again. He's very drunk.
Oh, Philip, this is an awful house.
It isn't very nice, is it?
Listen, Margaret, something happened
upstairs just now.
Oh, Philip. Not something else horrible.
No, this was nothing horrible.
It was a voice calling from behind a door.
A tiny voice, rather like a child's.
I think I ought to go and see what it is.
You'll have to come with me.
I'm not going to leave you alone again.
He'll be all right.
Take my hand, darling.
- Oh, Philip.
- What is it?
Sit down here a minute, darling.
Thanks.
- Well, what happened then?
- Well, then the war ended.
- What about the girl?
- Oh, the girl I left behind me?
- The girl you were in love with.
- Why, she got married, Gladys.
What a beast.
No, on the contrary, a lady
of rather good judgment.
Now, let's talk about
you for a bit.
I know what you're going to say.
You're going to ask me about Bill Porterhouse.
Clever, Miss Perkins.
I don't mind telling you.
I'd rather like to.
Bill's all right, really.
Of course, I don't love him.
Of course, he gives me money.
Oh, not very much.
Just enough to keep me going.
You probably won't believe me,
but Bill doesn't...
he doesn't expect anything.
Do you know
what I mean by anything?
Yes. I know what you mean by anything.
He likes people to think he's ever so gay.
You see, for all his money,
he's a bit lonely.
Yes, I spotted that when he told us
the story of the cotton dress.
I think he's in love with
that little dead wife still.
I'm sure he is. I suppose that's why
he only wants me, well, for company.
He likes to sit on my bed at night
and boast to me about the things
he's done during the day.
Well, that's harmless enough.
Mind you, I'm not pretending to be
any better than I am.
You're a nice creature, aren't you?
I like you, awfully.
And I you.
What are you thinking of?
- You may not be very pleased.
- Risk it.
I was thinking that I would like to pretend
that I was your lover
and that you were mine,
Gladys, body and soul.
I'd like to take you in my arms and hold you
and press you to me very gently, very tight.
I'd like it, too.
Would you, Gladys Perkins?
Why, then, let's pretend.
Listen. Gladys Perkins has an idea.
I think she must have gone mad.
She... she...
She wants to live with you.
Oh, I'm just flinging myself
at your head.
I've got a crazy idea that I might help you
to be a useful person.
Darling, Perkins...
Do you think I'm mad?
Quite mad, my darling.
And thank God for it.
Well, what do you say?
That's what I say, Perkins darling.
But I've got a better idea than yours.
An improvement on it.
What is it?
Why, it's just this... No, I won't tell you here.
There's magic here.
I'll tell you later on in the house,
perhaps even in the cold light of morning.
Tell me now.
- Come on, let's go back to the house.
- No! No, let's stay here.
- You're cold.
No. It's just the idea of going back
to that house that made me shiver.
I've got a funny feeling something dreadful
might happen to us if we go back to that house.
Perkins, Perkins.
You've my strong right arm, haven't you?
All right. Come on.
No, you can't put on those wet shoes.
I'm going to try to carry you.
I'm a devil of a weight.
Well, if you're too heavy for me,
I shall drop you in the mud and go on alone.
Hello. Where have you been?
I went out to the car to get a drink.
And I went with him.
She got her feet wet.
- Oh, she got her feet wet?
- Yes, she got her feet wet.
Well, what the devil's been happening here?
I don't know what the devil's
been happening here or anywhere else.
I don't know what's been happening
anywhere.
I went into the old girl's room to close
a window and came back and found this.
Where are all the others?
I don't know any more than you.
Mister Waverton went upstairs
with Horace Femm to fetch a lamp.
I suppose his wife joined him.
I've been asleep.
So, you got your feet wet?
Yes, Bill. And that wasn't all, either.
Yes, I didn't suppose it was.
I don't quite know how you'll take this but...
well, I've got to get it off my chest.
Come on, let's have it.
I've fallen in love, Bill.
Oh, you have, have you?
With him?
- Yes, with him.
- Darned fool.
Probably. But we don't choose these things.
- Has he got any money?
- Not a penny.
But you're going out with him?
Yes, Bill. Are you angry?
I think you're a lunatic.
But I'm not angry.
He took it pretty well, didn't he, Perkins?
- I told you. Bill's all right.
- He is indeed.
Wonder where the others can be?
Listen, Bill. She hasn't told
you everything.
Hasn't she? Why not?
Because she doesn't know
everything herself.
- We're going to be married.
- Oh, are you?
At least, if she'll have me.
I'm going to ask her tomorrow.
In the cold light of morning.
- Will you come to the wedding?
- I think you're off your head.
Do you?
No. I don't.
I think it's probably the best day's work
you've ever done in your life.
Ah, Bill, Bill...
Who told you that you could call me Bill?
Ha, ha. Well, you try and stop me.
Now, look here, come and make yourself
useful and put this table on its feet.
Huh! That's no way to treat roast beef.
Miss Perkins, tin the roast beef.
Tin it yourself.
Sure you feel better?
Yes, I'm all right.
Well, let's go on.
This is the door.
Who are you?
I'm Mrs. Waverton. This is my husband.
Are you Sir Roderick Femm?
We came in because we thought
we heard you calling.
Can we get you anything?
Can you take it yourself
or shall I give it to you?
I can take it myself, thank you.
Now, what was that noise?
- Was it... Morgan?
- Yes.
Morgan is a savage.
I, er, I must apologize.
But we have to keep him here.
You shouldn't have come here.
I'm very sorry but, really,
we couldn't help it.
Oh, I... I don't mean that.
I was never inhospitable. Never.
This house was always filled with guests,
once upon a time.
When you came, what did they tell you?
Why, they told us you were an invalid.
- Was that all?
- Yes.
You've seen my son, Horace?
And his sister, Rebecca?
Yes.
And Morgan. I would like to tell you all
about it but... but there may not be time.
You see, when you're as old as I am,
at any minute, you may just die.
Oh, please don't talk if it tires you.
This is an unlucky house. Two of my
children died when they were twenty.
And then... other things happened.
Madness came.
We are all touched with it a little, you see.
Except me. At least, I-I don't think I am.
Would you like to go to sleep now?
No. Not just yet. You see, it may be...
It may be what?
Dangerous.
You mean Morgan?
No. Not Morgan.
I mean from my eldest son, Saul.
Saul?
They didn't tell you about Saul?
No, they didn't.
Saul is the worst, you know.
We have to watch him.
Because you see, he wants... he just
wants... to destroy, to kill. Poor Saul.
Where is he?
I know where he is. He's upstairs
behind that bolted door, isn't he?
Yes. Locked in.
Saul is why we have to keep Morgan.
But if he did get out?
Saul quite certainly would
set fire to the house.
He tried to once before.
He wanted, he said,
to make this house a burnt offering.
But isn't he safely locked in?
Yes. But you see, if Morgan is bad, I, er,
I think he might, er, open the door.
Philip. What if he's come to?
Wait here. I'll go down and look at him.
He's gone upstairs. I heard him.
He's gone to let Saul out.
Wait for him downstairs and kill him.
What are we to do?
Can't we stay in here?
No, supposing he set fire to the place?
Come on.
But what about Sir Roderick?
We must lock the door.
Sir Roderick, I'm going to lock you in.
He's asleep.
What is it?
Listen, there's a madman upstairs.
Morgan's let him out and he's dangerous.
- We've got to do something.
- Good gosh. Where are they?
Upstairs.
But they may come down any minute.
That's all right, my dear.
I knew I felt something dreadful
was going to happen.
- Hadn't we better get out of the way?
- No, we can't do that.
He might set fire to the place.
He's tried it once before.
Well, let him. Let the rotten old
place burn. I wish it would.
That's all right but what
about the Femms?
What is it?
Your brother's out of his room.
What? Saul?
Look.
Here. Get back.
Take him back, Morgan! You hear me?
Take him back!
Take him in the kitchen!
Take him inside!
Lock him in the kitchen!
The sins of the fathers.
Come on, you!
Come into my room!
No! I'm going to stay here.
Then, stay here!
There's going to be trouble.
Oh! Penderel!
Come on. Come in here.
No! I don't want to be shut up.
I'd rather stay.
Gladys, for heaven's sake,
come in here. Margaret.
No. Oh, all right.
Wait a minute.
Here, light this.
Oh, I love him so.
I just love him.
Please.
Please don't touch me.
Well! What is it?
Listen, don't put me back.
Don't let them put me back.
I'm not mad.
I swear before heaven I'm not mad.
It's just that they've locked me up here.
They're all wicked.
Why should they lock you up?
They're frightened of me.
I know something about them.
Years ago, they killed their sister Rachel.
But I wouldn't tell! I promised I'd never tell.
And they've kept you here
all that time for that?
And Morgan... I tell you, he's the devil...
Morgan beats me.
Don't leave me!
Stay with me!
That's all right. You sit here and wait.
I'll be back.
The door's locked!
Miss Femm must have locked it.
- It's locked, is it?
- Yes, it is.
I'm glad.
Then, you can't leave me.
Listen, we've got to help
the others with Morgan.
Isn't there some way
of getting through?
No. No way...
But there must be
a back entrance into the house.
Stop!
I want to tell you a story.
- Who's in there?
- Nobody.
Friends of yours?
I tell you, nobody.
Shall we invite them out?
You... you were going to tell me something.
Yes. So I was.
Don't you...
won't you tell me that story?
Yes. Shall we sit down?
Yes. Let's.
Who is in that cupboard?
Nobody. Tell me what
you were going to say to me.
Are you interested in flame?
Why... why, yes. Yes, I am, rather.
I've made a study of flame.
Have you? That happens
to be very interesting.
I know things about flames
that nobody else in the world knows.
Won't you tell me?
I'd like very much to know.
Why should I tell you? You wouldn't
tell me who is in that cupboard.
Well, I did tell you. Besides, you know,
it isn't fair to make me curious
and then just not say anything.
You'd like me to tell you
all about fire, would you?
Yes, I wish you would.
Well, first of all, I learned
that flames are really knives.
They're cold, my friend.
Sharp and cold as snow. They burn like ice.
Oh. That certainly is very...
very interesting.
So, they're really like knives, are they?
Well, do go on.
Tell me what else you found out.
Oh, a lot of things.
My friend, sit down.
So, you thought
you could cheat me, did you?
You thought you could leave me sitting here
and I wouldn't notice.
But, you see, I am a clever man also.
That is why we understand one another.
That is why you understood so quickly
that I wanted to kill you.
We understand each other so well,
don't we, my friend?
Yes. Yes, indeed we do. From the start,
somehow I... I liked you
and I... I thought you liked me.
Like you? My friend, I love you.
Did you know my name is Saul?
Saul, my friend.
And Saul loved David.
Yes, indeed he did.
But Saul was afraid of David because the Lord
was with him and was departed from Saul.
And it came to pass on the morrow
that the evil spirit came upon Saul
and he prophesied in the midst of the house.
And David played upon the harp with his hand.
And there was a javelin in Saul's hand.
And Saul cast the javelin.
And he said, I will smite David
even to the wall with it.
And David appointed out of his presence
twice. Twice, my friend.
And the third time... the third time...
you must be careful.
Listen. I'm your friend. I'm on your side.
It's silly to lose me. If you lose me...
Look! There's Morgan!
He's come for you! Morgan!
Stop! Don't move!
Philip! Philip!
Oh, let go! Can't you see?
There's Penderel!
Let me go to him. Go on, let me go by.
Go on, let me pass.
Ooh, you swine. But I'm not afraid of you.
I'm going to him. Do you hear?
Oh, how could you?
Listen, you've got to let me alone, do you hear?
I've got to go to Penderel. He's hurt.
Oh, how can I make you understand?
He's hurt.
I've got to look after him
and the other man, too, Saul.
They're both hurt.
- Are you all right, Margaret?
- Yes, I'm all right, darling.
Gladys.
It's all right. Come on now.
You feeling better?
Yes, I'm not so bad.
- What happened to you?
- That was Morgan. He hit her.
Come on.
I'm all right now. Where's Penderel?
I've got to look after him.
You'd better not go over there.
Come with me.
- He's alive!
- What?
He's alive, I tell you!
He's alive!
Good Morning.
Good morning, Mr. Waverton.
The floods have subsided considerably.
Thank heaven for that.
I think it will be possible for you
to send for an ambulance now.
You mean we can go?
Yes, I'm sure we can go now.
Come along, darling.
You're going to stay here with Gladys,
aren't you?
I am. Don't be long.
We won't.
We'll be as quick as we can.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
So happy to have met you.
So, I'm really dead
and gone to Heaven?
No, it's morning and
we've only just left hell behind.
Morning?
Yes. Cold light of day. Wasn't there something
you were going to tell me in the cold light of day?
Come to think of it, there was.
Perkins. Will you marry me?
Subtiltles corrected and synchronized by
job0@whatkeepsmebusy.today