I didn't end up getting much sleep.
I went and had my... very first kiss.
Well, good morning, Miss Nikaidou!
G-G-G-Good morning!
You're up early for a day off!
Everyone else is still sleeping,
so go ahead and eat.
Oh, okay...
Wonder if Kanade's a sleepyhead, too?
Kaho.
K-K-Kanade?!
I can't take it anymore.
T-Take what?
W-We can't!
Not now—not here!
If we don't say anything, he'll never know.
Is he serious?!
So... you don't mind, right?
Gimme your seaweed.
Go ahead.
Yay! Sea-weed! Sea-weed!
My boyfriend's a primary-schooler, all right.
First Love Monster
It's so early, and I'm already tired out.
Hello, J*ll-o!
I'm sorry to descend
on you in a group like this.
I had intended to come alone, but...
It sounded fun!
Just don't butt in, all right?
Huh? Did we have plans or something?
I have business with Kaho today.
Huh? Me?
Rather than stand around and talk,
let's repair to Kanade's room.
Why my room?
It won't do for us men to intrude
on the room of an unmarried lady!
What a gentleman!
Sought-After Undies
I-It's not much, but...
What an intimidating mood—like
I'm dealing with my mother-in-law.
You have got a lot of nerve, serving tea
you admit is "not much," you demon-in-law!
I hate you! I hate you!
Oh, please forgive me, Mother!
You're too modest.
It's terribly delicious.
What a sublime gentleman!
Now, then...
Let me say this again:
I am against you and Kanade dating.
I'll just cut to the chase.
What is it you like about him?
His face?
His style?
His pointless behavior?
Well...
Is it because he rescued you?
Do you believe... it's fate?
There is no deeper meaning
to Kanade's words or actions.
Come, enter into my embrace
and drift back to sleep!
Whoa! It's the Futonagon monster!
If we fall back asleep, we'll be late!
Think again!
He's a bigger fool than you thought.
He's really persuasive.
In short, you don't know Kanade well enough.
That's why I'm against you dating.
Kanade lost his mother two years ago.
The deep wounds from that
time now drive him to seek solace
from an older woman like you.
I... I have no comeback for that.
From the sound of things,
you're just spouting all kinds of nonsense.
Kana—
Kaho and my mom look nothing alike!
That's what bugs you?!
All right, so what do you like about Kaho?
Dunno.
Whaaat?!
Exactly.
You also know nothing about her.
Therefore...
Is that important?
What do you mean?
You don't fall in love with someone
'cause you know them well.
Love is that feeling of wanting
to know more about someone.
Kanade...
Gin, Tomu—let's go.
Aw, already?
I wanted to soak up the mysterious
naughtiness of being wrapped up
in another family's futon for a little longer.
Kaho, I'm still against this.
Um... thanks, Kanade.
It's nothing.
But listen, Kaho...
You want to know more, don't you? About me?
Uh-huh...
Then c'mere.
I'll teach you about me.
The me even my father doesn't know.
Even your father... on your bed...
N-No, we can't!
Not that—not yet!
I mean, you're in primary school, and—
Secrets and risk go hand in hand.
That's what growing up is all about.
S-So close!
K-K-Kanade!
I hid 'em here.
Hid?
If I'm going to teach you about myself,
I decided the best way would
be showing you what I can do.
You sure are good in math, huh?
Right?
Kanade!
How about some snacks for your friends?
What's all this?
I-It s not what you think!
What's this, Kanade?
Were you hiding these from me?
That's what bugs you?!
I'm sorry.
Why am I kneeling formally?
Hiding tests with scores
like these is serious business.
Please kill me.
Huh?!
I'm not going to kill you
over something like this.
But you have to take
responsibility for the things you do.
That's what Mom always said, huh.
Maybe I'll get you a tutor.
What?! No way! I don't wanna!
Huh? What did he just say?!
How can you face your mom
in heaven with grades like these?
Crap! I can't get 'em out!
I'm gonna have a peanut
tree growing out of my nose!
Got 'em! I was super panicked...
Ka...
Kanade, I don't think you're behaving right!
I'm sorry.
That was a fast apology.
You must really trust her.
Trust her?
She's my girlf—
Hey, I know! Miss Nikaidou,
if it's all right with you...
Huh?
Bamboo Primary School
Ro-sham-bo!
R*yal crown!
This week's goal:
No running in the hallways!
Bamboo Primary Student Council
Ro-sham-bo!
Shampoo-conditioner!
No Horseplay
on the Stairs
Ro-sham-bo!
Boysenberry bushes!
Ro-sham-bo! Break the tie! Tie! Tie!
This game goes by
"rock-paper-s*zzle" and "step roshambo."
Tie! Tie! Tie! Tie! Tie! Tie!
Despite regional variation,
the basic phrases are "r*yal crown,"
"shampoo-conditioner," and
"boysenberry bushes." However...
Ro-sham-bo!
C'mon, not "ro" again!
You'll never catch up to us that way!
You're going about this all wrong, Kanade.
Finding a way to beat your opponent with "ro":
That's the essence of the game.
R*yal crown...
...and golden throne!
Say... what?!
Okay, guys—come and get me!
Ha! You have dazzled us, Kanade!
I see it's time for us to go with plan B!
Ro-sham-bo!
Boiling w**ner, hot hot hot!
Shamrock underpants
covering my naughtiest places!
Roly-poly poop, curled in a cone!
...changing these keywords at will during play
often enhances one's
rock-paper-scissors capability.
Ro-sham-bo!
Bodacious boiling w**ner!
Bubble bubble bubble!
Boys are so dumb.
Ro-sham-bo! Break the tie!
Kazu could teach them a thing or two.
Right, Yuki?
Tie!
Oh, uh, sure thing.
Ro-sham-bo!
Roly-poly holy-moly pile of poop!
Hmm. A draw.
We'll settle this once
after-class homeroom is over!
Can't. I've got a tutor as of today.
If I don't get home pronto,
Dad'll dock my allowance.
A tutor?!
Dude, are you serious?
Secret, thrilling, one-on-one lessons...
What's this tutor like?!
Hmm? Oh, right.
They're...
Would you be Kanade's tutor?
Huh? I-I couldn't possibly! Me, teach?
Oh, that's too bad.
I'll have to look elsewhere.
I wonder who'll wind up being Kanade's tutor?
Tch. Where are you even looking?
I-I'm sorr—
You're like a pile of dogsh*t
on the road—but worse.
Learn your place, Miss Less-Than-Dogsh*t.
Why does Taga always have it in for me?
If I'm interested in anyone, it's Kanade.
What if Taga's the new tutor?
Now, Kanade, pollination is when
pollen goes from the stamen to the pistil.
Atsushi... words alone aren't
enough for me to understand.
You, a mere child, coming on to me?
Then...
I'll teach you so it's easier to understand.
Oh...
Just relax... see?
I'll be the stamen and you be the pistil.
I'm going to be pollinated!
Wh-What am I thinking?!
Ooh, stop it, Kanade!
Cut it ouuut!
Wait, Mafuyu.
C'mon, enough studying—let's play sumo!
Aw, why's it have to be sumo?
Your boobs are kinda like
a top-ranked sumo wrestler...
Huh? A wrestler? That's meeean!
Guess she accepted the tutoring position.
Huh?
You must be Kaho!
I don't want Kanade—in fact,
I'm after his family!
Hayashi Mafuyu
High School Sophomore
Nice meeting you!
I don't want Kanade—in fact,
I'm after his family!
Family? So... she means marriage, right?
Now that was a big sigh.
Arashi!
Hey, Kaho. Heading home from school?
I see how it is.
So Mafuyu is going after Kanade after all...
And then there's Taga...
Don't worry.
Mafuyu's tastes are a tad off-kilter.
Her tastes?
And Taga's personality and
disposition are skewed, that's all.
O... kay...
We're home!
Hmm... not here, either...
What's the matter?
Hmm? Oh, hello, you two.
Seems I'm a little short on dirty laundry.
You don't mean Chiaki's, do you?
Did some pervert steal them?!
No, no!
They're mine.
And who'd steal an old guy's undies?
That's the phone.
So this is Mafuyu's room.
Is this really going to turn out okay?
Huh? What's that?
Is she... in pain?
Um, are you... okay in there?
She doesn't look okay!
So fruity...
Could those be the landlord's...
You saw me!
I-I didn't! I didn't see anything!
Mafuyu?
Why, hello there...
Nooo!
S-Someone, please!
That voice—
What's all the fuss—
P-Please, help me!
I'll protect he—
She used Kouta as a springboard?!
Run... away...
Sh-Shinohara?!
Hey, why are you running awaaay?
How did it come to this?
Stay right there!
I have so much to teach the new girl!
D-Don't trouble yourself!
Dear me, look at you quiver!
It's all right. Nothing to be afraid—
I should be safe here... right?
Found you.
Please, spare me!
Wait!
Kaho!
Hi-yah!
There it is!
That was a close one, all right.
Are you okay, Kaho?
Yeah, more or less...
She's...
...eating the undies?!
Well, Mafuyu?
Don't tell us you haven't had enough.
I ate them all up.
My tummy's full.
Mafuyu...
Okay, you're on your own now.
See you, Mafuyu.
Huh?
What did you think when you saw me?
I-I'm sorry...
I'm not asking you to apologize.
I'm asking what you thought.
What's wrong with smelling
the scent of someone you like?
Liking their scent is scientific
proof that you're compatible.
So it's only natural that
Shugo and I should be wed.
Shuugo?
I told you: I'm after Kanade's family.
Kanade's... father?
Huh? But, he's, like...
way older than you, right?
Huh?
What of it?
Like you're in any position
to find fault in someone else's man.
You're the major perv dating
a kid in primary school.
Major Perv
Hey, perv: What is it about Kanade, anyway, huh?
His face? His body? C'mon, out with it!
I-It's not that!
Kanade's the first person
to really get mad at me.
Who cares, nimwit?
If that were true, you must be failin' for me,
since I'm super mad at you right now!
I-I don't think it's that logical...
Anyway, will you do
a favor for your dear pal Mafuyu?
First, speak of this to no one! And...
...take these back.
How did this happen?
I'm glad Mafuyu's not my rival, though.
Whatcha smiling about, Kaho?
Huh? Aren't those...
Kanade?!
He's going to think I stole his dad's undies!
N-No! I just—
These are the undies I gave Mafuyu!
Eh?
She asked me for something
with the scent of the person she liked.
But those are your father's.
In her own way, Mafuyu's
giving a shape to her love.
You gotta support one
person feeling love for another.
So that's how Kanade sees it.
He's so innocent...
Kaho, your face is all red.
Too close, Kanade.
Doesn't feel like a fever...
I know!
K-Kanade?!
You're tired. I'll make you feel better.
I-It's the thought that counts—really.
Thoughts alone are no good.
It's the same as doing nothing at all.
If you don't give shape
to your feelings, what's the point?
So he's giving shape to his feelings for me?
Miss Nikaidou?
It's all right. Let me handle this.
Mmm. That feels good.
How about here? You like that, Kaho?
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
Oh—no—not so tight, or I'll...!
All on the next First Love Monster:
"I know—To the Bath House!"
Next Time