It's morning.
No matter how much happens...
...morning will come.
Coming!
Yo!
Want breakfast?
Y-Yes! I do! I'll be right there!
'Kay!
Of course—when we live under the same roof,
we'll see each other right when we wake up.
Just so you know,
I'm against you and Kanade dating.
Yeah. No way can I be
with someone in primary school.
Good morning!
You must be Miss Nikaidou.
Y-Yes, Nikaidou Kaho.
Sorry I've been out.
I'm the landlord, Takahashi Shuugo.
Huh?!
Takahashi? So that means...
Might you be Kanade's...
Father, yep!
Shuugo Takashi
This guy?
Househusband
K-K-K-Kanade, be quiet!
Wake up, Kouta!
Sorry he's so loud so early in the morning.
N-Not at all...
He's always been a rambunctious one,
but after his mom died two years back,
he's getting to be a real handful.
C'mon, Shinohara, do something about Kanade!
Cut it out, Kanade! I'm up already, I'm up!
Ah, but just think of him as a little brother
and play with him every now and then.
S-Sure...
L-Little brother? He's my boyfriend!
Not that I can tell him that.
First Love Monster
Wh-Who are you?!
You must be Kaho! You're so cute!
So cute, cute, cutey-cute-cute!
Behind you!
B-But you're the cutest
in the whole wide world, Chiaki!
What on earth is going on here?
That's Nagasawa Arashi,
a grad student and Chiaki's boyfriend.
Why, you...
Boyfriend and girlfriend, huh?
Time to dig in!
Wh-What is it?
Gimme your seaweed.
Oh, uh, here.
Thank you!
Yours, too, Kouta.
I-I already ate it!
Tch!
And Arashi?
You can't have it.
Aw, c'mon, Arashi—
You sit down!
But—
One packet of seaweed per person. Got it?
Yeah...
Kanade bumming his beloved
seaweed off people—so cute!
Oh, that's right, Miss Nikaidou...
Yes?
I haven't explained the various ins
and outs of Kasumi House yet, have I?
Right.
I can do that later, if you don't mind.
Please do, then!
Th-Thanks in advance.
Taga is so kind...
So, like, what do you do when you're dating?
C'mon, tell me!
Geez, Kanade—not in front of everyone!
And your dad, too!
Where'd that come from?
Well, thing is—
Uh-oh!
Probably from those soap operas
he's been watching lately.
Ah, the TV again.
Phew. Wait...
Did Taga's covering for us actually work?
Oh, hey: Arashi, you're
dating Chiaki, so you must know.
What do you do?
Hmm... like, call her
first thing in the morning?
Call her?!
And call her when you leave the house.
Can't you text her?
But when you're dating,
you want to hear her voice!
Huh.
But it looks like Chiaki has
me on her reject list these days.
Duh! It's way too creepy to be
calling me 90 times a day when we live
Nagasawa Arashi
Mobile
Today
Missed
All
Edit
in the same building!
But I get three feet from you
and already I want to hear your voice!
Five calls, max!
Okay, okay. Five it is.
Five calls...
Kanade, it's plain to see
that Arashi is not a role model.
Oh, okay. Then you tell me, Kouta.
Who, me?
Well, uh... you can... hold hands, and, uh...
Kanade, asking Kouta the
Virgin is even more useless.
Virgin?
Th-That has nothing to do with this!
But you are a virgin, aren't you?
Hey, Kaho...
What's a virgin?
Hey! That's not something you ask a girl!
Now eat already!
Aw!
Why won't you tell me? Meanie!
Never mind that, Kanade—
weren't you supposed to hang out
with Gin and Tomu this morning?
Oh, right!
The landlord usually makes our meals.
Tell him if you're opting out.
Okay.
We have free reign of the kitchen...
...but don't eat anything without permission.
Oh, and if you keep anything
in the fridge, put your name on it.
Like pudding and stuff.
Got it.
And the bath.
Here's the timetable; write your
name by the bathtime you'd like.
Don't worry: it locks.
Okay.
And that should cover it.
Thanks; that's very kind of you.
It's nothing, really.
Oh, about your welcome party...
Huh? For me?
Of course. How about my room, later today?
Oh, sure, that'll work.
Good! We're all so glad you're here.
Thank you so much.
Okay, see you later.
Uh-huh! Thanks again!
A welcome party?
I'm a little nervous, but happy, too.
Oh, could you put any
cardboard boxes out by the trash?
Sure thing.
I'm heading out for some shopping.
S-See you later!
lf Kanade's dad found out
I was dating his primary-school son...
Indecent?
Indecent
Criminal?
Criminal
Perverted?
Perverted
...Yeah, that would not be good.
Wh-What are you doing?!
What? I like upper arms!
Yeah, but so suddenly?
Can't I?
Well, it's more that, uh...
I mean, you're my girlfriend.
Girlfriend? Oh, geez... I'm blushing...
You can't go around touching girls.
Unless it's your girlfriend.
That's what I've been taught.
By who?
My mom.
Your mom told you that?
Yep!
I still can't believe
this guy is in primary school...
Kanade! We're here for some ele-fun!
Oh, Mr. Elephant, your trunk is so long!
And your w**ner, too—
it's sooo long! Boi-oing!
He's in primary school, all right.
Bamboo Primary's jump-rope
competition is early next week,
so we're gonna practice!
Oh, are you?
I want to beat the record in criss-cross!
Cr-Criss-cross?
"Criss-cross" is a highly
difficult variation on jumping rope,
wherein the jumper must
jump through the gap formed
where the rope is crossed.
It's also called "double jump" or
"speed jump" depending on the region.
Incidentally, we have confirmed reports
that the sting of a jumprope
against one's bare leg as a child
has opened some individuals' eyes
to masochism in adulthood.
I'm a criss-cross pro—
I can jump 30 times in a row!
I'll show you, Kaho.
I-I sure would like to see that.
I'm practicing triple-unders!
I'd rather tie stuff up instead!
Aw, but jumping is way more fun!
Good morning, Kaho.
G-Good morning.
Hey, Kaho, come jump rope with us!
Well, uh...
I-I still have a lot of tidying-up
to do after my  move-in.
Oh, okay. Well, come when you're done!
Y-Yep, I will—when I'm done!
Okay, off we go yodel-oh!
Off we godel-odel-oh!
Yodel-ay-pee-poo!
Byeee!
If you'll excuse us.
Uh, g-goodbye...
Now that was a big sigh.
Um...
Truth is, I go for "pretty girls."
Pardon?
Well, to be precise,
I like boys dressed as girls.
So basically girl-boys.
" Girl-Boys "
What?!
Like Li'I Renren! Maybe you
don't—um, so what l mean is... this:
This is all my Li'I Renren collection!
Y-You sure do like those dolls, huh?
Aren't I lucky? OMG, I can't stand it!
Isn't Li'l Renren the cutest?!
I could lick him all over!
A little tee-hee right here,
a little ooh-hoo where he's ticklish...
Oh, my fantasies are
in overdrive! I'm breathless!
Sorry I lost myself like that.
You must be scandalized.
But you know, Chiaki still
accepts me, even like this.
So it's okay.
You're big-hearted enough
to accept your partner, right?
Even if he's in primary school?
No sweat. What's five years?
Chiaki and I are five years apart.
Age has nothing to do with it—
as long as you have love.
Love?!
Yeah, love. Love!
But I can't help feeling
that a girl like me has no excuse
being Kanade's girlfriend.
Kaho, I feel like saying "the likes of me"
is being rude to Chiaki,
who accepts me for who I am.
I heard saying "the likes of me"
will mess you up for real.
He's right.
Kanade did accept me.
Now I've got to accept him, too!
Nagasawa's so kind.
For him to give me advice like this...
I'm heading back to my room.
Thanks for all your—
Oh, my little Renren—
you're so adorable!
Now for my thrilling
live-on-the-air costume change—
Renren
Spotlight Artist of the Week
after these messages!
Renren
Spotlight Artist of the Week
Just kidding! Tee-hee!
Sorry I'm late!
Where are they?
Well, it sure is precious to me.
What are they talking about?
Something precious to him?
What's that saying,
about always being together?
I know! "Joined at the n*p"!
Tomu, you mean "joined at the hip."
Right—it's like that.
Yeah!
But I wasn't far off with "joined at the n*p"!
Kanade?
What if this precious treasure
suddenly went away tomorrow?
Ever think about that?
Stop it! l don't wanna
think about anything that scary!
Yeah, Gin, quit with the scary talk!
Ah. You love it so much, it could
poke you in the butt and it wouldn't hurt.
Poke you in the eye, you mean.
What?! That would definitely hurt!
Right? Not in my eye!
Um... you seem to be having
a very serious discussion.
What are you talking about?
Our most precious partners!
Partners?!
Never mind—we shouldn't
talk about this in front of Kaho.
C mon, let's be done with this.
Oh...? So he's hiding
something he can't tell me...
I'm really sorry.
We don't want to be mean to you.
I mean, you're the only one here without one.
A w**ner, I mean.
C'mon! N-No more of
this—not with a lady present!
Huh? No more of what?
No more "beep" talk!
Hmm? Can't hear you.
"Beep" talk, I said!
What's this "beep" stuff?
Just say "w**ner" like the rest of us!
I will not!
I'd give you one if I could...
well, I only have the one. Sorry.
I'm sure you'd like one, too.
No, I don't want one!
Not in the slightest!
Are you serious?
But our precious w**ners mean the world to us!
I was sure you of all people would accept
this treasure that we hold so dear!
To think you'd be so quick
to say you don't want a w**ner at all!
Now what? Kanade's getting all depressed!
Um...
I do want a w**ner, Kanade!
Of course you do!
That's a given! Ha ha! Right? Phew!
Did I just blurt out
what I think I blurted out?
I knew you'd understand.
I mean, who doesn't
want a treasure, am I right?
At least they're all
smiling again, though... right?
Kasumi
House
I never did get to see you
jump criss-cross, Kanade.
I'm done with lunch,
so we can hit the park again later.
Criss-cross! Criss-cross!
Sounds like fun.
Taga!
Nice timing, Kanade.
I just saw this ginormous
ladybug outside my window.
For real?!
Yep.
With ten spots, too.
A ten spot ladybug? Whoa!
I'm gonna catch it for sure!
Ten-spot! Ten-spot! Ten-spot!
He's a kid, all right.
H-He sure is.
The way his eyes twinkled
over a single ladybug...
So cute!
Shall we?
Um, yeah.
No one's here yet.
Er...
Oh! How much are we chipping in for the party?
I, um, left my wallet in my room,
so I'll just head back for a sec.
Taga?
Are you stupid or what?
Huh?
Waltzing right into the room
of some man you hardly know...
B-But the welcome party...
There is no welcome party. Nada.
You're a sheltered princess who's
never known hardship. You make me sick.
Falling for Kanade shows
just how stupid you are.
It's a huge giveaway when
you get all nervous and flushed,
yet you're strangely assertive—and boy,
that grinds my gears.
Sorry—it fell through.
Mom says I can't come to your birthday party,
so forget about that promise I made.
She said our families belong
to different social classes,
so I shouldn't play with you.
Who'd welcome you?
Kanade?!
That ladybug wasn't so big after all.
And it only has seven spots, not ten!
Ah. My bad.
And with this forehead-flick, you are forgiven.
Then why did you hit me?
You made her cry.
She's my girlfriend, and you made her cry.
You shouldn't make your girlfriend cry.
You have to protect her.
Kanade, did your mom tell you that, too?
Uh-huh!
What do I do how?
Looks like my monster really is way too cool...
On Duty
Shinohara Kouta
Um...
Afterclass Homeroom
I-I'm on duty today, Shinohara Kouta, so, uh...
Ooh, ooh! Question!
Y-Yes, Kanade?
What's a virgin?
Wha?!
You're a virgin, right?
What's that mean?
We wanna know, too!
What's a virgin?!
Wh-What's with the
public execution all of a sudden?
I'll tell you.
This virginity Kouta has is something fantastic.
Huh?
If he keeps it safe, he could become a wizard.
A wizard?!
Yes, and having had no attempts
on his virginity thus far,
Kouta here is a pure virgin—
the king of virgins, if you will.
Wow! Awesome!
Not really!
It's not awesome at all!
I'd throw it away if I could!
Throw it away?!
If you're just going to
throw it away, give it to me!
I'm not doing that!
No fair! Kouta's virginity is mine!
It's not yours, either, Kanade!
Then it's mine?
No, Tomu!
Wait—what is all this, anyway?!
I'm unclear: is virginity
worth getting so worked up over?
Oh! Do you want to be a virgin, too, Kazu?
Okay, we can all become virgins together!
Virgins!
Don't worry.
You are all virgins.
Oho! Really? Yesss!
And in fact, if I could use
this moment to come out myself...
I'm a virgin, too.
What?! But you have a girlfriend!
Chiaki's the one I love,
but I only desire girl-boys!
Girl-Boys
Awesome!
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
Kaho's at the mercy of Kanade, cool beyond his primary-school years,
and the other residents of Kasumi House. But when Kanade asks her
to do what a couple does, her emotional tension is cranked up to 11!!
All on the next First Love Monster:
Next Time
"It's My First"
"It's My First"!
And now for a match! Renren, chon!