First Love Monster
A Hushed and Crabby ♥ Love Song
Well, here I am.
Hello?
Father?
Mother?
Is this...
Kaho's Room
Kaho!
Kaho! Kaho!
My brother! What are you doing here?
You're back from America?
Yes, my project has slowed down a bit.
But once I arrived, I found my dear
Kaho had moved out on her own...
...with father and the rest gone
to some random villa or the like.
The place is utterly deserted!
And so you got in touch with me.
From all your phone messages
and telegrams, it seemed serious.
I got worried and came by.
It all worked out.
It brought us siblings
together again, just the two of us—
and for that, I'm glad.
But, hey, what's with all these kokeshi dolls?
Yes—aren't they all so adorable?
There are lots of theories behind kokeshi...
...but I like the one where the
name means "child transformed."
Child Transformed
When I could not cherish you,
I would make a kokeshi, coo over it,
and distract myself from my loneliness.
Oh, but today is the best day ever for me!
I am grateful, ever so grateful
that you have come, Kaho!
Why did you leave this place
and start living on your own?
I thought it over, in my way.
I... I... I'm so sad.
My darling delicate Kaho,
sullied and shattered in the big city...
It made me realize that I'd grown
too dependent on you and my family...
...as you tried to protect me.
Please, depend on me!
Lean on me so hard...
It's not just that.
All my own problems...
I blamed them on my family, on everyone else.
I'm sorry.
By all means, go ahead and blame me.
It's all my fault. I went to America
and couldn't rescue you
when you were in anguish.
No, it's not your fault.
You know, I've been wondering.
Why exactly did you go to America, anyway?
Mother and father said they didn't
know the reasons behind it, either.
Oh, never mind about me!
H-How about we watch some TV? Hmm?
C-C-C-Crab!
C-C-C-Crabbity crab!
Crab-crab-crab-crab!
Crab-crab-crab-crab crab!
Let's eat crab
I know...
...tonight we shall dine on beautiful Echizen crab!
Oh, my!
C-C-C-Crab!
Crab, crab, crab...
C-C-C-Crabbity crab!
Hey, where did you get this car?
It's a rental.
You rented it for me?
Guess so.
Why are you so nice to me, anyway?
I lost my mom, too, when I was about your age.
Seeing you reminds me of my childhood...
And I can't let you be.
But you sure are mean to Kaho.
It's not like she's the only one I'm mean to.
The woman my dad remarried was like that.
I hate wishy-washy women.
Wishy-washy?
But Kaho...
Come, you must be hungry.
Dinner is ready at last.
I had no time to prepare—
I'm afraid this meager meal
is all the caterer could offer.
Our household's sensibilities
are as wonky as ever.
It's just right.
Let's dig in.
That seasoned seaweed
would remind me of Kanade...
Wh-What is it?
Gimme your seaweed.
Oh, uh, here.
Thank you!
Was it not to your liking?
It was.
Kaho sucked on these very crab shells
with her own darling mouth.
And this is the pit from the picked plum
that Kaho placed in
her mouth and licked all over!
Brother?
How did you find your bath?
Thanks for letting me go first.
It felt great.
Good to hear.
You must be exhausted.
I used a futon dryer to
get your bed nice and fluffy.
Um... I'm going back to Tokyo tomorrow.
To Tokyo?!
No!
Just a little longer?
You came all this way—why
not take it easy for a while?
This just...
...feels like I'm running away.
Running away? What from?
Sorry—I am exhausted. I'm turning in.
Good night.
Good night, Kaho.
It's not like I'll have any messages... right?
Kaho seemed a little off somehow.
What on earth happened to her in Tokyo?
A doting brother such as
myself cannot help but worry.
Good morning!
Good morning, Kaho.
Breakfast is served.
Starting the day with another feast, I see.
You seemed a bit unwell yesterday...
...so I put in a special order with the caterer
for snapping-turtle soup and roast eel on rice.
Huh?
I... seemed unwell?
Yes.
You may put on a
brave face, but your brother can tell.
Kaho... was it something
painful that sent you back here?
G-Good morning, Kanade!
I can't hide anything from you, huh.
Well, I have been looking out
for my darling sister all this time.
The truth is...
I fell in love.
Love?!
Yes. My first love.
And this rogue is in Tokyo?
What's his occupation?!
His pedigree?!
He must be quite the smooth
customer to win your heart!
Oh, um, actually, it's over.
I have been dumped.
Dumped?!
It can't be!
There are villains in this world
who would dump Kaho?
Kaho! Come out and play!
Huh? That voice...
Is that Kanade?
Nikaidou
Kaho! Come out and play!
You came to play?
So what should I say?
Kaho! Come out and make up!
Kaho isn't here right now.
When is she coming back?
She's never coming back.
Brother!
What are you doing?!
Hey, Kaho is too here!
Kanade!
And Taga...
What are you doing here, Kanade?
I came to see you.
To tell you how I really feel.
Wait!
You lied.
And you keep getting in the way.
I beg your pardon?
Oh, Daikoku, this is—
Who are you, anyway?
Who are you?
Her brother!
Her ex-boyfriend!
Her ex, eh?
I have heard about you!
The shiftless fiend who dumped Kaho!\
I will not forgive you!
Kaho! Let's talk over there, alone.
I won't let you!
You'll go off into the shadows, just you two,
and you'll sm-sm-sm-smooch
or something, I know it!
Smooch?
Oh, we have done that already.
I-I won't allow it!
I'm her brother, and I say no!
We shall have a proper duel!
A duel?
Red Light, Green Light!
Gr—
Green light... red light!
Green light...
This confrontation of the century,
with Kaho on the line,
is "Red Light, Green Light"?!
Green light...
So you say, but you sure
are going along with it.
And just who in blazes are you?
Red light!
Tch, no one's moving...
Green light...
Brother, that's Taga.
We live in the same building.
The same building?
Don't fret: I have zero interest in your sister.
Red light!
Green light...
I don't know whether to be relieved
or insulted by your rudeness.
Kaho is super-cute!
...and... red light!
Green light...
Say, why is that ex-boyfriend
wearing gym clothes?
Is it that—that "cosplay" thing?
Believe it or not, he's in fifth grade.
Primary school.
Red light!
Fifth grade, with that appearance?
Enough with your joking around!
Ask your sister if I'm joking.
Red light!
K-Kaho's first love is in primary school...
How could I let such a thing
happen to my beloved Kaho?
Red light!
I, Nikaidou Daikoku, have made
the biggest mistake in all my 29 years!
Okay, out!
Kaho's brother moved!
Kaho, why were you dating a primary-schooler?!
I don't have a reason.
I just came to like him.
And you even sm-sm-sm-smooched,
too, didn't you?!
But Kanade's dumped me, so...
Oh...
Hey, dummy, why do you
think Kanade came here, then?
Huh?
Red light!
Why? Um...
Okay, Kaho moved, too!
All right!
Atsushi's the only one left.
Green light...
Okay, you're cut loose.
Aw, rats!
So I win.
Since I'm the winner,
I'll take this idiot girl here.
Not so fast!
You just said you had zero interest in Kaho!
I don't, but I'll take my prize.
Even if it's a consolation pack of tissues.
Tissues?
You can't!
Hm?
Refusing to admit you have lost?
Doesn't that go against what
your mother told you, Kanade?
Oh—bring up his mother, and Kanade will...
It does, but...
But...?
But I still can't hand
Kaho over to you, Atsushi.
I get it now.
My world without Kaho...
...was like a hell ruled by
the Dreadlock Lord of Darkness!
Dreadlock Lord of Darkness
Ooh, Kanade, so close.
You don't need that "-lock" in there!
——
I want to see you, talk to you, every day.
I love you, Kaho!
Kanade!
Rich words coming from
someone who used Kaho so!
Boy, are you easy.
Dumped. Depressed. And a single
"I love you" gets you all moony.
Cheap as breadcrusts sold for a dime.
And yet you get so full of yourself
when the ducks at the park swarm you.
That's why I'm itching to make you
see that you're nothing but breadcrumbs.
How rude!
If Kaho were bread,
she would be a top-shelf baguette!
No, a fried bun!
Either way, what, she's still bread?
Pardon me?!
Your attitude is the very definition
of how one teases the girl he loves!
Perhaps you do care for Kaho after all!
Is it true, Atsushi?
Is that why you came with me?
I see...
I hadn't realized it, but maybe I do.
Maybe I bully her because I love her.
Yes, I love this stupid, simple, wishy-washy,
moldy breadcrumb of a girl,
not even fit to feed ducks.
That's not something
you say to the girl you love.
Taga's found a whole new game, that's all.
I want to hear what Kaho has to say.
I love you!
I want you to go out with me again.
Kaho!
Don't be taken in by his sweet-talking!
I... can't go back to the way we were, Kanade.
You're not being taken in?
Brother...
I'd like to speak with Kanade alone.
The thing is, I do love you, Kanade.
But...
But I'm a kid, and too selfish?
The way it stands now, we'll just
keep repeating the same old things.
I don't want to be hurt...
...and I think I'll start doubting your feelings.
Then I'll turn into a grown-up you can trust!
I like you the way you are now.
No need to grow up in any hurry.
What I love is you just as you are.
Then what should I do?
Do you remember?
The day I met you?
Falling in love with you made me realize:
I knew I couldn't stay the same...
...that I would have to change.
You don't get it at all!
If you like me the way I am,
I like you the way you are!
Let's stay together.
Our combo moves will give a huge boost
to our power and our special attacks!
What is he talking about?
I saw it at the school arts
festival in third grade:
the prince and princess,
bound together for eternity.
So: You fell in love with me,
a primary-schooler. What now?
My heart's pounding so fast,
and I love Kanade so much...
I don't care what anyone says.
I want to be with him!
Okay, listen to this:
To Kaho, at 15:
"Love Song to Kaho."
Love Song to Kaho
Takahashi Kanade
What is this?
It's not excitement...
Your love alone is like
110-million times the power
No one can steal it away
Not even the ogres of hell
It's not that I got hurt
I hurt you—now
And then tumbled into hell
Kaho! Woo!
It's not subtraction, no
Me! Woo!
It's addition—no, more like
Multiplication, right?
Your warmth
Your upper arms
Your skin
Skin, fin, fif—fifteen!
Now all you have to do is nod
My ticket out of hell—get you!
So say "yeah" and get a smooch!
Kaho, let's get married!
C-C-C-Crab!
C-C-C-Crabbity crab!
Crab-crab-crab-crab!
Crab-crab-crab-crab crab!
Let's eat crab
Crab-crab-crab-crab!
Crab-crab-crab-crab crab!
Echizen Crab Board
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
After Kanade's proposal, Kaho returns to Kasumi House in a daze,
where she's shocked to find another couple preparing to walk down the aisle!
All on the next First Love Monster:
Next Time: "A Proper Rom-Com For Once"
"A Proper Rom-Com For Once"!
And now for a match!
Renren, chon!