If you're not eating this, I'll take it.
Huh? Geez! But I love it—
I was saving it for last!
Ah...
Hmm? What is it?
Say that again, would you?
Say what again?
Why hadn't you eaten your seaweed yet?
Huh?
Because I love it?
Okay, got it.
I've memorized the way you looked
and sounded when you said "love" to me.
L-Look, it's the seaweed I love, okay?
Oh, I know.
Still... a guy can dream, can't he?
C'mon, let's go. We're gonna be late.
I do like seaweed, but what I like even more...
Dumb ol' Kanade...
First Love Monster
Adorable  x  Abnormable
This rain sure came out of nowhere.
Yeah...
Our shoulders are so close...
Kaho!
Your skin's like marshmallows...
I could eat it up.
Ow!
I think I twisted my ankle.
Kaho... hang on tight.
Huh?
Kanade's heartbeat,
his hot breath—they surround me.
What now? I want to stay like this forever!
That ought to do the trick.
Th-Thanks, Kanade.
You're good at this first-aid thing.
I'm aiming for Tokyo University,
so I'm studying all kinds of stuff.
A rainbow! Look, Kanade—a rainbow!
You know what? They say there's
treasure buried at the end of the rainbow.
Ever since the day we met,
there's been a rainbow in my heart, too.
And my... my treasure...
It's you, Kaho.
Kanade...
We don't want your sprain to get worse.
Rest here in the infirmary, okay?
I'll get my teacher's permission
to leave early and come get you.
We'll go home together.
Huh? You're coming, too?
Gotta have a hero to
keep the treasure safe, right?
Never know when a bad guy's
gonna come by to steal it!
Would you look at that!
A bad guy—here, of all places.
That's no way to talk to your teacher, Kanade.
Wait.
I won't give you Kaho.
Fine by me. I'll just have to take her.
Is Kanade going to be okay?
I mean, a skate-off against Mr. Taga...
What gives, Kazu?
Don't you have any faith in Kanade?
It's not that...
Mr. Taga's the legendary roller-skater
who once took the world by storm:
Rollin' Atu-see!
Performing Worldwide
All Other Entertainers Grovel Before Him!
Rollin' Atu-See
Atu-see!
Ya mean... Taga's that Rollin' Atu-see guy?!
Rollin' Atu-See
Atu-see!
Also known as "Mr. Rolling Eternity"!
Mr. Rolling Eternity
—
Eternity!
The same one feared as the
"Pandora's Box on Wheels"?
Pandora's Box on Wheels
On wheels!
It's started!
Canelé pastries came out of Taga's armpits!
And soft mochi rice cakes came out of Kanade's!
Look!
Kanade's mochi cakes
are engulfing Mr. Taga's canelé!
White canelé? This is revolutionary!
Th-This warmth, brimming with kindness...
There's soft mochi inside the canelé, too?!
Canelé with a soft mochi center?
Can this mean... Kanade was
already inside Taga's soul?!
Ridiculous!
Chewy, crispy, chewy...
Kanade's heat is radiating through
Taga's canelé both inside and out!
It's gettin' hot in here, all right!
The Earth gone white...
You were sketching out love
across this big campus of ours.
You win, Kanade.
Taga
Kaho? I got that early-dismissal form stamped.
You may still be sleeping now...
...but if you ever start to love me
so much you can't live without me,
be sure you wake up, Kaho.
I've been like that for
a long time now, Kanade...
You're awfully glum today, Kaho.
Did something happen with Kanade?
N-Not really!
In the setting sun / Soft cheeks flushing
hotly pink / Here, then: here is love.
Ooh, Kouta, a haiku!
Keeping the spirit of popular poet
Matsuo Basho alive, I see!
Kaho stimulates my haiku-heart.
That expression of hers was sublime!
A rather fine poem, too, if I do say so myself.
Mayhap I'll submit it to the
haiku column in am-am Magazine.
You can't! It's too embarrassing!
I won't—if you speak of
the worry hidden in your heart.
Kanade's... too dazzling.
Sorry! You just had the
most amazing look on your face.
Hey, Kaho—I've got an exhibition
coming up in New York. Model for me?
I haven't taken my showpiece photo yet.
In the setting sun / Tinting the tears
that now fall / Here, then: here is love.
Arashi, take a look at Chiaki, would you?
Arashi, a-are you going
to make Kaho your m-model?
I don't want you to! Let me
be the only one in your viewfinder!
You've finally told me
how you really feel, Chiaki.
Come on—my lens is always
focused on you and you alone!
Arashi!
How wonderful! I want to be like them.
Dear, dear—and me the
only one unattached. How lonely.
Huh?
But you're so popular with the girls, Kouta!
Seems romance doesn't
quite fit that 5-7-5 pattern.
It's a struggle, I tell you. I'll be
partnered with poetry for a while yet...
Hey.
Kanade? Um, I—
Shh. My manager's looking for me.
Kanade? Hey, Kanade!
Your... manager?
I'm sorry, Kaho. I've kept it
from you all this time, but I...
I'm an idol.
My dad runs a talent agency.
He first let me on the lot when
he needed someone to play Passerby A,
but after that...
An idol?
Girls squeeing at events,
squeeing at meet-and-greets,
squeeing at magazine interviews,
squeeing when he says "p-o-o-p"?
That kind of idol, right?
My... my heart hurts, somehow.
Here I thought he was mine alone.
So, listen...
Oh, uh-huh? What's up?
There's this preview event for the
premiere of this drama I'm starring in,
and I'll be reenacting key scenes as part of it.
I'll have to do a kiss scene.
How does your drama's kiss scene go?
Like this.
No, Kanade—don't kiss me there!
Where would you prefer?
It's not fair! You're always
winding me up like this...
I mean, in the infirmary today—
So... you heard my confession?
So my secret's out.
Now I don't know which way to turn.
I'm so lame.
No, you're not! You're cool, Kanade!
Wow, Kanade, your ears are bright red!
Because what you're saying
makes me want to jump for joy!
Honestly, I've wanted
to say this for a while now:
Kaho, be my girlfriend.
I will!
You shine so brightly,
and your words hold such happiness...
I smiled, looking like I was about to cry.
This love: it's adorable.
Miss Nikaidou? Miss Nikaidou!
Hey!
Kaho-yan! Kaho-yan?
Huh? Am I...
Hey! You okay?
Kaho?
Come on back!
What the heck, Kanade?
Fightin' with Kaho-yan again?
Fighting? That's right! I—
Don't touch me!
I just...
I can't be...
...with you anymore...
So that was a dream? A daydream?
Bye, Kaho.
W-Wait, Kanade!
Don't get too close!
I've changed.
So I must go on a journey.
I might even marry Sadako someday.
Sadako's a dog. Can you even marry a dog?
Kanade—it can't be!
Sadako bit me.
Are you serious, Kanade?!
This ain't good... no, sirree!
Wh-What's going on?
Sadako's a human-faced dog!
Eh?
If you're bitten by a
human-faced dog, you turn into one.
I got a friend in Shiga whose relative's
cousin's uncle's coworker's son got bit,
and he turned into a human-faced dog!
Wait, what? What is this?
I'll be a dog soon!
Kanade! No, Kanade!
Huh? Whaaat?!
They totally believe it!
Listen up, Kanade:
This is not a human-faced dog.
It's just a regular ugly dog.
S-Say what?!
Once I found out you were
secretly looking after this ugly dog,
I took this ugly dog to the vet
and got this ugly dog its shots.
So... so Kanade...
Right: he won't turn into a
human-faced dog. He'll stay human.
Kanade!
Thank goodness!
Hooray for Kanade!
This is wonderful!
It's better this way!
What the hell?
Huh? Kaho?
You can totally tell just by looking!
All this fuss 'cause you fell for an
urban legend hook, line, and sinker! Geez!
How obnoxious can you get?!
You're always like that, Kanade!
Kaho?
You're always, always, always,
always saying the weirdest things!
Since we met, you've set up
I don't even know how many gags!
The biggest thing about you is that body!
I keep telling myself it's a
growth spurt, but is it? Is it really?
Nope! I don't care if you suddenly grow bigger—
but you can't just explain
it away as a growth spurt!
It's too darn sloppy!
Here I thought your backpack was a custom order,
but no, it's ready-made
and just jammed onto your back!
You wear that gym outfit every single day—
how many gym outfits do you have?!
And those bangs!
They're always in that M shape—
doesn't anyone tell you to cut
them when they grow into your eyes?
For as much as you act the
grade-schooler when it's convenient,
why must you do the hunk thing
when it comes to your bangs?!
Forget the "p**p" and "w**ner"
schtick and cut your bangs!
That's how you end up missing
the truth you've got to see!
Our first date was a stroll
around the neighborhood!
You pushed me down onto my bed,
but then gave me a massage—
and a good one, too!
You're all "P**p! W**ner! P**p! W**ner!"
Just when I was glad not to
be traded for a Pachimon card,
you suggest we all date together!
And all the "p**p" and "w**ner" talk!
You used a hula-hoop
to decide if we should break up?
P**p!
You proposed to me on a harmonica?!
W**ner!
P**p and w**ner, you saw me in my underwear
with no p**pin' reaction!
P**p! W**ner! P**p! W**ner! P**p! W**ner!
What's so funny about p**p and w**ners, anyway?!
You're a riot, Kaho!
That was a ton of poop and w**ners!
I'm sorry, Kanade...
Huh?
For all those crazy complaints
to come spilling out...
That shouldn't come from the likes of—
No saying "the likes of me." Remember?
Kanade...
But hey, ending your sentences
with "poop" and "w**ner" is super fun!
Leave it to you, Kaho! What a find!
That girlfriend of his is a real piece of work.
Is that what grown-up women do for dirty jokes?
That's the girl I fell for once upon a time:
Kaho-yan! No, Kaho-chin! No, Kaho-p**-p**!
Kaho-p**-p**!
Kaho-p**-p**!!
Kaho-p**-p**!!!
Kaho-p**-p**! Kaho-p**-p**!
Hey there, gang!
The afternoon events are about to begin.
Kanade...
Relax and enjoy your sports festival, now.
I will! Thanks, Atsushi!
White
Team
Red
The meat's ready, folks!
Okay!
I'll take some meat, w**ner!
Me, too, w**ner!
Looks good, w**ner!
It's crazy tasty, w**ner!
What's that? What are you all saying?
W**ner!
It's a game they picked up from Kaho.
What?! I didn't see that coming...
Sniff... sniff...
The smell of your lower half
is a feast unto itself, Shuugo.
Mafuyu!
Please stop—that kind of thing
could get you in trouble!
C'mon, Sadako, s*t up and b*g.
I understand that dog is
coming to stay at Kasumi House.
Uh-huh. Taga worked
things out with Mr. Takahashi.
From this distance,
Kanade looks like the ideal boyfriend.
He does, doesn't he?
But I don't just want to look at him from afar.
I don't want Kanade to be just this hot guy.
I see. Well, that's fine.
Oops, I'm out of meat.
Let's get seconds, Arashi.
Sure thing, Chiaki.
Hey, Kaho...
Kanade, that's great news about Sadako, huh?
When I saw Sadako abandoned like that,
I thought she looked just like you.
It was like you were abandoned...
and I just couldn't leave her like that.
A-Are we really that alike?
Yeah!
Sadako...
Kaho...
Let's stay together forever!
He's so cool, I feel this tightness in my chest.
He makes so little sense
sometimes, I'm just shocked.
But that's Kanade.
Thank you for meeting me, Kanade.
Thank you for making me your girlfriend, Kanade!
Kaho, Kaho!
This is for you.
Thank you, Kanade!
The monster called
"first love" is still coming after me.
But I think I can take any attack it dishes out.
After all, I love Kanade
just the way he is—right now!
Eh?
Huh? Sadako's got a w**ner!
Yep, that's a w**ner, all right.
No mistakin' that w**ner.
So she's a boy?
Yup. The "ko" in "Sadako" is for "coj*nes."
So she's ugly and a boy?!
Afterclass Homeroom
This is our final meeting, so I'd like
to take this opportunity to say something.
I think of Kanade a trillion times more
than that crappy dumb idiot girl does.
When it comes to caring about
Kanade, I simply can't be beat.
Ya can't get away with sayin' that around me!
With all due respect,
I'm certain that I was more seriously
worried for Kanade than you were
during the human-faced-dog incident, Taga.
Ah! It tickles when you lick me there!
Caught up in your grown-up common sense,
you'd made up your mind at the start
that Sadako wasn't a human-faced dog.
But I considered the possibility that he was,
and if Kanade became one himself,
I was prepared to, too—right along with him!
Oh! Th-that's my gyun spot! Don't...
Well, I thought of that, too!
I'd decided to dedicate the rest of my life
to developing a drug that would turn him back!
Y'all are thinkin' too hard!
Human-faced dog or no, Kanade's still Kanade!
I could spend my whole life with dog-Kanade!
He'd be my dog, and we'd
live together happily ever after!
Kanade could never be happy
living with the likes of you.
I'm sure he'd choose to live as my dog.
Ack! Not so hard! Not so... much!
No, Kanade is my dog!
He could be a family dog with me!
A big-family dog!
My dog.
He'd be happier as my dog!
My dog! No, mine! He wants to be mine!