Looks great!
Since I've gotten used
to meals here at Kasumi House,
I've come to realize my family's
breakfasts of snow crab five ways
were not the norm.
I prefer this in the morning.
Well, except for one thing...
These are the thousands—no,
dozens of thousands of organisms
packed inside a female cod's belly.
Scientifically speaking,
a mass of cell nuclei...
Well? When you think about it
like that, doesn't it squick you out?
Just me, then? All righty.
There's enough for seconds.
But it's all right.
I just need to brace myself
and gulp it down in one fell swoop!
That's one down!
And I managed to avoid turning into a merlion.
Now for this last one...
Kouta, Arashi—gimme your seaweed!
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, same here.
Geez! You ate it already?
Kaho...
Gimme your seaweed!
Kanade! I told you:
one packet of seaweed per person!
Aw, but there's only six pieces in there!
It's okay. Here.
Thank you! Oh, and...
Thanks for the grub!
Could Kanade have eaten
that knowing I don't like cod roe...?
First Love Monster
It's My First
Who'd welcome you?
Ignoring me?
If you hate me so much,
shouldn't you ignore me?
Just pointing out your rudeness.
If you're not ignoring her,
that must mean she interests you.
Right?
Stay out of this!
Did you know?
Interest, in that you can't let
someone be, is like affection.
It's famously said that the
opposite of "love" isn't "hate"—
no, the opposite of "love" is "indifference."
Um... what are you getting at, Chiaki?
You want to be ignored,
but Taga can't ignore you.
Clearly this is unrequited love on Tags's part.
Please stop!
You say that kind of silly stuff,
and Taga is bound to...
Bound to... what?
Shinohara, Taga—you sure are popular, Kaho.
Why is Shinohara's name coming up?
And besides...
There's no way Taga likes me!
There might be.
I found it strange myself.
How is it I could care for
a clumsy, dim-witted numbskull...
Yeah, right, you moron!
If I'm interested in anyone,
it's Kanade, not you, stupid.
What's that supposed to mean?
That he prefers Kanade over you, no?
C'mon, Shinohara—come out
of hiding and let's hit it!
Huh?
Shinohara?
Honestly.
Good morning, Miss Nikaidou!
Kaho!
Kanade!
Kaho, today's the day
we get our mission underway!
Let's do something boyfriend-girlfriendy!
Huh?
Let's have a date!
Of course...
Hurry up!
I freeze up when I see Kanade, but I guess
this is normal for primary-school kids.
Somehow I'm afraid to see
Kanade when he's at school
Bamboo Primary School
It's not every day you see a
high-schooler waiting for her date
with a primary-schooler.
Maybe I should just go home.
But... it is a date.
If I don't show up at our meeting spot,
Kanade's bound to worry.
Kaho!
Kanade?!
Sorry I kept you.
N-Not at all!
Lately us boys have been
all about the climbing poles!
I-I got that.
Yoo-hoo! C'mon, Kaho—you climb up, too!
But I'm wearing a skirt.
You can see Mt. Fuji from here!
Uh, I-I'll pass...
Oh. Then...
Let's get this date started!
By "date," you mean...
Well...
Y-Yes?
Anything you'd like to do on a date with me?
Huh?
What do a boy and girl
do when they meet one on one?
What do they...
This is my first date—I haven't the foggiest!
P-Probably a date is like...
going someplace fun together?
Someplace fun, huh?
I know C'mon!
I'm gonna show you the funnest time ever today!
Kanade!
No one's ever put it quite that way before.
I can't help but get excited somehow...
What do you think, Kaho?
A present—from me.
Only the finest date for you, Kaho!
What a ridiculously unrealistic fantasy!
Kanade's hardly the type to dress
like a prince and play the harp.
He's a recorder-tooting primary-school kid!
Um, Kanade, where are we going?
The park!
What do you think, Kaho?
Only the finest date for you, Kaho!
There I go again!
I know it's my first date,
but my fantasies are out of control.
I've got to face reality.
Hey, Kaho! Over here!
Oh, okay!
Let's do this together!
And this... this is my reality.
Bring me a bucket of water.
The spigot's over there.
Oh, okay.
Five more, please!
Got it.
Next we'll start building up our mountain.
Okay.
Pick the pebbles out of the sand
so it won't collapse so easy.
Uh-huh.
And once the sand is piled up,
give the surface a good smack to harden it.
Wherever it looks weak,
use that sticky sand to reinforce it.
Okay.
So there's this new café by the station.
Oh, really? I'd like to check it out.
Then let's go!
Really?
What am I even doing?
Hey, you're good at this, Kaho!
Huh?
Thanks to you, today's mountain
is super well-balanced!
I've made tons of these before,
but never as awesome as this!
Kanade, you have got sand on your face.
Huh? Get it off, wouldja?
Hang on.
Ow, Kaho—that hurts!
It's really stuck on there.
Okay, all set.
Thank you!
Okay, that's enough mountain-building.
Now we dig a tunnel.
A tunnel?
A tunnel won't make a nice sturdy
mountain like this fall apart.
I'll go from this side.
Kaho, you dig from over there.
Okay!
This is one sturdy mountain, all right.
Need some real elbow grease
to dig to the middle.
Y-Yeah.
Don't make the tunnel mouth too wide, Kaho.
Oh, okay.
Kaho, try jamming your
hand further into the center.
All right.
We're connected!
Uh-huh...
Look at you two lovebirds.
We are on a date!
A date, eh?
Hey, it's Arashi!
Um, well, more like a "date"... er...
And what a nice date it is, compared to us two.
That's the way, Li'l Renren!
Fantastic! Good job!
Isn't this a better pose?
Yikes, Kanade! Get your sandy mitts off that!
That's my ultra-super-rare limited-first-edition
"Poseable Cat-Ear Li'l Renren, Bashful Version"!
This one, then! I see London, I see France—
Hey! No peeking under that skirt!
These figurine photo shoots are a regular thing.
I see.
Is this park not good enough for your dates?
Um... Doesn't it bother you, Chiaki?
Doesn't what?
Uh, well, it's just...
Oh, you mean Arashi being
a disappointment as a boyfriend?
No, I—
But he looks good, doesn't he?
Huh? Well... yes.
That's what counts!
Um...
Kanade's got good looks, too.
Uh, well, that's... that's true.
Then you're good.
You seem to be worried about
Kanade being in primary school,
but I see no problem here at all.
I guess you're right.
I do have fun with him...
...though this is a far cry from a lovers' date.
The kind of date doesn't matter.
There are as many dates as there are couples.
Chiaki...
Besides... Arashi is stupid nice.
Huh?
Nothing.
Chiaki, Kanade's nice, too.
Eye lasers! Whoa!
You'll pull his eyes out!
And a butt bazooka! Ha ha!
You'll take his butt off!
Hey, Kanade, aren't you on a date?
Don't leave your girl hanging!
Oh, right!
Okay, Kaho, mission complete!
On to the next one!
The... next?
Here we are!
Kobayashi's
Candy with Character
Toys for Tykes
It's... Kobayashi's!
A penny-candy store?
Hey, it's Kanade!
Oh, you guys are here, too?
Wait, didn't you say your date was today?
We're smack in the middle of a mission.
I brought Kaho to one of my favorite
stores so she could get to know me.
I get it. So you came to pay
respects to the counter hag.
Counter rag? At a penny-candy store?
Their counter hag is real famous.
Who you callin' a hag, you nincompoops?!
You keep spittin' on
my candy without buyin' any,
Counter Hag
you can get right outta here!
There it is: the counter hag's
"Get Outta Here" attack!
Hello, ma'am.
Oh, my, Kazu—you came, too?
Here, dearie, have a sucker.
She's always playing favorites.
Thank you very much.
That's Kazu: our sixtysomething old-lady killer!
Oh, wow, these take me back!
Kanade!
Are you okay?
Tomu, you chicken—not in the face!
Prepare yourself—
Hey, now!
Take that ball and play outside!
Count me in, too!
Okay, let's play three-lives outside!
Whaaat?!
Kanade's going off to play
with Tomu and the others? No way!
I'll take that!
Yes way...
What is "Three-Lives"?
Similar to the individual
match that is dodgeball,
in "three-lives" a player is hit
three times before he or she is out.
Its simple rule and casual
style—no need for a court—
have won it more than 400 million players.
400,000,000 People
Now attracting attention
for outstripping kabaddi,
it's on track to feature at the 2020 Toky—
Geez, Gin! You were aiming
for my balls, weren't you?!
Ball-oney! Don't get Testy!
Why, you...! An eye for an eye!
A ball for a ball!
Try my demonball on for size:
Thunder Vacuum Nyaho
Nyaho-Tamakloe Do You Remember Me!
Hey! Blatantly aiming for
the balls is an illegal move!
Il-le-gal!
Aren't you on a date?
Don't leave your girl hanging!
Oh, man—I was in the middle of a date!
I'm out!
What? But it was just getting good!
I was this close to abandoning our mission!
A date's a date till we get back home!
C'mon, just a little longer!
Tomu! Take a hint.
The second half of any date is key.
We've got to let the two of them be
alone—tenderly.
"Tenderly"?
Get out of my way.
Huh?
I said, "Will you please move?"
If you're in high school,
surely you're learning English.
What's up? Gotta poop?
Huh?
You're so quiet and with such
a serious face—so I figured: poop!
N-No, I don't!
Don't hold it in.
Poop is nothing to be ashamed of.
Look, it's not that!
Then what?
Uh, well...
See, Kazu and Taga are both
against us dating, right? So...
Oh, is that what you're worried about?
Having obstacles—within reason—
only fans the flames of love.
That's a pretty grown-up thing to say.
Did your mom tell you that, too?
Huh? I came up with all that myself.
Oh, did you?
'Course I did! Same as for nearly everything.
I came up with dodgeball
and the newest Yummy Stick flavor!
There always were plenty
of kids who said stuff like that.
Here, Kaho, eat this.
Mission three: A couple happily
eats the same thing together!
Um...
How do I eat this?
Haven't you ever had cake-on-a-stick?
Real fans have crazy ways of eating them,
but normally you just chomp them from the top!
No, I mean...
Don't tell me, Kaho—
you have never walked around while eating?
N-No. If I concentrate
on holding this, I can't walk,
and if I focus on walking, my mouth won't open.
Here. Say "ah"!
Huh?
So sweet and delicious!
Yep!
We made it!
Uh-huh! Thank you for one spectacular date.
Not so fast, Kaho.
Huh?
The date's not over yet.
This is our final mission.
Our final mission?
The goodbye kiss.
The goodbye kiss...
Not like that.
Couples kiss...
...here.
Kanade... that...
that was... my first... kiss...
W-Were you watching?
Uh, no, I wasn't!
Well, er, I wasn't not watching,
but... I wasn't spying!
I mean, I accidentally saw it.
It slipped into my vision!
I saw that, I saw that!
I saw you see that!
It's a shock for the girl
you like to be going on a date,
but to happen to catch her kissing?
Cut it out, Chiaki.
And what's worse, she was
kissing a primary-school kid
who's way cooler and way younger than you!
Can't bounce back from that!
Yes, it's true.
I do like Miss Nikaidou,
and I was spying out of curiosity!
That kiss with Kanade really was a shock...
But that doesn't mean
it's any kind of fun to mock
a person's feelings for someone!
Oh, it's fun, all right!
This kind of intel is just my cup of tea.
Hmph!
Why don't you just come clean
and tell Kaho how you feel?
C'mon, Chiaki hates it when
people can't make up their minds.
English
Today we'll be having
an English lesson for a change.
Aw, studying? I hate studying!
Now, we may be in primary school,
but English will be compulsory from here on out.
We'll start with a simple greeting:
Hi! Nice to meet you. My name is Kazu.
Okay, now you try:
"Hi! Nice to meet you. My name is Kazu."
Hi! Icy meat stew. I'm lame, this Kazu!
I am not lame! And what's this "icy meat stew"?
Hi! Mice to neat you. Om nom—it's Kazu!
I'm not eating.
Hi! Nice to eat you. Om nom nom Kazu!
I said, I'm not eating!
Hearing ability: zero.
It's the miso-paste penalty for you all.
Miso-Paste Penalty
You know these visuals are totally not okay!
Poop! Poop!
Till next week! See you!
See you!
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
Kaho's heart is still pounding after her first kiss with Kanade.
But when Kanade's tutor arrives... Another storm's a-brewing!
All on the next First Love Monster:
"Sought-After Undies"!
Next Time
"Sought-After Undies"
And now for a match! Renren, chon!