I bet Kanade doesn't
even think of you as a woman.
You're gonna catch a cold.
Colds can turn into all kinds
of worse things. Gotta be careful.
Bamboo Primary School
Kanade...
You can borrow this umbrella.
I borrowed it from school,
though, so don't lose it.
Okay.
Well, I've got some business
to attend to, so I'm off.
Business?
Later!
First Love Monster
No Peeking! Kanade's Secret Diary
Pretty small umbrella.
Well, of course: it's the
standard primary-schooler size.
That thing won't keep you dry.
Taga?
It'd be a real pain if you caught a cold.
Mind you, I couldn't care less
if a garbage girl catches a cold,
but there's a chance it'll spread to me.
The very thought gives me chills.
I'll give that umbrella back to Kanade.
That Kanade...
Why'd he come home
and then go right back to school?
Sorry I'm late.
Aw, you got wet after all, didn't you.
Sorry 'bout that, Sadako.
I was going to bring you
an umbrella, but on the way I—
Who's there?!
Atsushi!
Is that... Sadako?
You could at least introduce us.
You don't hide anything from me, right, Kanade?
I'm begging you, Atsushi—
don't tell Kaho about Sadako!
Why not?
They can't meet each other—not yet.
Besides, I want to explain this to Kaho myself.
Understood.
This will be our little secret.
Want to pinky-swear?
Kaz and the others know about Sadako.
That makes this...
...a promise between men!
You have gone and grown up, haven't you, Kanade.
Kanade sure was in a hurry.
A paper airplane?
Bamboo Primary School
Sports Festival
An announcement for their
sports festival?
This could be important!
Secret Diary
Huh?
Kanade's... diary?
I wonder what he's written in there?
His true feelings, maybe?
Ah!
An!
Even if his true feelings are in there,
reading a diary is against the rules!
I bet Kanade doesn't
even think of you as a woman.
But... I want to know.
I want to know how Kanade feels.
"I want to be with her every day...
I want us to be together always.
Even after I come home,
I'm worried someone else will take her.
I'm going to have to tell
Kaho about Sadako at some point.
This is my critical mission!!"
What... is this?
Secret Diary
Who's this... Sadako?
That's low.
Reading your boyfriend's diary? Really low.
So it's true.
You are trash.
sigh
Keep on sighing like that
and you'll chase happiness away.
Chiaki!
I think happiness might
already have flown the coop.
Don't tell me: Kanade, right?
Maybe primary-schoolers ought to
be with other primary-schoolers after all.
Takahashi
Crabita
What makes you say that
at this stage of the game?
You're going to wait and
see how he matures, right?
Yeah... but Kanade might be cheating on me.
Kanade, cheating?
Yes.
Probably with a girl
named Sadako at his school.
He wants to eat snacks with her...
it looks like he's given her the
jump-rope that his mother left him...
Hmm.
And that's not all!
It feels so good to hug Sadako that
Kanade never wants to stop hugging her!
He even wants to see her in his dreams!
I see...
In a relationship like ours,
emotional infidelity is the hardest kind.
After all, our feelings
for each other are all we have.
For a supposed emotional affair,
you sure know a lot of details.
I secretly read Kanade's diary.
You're the worst!
Reading someone else's diary?
You suck, Kaho Nikaido.
Yes. I am the worst.
Hey, Mafuyu—
thanks for the free show.
Eek!
Those are the landlord's underpants!
I'd say you suck for wearing stolen underwear!
boing
Yeaaaah, I suck.
But what I don't do is read diaries.
Diaries contain a person's heart.
You can peep into a bathroom,
but not into someone's heart.
Even if it's just for show!
You can strain your ears
to hear what's going on inside,
stand guard while he's bathing,
drink his bathwater to stay healthy,
sniff the shoes he's just taken off,
swap your chopsticks
for his when he's not looking,
take his old toothbrush out of the trash...
I understand—all too well!
When you love someone too much,
you want everything of theirs!
Their chewed gum, their sneezed-in tissues...
Even such things as these are dear.
I don't know about that brother of yours.
That is why, Kaho, you need not
feel badly for merely peeking at a diary.
Never mind your diary—
I check your postal deliveries and
your phone messages daily, without fail!
Brother... that's my phone.
Beep
Oh.
A message.
Wait—you unlocked it?
Reply ♥
Sending Message
You're even writing back as me?
Cool
Brother...
Come on, brother!
Hey!
Kanade!
The sports festival is tomorrow?
You have to tell me earlier!
Ah! My paper airplane!
Now think about what you have done.
I've told you not to fold planes
out of important handouts!
La la la! I can't hear you!
Well, shoot.
Now what?
Tomorrow's my trip with
the neighborhood association.
Neighborhood Association Outing
Kurobe Dam
Get Your
Dam!!
Card Here!
No way!
Then what about my lunch
for the sports festival?!
I'm done for...
No lunch for me at the sports festival tomorrow...
Woe... woe...
It might be tough the day before,
but I'll see if I can get out of the trip.
I can make you a boxed lunch,
but you'd be eating it
all by yourself, poor thing.
It's okay—go on your trip.
This is all my fault, anyway.
Oh, um....
If it's all right with you, I—
I'll go.
Taga?!
shine
Atsushi! You'd really come?
I wind up going every year, don't I?
Kota and the rest will come watch, too.
And on your day off, no less! Thanks.
Every year, I get roped into participating.
gloomy
cool
I can see that.
Kaho, are you coming, too?
Of course, Kanade!
Yesss!
Please move.
Boy, you have got some nerve.
Especially having read Kanade's diary.
Excuse me...
As for tomorrow's sports festival...
See you there.
Now, let's kick off Bamboo Primary
School's sports festival!
Bamboo Primary School Sports Festival
Wow... lots of cuties here!
Where are Kanade and his friends?
Is that them?
Entry Gate
5th Grade
Well, there's no losing sight of that bunch.
Now for warm-up exercises.
First through sixth grades,
give yourselves plenty of room!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
Gotcha!
They stand out, all right—
for better or for worse.
I'm gonna take some great shots today!
Next up is the fifth-grade ball-toss.
The ball-toss!
Is that how it's supposed to go?
They really are physically head
and shoulders above the rest!
Hey, you boys! Let us girls play, too!
Yeah, that's right!
Boys are used to handling balls.
Or is it something else?
Do you love balls that much?
Gross! You guys are seriously the worst!
Missed me.
Take that! And that!
Come on, class—don't fight!
And the winner of this event is: the white team!
Tch!
Fight! Fight! Red team!
Cheer Squad
Go get 'em, go get 'em, rrred!
Yeah!
Give it some o' that fightin' spirit!
Moving on: the fifth-grade tug-of-war.
Really bear down now, team!
Okay!
Don't bear down so hard
that you poop yourselves!
Poopity poopity poop!
Poop ourselves?! As if!
Let's get a little louder!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Okay! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
How do you tell prostitute to get out?
Leave, ho! Leave, ho! Leave, ho!
Bear down, girls! Bear right on down!
For your future childbirth! Come on!
Shut up, Sannomiya!
Ugh, boys!
They totally suck!
Uh-huh...
I don't wanna...
Oopsie-daisy...
And the winner is: the white team!
Ow ow ow...
If the red team loses,
it's all the boys' fault!
Tch!
Takahashi!
Is your knee okay?
My knee?
I just scraped it a little.
I-I'm doing first aid.
We have bandages—should I...
...get you one?
It's okay.
A little spit and it'll heal right up.
So that must be Sadako...
A high-schooler jealous
of a primary-school kid?
That's going beyond
pathetic straight to unsightly.
Unsightly is fine by me.
I rather think it's you, good sir,
who's jealous of this Kanade boy.
Me, jealous?
Now, I can't let that go on by.
Now, now, let's calm down—
You shut up!
Why is it always only me?
Now it's time for the
parent/guardian scavenger hunt.
Those in the parent/guardian seats,
please gather beyond the entry gate.
Don't tell me...
Who's doing the scavenger hunt?
You, of course.
But I'm so slow!
Why do you think we brought you along, anyway?
I don't want to!
Last year I was last in the bread-eating contest,
and Tom and his pals teased that it
should have been a lead-eating contest!
Get over there already.
Out of all the virgins, you're my slave.
Oooh! So we're both slaves?!
You bet!
Ooh...
Let the parent/guardian scavenger race begin!
On your marks... get, set...
dash
vrooom
Down to the last card? Already?
And it's in a sealed envelope!
Wear Women's Clothes
What the—?!
This isn't a scavenger hunt—
it's a costume race!
Hey, lady!
I've got to hurry!
But... women's clothes...?
Li'l Renren! All gyun-gyun-gyun!
Um... Arashi?
Do you have any... women's...
Which do you like, Kota?
Japanese, Western, or Chinese?
I-It's not lunchtime yet!
Ren...
Japanese
Renren
...ren...
Western
Chinese
...chon!!
Western.
Changing made me so late!
Hanako?!
I-I'm sorry—I'm in a hurry!
H-Hey, Hanako...!
Hanako!
Kaz, they been lookin' for ya over thataway.
Okay.
That brings our parent/guardian
scavenger hunt to a close.
We did it!
Nice work!
Another year in dead last, Kota?
I took some great photos
and posted them on social media!
Kaho!
The footrace is coming up next.
Uh-huh! Good luck!
I'm gonna come in first—and when I do...
...we'll smooch.
K-K-K-Kanade!
Not so loud!
Is that a no?
No, not exactly, but...
Well, if you say no,
then I'll really want to do it.
So I'm getting that smooch either way!
Oh, that Kanade...
Now for the fifth-grade footrace.
On your marks... get, set...
Kanade's...
...so cool!
Goal!
That was so fast,
I didn't get to take a picture!
Yay!
What's up?
I saw Hanako earlier.
Seriously?!
Where could she have gone?
I hope I can see her again.
And with that, the students'
morning events are complete.
While the students are eating
their lunches, we'll have a presentation
from the local seafood
association on our stage.
Oh, man... it's Li'l Renren, in the flesh!
Master Kaz, it's poor manners to leave
one's seat unnecessarily during meals.
I know that!
Seafood Festival
Fish
Hi, everyone! How are your lunches? Tasty?
So tasty!
It would make me sooo happy
if you had seafood in your lunches today!
Now, I'm here to show you all the Renren Dance!
See if you can learn it—and
dance and sing along at home!
Okay, start the music!
Gyu-gyun ga gyuun (ga gyuun!)
Do the Renren Dance with a gyun, gyun, gyun!
Let's dig in!
Seaweed, seaweed, seaweed combo!
I hear we've got crab croquettes today!
Crab cro... quette... s?
Eat the fried chicken.
Is Kanade really going to kiss me?
He's got to be thinking
about that Sadako girl, too.
I don't really know how Kanade feels.
Oh, right. I forgot.
Kaho!
Come here a sec.
Okay.
I know—if I get to talk to Kanade alone,
I've got to apologize for peeking at his diary!
And... I need to ask him
about Sadako once and for all.
Um... hey, Kanade—
The truth is, I... I read your diary.
I've wanted to apologize
all this time. I'm so sorry!
You... read it?
So...
...who's... Sadako?
You want to know?
Kaho...
Close your eyes.
What's going on?
He's acting different.
He's not going to fob
this all off with a kiss... is he?
Because that's not going to fly!
And yet... and yet...!
Aaaah!
See? That's Kaho!
This here is Sadako.
That's Sadako?
You can probably tell,
but she's a dog with a human face.
Huh?
She's dangerous, so I was going
to get her more used to me
before I introduced her to you.
Sadako gets all worked-up when she's hungry!
So it turns out Sadako was a dog.
I got all worked up over nothing!
What happened?
We heard this crazy scream!
Did you see a ghost or something?
Huh? What's wrong, Kanade?
You're all pale!
Don't touch me!
Wh-What's going on?
I... just...
...can't be...
...with you anymore...
What do you mean?
We'll keep on growing straight and tall
Just like the green bamboo
Come, friend
Take up this planet's future
Burning with hope
Send it onward and upward!
Bamboo Primary, Bamboo Primary
Bamboo Primary, where you are
Our dear school
Bamboo Primary, Bamboo Primary
Bamboo Primary, where you are
Our dear school
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
First love, friendship, youth... The lovely, shy high-school girl Kaho
and the breezy, earnest primary-school boy Kanade run into one another
again and again, spinning out miracle after miracle.
All on the next First Love Monster:
"Adorable/Abnormable"!
Next Time
"Adorable/Abnormable"
And now for a match! Renren, chon!