I'm not about to lose!
My justice will never lose!
It's always the same with you!
Time to realize the error of your ways!
Which one? Who will it be?!
Kanade!
Tomu!
T-Tomu won!
No...
The real winner is love.
I-It's poop!
Phew! That was a blast!
I'm exhausted.
Next time, let's have a space-robot war!
Yeah!
"Love," huh?
First Love Monster
Kanade's Telephone Helpline
Security Office
Thank you very much for everything.
Get home safe, now.
Yes, sir.
Sorry you had to come and get me, Mr. Takahashi.
Why were you snooping around
a primary school in the first place?
Kaho's in a real fix.
And she can't talk about it.
To be ignored by her ex Kanade
and mistaken for a stalker?
It's complicated, huh.
Oh, that's right: you got a call from home.
Huh?
They said you weren't answering
your cell. It seemed urgent.
Received Calls: Brother
87 New Calls
Oh!
That urgent, huh?
You have telegrams, too.
Telegram,
Miss Kaho Nikaidou: Contact ASAP
Look at them all...
I-I'll just give him a call.
What's with that moan?!
I... I'm going home!
What?!
Hey, Kanade, what was
your deal in dodgeball today?
Going down in one hit—isn't your heart in it?
I've got something to say, too. Look here!
When it comes to serving fair
lunch portions, you can't be beat!
So why do I have two carrots?!
It's not like you!
He's right. It's not.
I can't say I'm quite myself yet either...
...but looking at you, I think we're the same.
Kanade, you're lovesick, aren't you.
You did break up with that one girl, right?
So it's a new girl?
What a play-ball!
Right?
That's playboy!
Hanako.
Who's Hanako?
Hey! Are you listening?
Who's Hanako?!
Kaho...
What the heck is going on with Kanade, anyway?
At times like this, there's only
one thing we, as friends, can do!
The Ten-Time Quiz!
Yay! Yum-yum eat-'em-up!
Kanade, say "rest" ten times.
Rest, rest, rest, rest,
rest, rest, rest, rest...
In the "ten-time quiz" game,
one person makes another
say a given word ten times,
then asks a question to provoke
an incorrect, yet amusing response.
It is said to have its roots in ancient Rome,
where a pizzeria owner would
jab his cusTomuers with his elbow
when they inevitably fell for
his trick and said "knee" instead.
...rest, rest.
Now add a B!
Rest-buh.
Huh?!
No, it's "breast"! "Breast"!
That's right! Kanade got it wrong! Ha-ha!
Kanade...
He got it wrong!
Rest-buh!
I'm home.
Pardon the intrusion.
Hey, Kanade.
We're having your favorite tonight:
batter-fried fishcake with seaweed.
You're supposed to gargle when you get home.
What's going on with Kanade?
I think he must be lovesick.
Huh?!
That Kanadeis not Kanade.
But I don't know what to do.
I followed him home, but...
Oh, I see. Now that is a problem.
Children's Telephone Helpline
Let's
talk it
over!
A        A
A           A
Got questions or problems you can't talk
to Mom about? Talk to smart grown-ups
who can answer all your questions!
We're waiting for your call!
A                                               A
A                                                       A
A                                                  A
A                                               A
"Children's Telephone Helpline"?
You mean, kids can call this number
and a grown-up will answer all their questions?
All of them?!
Really? Awesome! Let's do it!
What are we gonna ask, huh? Huh?
They help with your problems...?
Something naughty?
Kanade! Don't you have
something you want to ask?
M-Me?
Oh! I have something
I wanna ask a grown-up about!
You do?!
Yes.
Okay, let's borrow Dad's cell!
Yeah!
Yesss!
Kanade and the gang seem interested, anyway.
When you mentioned running
a children's telephone hotline,
I wasn't sure what to expect.
I just wanted to help out those kids,
so worried about Kanade.
But really?
Do you think Kazu will call anytime soon
I've got something to ask him!
L-Like about you-know-what and such-and so!
Don't the kids do the asking?
This can't end well.
And you-know-where!
Hello?
Excuse me, is this the
Children's Telephone Helpline?
It's Kazu! So soon?!
Um, hello?
What underwear are you wearing?
Wh-What happened?
I must have dialed the
wrong number. I got a pervert.
Arashi, don't tell me that's
what you wanted to ask him!
I instinctively blurted out...
You're the worst!
...what I most wanted to ask.
Those kids are taking these calls seriously!
Next time, I'm picking up!
Incoming Call
H-Hello, Children's Telephone Helpline.
I have a question: Which is softer, a rest-buh—
no, a breast or a cream puff?
Whaaat?!
Breasts: close encounters of the third kind.
Who cares about that stuff?
Huh?!
Th-that s right. Boring.
It is not! Let's see you answer, Kazu!
You might have touched a breast,
so you know which is softer!
I-I don't know! Don't ask me!
Something's fishy!
Normally you'd say,
"That's not even possible!
No way—have you seriously
felt up a girl's breasts?
I didn't say I felt them up!
I-I just bumped into them!
So you touched them?
Whose? Hanako's?!
Hanako's, right?
Quit being weird!
The helpline person will hear—
What's up, Kouta?
He just bumped into them!
Lucky! I'd like to touch and
pet girl-mode Kouta's breasts,
even watch him from afar and take pictures,
play guessing-games like, "Is this your nipple?"
And if that's off-limits,
then I can move to his...
He just bumped into them!
I'm asking you nicely: please stop!
Why would you even say such things?
Don't you have a girlfriend?
What about Chiaki?
Kouta, I love Chiaki more
than anyone in the world.
However...
What I'm saying is:
I love Chiaki, but I desire girl-boys.
For a second there, you'd created this illusion
that you'd said something amazing.
A first-rate pervert's trick.
You flatter me.
Advice?
It doesn't have to be.
Just what you're thinking, what's bothering you.
Putting it into words
should help you understand.
Hello?
Is this the Children's Telephone Helpline?
Yes, it is.
I...
What is it?
Don't overthink it.
Just say whatever is on your mind.
I thought I wasn't lonely with everyone here.
Yes?
But I am lonely, somehow.
Why is that?
I want to talk about
our class killifish laying eggs...
...but the crayfish I put in the tank ate them all.
And about Hanako who lives in the bathroom...
...and about Gin throwing up
the carrots he ate at lunch...
You can tell me.
I want to tell Kaho.
Aren't you the one who ignored her?
Yeah, but a world without Kaho is hell!
Don't tell me...
I just can't. I can't stand
not being able to see her!
H-Hello?
Um, if you have realized
someone is precious to you,
you should tell them!
Tell her?
That's right—tell her!
She's not around anymore.
Why not?!
She went home.
Huh?
You might not see her again.
So what's the plan?
If you're okay with this,
then it's over and done with.
I'm not.
So... what's the plan?
I...
I'm going to got Kaho!
So you're really going?
Yeah.
Miss Nikaidou's from Kanazawa,
out in the Hokuriku region!
That's five hours by car.
And yet...
You're going by bike?!
What are you talking about?
If you have a bike, you can go anywhere!
I'm going, too!
Travel with a friend, live with compassion
Me, too. There have been
UFO sightings where we're headed!
I'm comin' along, too!
I'll head home to Osaka on the way!
Gin, what the heck is that?
Not by bike you're not!
It's too dangerous for primary-schoolers,
Seaweed!
The dried kind?
Osaka is in the other direction,
Nope, fresh!
and you're not listening...
Huh? What's that for?
We're doing this...
Yeah?
...fresh...
Oh?
...and funky!
Really?!
Awesome!
You need a helmet.
Thank you!
Okay, see you 'round and around, propeller!
Propeller!
Go!
Where are you going, Taga?
Why does it matter?
You're so nice.
Care for a boxed lunch, ice cream, beer, coffee?
What kind of lunches do you have?
Sandwiches, fuTomuaki sushi, and a seaweed set.
A seaweed set, then.
Thank you very much!
Seaweed: Kanade's favorite.
Kaho, gimme your seaweed!
Stare.
Here!
Hooray!
It's a festival of seaweed! Seaweed, yay!
Three-second rule! Annnd safe!
My little seaweed pals!
First stage: the straightaway!
Just leave straightaways
to the Naniwa Speed Coaster here!
Ain't nobody passin' me by, I tell ya what!
What is it, Speed Coaster?
I forgot the one thing that can cramp my style!
What?!
Red lights!
It's a long one.
"Against the red light..."
"If we all cross together..."
"...there's nothing to fear!"
No!
Why not, Kanade?
We're trying to get you there faster!
Don't you even care?
Crossing
Would you crush the feelings
of the crossing guard,
who helps us cross with a
"Take care and see you later"?
Yeah, my moms is a crossing guard.
She dresses all in yellow tiger-stripes, though.
Hey, the light changed.
Second stage: the slope!
I'll handle the climb!
Huff, huff, huff, huff!
Isn't this when people drop out from heat,
exhaustion, and loss of focus?
Here's where it comes down to guts!
Bro!
Don't worry about me!
Go on, Kanade!
I'm sorry, Bro!
Third stage: the mountain!
We're crossing that mountain!
Why?
Is it a shortcut?
Because it's there!
Got it!
Huff, huff, huff, huff!
Tomu!
Tomu! Gin!
Kanade!
Dog poop!
'S no use, huh.
What can you do? We all got flats.
I've got to get to cram school.
Kanade, it's time.
I won't give up.
I'm going, even if I have to walk—or crawl!
Kanade!
If you want to go that badly, hop in.
Atsushi!
I'll take care of your machine!
Tomu!
Never fear—I'll make it to cram school on time!
Gin!
Show 'em your manly spirit!
See you later!
Well, here I am.
I'm home!
Afterclass Homeroom
Boy, do I have a scoop for you!
According to my big brothers,
when you're going
60 km per hour on your bike
and you do this...
...it feels like a breast!
Cool!
What? It does?
It's called "air petting"!
So it's all-you-can-touch boobs!
Worth a try, huh?
But can you even go 60 km per hour?
Let a grown-up show you how it's done!
Good luck, Arashi!
Fight!
Kazu, isn't this 60 yet?
Why are you asking Kazu?
B-Because he's good at numbers?
Because Kazu is beautiful!
What?!
Tell me, Kazu: am I... am I there yet?
I can't wait! I'm there! Ohhh, I'm so there!
Shut up.
Taga, you can kick me more...
You damn pathogen.
Hello, police?
Fantasy abandonment?
We have a deviant here.
Sure! I'm the strongest around!
Please come right away.
Yes. The address is...
Renren here!
Coming up on First Love Monster...
Kaho reunites with her brother Daikoku at her family home in Kanazawa.
Meanwhile, Kanade and Taga arrive, hot on her trail! It's standoff:
Daikoku, Kaho, Kanade, Taga. Who will make the first move?
All on the next First Love Monster:
"A Hushed and Crabby Love Song"!
Next Time
"A Hushed and Crabby Love Song"
And now let's do an impression
of a boiled Echizen crab!
Ready, and: chon!