The card for Kaho-yan!
Let's all date together!
You, me, and Kaho-chin.
I'll take her.
I just can't!
First Love Monster
Kota! Gimme your seaweed.
Stare.
Again? I already opened the packet.
Hula-Hoop Hullabaloo
That's all right. Gimme your seaweed!
Okay, you can have it.
Yay!
Kaho, gimme yours, too.
Er... huh?
Uh-oh—I bet Kaho's mad.
Mad?
I mean, that whole thing
yesterday just happened.
But why?
Don't you wake up friends again
the day after a fight?
That's just for kids.
I suppose it's too much to expect
you to understand a woman's heart.
A woman's... heart?
Bamboo Primary School
You delivered your letter, right, Yuki?
What?! You really did? That love letter?
Who'd you give it to?
Um...
Yuki's got some high ideals.
With an emphasis on the visual!
A boy in this class, eh?
Kaneko?
Big
Mommy
3-Hour Slapstick Special
The Kaneko Clan
Kaneko Family Rule
All in Primary School and Younger Bathe Together
He stands out too much.
Just yesterday, there was another
TV special on his huge family.
Super-Sized!
I bet even dates with
him would be broadcast live.
Totally no way.
It's not like you saw yesterday's
"Big Mommy" show anyway!
Okay, then Sannomiya?
I was busy with transmissions
from the SM78 nebula last night.
Were you summoning UFOs again?
Totally gross.
No—the UFOs were summoning me!
Sannomiya is no way.
Nope nope!
What about Takahashi?
Oh, rats!
I lost my backpack somewhere!
Oh, well.
Right?
You bet.
Yeaaah... I don't think so.
I heard Takahashi is dating a high-schooler.
I know!
And they're living together
under one roof!
Whaaat?!
Therefore, the best guy in our class is...!
Master Kaz!
Take your seats, class.
Since the teacher's out,
we'll use this time to discuss our event
in the school sports festival.
Ooh, soccer!
Dodgeball!
Tetherball!
Quiet!
Raise your hand if you want to speak.
Me!
Kanade Takahashi. Go ahead.
Someone forgot something in my desk.
Eep!
Geez, such tiny writing.
"I'll be waiting at the
equipment shed after class."
Public Execution
That wasn't left behind—that's a challenge!
Well, challenge accepted!
I'll help you out!
So who's the wise guy?
Eeeep!
Some Jane Doe.
Looks like a girl's handwriting.
Hey, isn't that...
That's a love letter!
I'm sure it is!
Totally a love letter.
Kanade!
You are gravely lacking in delicacy!
Deli-cassie? Is that a lunchmeat?
It's not food!
I mean, you're cruel to be reading
a love letter in front of all these people!
This is a love letter?
Tch, it's not a challenge?
If it's a love letter, then never mind.
I'm dating someone.
But hey, Kanade, didn't you
two have a fight yesterday?
Did you make up?
No.
And she ate my breakfast seaweed, too.
They're fighting?
What if they break up?
Quiet!
Takahashi Time is over.
We'll move on to our main topic:
the sports festival.
Soccer  Softball  Volleyball  Basketball  Tetherball  (Dodgeball)  Two-Lives
By majority decision...
...we've elected to play dodgeball
in this year's sports festival.
Frankly, I'm sick of dodgeball.
What did you expect?
Some students have matured so suddenly
that their physical prowess clearly
differs from that of the rest of the class!
Ah!
I guess you are at a disadvantage, Kaz.
Height-wise, I mean.
What was that?!
I'm well on my way into
my second growth period!
You apologize to Noguchi!
Apologize! Apologize!
I can't hear you! La la la!
Takahashi, you're the worst!
Now, now—everyone calm down.
Pardon me for losing my composure
in such a juvenile fashion.
Looks like I need to grow more
both in height and as a person.
So cool!
Oh, Master Kaz, you're so grown-up!
That's a five-year class president...
...and future student council president for you.
Whereas I am destined to take over
my family's OB/GYN practice,
provide exams to all the girls in this class,
and guide them through easy childbirth!
Gross!
Kanade, don't forget your backpack again!
Yup!
Those girls really did a number
on you in today's class meeting, huh?
I don't care how likeable I am to girls.
Wamuu Monthly
Mystery
of the
Pyramids
Fortune and Happiness!
And lately I've gotten
so used to being called gross
that it's actually starting to feel good.
Seriously?
I want them to like me!
I wanna be popular!
That's an unreasonable
demand as long as Kaz is around.
Kanade!
Bro?!
Yo!
What, that cousin of yours is still around?
He's staying at our place as of yesterday.
Huh?
I been waitin' for ya, Kanade!
Thought I'd beat some
manly spirit into ya, y'know?
Manly spirit?
Yeah! If you're a man, ya can't
be makin' Kaho-yan cry like that!
I'll teach ya a lesson...
Play a tennis match against me!
You wanna start a fight, I'll finish it!
Bring it on!
I'm tough!
Here goes!
I have no idea how to keep score.
Fear not.
Their battle has gone
far beyond the concept of points.
Take this! My killer move...
The Tornado Serve of Destiny!
Drop my guard with the sound of yer recorder, then hit me with an ultra-high-speed serve!
That's my Kanade!
Which means I...
...will speed up this ball as I sack it on back!
Here s a ballsack serve, cornin' atcha!
Ball
Sack
Well?
Didja learn yer lesson?
Kanade, ya can't beat me!
I got too good a handle on your weaknesses!
Weaknesses?
I don't have any weaknesses!
Ya once promised a girl
you'd marry her, didn't ya?
Huh? News to me.
In fact, ya said, "Marry me!"
I totally did not!
Oh, I heard it, all right.
When?!
What hour? What minute? What second?
How many times had the Earth turned?!
20 thousand times!
So, what hour?
Happy hour!
That's one heck of a battle.
What minute?
The last minute!
What second?
Does it even have an end?
Seconds for dinner!
Ya give pretty good, y'know?
You, too, Bro.
Yeah, but Kanade, 's pretty low
to be forgettin' ya proposed an' all.
I did not either!
You're mixed up somehow!
Dude, it was Yukie!
My moms!
Ah, I did!
When I was a kid!
Well, Kanade, I got to know yer
manly spirit with that tennis match!
But ya know, ya totally fail as a boyfriend.
I fail?
'S like ya don't understand a woman's heart.
The girls in my class said the same thing.
Namiko has a short fuse, too.
She's all "Clear your dishes
when you're done eating"
and "Don't use so much shampoo. "
I don't really get women.
Well, women can't be understood in a day.
You gotta work on it day after day.
Speaking of a woman's heart...
If I could be of assistance?
And with that...
Our top-secret mission!
This meeting of the Women's Heart
Research Team is now in session!
Whoa, my butt is so breezy!
Can we really understand
a woman's heart like this?
I reckon it's the only way,
dressin' up like this
to be a woman, body an' soul!
Okay, time for yer shot! Tee-hee!
Now that you mention it...
I feel like I'm starting
to understand women, too!
Fair Gin's doing full-throttle channeling!
The surging cosmic radio waves
are tingling all through my body!
Looking good, everyone!
Ah, wonderful!
To think I'd have the chance
to see my secret stash of costumes
come to life before my very eyes!
Hey... hang on a second...
This also has nothing to do with me, right?
So why... why am I...!
Adorable!
Those teary eyes—I'll just take a shot!
Clothes make the man, right?
This is better than I'd ever dreamed!
Clothes make the idiot?
If only you could wear that every day!
We've broken new ground.
Look at Kota, getting all that praise!
Ooh, li'l Renren!
It's not praise if you're not happy about it!
That's just fine. Kota's absolutely
charming when he's embarrassed!
See?
Most guys put on a skirt
and get over their nervousness right away.
Oho! Kanade has grabbed
Joji's back in a cobra twist!
Joji is staying close to the ground...
...and he's flipped him in a figure-four hold!
But he moves out of the figure-four hold...
...into a tickler grip!
That's gotta tickle Kanade till it hurts!
Tag me in!
Live
Okay, we've swapped out both wrestlers!
Ooh, Tom catches Gin in a
scissor sweep right off the bat!
Live
What's this?
He's movin' right into
an electric massage!
Electric Massage
The electric massage is
a secret, forbidden technique
in primary-school kung-fu.
Its history dates to before the common era,
when, while wrestling in an ancient Ol*mpics,
a certain Elektros Masáz
began persistently massaging
his opponent's crotch with his foot.
Even now, its mix of pleasure
and danger give the move
a strong following as the
ultimate "skinship" between boys.
C'mon, your clothes are
going to get all wrinkled.
That's enough wrestling!
Um... I'm going back to my room.
Huh? Already?
Aw, not yet!
C'mon, Kota, have some fun!
Look, just because it's fun for you
doesn't mean it's fun for everyone.
You can hurt a person by
forcing your ideas on them!
I'm not looking to play
all friendly with you and Joji.
This isn't fun for me at all!
Just be honest.
But in a sense, I feel he's got more
of a woman's heart than any of us.
I... remember...
What Mom said...
Don't do what someone dislikes.
So if Kota isn't having fun,
we shouldn't force him to
do something he doesn't like.
I get it. Real grown-up, Kanade!
But it looked so good on him!
That committee meeting went
on longer than I'd expected.
Quit wafflin'! If you hate that outfit so much,
take it off already!
I see London, I see France!
I-I'll... I'll never get married now!
They're not down here, so Kanade
and the gang must be upstairs?
Tears?
Oh! My apologies!
Did she drop this?
"You are three kinds of sweet-tart berries.
Your eyes are blueberries.
Your lips, raspberries.
Though I want to be by your side always,
your fruits are far out of reach."
What... what is this?
Wait, please!
I'm home!
Kaho!
Was there a girl here just now?
A girl?
I didn't see anyone.
That can't be...
What about her?
I'm not sure myself...
But... I want to see her again.
So badly... so badly, I'm shaking.
I want to know the reason for her tears.
Stupidly enough, it's all I can think about.
What is this I'm feeling?
You're pretty cute, you know?
It's probably... your first love.
My first love?
I felt the same way the
first time Kanade and I met.
I see... So this is my first love...
Kaz!
Where have you been?
I... I seem to have fallen in love...
Love?!
With the owner of this poem notebook.
Her tears and her pure heart touched me so...
This is it...
...it's love.
Huh.
Well, can't say I'm real clear on
everything, but good for you, Kaz!
Thanks!
At last I understand how you
and Kaho feel, being in love!
Kaz, the girls' favorite, in love!
Those girls are going to flip.
Um... why are you guys dressed like that?
Can't tell you.
We're in the middle of
a top-secret mission.
I-I see. Sorry.
Don't let me keep you.
This is it: Takahashi's house.
Is the rumor true about them living together?
Can I help you?
Oh, no, er...
Ah.
It's dark out, so be careful on your way home.
Squee!
Grown-up guys really are the best!
Women even start out annoying.
What's the big idea, Kanade?
Sheesh! It's tutoring time, you know!
Hmph!
Go on home now, boys!
Yes, ma'am!
And you change clothes, Kanade.
What are you wearing?
Why, Shogo will never trust me
as a tutor if I let you wear that!
And that will not happen.
Hey, Mafuyu... what would you do
if you made a special person mad?
Intermediate Kanji Drills
Takahashi
Apologize, apologize, apologize
till you're blue in the face!
Sliding kowtow, jumping kowtow,
rolling kowtow, flip kowtow...
I still don't know if she'll forgive me.
Hmm. That's true.
Give yourself a punishment.
Seeing you overcome
it will show her you're serious.
Or even... give it to me...
Punish me... Get angry, Shogo!
Hurt me!
Look at me like I'm garbage!
A punishment, huh?
I mean, Kanade's a primary-schooler.
He can't love at the same speed as I can.
Kaho!
Kanade...
Can we talk?
What a serious face...
Is this good or bad?
I've been thinking, about you...
and about what a "good man" is.
I'm going to hula-hoop 200 times.
Sorry?
To punish my useless self for not
being able to understand the feelings
of the woman he loves!
"The woman he loves"?
Is that me?
My best record is 175 times.
If I make it to 200, I'd like you
to forgive me for yesterday
out of respect for my manly spirit.
Kanade?
I will do this—and I won't
hand you over to anyone else.
Hup!
This is too surreal, Kanade...
You're almost at 200!
You can do it, Kanade!
195, 196, 19—
Kaho...
Let's break up.
Huh?
My heart is a drumbeat!
Even though I can't see,
I'm still drumming away!
Look at this grubby Cinderella!
Oh... Detective...!
I can't hear you.
Again!
Yes, instructor!
I am a clumsy, slow
and stupid single-celled water flea!
Snicker snicker snicker!
This is awful...
Putting sea urchins
in my toe shoes?
My blood is boiling-hot magma!
Touch me and you'll get burned!
Bamboo Primary
1st Half
2nd Half
Kasumi High
1st Half
2nd Half
Well, boys? Humiliated much?
We are!
Dazzling drama doesn't disappoint—
all on the next First Love Monster!