Stop!
It will soon be 12 hrs.
since the incident occurred.
This morning, a security van
was attacked on a street in Kamata.
260 million yen in cash
was stolen by
a group of 3 perpetrators,
who broke through the emergency cordon.
The perpetrators seem to be armed.
With their escape route severed,
the perpetrators drove
their vehicle into a shopping mall
and took some 50 shoppers
and store clerks who were there.
The perpetrator group
consists of 3 males.
One is between 60 to 70 years of age.
Yuji, did you know?
Big bro, don't talk.
We were supposed to be fired yesterday.
They only want half the part-timers.
That sucks.
Hey. you there!
Told you not to talk.
Sorry.
Come.
I'll blow your brains out.
Kill the lights, dammit.
A perpetrator has appeared
with a gun on a hostage's head.
I repeat.
At 7:23 p.m.
one of the perpetrators...
Check their faces on the database.
Yes, sir.
It's long past 30 min.
Don't you care about the hostages?
I'm Reiko Usagi (Bunny). MPD
Special Investigation Squad.
You're hurt. Are you okay?
Never mind. What's the answer?
I don't talk to you.
I apologize the response is delayed.
And?
We are trying.
Qnly...
It's not easy to find a bus
with more than 50 seats.
We can get a micro-bus with 20 seats.
Oh, really?
In return, release the 30 hostages
who cannot board the bus.
What do you say to this condition?
Bunny's going for the frontal attack.
Insp. Kizaki, the list of the hostages.
Chief.
Identities of the hostages confirmed.
Hostages' hands are bond by duct tape.
Not going to the scene?
Promotion test's coming up.
Heard a siege situation like this
comes out it in the test.
Don't you have to go out there?
I'm worried about his studies.
Coming along?
Yes.
Yumi, that hand. You're too friendly.
Just for the record,
tell me your name.
Lay off him.
Your name.
It's...Yusuke Kimoto.
Mr. Yusuke Kimoto.
Yusuke Kimoto. He's a part-timer.
One with the gun is Kazuo Tanimura.
2 priors or robbery and assault.
Seems to go berserk when excited.
The uniform they hit,
breaking through the road block.
Died in the hospital.
Tanimura, come back in.
These bastards are playing with us.
I said come back in.
He's one of you, but can't control him?
Yes, that's right.
The situation can end shamefully
unless it is resolved quickly.
What about my terms?
Ah, yes. Please give us
some time to think about them.
We will respond as soon as we can.
He's too calm. This is bad.
Could be bad news.
There's no time.
You're really a nag, aren't you?
Okay?
Tanimura, I don't want you to forget
that what we are conspiring
is an orthodox hostage situation.
At least so far.
CI Chief.
But...that is...
What's going on?
Supt. Kirisawa. I'm Nakamaru, SAT.
You seem to...lack calmness.
Shut up.
What?
That gun...
I'll keep it.
I promised the hostages
won't be harmed.
L...never...never...lie!
Under this circumstance
can you be certain
you can control yourself?
Chief, a gunshot in the mall.
I heard a gunshot.
A gun was fired inside.
Bunny, get away from there.
Bunny! Get back!
What? What happened?
What do you think?
Well?
Is the weight of life the same
for everyone?
Get back.
But...
SAT is in command.
Forced assault...
M PD General's order.
- We've just begun.
It's already 12 hrs.
It's not time wasted.
Bunny.
Have you heard of Mark Chapman?
Shot John Lennon.
Did he really?
On Dec. 8th exactly30 years ago,
in front of Dakota House in N.Y.,
a 25-year old man named Mark Chapman
shot ex-Beatles John Lennon
in the back 5 times.
He was arrested on the spot
and is still in prison.
What's he getting at?
What if he is released on bail?
He will likely be killed
by John Lennon's fans.
Justice Dept. thinks so
and won't release him.
Listen well.
Mark Chapman killed
an international celebrity
but his life is protected by the state.
Obviously,
isn't there a difference
in the weight of life?
Why did cut the line?
Why?
Not only the weight of life.
What about our world now?
Are people guaranteed lifestyles,
befitting their hard work?
Honest people lose out and are battered.
Don't you want to
change such a world?
I am confident I can change the world.
I Will
show you that.
They'll go for
forced assault.
Everybody, bear witness.
The time has come.
Cut the line?
No intention to negotiate further.
Usagn
No! Stop!
It's a trap!
Stop! Perpetrators are among them.
Are you all right?
Freeze!
Lose the gun.
He's apprehended.
How do you
change the world?
How?
Just watch
what I do.
Watch you?
Tell me. How do you do it?
More on Kamata Shopping Mall.
Secured by the police, the hostages
were transported to a hospital
for treatment of injuries.
I was blindfolded.
Didn't know what happened.
It's aired nationwide.
Yusuke! Watch this!
How much savings do you have?
No money, no work. Get a life.
Damn it.
The money the perpetrator left.
Should've taken it.
Big bro.
C'mon. I'm just kidding.
So hot.
We also know
there was another accomplice.
After the explosion, he escaped,
hiding among the 50 odd hostages.
METROPLITAN POLICE DEPT.
2ND BLDG.
When the line was cut,
I realized it was a trap.
But it was too late.
And we overlooked the perpetrator
among the hostages.
Couldn't be helped
in that chaos.
He...still hasn't spoken a word.
This is the gun you had.
Can't trace his identity from
fingerprints and items on him.
Who the hell is he?
He could've escaped if he wanted to.
Besides all the money was there.
Oh, whatever.
It's not our case anymore.
Yes. I'll take the evening flight
on the 27th as scheduled.
At New Chitose Airport...
Yes, I will be there. Thank you.
Hokkaido? That's great.
Heard you took a vacation
at the same time as me.
There's nothing worse
than running into you.
Seeing seals at Asahiyama Zoo?
No, I'm not.
Ah...attending my high school friend's
wedding reception.
Find a guy there and get married.
And don't come back.
Kizaki, where are you going?
At least it's not
Hokkaido.
Everyday...l see the same dream.
Of what?
Of you dying.
7 years...
For 7 years you come
to visit me every single week.
Because you say you'll die, if I don't.
Why do I see the same dream?
I thought our meeting
would be terminated
only by my execution.
Never thought
you'd die before me.
See the dream, too?
No.
Then, why that look just now?
Why did you have that look?
You never cease
to surprise me.
What do you mean?
What do you mean?!
Only I can understand that.
Today, you came to bid
your eternal farewell.
That is what
only I can understand.
Please come again.
Thank you. Please come again.
That passenger's name and flight No.
Flight 201 for Hokkaido.
Name: Kazuo Takada.
Kimoto, Yusuke.
How do I do it?
It's a fine day today.
Ma'am.
Police?
Later.
We are taking off. Please sit down.
Hey, this plane's going to Kite-Kyushu.
You're going to Hokkaido. Aren't you?
MAIL SENT
RECEIVED MAIL
Chief Kirisawa.
What's up?
A photo from Usagi's mobile.
From Bunny?
Who is it?
A pretty boy. And young. Some catch.
Showing off her guy from a plane?
- Horsepower 201 pound thrust
- Ready.
- Done.
- Horsepower 201 pound thrust
- Got it.
From that hostage case?
He was a hostage.
His name is Yusuke Kimoto.
$0?
He drew my attention,
and somehow stayed that way.
Somehow, huh?
Oh, no, not again.
Your somehow
always leads to big trouble.
Much obliged.
Ouch!
Who is that?
Just a colleague, who
somehow gets on the wrong plane.
It's still confidential.
My fiancée...Yuka Donoue.
How do you do? I'm Usagi.
Wasn't told about her.
Neither was I.
I won't bother you.
You should've reported it
before we took off.
I'm sorry.
Hey, give me a break.
Should've told you
before take-of, but...
What shall we do?
Go back to Haneda.
Police officer or not, if not
on the passenger list, we can't fly.
Contact ACC.
Copy that.
Skybird two zero one request
turning back toward Haneda Airport
What's wrong with her?
What's going on?
Usagi is a stowaway
on Skybird 201 for Kita-Kyushuu.
Captain's message
via Air Traffic Bureau.
Against the law. Plane'll return
to Haneda to get her off board.
I knew it.
Kizaki is on that Skybird 201
bound for Kite-Kyushu.
He left a memo.
Something going on with him?
Nothing really.
Well, about this man...
He looks like a hostage in...
Yusuke, can't quit now.
I know.
What do you think?
I think it's unlikely, but...
Unlikely, huh?
I can do it...l can do it.
It's your unlikely, Usagi.
I smelled oil...gun oil.
I'm not mistaken. I hate this smell.
I'm sorry. I go first.
Be quiet.
Some cold drinks.
Here you are.
Don't do anything.
Passengers, please listen.
This plane will now
be under our control.
Behave and you won't be harmed.
Don't go now.
Knew it.
Hijack.
Don't you have a better excuse?
Stay in your seats.
Is he the only hijacker?
He's just a kid. It won't be hard.
C'mon.
With my signal
we both take him.
All right?
Another must've entered the cockpit.
Then, he's alone here?
You never know.
If he's alone...
Let's take him.
Later.
Now.
Better not come up with funny ideas.
So, there was another one.
Captain, how come
Mt. Fuji's on our left?
Flying in the opposite direction.
We're going back to Haneda.
What? Why are we going back?
What for?
What is it?
Heading back to Haneda.
Why?
Something happened.
Suspected instrument malfunction,
but seems sound now.
If so,
fly the official course.
Move those passengers here.
Hurry!
What did you just push?
Hasegawa.
Come back.
Hijack signal!
Issue emergency.
Fasten seatbelts securely.
Please don't stand up.
What happened?
Fasten seatbelts...
It's a hijack.
Are you all right? We'll get help.
Passengerfist
The passenger list. Hurry up
The name?
Hurry UP-
My wife is ill.
I'm sorry.
I am truly sorry.
What's the ransom demand?
Must be about 500 million?
I'm Kirisawa, MPD,
Special Investigation Squad.
I'm Supt. Sakuma.
- Anything from the hijackers?
Not yet.
Please transfer the line here?
Need to record the voices.
Can you do it?
I will, but there are other planes.
We won't interfere.
Okay, guys, let's do our work.
This is flight 201.
Are the police there?
I'm Kirisawa, MPD SIS.
Hello.
There are some things to confirm.
Any injured?
Yes, there is.
Co-pilot Hasegawa was shot.
Hey, don't bud in.
How bad is it?
Not treated for long,
he could bleed to death.
POSSESSES GUN
ls there a doctor or a nurse on board?
Is there?
Things don't always
work out so conveniently.
Trying to play a nurse?
If I can get near them...
Don't be rash.
DEAR MOM AND DAD,
THANKS FOR BRING ME UP...
Regular mobiles
won't work in this altitude.
How can I contact land?
With a satellite mobile.
Regular passengers won't have one.
Maybe the crew. For emergency?
If so, the pilot.
The pilot...
But the cockpit is
under control of the hijackers.
Your name. Tell me your name.
What's it to you?
Is he Yusuke Kimoto?
The voice-mark doesn't match.
He's a 35 to 40 year-old male.
Have it your way.
From now on, I'll call you Mr. Asshole.
Very funny.
Well, Mr. Asshole, first...
I'm Mark Chapman.
Is he joking?
Playing his game, huh?
Either way, he's an asshole.
Well, then, as you like, Mr. Chapman.
Let us confirm
as our mutual understanding.
You and I are responsible
for the lives of
159 passengers and crew.
Let us continue our talk
with that in mind.
The weight of life...
How heavy is it?
NAME
Who is he searching for?
This is bad.
My name is not on the passenger list.
IF YOU HAVE SATELLITE MOBILE,
CONTACT NEAREST CA.
Your name.
Seiichiro Kizaki.
Not on the list.
There is no Kizaki.
Impossible...Look carefully.
My fault.
When reserving tickets,
I registered you as Donoue.
I haven't decided
to marry into your family.
Well, then, Mr. Chapman,
what is your purpose?
Why are you and
your associates doing this?
We have one demand.
HIJACKER ? PLURAL
Mr. Keiichi Mido is detained
at Kamata East Police St.
We demand his immediate release.
Keiichiro Mido?
We want Master Mido
returned to us.
Master?
We will give you 1 hour to respond.
After that,
we'll kill a passenger every minute.
They can't do that.
Was he there?
Yes, 57-K.
Ex-Diet member sec. Yoshinao Kawano.
What do we do next?
Big bro., calm down.
Take all he has on him.
- Yes, I will.
Shall I do it?
I can do it.
At present, the hijackers demand
immediate release of Keiichiro Mido.
No demand for ransom.
Who is this Mido character?
CREATE THE FUTURE LEAGUE
Political society?
Under investigation now.
You're Kirisawa, right?
Yes, sir.
Is the safety of
the crew and passengers confirmed?
Not all is accounted for,
but the co-pilot was shot
and seriously injured.
And in the additional report
by coincidence,
SIS members Capt. Kizaki and
Sgt. Usagi are on that plane.
So, are they coping
with the situation aboard?
At present, we are
unable to contact them.
We are in the dark.
It's a dangerous situation.
Could they take action on their own?
They have been trained
to act calmly and rationally.
I assure you they would
never act recklessly.
Excuse me.
The cabin has calmed down.
Let me see.
Don't worry. You'll make it.
Can't treat him here.
May we move him to the cabin?
Please.
Thank you very much.
Oh, and Capt. Kano.
Ventilation of ducts
connecting top and bottom is bad.
Top and bottom?
Yes.
Connecting top and bottom.
If possible, open some other duct.
Hey, wait.
Besides that...
Negotiate with the police all you want,
but think about this plane, too.
This plane has fuel
for less than an hour.
It's bound for Kite-Kyushu.
It should fly for 5 more hrs.
You know we almost had to
go back to Haneda.
So what?
Passenger planes fly
on a delicate balance of weight.
Weight of 159 passengers and crew,
weight of cargo.
And weight of fuel.
The plane was too heavy
to go back soon after take-off.
You dumped most of
the fuel at that time?
Anyway, this plane
has less than an hour left.
Hey. Hey.
What?
This was passed around.
If you have satellite mobile,
contact nearest CA.
Who passed this?
Damn it! Who is it?
Excuse me.
I've been trying to
hold it, but I need to go.
Please let me.
Sure. You may.
Me, too.
In your dreams.
Big bro.
Okay. One at a time.
Ah, can you...
Yes?
You see my flight bag there?
Can you take out the operation manual?
It's in the inner pocket.
I see.
Find it?
It's an A-4 size sheet.
Manual on ducts
connecting top and bottom.
Thank you.
BON DANCE FESTIVAL
Yes, this is it.
Hard work, but it's worthwhile.
Keep it up.
Thank you very much.
You saved my skin.
I felt he's a type to go berserk,
if he loses his head.
What do you think?
If we separate them,
we can each take on one.
Hurry up and go.
Hang on a bit more.
Trying to be a hero
at such a time can be fatal.
Hello.
This is Usagi.
Bunny?
Where are you?
In the toilet. I'm using
the captain's satellite mobile.
The facts.
3 perpetrators.
The main in the cockpit:
Other 2 are in the cabin.
2 in the cabin...
Can't they take them?
Prime Minister.
Any demands from them?
Yes, the release
of that shopping mall perpetrator.
The police announced
the hijackers' demand.
Kiichiro Mido, principal perpetrator of
the shopping mall incident 7 days ago
is detained at Kamata Police St.
The hijackers are demanding
his immediate release.
Are 2 incidents related?
Police are examining this.
Mido?
Keiichiro?
There's no time.
Perpetrators say they will
kill the passengers after 30 min.
They're only bluffing.
With all due respect,
such optimism can be dangerous.
And the plane's fuel
won't last one hour.
The perpetrators are
beginning to be desperate.
You think
we should give in to hijackers?
Release Mido whatever his name?
The fact is: 159 lives are
in the hands of the hijackers.
We are not yielding to such morons.
Our country does not
yield to terrorists.
Each of those 159 hostages
has a family.
Friends and a lover, too.
Only 30 more minutes.
Some case we have.
Katayama, what brings you here?
Went to Haneda guarding
Foreign Minister, but got stopped.
His trip's cancelled.
Came to watch to kill time?
Of course not. Foreign Minister's
worried about this case.
Knowing we're friends, he wants me
to persuade you unofficially.
Persuade?
Defense Ministry has been told.
The hijacked plane is maneuvered
to US military monitored zone,
it'll give US an excuse
to scramble their Phantoms.
Shoot down a private plane?
It's just an option.
Hey, we're conversing unofficially.
So, their true colors.
They want to show that
our gov't won't yield to terrorists.
I'll have Flight 201land safely.
I don't care if our gov't loses face.
Tell Foreign Minister I said so.
So sure of yourself. How come?
Cause Bunny and Kizaki are on board.
Kirisawa.
Why didn't you say so?
Oh, hi.
You're doing well.
Supt. Kirisawa.
Any information?
A tenant in Mido's ex-flat said
that when he moved in 5 years ago,
he told people he was a journalist.
A journalist?
Those, who stayed with him
to the end, adored him as a guru.
This is it.
POWER OF THE PRESS
INTERVIEW:
SOICHIRO AMAMIYA, JOURNALIST
It's so sad, isn't it?
Who'd have believed
he would be released
by such drastic means.
JOKER
Well prepared.
So, you have a satellite mobile.
I see...
So, that's it.
Don't tell me...
You want me
to persuade the young men
taking their stand up above.
Is that too much to ask?
You're a fool.
Is it funny?
Among the hijackers,
2 are real brothers.
Until now, they barely survived,
working part-time.
The brothers are
just ordinary young men.
What did you
do to them?
What did you say?
You're only using them.
They are seeking...such a thing.
Young people are like that.
They finally found
what they can stake their life for.
Now is their time of splendor.
Aren't they beautiful young men?
If I tell them to stop,
they will.
If I tell them to kill, they will.
If I tell them to die,
they will.
Can't you see?
I am protected...like Mark Chapman.
Any response from below?
Not yet.
If the hour passes, we start killing, right?
I've decided which one to kill first.
So rich at that young age.
Can't stand him.
Big bro.
What's wrong? I'm one to do it.
We don't kill any hostage.
Mr. Mido said so, too.
This certainly isn't my day.
Shu.
Oh, Well, if I die, that's that.
What're you saying?
Sir, it's no smoking.
Oh, give me a break.
And don't sir me.
I haven't been treated with respect.
There's no time.
The fuel runs out in 30 min.
The gov't just won't respond.
Can't afford to wait.
I agree.
I'll continue my negotiation
with the asshole.
While I keep him in the cockpit,
can you and Kizaki
take on the 2 in the cabin?
Yes.
As I start talking to the cockpit,
I'll ring your mobile once.
That's the cue.
Copy that.
This was passed around the passengers?
Yes.
Captain.
Yes?
If I'm not mistaken,
pilots of this airline
are required to carry satellite mobiles.
It's a call from the control center.
Ignore it.
That bitch.
THERE ARE 2 RATS
AMONG THE PASSENGERS.
You stay here.
That was good teamwork.
Why won't he answer? Asshole Chapman.
Chief, what's taking you?
Open up. Open UP-
Come out! I know you're in there!
Come out!
Kimoto.
You've been on my mind,
since the shopping mall incident.
So when I saw you at Haneda Airport
I felt something bad
was going to happen.
That's why I followed you to this plane.
You're lying.
No, I'm not.
Being part of this, what's your future?
Shut up!
I want to talk.
I want to talk with you.
The decision you are about to make,
will change your future completely.
My future?
Are you able to kill people?
Are you?
Trust me.
I will protect you.
Must end this quickly.
To the rats hiding
somewhere in this plane.
I will slowly count to 5.
I recommend you come out
during the count.
If not...
some passengers will lie dead here.
1...
2...
3...
C'mon, rats! Hurry up and come out! Rats!
You hear?
As I thought.
So you're a rat.
Not a rat, a bunny.
They're different.
How did you know about me?
A deck of cards has a Joker.
Now,
let's have the other rat come out.
Do you have time for this?
This plane will run out of fuel
in less than 30 min.
Negotiating takes time.
To continue negotiations
you need to fuel up.
But the assault team
could take advantage.
Yes, they could.
Passenger safety is my priority.
Let me handle it.
I will stop the assault team.
What I hate the most
are people, who subdue
everything with strength.
Those on the side of the state
willingly lie for their objective.
The police is the foremost example.
I don't lie.
If this plane crashes,
you won't achieve anything.
No more negotiations.
Bunny, what's going on?
Improvising can fail.
Unfortunately,
a passenger's dead.
You people are responsible.
Chief Kirisawa, Usagi's sister
and friend are...
I'm Rumiko Mimura. Where is my sister?
She's on leave, but I can't contact her.
I can't tell you the details,
but she's on an emergency duty.
Didn't my sister tell you?
I introduced
a Sapporo hospital to Reiko.
Hospital?
The hospital called, because
Reiko didn't go. They're worried.
About what?
There's a blood clot in her heart.
Must be operated quickly.
I should've gone with her.
Reiko has a bomb in her heart.
Stress on her heart can be fatal.
I want my sister back!
Shall I kill you?
Then, in return, promise
to land this plane safely.
Trying to be cool?
The only bargaining point
is the release of Mr. Mido.
Nothing else.
Inspector General.
A gun was fired in the plane.
One passenger possibly dead.
But there's still time.
I guess we must reach a decision.
M. Kurihara, what do you propose?
Release Mido?
What will the int'l community say?
Who cares about that.
Like publicizing terrorism
works in Japan.
Yes, he's right.
Then, tell me.
Is Japan supposed to save face,
sacrificing 159 lives?
Reach a decision?
We'll release Keiichiro Mido.
Then, do it immediately.
We're processing it.
Put that on live TV broadcast.
What?
Lower the altitude to 1,700 ft.
1,700?
Yes, 1,700!
At that altitude
we can receive the TV waves.
Go that low?
Minister, a word, please.
Whatever they may say here or abroad,
human life is of utmost priority.
Human life is
heavier than Earth. That's my belief.
The broadcast's starting.
A historical moment.
Our Master Mido
will be free.
If Mr. Mido is released, we can land.
Nakagawa.
Change the world? I don't care.
Don't forget what you promised.
What d'you mean?
Shut up!
I don't care about Mido
or whatever. I only trust him.
You're smart. If we have money,
go to college and get a good job.
Bro...you're mistaken.
I don't care about those things now.
Japan will be
the laughing stock in the world.
Is that your wish? Mr. Mido...
or rather journalist Yuichiro Asamiya,
ex-reporter or Howa journal.
What?
30 yrs. ago, you reported
the civil war in Colombia.
I'm just a reporter, who idolized you.
That was long, long ago.
That's right. Long, long ago.
What are you now?
Blackmail politicians or their weaknesses.
You're only a hoodlum.
A world uninfluenced by money.
What is that? Tell me.
Wasn't finding that answer your job?
Did you give UP?
In the near future, I'm going to
turn this country upside-down.
For 30 years, a bigwig politician
continued giving taxpayers' money
illegally to companies loyal to him.
The one who laundered all this money
was Keiichiro Mido.
Well, such a rumor did come up.
Were you pursuing that?
You should write it.
Are you kidding?
I value my life.
Then, tell me.
What is Mido planning to do?
Mido is about to be transported.
For a glimpse o his face,
a multitude has begun to
gather around the transport route.
Here he is. Mido has appeared.
Mido has left the police station.
Mido is wearing a white suit.
Escorted by several POs,
he looks solemn.
They are walking towards a car.
When released,
will Mido join the hijackers?
But where the hijacked plane
will land is unknown.
Emergency dispatch!
Station men around Kamata Police St.
- What happened?
He's shot.
Mr. Mido...
Why...?
Why?
Unrelated to you people,
something is moving.
I don't know how important
that man is to you,
but is he worth doing all this?
He said he can change the world.
He said he can.
Those who study and
work hard will be rewarded.
Said he will make such a world.
Is that your excuse for this?
Don't you think this world is wrong?
There's no time for that.
What is important now
is the life of all who's here.
Of course, yours, too.
The money.
What about the money?
It was a mistake to bring you in.
Compared to your brother,
you lack calmness.
Sorry about that.
That gun...
I'll keep it.
Won't allow impulsive shooting.
Big bro.
Don't.
Yusuke!
Big bro!
Don't move.
Are you a ghost?
If those boys did well,
I wasn't willing to step in.
Big bro.
Big bro!
Sorry about it.
Where to?
Kimoto.
What if the purpose of this hijack
was not to release Mido,
but to murder him?
How can...?
I told you
something is moving
unrelated to you.
Fuel tank will be empty.
Did you think you'd be safe
as long as you sat there?
Bunny!
The cargo room...
The cargo room. Hurry.
Oh, no...The bomb...the bomb!
Cargo room! He's planning to escape.
Run out of fuel
or the bomb explodes.
I wonder which is first.
Nakagawa.
What's going on?
Don't come!
Bunny.
Where is it?
Did I switch it on?
If you let go, the thread may break,
or loosen the thread to
neutralize the safety.
Either way, bang!
Or...
I can push this button.
What do you...?
The parachute...
That's why the low altitude.
Escaping alone?
Sorry for being smart.
It works 100 km. away.
When I reach the ground,
I'll push the button.
I wasn't told about
setting a bomb in the plane.
Nakagawa.
My plan from the start.
My dear blue clown,
job well done.
Damn!
Bunny.
Hang on.
Thank you.
Before he lands, we must
do something about this.
Mr. Mido told me
he won't take anybody's life.
That he'll make this a country
where life is valued.
If so,
don't give up.
Is anyone an electronics expert?
We need to defuse a bomb.
We need someone,
who knows about electronics.
Is there anybody?
Things don't work that conveniently.
Don't, Bunny.
Please not the go-for-broke.
But...
Not that,
I may not look it, but I have
a Master's degree in electronics.
But with the recession,
no company wanted me.
So, I began an IT venture and succeeded.
I switched my life to money making.
Satellite transmission.
He said it's good for 100km.
Connects to antenna
for the satellite wave.
Some can be dummies.
Cut one of them?
If you cut this...
Maybe.
Maybe?
There's no blade, so pull one off.
Pull it nicely.
No time. Do it.
Venture business is a gamble.
And I came out a winner.
I have just landed.
Are you positive?
Then, it'll be done as scheduled.
Yes.
Job well done.
I hope my luck is still with me.
Thank you.
How long
will continue winning?
Say...
Must I keep holding this?
Yes, you must.
We count on you.
How many more minutes of fuel?
10 min. We must take
the shortest route and land.
Can you hear me?
Bunny...
How's Capt. Kano?
He's wounded and cannot pilot.
Co-pilot is unconscious.
I know there is no time.
I will land this plane.
Oh, c'mon.
That's reckless.
Bunny, isn't there
anyone more appropriate?
If there is, why am I here?
What're going to do?
Bunny,
you kept something
very important from me.
What could that be?
Hurry. What am I to do?
Well, what?
Chief!
Bunny,
you must land the place safely.
I Will
land this plane.
It's my duty.
Bunny.
Just for basic information.
Have you piloted any small aircraft?
Like a Cessna, for example?
No.
Good.
That way you won't
have any preconception.
Only, you must listen carefully
to every word I say to you, and
precisely follow my directions,
Am I clear?
Crystal clear.
First of all, we will be able to
guide that plane by radar.
We can navigate
the plane to the airport.
So don't touch any instruments,
until I tell you to.
That'll certainly be fine with me.
In 3 min. you should see
the runway in front of you.
Look carefully for it.
The fuel is almost gone.
It's a one-shot deal.
Okay.
About the fuel...
Will it last? I...
Well? Are you beginning
to see the runway?
I see it.
Well, then. Let's begin.
First, on the right of
the seat you're sitting in
there are 2 white levers.
The throttle levers.
Slowly pull them to your side.
Pull until the numbers on the monitor
in front of you becomes 70.
You're doing fine.
Keep it there.
Next, the white lever next to them.
Not that.
On the right side.
The flap.
This one, right?
How many?
Five.
Okay.
Now, we lower the nosewheel.
The wheel-shaped lever in front.
Pull and lower it.
The light will turn green.
It's still red.
Try once more.
Yes,
Still red. No change.
Once more.
It changed to green.
This time,
Turn the flap to 25.
What do I do next?
Captain?
Captain!
Captain! Captain!
I'll take over from here.
Push the control stick slowly forward
to lower the altitude.
Lower the throttle
until the numbers become 60.
There's the altitude gage
before the control stick.
Looking at that, adjust it to 1,000 ft.
Lower your head.
Darling.
What are you doing?
Don't come. Don't come here.
Please calm yourself.
We're saved.
Thanks you, muscle man.
Please watch your step.
Apprehended Yusuke Kimoto.
Yuka.
I'm a Kyushu woman.
I won't let my husband suffer.
C'mon. Hold it steady.
I'm yours forever.
Please.
Ah...
Thank you very much.
She really did well.
Bunny!
Human life is heavier than Earth.
Minister Kurihara, your words move me.
It's over now.
Yes, it's over.
I can't
end it like this.
Sister!
Make Way!
You asked for me?
I am Kawano. I used to be
METI Minister's secretary.
Yes, and...
I must hold a press conference.
Protect me until that time.
That's METI Minister
Kurihara's ex-secretary.
Kurihara will be the next premier.
Probably wanted to sever the dark ties.
Kurihara will have
Mido released and then killed.
Hijack was the tool.
At the same time,
to silence that ex-secretary,
he intends to blow up the plane
with all 160 on board.
What a...
Those clinging to power,
disregard human life.
The ones used were...
Innocent young men.
Absurd and unforgiveable.
You're righteous for your age.
It's absolutely unforgiveable.
There's a short run now.
Sister.
Cardiac arrest.
Minister Kurihara.
In exchange for Reiko's life
the bad guys were caught.
How heavy is the 159 lives
Reiko saved,
staking her life,
really isn't my concern.
For me, the fact that Reiko is gone
cannot be compared to Earth.
It lost the existence
of the universe itself.
But before that,
does the universe have
meaning in its existence?
What will you dream about next?