Everybody dies.
Some fall from a window and die.
Others die when an air conditioner
falls from a window and hits them.
Some people drive and hit something and
die. Some people get hit by a car and die.
Some are knifed. some are shot.
some are strangled.
some bleed to death
with bare hands and die.
Some people die when
a neighbor is smoking and sets off a fire.
some people just die from smoking. Some
die from lung cancer. stomach cancer.
Some die from heart attacks. strokes.
People get cirrhosis of the liver and die.
Some freeze to death.
some die from pneumonia.
Some die from heat stroke.
some from getting bit by mosquitoes.
Some just die from throwing up.
Some people get bit by dogs and die.
Some fall off a horse and get trampled.
Some are trampled to death
by other people. Some get old and die.
I'v made up my mind. I have only
one death. I want my death to be for you.
Hello?
Go out the door on your left.
Hell pick you up at the bus stop.
OK. thank you.
- Excuse me. I'm gonna go to the rest room.
- OK.
Hi. Can I have
three vegetable egg rolls to go. please?
Thank you.
You don't have to heat them up.
Thanks.
- Please just stay in.
- OK.
Hello?
Please dont go outside again.
Close the window.
Oh. OK. I'm sorry.
Hello?
Please take a look under the pillow.
OK.
Youre gonna take them into the bathroom.
put them on and wait.
Please dont come out until we call you.
OK. Thank you.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
- I'm OK.
Um... Stand up.
All right. now walk forward
towards the sound of my voice.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna let you
bump into anything. Come forward.
Keep coming forward.
Now turn towards the sound of my voice.
Good. Walk backwards.
Good.
Keep going.
Turn to your left.
Backwards.
Stop.
Turn around.
Place your hands on the wall.
Step your feet a foot apart.
Turn around.
Fall backwards.
Fall straight backwards.
OK. You can turn around now.
All right.
now why don't you have a seat on the bed?
You must be pretty tired.
You had a long trip.
Yeah. it was pretty long. actually.
I've never been cross-country.
so it was cool. You could see...
Is this all you brought?
- I have a little blue bag in the bathroom.
- OK.
OK.
Come on out.
- I will wait for the red light to turn green.
- Good. Again.
- One more time.
- I will wait for the red light to turn green.
- OK. next.
If I think I've been noticed
or there's a small chance I may be caught.
I must execute the plan immediately.
even if there is no one nearby.
Again.
If I think I've been noticed or
there's a small chance I may be caught.
I must execute the plan immediately.
even if there is no one nearby.
Good. One more time.
If I think I've been noticed or
there's a small chance I may be caught.
I must execute the plan immediately.
even if there is no one nearby.
If you have any questions.
now's the time to ask.
I'm sorry. I want to do everything right.
but why would I do it if no one's around?
I want pizza.
Will you please eat with me?
I don't want to eat alone.
- Are those the only clothes you brought?
- What?
Are those the only clothes you brought?
- Um. no. I have a sweater in my bag.
- OK.
Do you want me to try it on for you?
- That's OK. Is that all you brought?
- Mm-hmm.
OK. what size are you?
I can fit into a 2. but not if it's. like.
over here.'cause then it's too tight.
I can fit into a 3-4.
or if you have to pick between
small. medium and large. pick small.
- What about shoe size?
- Um. size 9.
Ready to make a video?
Are you ready to make a video?
Don't you want to make a video
for your parents?
My parents are dead.
Let me see the other one.
There you go.
Slide that in.
OK. Go ahead. please.
Help me with the top.
OK. Let's button this.
Here.
Good.
Good. OK.
Just zip this up.
There we go.
OK.
Lift up your hands.
Put it down.
All right.
OK.
OK. Maybe she should put it down?
You want it down?
OK.
Excuse me. could I have a Kleenex?
I feel like my nose is getting shiny.
Put this right there.
Hold this.
Put this hand right there. Hold that
and you want to keep this hand on it.
- You've never held a gun before?
- Mnh-mnh.
No?
- I could try to memorize it.
- No. take this out. OK.
Hold it lower.
Maybe you can hold it right above
the camera so she's looking straight ahead.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Go ahead. Action.
How can I know my motives are pure?
You'll see through me.
What if you see things I don't see?
Has to be for you. not for them.
Not for him. They'll think it's for him.
But you'll see. You'll know.
Don't think I'm doing it
for the wrong reason.
I don't think I am. but what if I don't know?
How can I be sure?
You'll see right through me.
Hello?
OK. thank you.
- Good morning.
How are these shoes?
Well. they feel like they might be a little big.
That's OK. though.
I can put some Kleenex
in the toes of the shoes.
Yeah. those are pretty big.
Can I have your wallet. please?
Thank you.
- Who's this?
- My little brother.
Could I keep that photo?
I wish I could say yes.
It's OK. I understand.
Can I have your cell phone?
Have you called anyone or has anyone
called you since you've been here?
No. just you guys.
Do you have any other articles
that might identify you?
- I have my house keys in my bag.
- That's OK. We'll take that away anyway.
Now. you're probably not gonna need this.
but I want you to memorize it anyway.
Is this a real person?
Leah Cruz. 3312 Douglas Avenue.
Longfield. Colorado 80536. April 10. 1987.
- Spell your last name.
- C-r-u-z.
- First name.
- L-e-a-h.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Zip code.
- 80536.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Spell your full name.
- L-e-a-h C-r-u-z.
- City and state.
- Longfield. Colorado.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Say your last name.
- Cruz.
- Spell it.
- C-r-u-z.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
Height.
Your height is your height.
It's the same.
5'6'.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Aries. Street address.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Spell your last name.
- C-r-u-z.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- City and state.
- Longfield. Colorado.
- Spell your last name.
- C-r-u-z.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Spell your full name.
- L-e-a-h C-r-u-z.
- What's your sign?
- Aries.
- Zip code.
- 80536.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Spell your last name.
- C-r-u-z.
- Zip code.
- 80536.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- City and state.
- Longfield. Colorado.
- Spell your last name.
- C-r-u-z.
- Zip code.
- 80536.
- Street address.
- 3312 Douglas Avenue.
- Date of birth.
- April 10. 1987.
- Spell your full name.
- L-e-a-h C-r-u-z.
Here. take this pin.
I want you to prick my finger with it.
One more time. a little harder.
You can do it again. harder.
Now give me the pin.
Hold out your hand.
- Did that hurt?
- Unh-unh.
No. it didn't hurt.
What about that?
- Did that hurt?
- No.
- No. what?
- It didn't hurt.
It didn't hurt. OK.
That's all you're gonna feel. It's like...
like a bug bite. right? A mosquito bite.
You've been bitten by a mosquito.
It doesn't hurt. right?
It's gonna be over so fast. you won't
have a chance to see or hear anything.
- OK?
- OK.
All right... just lift up. Thanks.
OK?
- Thank you.
- OK.
You OK?
All right.
Watch your head.
Keep going.
- Thank you.
- Keep going.
Step. Step.
Step.
Could you let us know what's going on?
Yeah. we were just saying that this one
fits well. That this fits well.
- How's that?
- Good.
We're just gonna shorten the straps a bit.
We can add a strap around the waist
between these two straps here.
It's up to her.
Would you like a strap around the waist?
No. no. it's OK.
Can you just walk back and forth?
Yeah. That looks quite natural.
She's pretty.
That's good. Walk a bit more.
If you shift your weight a little bit forward.
it will help with your lower back.
And you can also hook your hands up
underneath here.
Good.
- How's it feel? Is it too heavy?
- No. it's OK.
It's about 30 pounds.
but most of the weight is in the nails.
- We can take some out if you like.
- No. you can put more in if you want.
These don't work.
so you can wear them around your neck.
It's very easy.
This switch locks it.
And you just flip it to unlock it
and press this button.
- OK. It's this button here?
- That button. The other buttons don't work.
You just flip it to unlock it
and press this button.
Go ahead. try it.
It's not connected now.
Try it a few more times.
One more time before we connect it.
- Hi.
It's a different color.
The car - it's a different color.
Thank you.
- Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
Can I have two pretzels. please.
with mustard?
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Have a nice day.
Excuse me.
how can I go to Times Square?
Straight up and make a left
and you'll be right there. OK?
- Thank you.
- All right. have a good day.
Guys. are you fans of comedy
shows? Check it out. Come check it out!
Beautiful thing in the world as of right now!
- Oh!
- Excuse me.
Excuse me. Would you take
our pictures with the horse?
OK.
I'm sorry. I can't.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Thanks.
Ooh!
Are you alright?
- You need help?
- You OK?
You OK?
Alright...
Be careful - your Walkman.
Julissa. can I use your phone?
it's like.'Oh. she was so sweet.'
I want all the flowers. Whoever doesn't
see me. I'll come and haunt them.
- Now I know.
- You better come and bring a lot of flowers.
- I don't know.
- Tu tienes algo ahi negro.
Sacamelo entonces.
- Fix it!
- Don't poke my eye out!
Well. fix it!
I got it. Never mind. I got this.
- Julissa. what are you doing in there?
- You do not need to know!
What you want?
Where's my lighter?
You better go to Julissa's
or Jennifer's house or something.
I'd rather be thrown in some ocean.
in Hawaii or something.
Ya yo veo
que tu ta pasa sinceramente.
I need sneakers too. man.
$ 2.16. Here's your spoon.
Thank you.
Enjoy your pudding.
- Can I have a slice of tomato?
- That's all?
- Yes.
- That's 65 cents.
Please insert another 25 cents.
City and state. please.
I don't know what the city is but the state
is New Jersey and it's Motel 7.
Please hold.
Information.
How may I help you?
I dont know what the city is.
Its New Jersey and its Motel 7.
Please hold.
This is a long distance call.
Please insert $ 1. 25.
Motel 7. How can I help you?
Hi. can you connect me
to room 272. please?
No ones checked into that room right now.
OK. thank you.
Excuse me.
Hi.
Excuse me. Do you have a quarter
I could have for the phone?
- Sure.
- Really?
- There.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Do you have a quarter
I could have for the phone?
- Sorry?
- A quarter that I could have for the phone?
Actually...
Thank you so much.
Excuse me. do you have a quarter
I could have for the phone?
- For what?
- The phone.
- The phone?
- Uh-huh.
- Sure. I'll give you a quarter.
- Really? Thanks.
You're welcome.
- I dont' know. Here.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
- You're looking for a quarter?
- Uh-huh. for the phone.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I cant answer my
cell phone now. Please leave a message.
Welcome to coast-to-coast collect.
To make a collect call.
please state your name after the tone.
It's me.
Please hold while we verify
if the party will accept the charges.
Hi. honey.
Did you lose your phone?
Hows Chicago?
Are you girls having a nice time?
Hello?
Hello? Honey. we cant hear anything.
Can you hear us?
- Hello? Hello?
- Can you call back again?
Honey. you want
to try calling from a different phone?
- Miss. you dropped...
- It's OK. Please don't touch it!
I'm just trying to be a gentleman.
Damn. it's pretty heavy.
- What you got in there. body parts?
- A bomb.
Stop joking. Seriously.
what you have in there?
- It's just books. Schoolbooks.
- You're a schoolgirl? I like smart girls.
All right. so you have a boyfriend
or any friends?
- What?
- Do you have a boyfriend or any friends?
- No.
- You don't? Be honest with me.
You don't have to be scared.
Just tell me the truth.
No. I didn't mean to s...
Um. no. I-I don't. I don't.
You're serious? I can't believe that.
You're pretty cute. Be real with me.
You can't be so closed in.
You got beautiful green eyes and shit.
Be real with a brother. I ain't trying
to bother you. You look pretty cute.
My brother's girlfriend's from Azerbaijan.
It's part of Russia.
She's pretty. but not as half as pretty
as you. You know what I'm saying?
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
So let me ask you a question.
Um. you know I work with myself. basically.
Trying to help 'em out. I do a lot
of calisthenics and stuff like that.
- I just want to show you something.
- No. thanks.
I ain't trying to bother you. but look.
I work on myself. as you can see.
I ain't trying to bother you. sweetie.
know what I'm sayin'?
I'm just trying to show you
that I work for myself.
Are you gonna blow me off like that?
Don't try to brush me off. Life is good.
Yo. green eyes. one second.
I ain't trying to bother you.
You got nice lips. nice eyes. I'm trying to
help you out. That don't count for nothing?
- That don't count for nothing?
- No. thank you.
I'm tired of girls that look like you.
Cavalry comes around.
you don't even know what to do with it.
You're probably one of those fancy girls.
like one of those Frappuccinos and shit.
Are you gonna brush me off like that.
like I ain't nobody?
I'm somebody. yo.
Come on. you know I'm somebody.
Aw. that's not even fair. yo.
Come on. Ma. it's not even that serious.
Why don't you want me?
Please give me a sign.
= Downloaded from www. opensubtitles. org =-