Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Episode 14
Boss!
There's not even an ant in sight.
Are you sure we weren't scammed?
For sure. What if it was
just a waste of money?
Do you wanna jump into
the Han River and sleep with the fishes?
Shut your traps!
Over there.
The package?
You're sure of its capability?
Within a hundred-meter radius, yes.
But it'll only last ten minutes
so a surprise attack is the best bet.
A surprise attack.
Thanks for the unexpected strategic tip
from a learned man like yourself.
Yonggu, give the man what we prepared.
Thank you. Then...
Guys, our fate will change for the better.
Say goodbye to the cold and hungry days.
Boss, what is this?
You wouldn't understand even if I
explained. I'll show you what it is soon.
Let's go!
This is the “Gimainmul” double goblets
Robin Hood sent today.
Can we use the X-ray room right now?
Is there a problem?
I don't think it's authentic.
No way.
I'm sorry, but you need to leave
because of the training exercise.
You can't leave once the exercise begins.
Sure.
What should we do, sir?
We have no choice. Let's take
a look at it tomorrow. Good work.
A fake Robin Hood.
Why are you so serious?
No, it's nothing.
I can go home early thanks to the training
exercise. C'mon. I'll buy you a beer.
Sure.
Okay then, the twenty-third security
training exercise will begin now.
Start!
Yes, sir!
Excuse me?
Chohee, why are you lagging behind?
Why? Did you see something suspicious?
No.
The exercise began
precisely at 2100 hours.
As you can see on the screen, we've sent
in the defensive and the offensive teams.
This is the last day I'm playing the thief,
and then I'm calling it quits.
Me, too. Not like the museum will reward
us for our efforts. This is too much work!
Can we make a pit stop at the restroom?
Idiot!
It's an emergency.
Me, too. I'm about to explode after eating
the watermelon Joohyun gave us earlier.
Hurry up. Hurry.
Where's the storage room?
Are we there yet?
Hold on. When I scouted
the area earlier, it was definitely...
Wait, is it a floor below?
My tingling senses tell me that the scent
of money is wafting down from above.
Stop confusing me and give it
to me straight. Above or below?
Imbeciles. How can you
screw up every step of the way?
I don't know why
I work with you guys. Honestly.
Boss, this is the storage room.
Good job getting all the way here.
Shall we get this party started?
Huh?
- The lights are out.
- What happened?
This time they're really going full out.
I know. I don't remember
the last exercise being so dark.
This is just a frantic attempt to look good
in front of the superiors. Showing off.
Exactly. And we worker bees
have to work our butts off.
Something's not right.
Officer Cho, try radioing in.
Why is it dead?
This is Eagle, Eagle!
Huh? This is dead, too.
Hold on. Neither the walkie-talkie
nor the cell phone is working.
What if something happened?
What if this isn't part of the exercise?
What if this is a real situation?
What?
Boss. Is this all ours?
Wow, this is amazing.
Am I dreaming?
Move along.
We don't have much time left.
What in the world happened?
Manager Kim, explain things.
The thing is... It's probably
just a temporary power outage.
The independent power system will
kick in soon, so the power will return.
How it is possible that all the security
systems are down with a blackout?
First, we have to analyze
the situation precisely.
I'll start by checking
the first exhibition room.
Chief, should I come with you?
No, please go to the electrical power room and find out what's going on.
Yes, sir!
Today's exercise is certainly
refreshing. Completely innovative.
This is a power outage.
Right. There was a power outage
when we raided the Iwazaki meeting.
I'm getting bad vibes.
The storage room.
What? Did you say the storage room?
It's possible. Everyone's in
the museum's interior for the exercise.
Gosh, you know the level of security down
there. What reckless fool would rob it?
No, it's possible the security system there
is also down during the power outage.
Shouldn't we go check, just in case?
Yeah. We'll head over
to the storage room.
You guys go to
the nearest exhitibion room.
Okay!
Chohee, Jinguk, let's go.
They're talking nonsense. Wait, what if a thief really does rob the storage room?
Wait, what if a thief really
does rob the storage room?
If this is a real situation,
we're all dead meat.
Boss, I've never seen so many treasures
in one place before in my life.
Hey, idiot, how are you
going to escape with that thing?
The “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook,
the “Chochung” collection,
and the “Maejukmun” vase.
First find Chairman Jang's items.
Then we sort through the expensive and
light treasures and wrap them up. Move!
Moving.
Oh, and try to find
the “Bihaedangjib,” too.
I need some of you to come with me
to the first exhibition room.
I'll leave the exhibition room
in planning to you.
Let's hurry!
What are you doing?
Why isn't the electricity on yet?
It takes some time to get
the emergency power running.
What? What are you going to do
if a thief takes this chance to come in?
Do you want to see
the museum get robbed?
Manager, sir, that
couldn't possibly happen.
How much longer
until the power is back?
Approximately a minute and a half.
[Accessing the security system.]
[Do you want to start
the back-up system?]
[Accessing the back-up system.]
What the?
Boss! What's happening?
Didn't you say the systems
would be down for ten minutes?
I thought so, too.
What happened?
Let's get out of here.
Hey, which department
are you guys from?
Run!
It's no use for you to run,
so turn yourselves in.
Chohee, are you okay?
I'm fine. Please report
things to the briefing room.
Hurry!
This is Eagle.
[This is real. Five intruders.
This is a real situation!]
All exits are to be barricaded,
including the front and rear exits,
and exits leading out of the parking lot.
What happened to the special task force?
They're almost here.
Boss, how will we get out of here?
Boss, let's turn ourselves in.
Shut your traps!
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm sorry for showing you
such a disgraceful image.
It's okay. Nothing will happen,
so don't worry too much.
We'll take care of matters here,
so you can go home.
Okay. Then I'll be going.
Hello, Director Kang.
Who are you?
The front exit is all clear.
What about the rear exit?
We're inspecting things now,
but everything seems fine.
And the east exit?
The exit has been completely sealed off.
Not even an ant will be able to pass.
There are supposed to be five men.
Then are they still hiding in the museum?
I'm not sure, but there's
nothing to report on our side.
Other than the director of the CHA,
not a single car has left the grounds.
Hold on. The director's car left?
Intruders in the museum.
I really can't believe it.
How could such a thing happen?
Yes, how could that happen?
How strange.
Which department are you guys from?
The regulations team, did you say?
Is that so important when we're all
serving the country and the people?
We'll guarantee your safety,
so please do not worry.
Ah, okay. Thanks.
Thank you, but we should've
brought along the secretaries -
Then again, the secretaries
aren't very important.
They'll be fine going home on their own.
Chief Lee!
What? Ah, yes? Understood.
Sir, we should take you home,
but we're in a bit of a hurry...
No, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Then, take care.
How could this happen?
Both teams running around like headless
chicken and letting them get away.
Thank goodness the security office
was efficient in handling the matter.
What would we have done
if something bad had happened?
Manager Kim, it's not like
we stood by doing nothing.
We'll devote everything
to catching the thieves.
You two should thank your lucky stars.
This is a real blow to our pride.
Who would dare sneak in
during our training exercise?
Let's get some rest today and discuss a
countermove tomorrow. I'm going home.
Okay, goodbye.
Chief, you should go home, too.
I will.
Chief, take this.
What is it?
There was a bit of a scuffle with the
thieves. Chohee managed to grab this.
Chohee? Is she okay?
Yes, she's fine and she went back
to the office to wrap things up.
Here.
Is there anything that
could identify the thieves?
No. Nothing of that sort.
I thought so. The thieves wouldn't
carry around incriminating things.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Gyoon Heo.]
Bumsang, sorry for calling you so early
in the morning. I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Please reappraise the items
that Robin Hood sent in.
Reappraise them?
Yes, I'll explain things in detail later.
Please reappraise them first.
No, there's no need
to look at them all.
What is this?
Isn't it some kind of chip?
This seems to be the cause behind
the crash of the security system.
If this chip came from Robin Hood's item,
that means Robin Hood is the culprit?
No way.
What do you mean Robin Hood is
the culprit? What are you talking about?
Some real thieves invaded the museum
yesterday during the training exercise.
Thank goodness the theft failed. The
power was out and it was totally chaotic.
I was wondering who was behind it,
and it turns out to be Robin Hood.
There's no way Robin Hood
would do such a thing.
Jeez, Bumsang.
How could you defend him
with the evidence against him?
Robin Hood, you bastard.
I thought you were a good thief.
But you're a sly thief.
That's even worse than
simpleminded thieves.
Officer Park, please find out this chip's
capability with the security team.
Officer Cho, please look into
where it could have been purchased.
I'm sorry, but I'll have
to excuse myself first.
Hello? Yes, Grandma. What took you
so long in answering the phone?
Yes, yes. I'm fine.
Let me talk to Gyoon.
No, the guy I sent there yesterday.
Named Gyoon.
What? He never arrived?
Boss, it may be
presumptuous of me to say this,
but this failure is entirely your fault.
What?
Why didn't you fill me in on
the whole picture beforehand?
If you had clued me in, I would
have prepared a more precise plan -
Are you pouring salt on the wound?
No, I just...
Boss, take a deep breath.
What are you doing?
His glass is empty.
I'm so frustrated.
We made it in and didn't get away
with even a cheap porcelain piece.
Shouldn't we be glad
we made it out safely?
And everyone will think
he's the culprit.
You're glad with that?
Chairman Jang is going to murder us all.
What am I going to do? I totally
boasted to him about a great plan.
See? You've repeatedly fallen out of
grace since the retaliation on Taesoo Heo.
You're in big trouble, Boss.
You know I took care of things by sending
in my boys. Why bring it up again?
Anyway! That was the incident that
put Boss on Chairman Jang's bad side.
Both of you shut up! You guys
don't know when to keep your traps shut.
[Your call has been transferred to
an automated voice message system...]
Why does he have his phone off?
He's worrying me to death.
Chohee!
Chief, you're here early.
Yeah. I need to check something.
Are you headed to the conference room?
Yes.
Let's go!
So how's Gyoon doing these days?
Gyoon? He went traveling.
Traveling? Where did he go?
He wouldn't tell me. He said he'd call
when he got there but nothing so far.
Chief! Did you find any clues
in the bag from yesterday?
No, nothing significant.
Is that so? Does that mean
yesterday's attack will remain a mystery?
No, I do have a suspect.
Really?
We suspect that Robin Hood
was behind the attack on the museum.
Robin Hood! The guys from yesterday
were Robin Hood's crew, were they?
It's bad enough they broke into the
museum, but they dared to kidnap me?
When I get my hands on him -
Chief Noh! Chief Kang!
Yes, sir?
Even if you have to mobilize everyone
in the CHA and the investigations team
I want you to catch those thieves.
Yes, sir.
Man...
He's just a thief, not a good thief.
He has accomplices and isn't a solo act.
The Robin Hood case is headed
in an unexpected direction.
I'm a bit disappointed.
I thought Robin Hood was quite cool.
I'm going to catch him myself.
Why are you exaggerating?
He sold our team's name
to the director! That bastard!
You're not even the chief...
You jerk!
Be the bigger person.
Chief Kang.
Chief Kang!
Yes? I'm sorry.
Why are you in a foul mood?
How could you tell? Were you staring
at me during the entire meeting?
Jeez, you twist everything around.
It seems I hit the bull's eye.
Anyway, was it really
Robin Hood yesterday?
Dunno.
Because he sent in Dad's items,
I thought he knew Dad.
So I don't feel comfortable
catching him myself.
What do you mean
you're catching him yourself?
I'm going to join
the Robin Hood investigation.
We should catch him
quickly to find out who he is.
Why are you doing unnecessary things?
What?
I mean it's not your job
to catch Robin Hood.
Why are you getting involved?
That's just being meddlesome.
Meddlesome?
That's harsh, don't you think?
I mean, anyway, you -
Bumsang.
There was something I didn't tell you
in the morning. Can I have a moment?
Sure.
Excuse us.
Yeah.
What is it?
Let me ask you point blank.
The Robin Hood you saw in front of
Minister Gong's house was Gyoon, right?
This was at the museum yesterday.
No. Gyoon did not sneak
into the museum yesterday.
So you knew that Gyoon was Robin Hood.
Yes, I knew.
It was Gyoon who returned
the three previous items.
But not the “Gimainmul” double goblets.
That definitely wasn't him.
Do you know where he is right now?
I heard he's traveling. Do you know where
he is now and where he was last night?
I sincerely hope Gyoon isn't the culprit.
But just like no one imagined
Gyoon was Robin Hood,
no one can guarantee
that it wasn't Gyoon last night.
Chief Kang.
Please contact me
as soon as he contacts you.
Do you really think I'll do that?
I can't dissuade you from chasing him,
but I'll tell you now that I won't help you.
Bumsang.
I understand you don't want
to see Chohee get hurt.
I feel the same way.
I, too, am sincere about her.
Is it really necessary to catch Gyoon?
If he was framed for yesterday's events,
then it's the only way to protect him.
Joohyun!
Where are you going?
To report our meeting to the head
of the security. Man, he scares me.
Why didn't you ask
one of the guys to go instead?
I wanted to, but the guys are out
with the investigations team
And Chief Noh left early.
He left early?
Is something wrong?
No, I don't think it's anything like that.
Did you notice he's
really different these days?
Since the Robin Hood case began, he's
always missing and leaves at six sharp.
Is that so?
I understand his retirement is soon,
but please advise him not to do that.
I will.
Then, bye.
Your brilliant idea
was to rob the museum?
I completely screwed up, sir.
I deserve to die.
Your life is already in my hands. But how
could you do something so reckless?
Ah, I wanted...
But you don't have
to worry about a thing.
It was perfectly set up
so Robin Hood would be blamed.
We even left his ID card there,
so everything will be fine.
Are you out of your mind? What if
Gyoon Heo is caught and spills all?
Just in case, we kidnapped him,
so there's nothing to worry about.
What do you plan to do with him?
Well, I'm in a bit of a pinch
thinking about it.
I kidnapped him because I thought
I had to, but now I'm not sure what to do.
Should I let him sleep with the fishes?
Why are you asking me that?
What? Ah, yes...
I don't know what you did in the past
and what you will do in the future.
Of course! That's a given.
Leave me. And don't be seen
anywhere near until I contact you.
Yes, sir.
Boss, what's gonna happen to us now?
What else? We have to lay low
until Chairman Jang's wrath subsides.
How did this happen?
This was supposed to be our big hit.
We got off easy because
we have Chohee Heo's brother.
If we didn't have him,
today would've been our funeral.
What happened?
Where did he go?
‘But just like no one imagined
Gyoon was Robin Hood,
no one can guarantee
that it wasn't Gyoon last night.'
Why did you suddenly
want to eat here of all places?
It's time to eat so let's just eat.
I always wanted to come here
but want to come alone.
Be honest. You feel bad
for snapping at me earlier, right?
When did I snap at you?
I never did that.
Besides, you're buying today.
Why should I?
Fine, I will. I'll buy.
Really? You always say that
and never buy.
Don't even.
I bought at least one meal.
Are you ready to order?
What's your most delicious dish?
How's this option?
It includes an appetizer, the main course
and dessert. And drinks are included.
Okay, we'll have two orders of this.
Hey! Why are you ordering for me?
Just eat it.
It's the cheapest thing
on the menu, isn't it?
You wanna pay?
Did you talk to Gyoon today?
Gyoon? No, I couldn't get in contact
with him all day. Where is he?
He must be at a place
with bad reception. Don't worry.
But it's strange.
Why are so many people interested in
Gyoon today? Both you and Chief Kang.
Is that so?
Hello?
Gyoon!
Why haven't you been
picking up your phone?
Oh, I ran out of battery.
Where are you?
Here? I'm at Sokcho.
Sokcho?
Jeez, you went far.
Gyoon, did you eat?
Did you sleep well?
Sis, I'm fine, so don't worry
if we lose contact for a while.
I'm perfectly fine. Okay?
Call me at least once a day.
Hey, let me talk to him.
Gyoon, Bumsang wants to talk to you.
Not right now, Sis. I have to get on
the bus now so tell him I'll call him later.
Bye.
Hello? Gyoon! Gyoon!
He hung up?
Yeah, he hung up.
Thank you very much.
Are you really going to
be fine on your own?
You think I'm a little kid? If anything
happens, I'll call you first. Satisfied?
Yeah, go on in.
I'll leave after you go in.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Bumsang!
Who could it be?
What's going on?
We have no choice. Come with me.
What?
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Let's go to my house.
What?
Then do you want to stay here?
Come with me.
- Hey!
- Come on.
Look, isn't that Bumsang?
I'll have to teach him another lesson.
Where are they going together?
Hey! Why are you curious
about such useless things?
Where in the world
did that bastard go?
Hurry and tell Boss
we couldn't find him.
Aw man, he's gonna beat on us again.
Drink some of this, okay?
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, is it really okay
for me to be here?
It turned out for the better. I was
uneasy about you being home alone.
I mean, I did promise Gyoon
that I'd take care of you.
There's nothing to be
uncomfortable about so relax.
Fine, then.
I'll trouble you for one night.
Sure.
I wonder who it was
that wrecked my house like that?
Maybe it was Robin Hood?
If it was, that means
he's no friend of my family.
I really don't get it.
Think about that later and get some rest.
You must've been shocked.
Yeah.
What? So you're telling us
that Chohee's brother is Robin Hood?
Oh my god.
Didn't I tell you the darkest place
is under the candlestick?
I guessed it would be someone related
to Heo, but who knew it would be him?
I'm certain Gyoon is Robin Hood but not
if he was behind the museum intrusion.
Though frankly things
aren't looking good for him.
Chohee will have a heart attack
if she finds out.
So what I want to say is that
we have to find him as soon as we can.
Unofficially, of course.
So you want to keep this
a secret from Chohee, right?
Won't that be for the best?
Yes, sir.
Hello?
[Bro!]
Gyoon! Where are you?
Bro, listen to me first.
I was kidnapped by Mr. Kim
on my way to your grandfather's place.
What? Are you serious?
Yes. I managed to escape,
so don't worry.
That's it. I'll go to you right now.
Where are you?
No, I found out a secret
behind my father's death.
Chairman Jang and Mr. Kim
collaborated to kill my father.
I'm not going to do nothing about it.
Hey, you're not thinking of
doing anything foolish, are you?
Gyoon, you can't do this by yourself. Let's
discuss this in person. Where are you?
Please take care of my sister.
Gyoon!
Is this enough?
Thank you, Uncle.
I'll pay you back for sure.
What are you saying? You punk.
Why would I lend money to you?
This is allowance I'm giving to you.
Thank you.
So what do you need this money for?
Things are really complicated in my head.
I wanted to go traveling
but I didn't want to ask Sis for money.
Traveling?
Uncle, I have to get going.
You're leaving now?
At this late hour?
Hey, kid. Where are you headed looking
like that? Sleep over at my house tonight.
It's okay. I already have a ticket
so I have to get going.
Oh, and Uncle? Please look after
my sister while I'm gone.
I will.
Uncle! I'm depending on you.
He's acting a little weird today.
‘No, I found out a secret
behind my father's death.'
‘Chairman Jang and Mr. Kim
collaborated to kill my father.'
Chief Kang!
So where is Gyoon right now?
He wouldn't say. I'm worried that he'll do
something reckless at his young age.
I did consider the possibility Chairman
Jang played a hand in Heo's death.
But I couldn't pursue that approach
because there was no evidence.
And there's another thing
you should know.
Today Chohee's house was ransacked.
What do you mean?
Someone broke in.
I assume it was Mr. Kim?
It seems they were
trying to recapture Gyoon.
And Chohee? Where is she now?
She's at my house.
I took her to my place. I didn't think
I should leave her alone at her house.
Yes. That was
the right move on your part.
I know you don't feel comfortable
hearing about this from me.
I know that we both
want to stay by her side.
Anyway, I will do everything I can to find
Gyoon. Thank you for contacting me.
Please find Gyoon. Please.
I will.
Is this the man who got into a huge fight
with Taesoo Heo seven years ago?
It's a recent picture
so he might look different now.
Don't pay attention to things like
the hair color and just look at his face.
That's him. That's the man.
Are you sure?
Yes! Those eyes, that mouth.
I'm sure it's him.
If we bring him in,
can you testify against him?
Sure.
Thank you for your cooperation.
- I'll see you soon.
- Bye.
- Chief, we're back.
- We're back.
Officer Cho, Officer Park.
Drop what you're doing
and focus on finding Mr. Kim.
Did that man just
confirm that it was Kim?
Yes, it's almost certain that Mr. Kim
was Chairman Jang's middleman.
So now our priority is to gather
evidence and find more witnesses.
Officer Park.
Yes, Chief.
Try to locate Mr. Kim through the
ex-middlemen. He's somewhere in Seoul.
Officer Cho, come with me.
Where are we...
See you later.
Are you up? Go wash up
so we can have breakfast.
Okay.
Tada!
Man, I haven't eaten at home in ages.
Help yourself.
You look like you live here.
I wish I could live in a place like this.
So, is there anywhere you want to go?
Why?
It's Saturday.
We should go clear our heads.
I'm fine. I just want to go home.
What?
Thanks for your concern,
but I'm not comfortable being here.
Then I'll sleep over at Jonggyu's place,
so you stay here.
Where did that come from?
Then do you want to stay
in a motel room by yourself?
Why would I go somewhere
other than my house?
You can't stay there on your own.
What are you going to do
if someone breaks in like yesterday?
I'll worry about it then.
You're not serious, are you?
Gyoon could come home at anytime,
and nothing's resolved by my staying out.
I want to go home,
get changed and stuff.
Chief, what if you get into trouble
for dropping in unannounced like this?
It's not so hard
living off a reduced salary.
Who is it?
This is Chief Shiwan Kang
of the investigations team.
This isn't our first meeting, is it?
You remember.
It's been a while.
What brings you to my house?
As expected, you don't beat around
the bush. Then I won't mince my words.
Do you know a man named Taesoo Heo?
Taesoo Heo?
Hmm, I don't think
I've ever heard of him.
Are you saying a well-known art collector
like yourself doesn't know Taesoo Heo?
Is there a reason I should know him?
He's such a famous art thief,
I assumed you had at least heard of him.
Or maybe you'll recognize
the name “General Shovel?”
Why are you asking me
about an insignificant art thief?
I was wondering if you knew
where I could find General Shovel.
He disappeared seven years ago,
and we have no idea where he is.
We have to arrest him, so I was
wondering if you had any information.
I want to repeat my question
as to why you're here asking me this.
This is how investigations are.
We examine those
who are indirectly related
and we look for contradictions
in the testimonies.
Like fitting together puzzle pieces.
If you're from
the investigations team,
you should be under
the Seoul district jurisdiction.
Yes, I am.
The last time we met, did I fail to mention
I was close with the police commissioner?
You think you'll be safe
after this insolent behavior?
There's a saying that fits this situation.
It's not over until the fat lady sings.
What?
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'll be seeing you soon.
Dear lord, Chief!
Did you wait long?
I was on the brink of
a heart attack the whole time.
What did Chairman Jang say?
Did he admit to knowing Taesoo Heo?
You think he would?
He denied everything.
Then why did you come here
when it's so obvious he would do that?
To test the waters.
What?
He'll know that
we've picked up on his scent.
He'll definitely take action
to cover his tracks.
And we need that
in order to catch him redhanded.
I see...
Is Officer Park at Chohee's house?
Yes, he should be dusting
for fingerprints with the forensics team.
Let's head over there.
Okay. Chief, what if Chohee
comes home while we're there?
We have to search her brother's room.
If something Robin Hood
related appears -
I've already explained things.
She won't come home until we're done.
Who did you tell?
Chohee?
Let's go.
Why are you stopping me
from going home?
Who says I'm stopping you?
Come with me somewhere first.
Where? Where are we going?
You talk too much!
I'll let you go homeso stop
complaining and come with me.
Where are we going?
Feel cooler?
Try and grab it!
Show it to me next time.
Hey, look at this. Doesn't it look
just like the one you gave me? Right?
It's similar.
But this one's fake.
What? But it looks the same.
It's fake, I tell you.
A Chinese dude made this one.
You say everything's fake.
How can it look so similar?
Did you use the set I gave you yet?
No.
Why? Couldn't bear to use it
since it's real Goryeo celadon?
No, I was waiting to use it
when my father came home.
That's why you bought three cups.
Making me feel bad.
Don't be. I'll use it next time with Gyoon.
You want to come over then?
You're going to invite me?
We have an extra cup. Let's use them
when Gyoon comes back from his trip.
Chief?
This was found in Gyoon's room. I think
he used it for his Robin Hood activities.
We have no choice.
Take it in as evidence.
And -
What else?
We found these, too.
What? Are you serious?
Why would those at Chohee's place -
Okay, Chief. I understand. Yes.
Who was that?
Chief Kang?
Yeah.
What's up?
Did something happen?
He wants to see me tomorrow
about the Robin Hood case.
Man, I'm hungry. Let's eat.
What would you like?
You're hiding something
from me, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I overheard your call
with Chief Kang just now.
What are they doing at my house?
And why is it necessary
for you to keep me away?
They're dusting for the fingerprints
of the guys who broke in yesterday.
And why wouldn't you tell me that?
I'm telling you now.
I thought you'd feel better not knowing.
You think I'm stupid?
You're hiding something, aren't you?
I'm not.
Why do you keep asking that?
Look at me!
Look me in the face and tell me.
What are you hiding?
What is it you're unable to tell me?
Hello, who is this?
[This is Ohseong Jang.]
Who did you say you are?
Chairman Ohseong Jang
of the Ohseong Group.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America