Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Episode 12
Hey, this is Bumsang.
[Bumsang?
Why would you call me?]
I have something to ask you.
Are you free right now?
[Now? I'm at home.]
I'll head over there, then. Yeah.
‘Yongcheol wouldn't get specific,
but I think it's a statue of Buddha.'
‘Taesoo stole seven national treasures.'
Take out the returned “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook, the “Chochung” collection...
and the “Maejukmun” vase,
and there are four remaining.
They are Duryang Kim's “Sansu” painting,
the “Gimainmul” double goblets...
the “Geumdongdae” incense burner, and
the “Geumdongyeorae” standing Buddha.
The “Geumdongyeorae”
standing Buddha statue...
Why does Bumsang want
to come over at this hour? Jeez...
The minister and madam said
they're going to be late tonight.
Then just go on home.
Okay.
Bye, Mary. See you tomorrow.
What a nice house
Yongcheol lives in.
Robin Hood?
Are you Taesoo Heo?
So why didn't Robin Hood show up?
He seemed to know like a bloodhound
when to steal Chairman Jang's items.
Why else?
He knew it wasn't a stolen good.
How is it that your intelligence
capabilities fall short of a thief's?
How tactless...
Shouldn't we charge him with
attempting to smuggle items abroad?
You idiot.
How can we when he just showed it
to Iwazaki or whatever his name was?
This is all your fault. You prodded us
into action with false information.
Fine, it's all my fault.
It's my fault we gave Chairman Jang
something to find fault in.
Chief, what should we do now?
The milk is already spilt.
We'll just have to settle the matter well.
Everyone must be tired.
Let's wrap things up here and leave.
Jeez, no one's even offering
to take responsibility.
- Stop it already.
- The next meal's on you.
Chohee!
Yes, Chief?
Are you headed home?
I thought about buying dinner
to make it up to everyone.
But I wasn't sure I could
keep a smile on my face.
And I didn't want to sit there
all sullen, so I'm just going home.
Rough day, wasn't it?
No. I just feel bad for causing
everyone so much trouble.
Everyone's just doing their jobs. Besides,
you're the one who's most disappointed.
The raid failed so we might
as well console ourselves.
We probably shouldn't drink.
What should we do?
It's okay, Chief. You don't need
to force yourself for my sake.
It's not because of you,
but because I'm really depressed.
But I know how you really feel.
There's really no need to pretend, Chief.
And tomorrow's another day.
Thank you for caring.
Okay then. Go home.
Okay, bye, Chief.
Gyoon.
Gyoon? I'm home.
Hey, Sis.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
No, I'm just tired from
working my part-time job.
I thought I told you not to work.
Jeez, how can I slack off
when you're working so hard?
Why are you so late?
Did you have a raid today?
For the Robin Hood case.
Bro, I mean, Bumsang told me
you guys think Dad is Robin Hood.
You think so, too?
All the evidence points to him.
Maybe he thinks he can come back if
he's Robin Hood and not General Shovel.
Sis.
Gyoon, only he knows the truth
so I'll find him quickly.
Let's ask him then, okay?
It wasn't Taesoo Heo.
It was a young man.
So who could it be?
Did something happen between
you and Yongcheol last night?
Oh, right. I forgot about
meeting Yongcheol last night.
He called me at dawn saying some
gibberish about you being Robin Hood.
Me?
Why is everyone accusing me
of being Robin Hood?
Who else thinks so?
What's going on?
It's probably Robin Hood again.
Robin Hood?
Happens so often that the shock factor's
gone. I wonder what came today?
The “Geumdongyeorae” standing statue.
How'd you know that?
Are you really Robin Hood?
Joohyun, what happened?
Same method as before. Bumsang
verified that it's General Shovel's -
Mr. Heo's stolen item,
the “Geumdongyeorae” standing statue.
It seems he stole it yesterday
while we were chasing the wrong rabbit.
The first thing we need to do
is find out who was robbed.
It was stolen from
Professor Yongcheol Gong's home.
His father is Minister Jintae Gong.
I believe Chairman Jang
recently sent it to him as a bribe.
Oh my god...
Chohee.
We need to talk.
Yes, Chief?
It's not a big deal. I just wanted to tell
you about the afternoon schedule.
Can we discuss that later?
Sure.
Let's go.
Notice the cold war between them?
It started a few days ago,
and I don't know why.
What is it you want to talk about?
What else?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm apologizing for misunderstanding
and saying things carelessly.
The reason I got so mad was...
The reason why isn't so important.
I acted in a way that would cause
misunderstanding, so I'm sorry, too.
Are we done?
I don't know what to tell you, Minister
Gong. It was a gift with good intentions...
Yes, yes.
I'll pay you a visit next time.
The whole thing ended up putting you
in an awkward position.
I know. Only my items are getting
robbed. It seems I'm being targeted.
It definitely has to be Taesoo Heo.
What happened with Chairman Iwazaki?
He returned to Tokyo today.
Seeing how he didn't take the pottery,
he was very angry. What should we do?
Ohseong Group's fate lies in
Iwazaki's hands so we must take action.
Look into the matter.
Yes, sir.
When will the landscaping
project be done?
This chaotic atmosphere
is only adding to my stress.
Today's the last day, sir.
Okay. Leave.
Are you done?
Yes, we just have
to make some final touches.
Thank you for working hard
in this hot weather.
Here.
Thank you.
Then please wrap things up.
Yes, sir.
Call us for any future jobs.
Sure.
Hey, boy!
That's enough.
Let's wrap things up.
Here.
Thank you.
You're quite good at this.
Sis!
Why did you want
to meet here of all places?
I wanted to buy
my big sister some clothes.
And where would
you get the money for that?
I got paid today.
Jeez, you should
just use it for yourself.
Shall we take a look?
Oh, this is hot. This one.
What do you think? It's perfect for you.
You want me to wear this thing?
I think Bro would really
enjoy seeing you in this.
“Bro” again.
Sis, let's buy some clothes, go out to eat
and watch a movie. It's all on me.
I can have dinner,
but I can't watch a movie.
Another item arrived at the museum.
I think Dad intends to return
all the items before coming back to us.
Sis...
But at least he's alive, right?
Can I choose what I want?
Man, I'm full. It was even more
delicious since my brother's buying.
Was it good, Sis?
Yeah, it was really good.
What's this?
This? It's for Dad.
I realized I never gave
Dad any gifts before.
I just said things like I hate you.
So I bought this to give to him
when he comes back.
So it's for Dad?
Yeah. Wanna see?
He always wore a hat, remember?
So I bought this hat and some shirts.
And I even bought
some underwear for him.
Sis, what are you going to do
if he doesn't come back?
Gyoon.
If Dad doesn't come back after you do
all this, what are you going to do?
He's alive so don't worry about it.
And I just told you, another item
came to the museum this morning.
I don't know where he is but he's alive,
and we'll get to see him again.
That's Robin Hood's doing! Why do
you keep insisting Dad is Robin Hood?
Don't tell me you believe he's alive
because you think he's Robin Hood.
Not exactly,
but I still think Dad is...
Why would Dad do that?
Dad isn't Robin Hood!
If that's your reason for believing
he's alive, then he's dead.
Then Dad is definitely dead!
What? What did you just say?
What did you say!
Think about it, Sis.
If he were alive, why didn't
he come find us? Why didn't he call?
If he's such a coldhearted person,
he should've died a long time ago!
He should be dead!
What did you just say?
You wish he's dead?
How could you say that?
How could you say something like that?
Everyone's waiting for you
at the pub nearby. You know why?
To comfort me for the
disciplinary action I received?
Yes. Our regulations team
is known for our loyalty.
I've been thinking.
Chohee's being really rude.
Why?
I mean, you received a three-month
salary reduction for yesterday's mishap.
But she hasn't even called to console
you. How can she be so indifferent?
She's suffering the most right now.
Compared to that,
my punishment is nothing.
But Chief.
How do you understand
Chohee's feelings so well?
Do you like her?
No way. You're not
the type to cheat on me.
Anyway, Chief, I can't stand
the humiliation you had to go through.
Speaking of which,
about Chairman Jang...
Revenge? The badger game?
How'd he know?
Chief, you are clairvoyant!
Oh, Bumsang!
We're going for a drink.
Want to come?
No, I have something
to discuss with Chief Kang.
You saw Robin Hood?
I heard Minister Gong received
a present from Chairman Jang.
I ran into him when I went to check
if the gift was one of Heo's items.
And?
If Chohee's father were Robin Hood,
he'd be close to sixty now.
The person I ran into
was a young man.
A young man?
From what I could tell from his physique
and his movement. I'm positive.
Then Robin Hood is not Taesoo Heo.
I'm telling you this because
I thought you should know. Then...
Bumsang, you didn't tell
Chohee this, did you?
No. I only told you.
You're the one who can find
Taesoo Heo the quickest.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Your call has been forwarded...]
Why isn't he picking up?
It's already late in the night.
Is that you, Gyoon?
Bumsang.
Gyoon isn't home yet?
Yeah.
That kid.
He shouldn't stay out too late.
What brings you here?
The thing is... well...
Let's make up.
Make up?
We already apologized to each other,
so why are we making up again?
But you're not over it yet.
You're still upset with me, right?
I don't know about you,
but I can't stand this anymore.
I hate you giving me the stiff shoulder
and ignoring me. So let's make up.
Let's make up!
Did you come here to
yell at me or make up with me?
So do you want to make up or not?
Jeez, why are you yelling?
This is my house.
So you wanna make up, right?
Depends on your future behavior.
I'll be good.
You should've said so earlier.
Man, my throat hurts after yelling.
Get me something to drink.
What?
Something cold. It's hot today.
Just tell me to leave, instead of looking
at your watch every two seconds.
That's not it...
Fine, I'm leaving!
Hold on.
Hello, Uncle. By any chance...
You're with Gyoon?
Thank god.
Please comfort him well, Uncle.
Yes. Okay, Uncle.
Goodness...
You fought with Gyoon?
Yeah.
How could you fight with him
when he cares for you so much?
We didn't exactly fight.
He told me that you're all he has.
He did?
I was jealous. It must be good
sometimes, just the two of you.
But you have grandparents. I was
so jealous when I met them last time.
Yeah, I guess you'd be jealous of that.
Then this unwanted guest is leaving.
You're leaving?
Yeah. Bye.
Are you going to be okay
with Gyoon gone?
Jeez, of course I'll be okay.
Lock the door and check the windows.
Just in case, keep your cell nearby.
Jeez. No one's gonna
kidnap me, you know.
Who's worried about you? I feel bad for
Gyoon who constantly worries about you.
Go home and get some rest.
Okay, bye.
Lock the door.
All right, go on then.
Sleep tight.
Robin Hood is one thing,
my life is another.
I can't give up my vacation
to catch a thief, right?
Of course.
Where do you plan to go?
Guam, Saipan, Boracay, Bali?
Bali!
Bali?
Si.
Speak in Korean.
Joohyun, where do you want
to go for your vacation?
Well, let me tell you that where
isn't important, but with whom.
Are you saying you have
someone you want to go with?
Let me just say that
it's definitely not you two.
Hello.
Look who's here.
You're Chohee's brother, right?
What was your name?
Gyoon Heo... Gyoon Heo, right?
Yes.
My sister isn't in?
Chohee's away from the office
and at the museum.
Ah, is that so?
Thank you.
Hey, Gyoon!
Isn't he being a little strange? So young
and yet he's as listless as a sick puppy.
Yeah, strange.
Lil' Bro! Gyoon!
Here.
Thanks for last time.
What?
Sending your sister
to my alumni reunion.
We had a good date thanks to you.
Right...
Why are you so listless?
Because you fought with your sister?
How'd you know?
Gyoon.
No matter how upset you are at your
sister, you shouldn't stay out all night.
Your sister is a woman,
and it's your job to protect her.
Yeah, I shouldn't have done that.
Yeah. Apologize to her later.
Um, Bro?
Can I ask you something?
Shoot.
Do you think that
my father is Robin Hood?
Well, truthfully speaking, no.
Then who do you think it is?
I have no idea.
But I'm really curious.
If it's not your father...
who's returning the items
he stole to the museum? And why?
Isn't it weird?
I guess.
Then again, that's not
something I should ask you.
I'm at the CHA, and I have
things to discuss with Chief Noh.
It'll take about two hours. Okay.
Chief! I'm glad I ran into you.
Please come with me, hurry!
Why?
This is urgent! Please hurry!
I was working on a word document and had just reached the fifteenth page...
when it suddenly shut down.
And you lost your file?
Yes. Chief, can you help me?
I absolutely need that file.
Sure. I'll look if there's
a back-up file, so hold on a sec.
Let's see, what's the file name?
It's CPLJH.
CP... and then?
CPLJH. Cute, pretty,
lovely Joohyun. CPLJH.
Why are you laughing?
No reason.
So Chief, how's the search
for Chohee's father going?
Well, we're completely in the dark.
I was thinking over
the matter earlier while eating...
and I realized there's an inconsistency
about this Robin Hood case.
What's that?
Honggildong, Iljimae,
Janggilsan, Imggeokjeong.
If you look at Korea's good thieves,
they all have some things in common.
Great martial art skills,
preternatural swiftness.
In the movies,
they fly all over the place.
So?
So Chohee's father
must be quite old by now.
So can he jump over
walls like in the movies?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You know what? You have the potential
to be a great regulations team member.
Chief, what do you mean? Are you
implying I'm not a great member yet?
No. No,
that's not what I meant...
Here it is. Is this it?
Yeah, it is.
Chief, thank you so much!
So what's so important
that you'd write fifteen pages...
Wait, it's...
Your summer vacation plans?
Yeah. I can't spend my precious
vacation in just any way.
You're going to all these places?
Chief, why are you so interested
in my summer vacation?
You're not interested in joining
me on my vacation, are you?
Ah, no. That's not...
If so, I'm very flattered
but I want to tell you, in your dreams.
Your sister should be coming back soon.
Why don't you wait and go with her?
It's okay.
I'm going home to cook something good
and practice begging for forgiveness.
Hey, that's too spineless.
Is it?
She's here. Chohee!
Gyoon.
Do you know how long
he waited for you?
Why did you show up
without calling ahead?
Just ‘cause... I was hoping
you'd appreciate the surprise.
Gyoon knows how to handle women.
Why don't we just have dinner together?
It's time to head out anyway.
That's okay.
Bro.
Are you gonna keep calling him that?
Oh ho.
The “Geumdongyeorae” standing statue
was stolen from my house?
Who dares to say such nonsense?
Who dares to slander our family!
You just need to simply say yes or no
to whether you were robbed.
I told you,
we weren't robbed of anything.
As I'm sure you know well, my father
is a minister of the government.
As a government employee,
he would never touch a stolen good.
This is a conspiracy!
I see. Anyway, thank you
for your cooperation.
Are you guys even attempting
to arrest Robin Hood?
What do you mean?
I have a suspect in mind.
Who is that?
There's only one person
who could plot this. Bumsang Kim.
He lost his marbles after
becoming a national hero.
I'm positive my guess is right.
What a headache case this is.
Chief!
A cell phone registered
in Taesoo Heo's name has appeared.
Really? It's not just
someone with the same name?
Same ID number as Chohee's father.
It was registered in Incheon.
First, submit a request for
permission to track that number.
And don't tell Chohee before we're
absolutely sure about his location.
That's a given.
Bro, thank you
for the delicious meal today.
No problem. I had fun.
Since you're already here,
come in for another drink.
Another drink? That's enough.
Why?
Thanks for today.
Go on home, then.
I'm leaving, already.
And if you ever have another fight
with your sister, come to my place, okay?
I'll feed you and
give you a place to sleep.
Then where will you sleep?
I can curl up wherever. My place may
be small but it's big enough for you.
You call that small?
What?
Ah... I mean, I would never
imagine you to live in a small place.
I see.
Hurry on home.
Okay, see you tomorrow. Bye.
Bye.
- Let's go in.
- Okay.
I give up trying to stop you
from calling him “Bro.”
What's wrong with it?
It's starting to roll right off my tongue.
You should stop while I ask nicely.
Want me to kick your butt?
Sis, Bro seems like
a really good person.
I more or less agree that he's
a good person, but he's not your “Bro.”
So stop calling him that,
even as a joke.
Fine, fine.
I really like Bro...
I mean, Bumsang, but at the
same time I feel bad towards him.
You feel bad about what?
Huh? Just...
The point is that I like him.
How lame...
And I'm sorry about yesterday.
I shouldn't have said that about Dad.
I'm sorry, Sis.
So you know what you did wrong?
Did it hurt?
It's okay.
I'm sorry, too.
Hey, we're even now, okay?
I'm going to go change.
You should go wash up.
Go on.
'My place may be small,
but it's big enough for you.'
You call that small?
What?
Ah... I mean, I would never
imagine you to live in a small place.
I can't help thinking it's strange.
How can he just say that casually
when he's never been over to my place?
What the...
No way Gyoon is...
How's the Robin Hood
investigation going?
What?
Who does the regulations team
think is Robin Hood?
Robin Hood?
Do you think that
my father is Robin Hood, too?
Truthfully speaking, no.
Then who do you think it is?
Dongpal, answer me truthfully.
Do you remember me telling you seven
years ago to take care of Taesoo Heo?
I remember.
So is he sleeping
with the fishes or not?
Um, the thing is...
Did you take care of him or not?
I'm thinking they
probably did a clean job?
“They probably did?”
What do you mean?
The truth is, I ordered some
ambitious kids to take care of it.
They're known for their good work
so I'm sure things were taken care of -
Idiot! Why'd you make someone else do
the job when I told you to do it yourself?
You made me do it even though
Chairman Jang told you to do it yourself.
I was a fool to have trusted
you the responsibility.
I'm a fool, right?
Sir, shouldn't we find out what happened
before Chairman Jang kills us?
You think I don't know that?
Go bring me the guys
who did the job last time.
What do you plan to do?
They're gonna kill me.
I'm going to confirm things myself.
Alrighty! We're about
to leave right now.
Chief.
Yes?
Mr. Nah is nagging us to hurry and come
to the Youngbuk-dong excavation site.
As soon as I put this away.
Must we do this when the ground's
all muddy from the monsoon rain?
- Let's go.
- Chief!
We received permission to track Taesoo
Heo's phone. He's in Seogyo-dong.
Seogyo-dong?
Yes.
Then let's head there.
When can you get here?
The ground didn't fall in due to the rain.
Seems someone dug it.
Those bloodhounds. How'd they
know about this new excavation site?
When is the investigations
team getting here?
Okay. They said
they can't make it today.
What?
They said they're busy and
to take care of things ourselves.
Those jerks. What about Bumsang?
Why isn't he here yet?
I'll give him a call.
Hey, it's me.
Didn't you hear about the case?
What case?
Ah, I completely forgot.
You forgot? How can you skip out
on an excavation theft case?
Sorry, but I'm going to
need a couple more hours.
I have some important business.
Okay.
[I'll be there as soon as I'm done.]
All right, then. Hurry and come.
I wonder what he's up to now?
Come sit down.
Okay.
Have a drink.
You haven't been around much
these days. Have you been well?
I know. I thought you threw in
the towel and gave up on learning.
Threw in the towel?
I still have much to learn from you guys.
The guy who specializes in safes
seems to be missing in action.
Him? His wife's in the hospital
and he's nursing her. Isn't that sad?
He is? We should go on
a hospital visit sometime.
You're so considerate
for a young man.
Completely different from other
young people. Here, have a drink.
Um, Chohee?
Yeah?
It seems nothing important was stolen,
so can we leave after a cursory look?
Yeah, I think that could work.
Chohee, so you do
know how to cut corners.
But shouldn't we at least wait
for the excavation team?
I already gave the museum
and the CHA research team a call.
Wow, that was
unusually efficient of you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
What is it?
It's nothing. Let's go.
That was a good meal.
Let's go for another round. It's on me.
I can't. I have an important customer
coming later. How about you, Mister Kim?
Sure, I want to learn how to identify
signatures and seals from Mr. Jeong.
Of all the things
to get passionate about!
If you had decided to study academically,
you could've ended up a judge.
Bye. Let's go! Let's go!
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
What are you doing here, Bumsang?
We need to talk.
Ugh, I'm wiped out.
I'm so dead tired.
Why are you complaining?
We didn't even go very far today.
And you were so excited earlier today
about filling Chief Noh's shoes.
Things would be different if
it were official. If I were really chief...
In my opinion, I think Chohee
should be chief rather than you.
What!
Joohyun, what are you saying?
Take today, for example.
We came back early thanks to Chohee's
efficient decision-making and judgment.
Whichever way you see it,
Chohee should be the next chief.
Joohyun Wang! What did you say?
Chohee should what!
Calm down.
Chohee, did I say something wrong?
Ah, the thing is...
Let's discuss this later.
We should call the investigations team
and set a meeting time for tomorrow.
Okay, I'll give them a call.
Mr. Nah, your expression...
You're not mad, are you?
No. I'm not mad at all.
Why didn't those jerks in the
investigations team show up today?
They're tracking Taesoo Heo.
Chief, what did you just say?
His cell phone showed up on the radar in
Seogyo-dong. Chief Kang is tracking him.
This shows that he's definitely within a
200m radius, but how will we find him?
We have to try.
Hi, Chohee.
Chief, what's going on?
Did you find my father?
We're trying to right now.
Where are you?
I'll head over right now.
I understand how anxious
you must be, but leave this to us.
Chief.
We have enough men here,
so don't worry. Just prepare yourself.
Chief!
The back-up is here.
Okay.
I have to go.
I'll call you later.
Name's Taesoo Heo.
In his late fifties.
About five-seven in height
and always wears a hat.
He's within a 200m radius, but since
he's mobile, we need to find him quickly.
Here.
Chohee, just go home.
No, I'm fine.
Stop being stubborn and go home.
I'll drop you off.
Go home and calm your nerves.
Do you think this time it's really him?
Why is my heart pounding?
I hope it's him.
'Who are all those people?'
Who do you think?
All the men of our trade.
Middlemen, ex-thieves,
lock experts, safe experts.
And men like me who do legitimate work.
It's just a friendly get-together.
And who's the young guy? Who's he?
Who? Oh, Mister Kim?
Mister Kim?
We just call him that. You know we
don't customarily ask for real names.
He's a sharp kid who wants to join the
trade and diligently follows us around.
You teach him one thing and he figures
out ten. Everyone's amazed by him.
He's good enough to follow
in General Shovel's footsteps.
Why do you ask about him?
Are you okay?
I'm not sure.
I'm nervous and excited.
Want me to stay with you?
No, it's okay. I called Gyoon
so he should be home soon.
You've been through
a lot of heartache.
It wasn't that bad.
When I finally meet him,
I have so much I want to say.
I have so many questions, too.
But when I actually meet him,
I don't think I'll remember any of it.
Yeah.
Um, Chief?
Yeah?
If Chief Kang finds Dad today,
will he be immediately arrested?
Why do you ask?
I was hoping he'd be able
to come home for a warm meal.
I don't ask for anything else.
I just want to cook a warm meal for him.
I'll talk to Chief Kang.
Wait for my call.
No need to walk me out.
Did you see this man?
I'm not sure.
Thank you.
Chief!
He's not near the subway station.
We should head in the opposite direction.
He doesn't seem to be moving much,
so let's sweep the area one more time.
Dear lord. Okay.
Hold on, Officer!
Isn't that the man?
Hey, Gyoon. Where are you?
No, no news yet.
Yeah, hurry home.
What brings you here?
Is Gyoon home yet?
No. Why do you ask?
I just have some business with him.
Hey, your hand...
Oh, this?
I'm here from the museum.
We heard some relics were found.
Ah, yes. We're finding mostly pottery
and bowls. Shell we head over to the site?
Sure.
Why are the police here?
Some human remains were found.
- Really?
- Yes.
If he used Heo's information to make
a false account, where's the real Heo?
I've got bad vibes about this.
What if in addition to
a false cell phone account...
a fake passport was also used?
And that explains the entrance records?
It's possible.
Then the real Taesoo Heo
could be dead...
Jinguk, don't say that.
Look, let's not be pessimistic.
Let's start by finding out how that
man came to use Taesoo Heo's name.
Okay.
- And Officer Park, you...
- Yes?
Hold on.
This is Shiwan Kang.
You're meeting your father
for the first time in seven years...
with a band-aid on
your finger. How clumsy.
You're that excited?
I'm a bit antsy and nervous and stuff.
Everything will be fine, right?
Of course. Congratulations.
You're congratulating me
when I haven't even met him yet?
What should I do? The food's getting cold.
Should I clear the table?
[Chief Kang]
Yes, Chief?
Subtitles Provided by MBC America