Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
The standard for beauty
can't help but be subjective.
Of course there are some commonly accepted beautiful qualities.
Round shoulders, a supple and
curvy waist, and skin as smooth as silk.
But more important than these
is the impression made.
- To give off one's own personal feeling.
- Time to close the doors.
Roger.
The first exhibition room is all clear.
The second floor art gallery is all clear.
The special exhibition room is all clear.
The rear exit is all clear.
What kind of impression are
you getting? Does it look beautiful?
Yes.
What do you think?
I think it looks like
a perfect, authentic item.
A perfect, authentic item...
But this is...
a fake.
Then how do you define
a real, authentic item?
Something that is relatively
antique? Something expensive?
Or something
made by a famous artisan?
It's not easy to find an authentic item
that is beautiful, historical and rare...
all at the same time.
But everyone here today is in luck.
The item I'm about to show you
is a true diamond in the rough.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Hey!
Ah!
Grab him!
Go after him!
Hold on!
Ow!
Get down.
Aw, man...
Aw, man.
Ouch.
Are you manhandling me?
Are you? I'll remember your face.
It really hurts!
Good job.
As you can see,
the situation was handled perfectly.
With our museum's security system, you have absolutely nothing to worry about.
Director, the Buddha statue
has disappeared.
What?
Perfectly handled, eh?
That's all the time we have for
today's "Discovering Cultural Assets."
I'm your host Hwayoung Lee.
And I'm the art expert
Beomsang Kim. Good night.
Who are you?
Whom do you work for?
I'm Chohee Heo from the Cultural Heritage Administration's Cultural Assets
Crime Regulations Team.
Night After Night
Episode 1
Stay still.
It tickles. Do it gently.
Are there a lot?
Yeah, there are huge chunks. How
do you even manage to hear anything?
Oh my, oh my...
Gently!.
My neck already hurts like crazy.
Who told you to take those
security training exercises so seriously?
You're not exactly young anymore.
They said to do it
like it was the real deal.
Good for you. Does anyone even
notice your efforts? Will you get a raise?
As the thief, you're supposed to make everyone's life easier by getting caught.
At your age you don't even know how to behave properly in the public sphere?
Gyoon! I told you not to criticize my behavior.
Yes, Sis.
Come here. Put your
head here, it's your turn.
You're going to get an earful
when you get to work tomorrow.
Was that your first
security training exercise?
Were you intentionally
trying to screw us over?
Chief Kim, I already
apologized for her. Calm down.
How can I when we were embarrassed like that in front of the director?
And Chief Noh, your subordinate is like this because you coddle her all the time!
Explain yourself. Explain to me
why you caused such a ruckus!
I was just following
the security training guideline.
What?
Rule three of the guideline says
to try one's best in any given role...
to recreate a realistic situation in order to properly preempt all possible outcomes.
I just tried my best.
Hey, Chohee!
What? You're
quoting the guideline to me?
Excuse me.
Hello?
What? Got it.
It's a tip that Hwaja Ji
turned up in Insa-dong.
I'll listen to the rest
when I get back. I'm sorry.
Hey, hey!
Chief Kim...
"Discovering Cultural Assets," you say? That TV program is quite interesting.
The president is quite pleased
that our school is receiving attention...
and our image is improving
thanks to your efforts.
I haven't done much.
I'm just merely a lecturer.
Praising me is an insult to the professors who work so hard to advance the school.
You're way too humble
for your own good.
If anyone deserves an
official position here, isn't it you?
Not at all, Dean.
I'm nowhere near qualified enough...
I'm far too young and inexperienced
to take an official position here.
I'm not ready yet.
Do you really mean that?
Yes, I do.
I feel so relieved
that you said that.
The truth is, the
appointment for professorship....
has already gone to
your colleague, Yongchul Gong.
Excuse me?
[His father is a public official.
We have to consider that, don't we?]
So what if he's the son
of a government minister?
You know what
an idiot Yongchul is.
It makes no sense
to give him the position.
Oh, hello, sir.
It's been a while, Minju.
Frankly speaking, in what way
is he better than me?
Are either his research accomplishments or lecture evaluations better than mine?
Does he have anything other than
being born into the right family?
I'm hardworking, competent
and the students respect me.
So how could they choose
that scoundrel above me...
- Hello.
- Oh my!
Oh my goodness!
How could they make that
blockhead a professor? Am I wrong?
When someone's talking to you,
you're supposed to respond, dear friend.
Do you really want
to continue living like that?
Like what?
Pretending to be
nice, humble and cool.
Aren't you tired of being
the master of pretenses?
You're so naïve.
There's only one
way to fight against...
public powers that try to ruin
my bright future, like Yongchul's father.
Appearing to be an excellent,
perfect and faultless person.
Is there such a person?
No, hence just appearing to be.
That's the strategy of my life.
What's the use of carrying that around?
Take notes. Do you have a pen?
You're spewing
nonsense. Gotta go.
Hey, where are
you going? I'm not done.
Can you give me an autograph?
Sure. Busy, huh?
Let's talk next time! Bye.
Your name is...
Hwaja Ji!
You should leave the regulations team and join our investigations team.
You're so talented at catching criminals, why limit yourself to art thieves?
I was going to wait for you guys,
but she was getting away.
Isn't this better than losing her?
Besides, she's not an art thief. She's an international smuggler of cultural assets.
Leave the arresting to us.
Acting so recklessly might get
you stabbed by a scary guy like me.
See this? Got this from the right-hand man of the Bendengee crime family.
It hurt.
If a you get a scar like this, people will think that you went through childbirth.
Take it down a notch,
all right, Ms. Heo?
Her spandex outfit
yesterday was killer...
The security guys were drooling
and talking about getting her digits.
Do they know anything
about her personality?
If they knew,
they wouldn't say anything...
Don't take it to heart, Chohee.
They didn't mean it in a bad way.
Are you okay?
Yes.
There's a joint meeting between the regulations and investigations teams.
Collect the relics and go on ahead.
Okay.
Good job, Chohee.
I'm so tired, but there's
still a ton of work left.
Chohee!
Yes?
The Hwaja Ji problem
taken care of?
Yes.
This is so incredibly like her. Why catch
a criminal we've chased for over a year...
right when it's time
to go home for the day?
And all by herself, too.
Going to earn all the honors by herself?
She doesn't have
a collective mindset at all.
I don't see what's wrong? She's pretty impressive. She tries hard and does well.
So what? She loses out to you in personality, beauty and education level.
High school dropout versus
a person who studied abroad in Japan.
Sangho, the first time you saw Chohee you said she was totally your type.
Your preference in women
has changed a lot.
It changed a long time ago. In the
20th century it was the glamorous type...
but in the 21st century
it's the innocent type like Joohyun.
We have to prepare
for the meeting, so hurry up.
Yes, sir.
What's Chief Noh's deal?
Why does he always coddle only Chohee?
Isn't it obvious from the way they always leave our dinner meetings together?
Are you two
gossiping right now?
I absolutely hate gossip.
Excuse me.
Don't gossip. Joohyun!
Yes, sir, it's me.
I'm on my way right now.
Yes, yes.
I'll see you soon.
"Where there is a will, there is a way." What excellent calligraphy.
I heard you were punted aside
for the professorship appointment?
What? Oh, yes...
I met your school's
dean the other day.
When I heard Minister Gong's son
was appointed, I gave him my two cents.
I told him not to regret it
when some other school lures you away.
Speaking of which, what do you
think about my helping you out a bit?
Have you ever heard of the two
national treasures that disappeared?
Are you talking about the items
lost during the Korean War?
National treasure no. 372, a blue vase with a lotus-arabesque design...
along with no. 413, a blue-white porcelain bowl of a chrysanthemum design...
was said to be lost or destroyed during the war and removed from the official list.
There was no evidence to back the theory that the owner took the vase to Japan.
People continued to search fruitlessly after its removal from the list in 1962.
Through Hwaja Ji
who was arrested today...
we've verified that Ichihiro Tanaka in Japan currently possesses the vase.
Are you saying it's authentic?
That's for you to decide.
Ah, right.
Since the news reached the chairmen
of Dongsan Group and Hyunjae Group...
the chance
of it being real is high.
But I don't trust
anyone else other than you.
If is it authentic,
what will you do?
The Cultural Heritage Administration
will go and retrieve the item.
That would be like
the blind daring of a fledgling.
The criminal investigations team will go. We'll definitely bring the item back.
I wish we could do that, but unfortunately we don't have the right to do so.
Since it's private property now, international law forbids us to recover it.
What a loss!
Our objective lies elsewhere.
This guy joined forces
with a domestic crime organization...
the Makdae Family and one of the three great yakuza families in Japan, Ryusekai.
He goes back and forth between Korea and Japan, smuggling cultural assets.
Known only as Mr. Kim,
we know neither his face nor his name.
But he has been putting out
feelers in order to buy the vase...
and he has contacted Hwaja Ji.
I don't care about the cost,
as long as the item is authentic.
I want it before
someone else gets a hold of it.
Wouldn't we be able to arrest him
if we asked the Japanese police for help?
Just arresting
Mr. Kim is not enough.
We need to take this opportunity
to round up even the accomplices.
Our ultimate goal is to acquire a complete family tree of the smugglers...
who are cooperating
with the crime organizations.
A complete round-up, you say...
For this mission, we ask the CHA
to dispatch one officer to Japan with us.
It should be someone
fluent in Japanese. Then...
I recommend Chohee Heo.
Chohee, can you do it?
Can you do it?
I will try my best.
Hanako Suzuki will
come looking for you.
She's an antiques dealer, and apparently we're not the only ones she contacted.
Be careful.
Hanako Suzuki...
Welcome.
I heard Hanako Suzuki made a reservation here for me...
Your name, please.
Bumsang Kim.
Please come this way.
Ah, one more person
will come in the evening.
She's already here and waiting.
Already?
Hello. I'm Hanako Suzuki.
How long has she been
using the name Hanako Suzuki?
About fifteen years? But not many
people know that Hwaja Ji and...
the famous Japanese antiques dealer Hanako Suzuki are one and the same.
The problem is whether Hwaja Ji
gave us all the information she has.
Then if she left anything out,
Chohee could be in danger.
Our team is staking out nearby
so there shouldn't be any problems.
If I had known,
I would have gone instead.
At least then
I wouldn't be so worried.
I understand how you feel,
but Chohee is a veteran at this.
She'll do just fine,
so don't worry.
Yes, I agree.
By the way, you're fluent in Japanese, right? Can you help me with something?
Oh, fo' sure I can.
An important fax is going to come from Japan. Can you tell me when it arrives?
Yes, sir.
Looks totally slick.
She has an hourglass figure.
Thirty-two inches, B cup, without a doubt.
He looks really familiar...
I'm well aware of your reputation,
Mr. Kim, and it's an honor to meet you.
Do you know me?
You're so famous in this circle,
how could I not know you?
Of course I know you, you thief.'
What an honor.
The TV appearances paid off.
When can I see the vase?
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
I forgot momentarily...
Um, I heard you were
quite fluent in Korean.
‘Wh - what?'
Ah, Korean...
I can speak it a little.
Your Japanese is so fluent,
I mistook you for a Japanese person.
You flatter me.
Can I see the item today?
I'm sorry, but the owner
is on a business trip.
He'll be back the day after
tomorrow. I'm so very sorry.
Business trip?
Until the day after tomorrow?
Is she bluffing?'
Stop doubting
and accept it, you jerk.
It can't be helped. I'll just spend
the time exploring the nearby area.
I will be your tour guide.
I don't want to be a bother.
It's not a bother at all.
Making sure that you don't experience any discomfort is part of my job as well.
I will be your guide.
If it's all right with you, then thank you. Ah, I'll be right back.
Why does she insist on being my guide? Does she have an ulterior motive?
Is she interested in me?
Ah, my popularity
is international, isn't it?
I came here to work, not play.
Bumsang Kim? The guy from TV?
No wonder he looked so familiar.
A TV personality
is a thief as well?
Your jacket.
Just as I thought.
No, let me.
Thank you.
Oh, by the way...
Yes?
What perfume do you use? The scent is, how should I put it, tantalizing.
It's... well...
It's cucumber
scented soap, you jerk.
Mr. Kim~
I definitely heard it was
room seven. What happened?
A woman named Hanako
reserved it in my name.
That's correct,
but Mr. Kim is already here.
I'm Mr. Kim,
so whom are you talking about?
Let me check once more.
Ah, hello? What?
Hanako was arrested?
Ah, sir, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize there were two reservations made by the name of Kim.
Sir?
Excuse me, aren't you Mr. Bumsang Kim from "Discovering Culture Assets?"
You are, right?
Get an autograph!
Can we get an autograph?
Ah, sir, would it be too much to ask if you could come look at some pottery with us?
Excuse me?
Sure, why not?
It's not a very hard thing to do.
Thank you.
Let's go, then.
Hello, Chief?
Bumsang Kim? He's Mr. Kim?
Yes, I didn't expect Mr. Kim
to be such a famous person.
Be careful not to get caught
until he contacts some accomplices.
I don't think he has
caught on yet, so don't worry.
Ah, did you ask the owner
Ichihiro Tanaka for his cooperation?
Turns out he's part of the yakuza. And he's extremely good friends with Hanako.
So much for that. I could be in trouble
if I get caught pretending to be Hanako.
As soon as we get his picture, I'll send it to you, so try not to run into him.
Mr. Kim, what do you think
about this one? Is it okay?
Anyone with an expert eye
for pottery would know.
It's an excellent blue and white vase.
Fifty thousand dollars is far too cheap.
This is worth 50 thousand dollars?
That would be a complete rip-off.
A rip-off?
What are you talking about?
That's one of the
cheaper prices in our store.
The piece this man here is buying
is worth 1.5 million dollars.
A 1.5 million dollar vase...
Wow, that's amazing.
May I take a look at it?
I'm sure just looking at it
is not a problem.
Though I'm not sure
you'll know anything just by looking.
Koreans may be good at making pottery, but we're the expert appraisers.
Ah! Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
I'll repay the 1.5 million dollars.
But only if this vase
is an authentic piece of art.
Wh - what?
You manage such a huge store...
and you don't know what color the bottom of an authentic vase should be?
Let me explain.
It's normal for pottery
baked a long time ago...
to become brown without shine
and luster due to natural oxidization.
But a replica would remain a shiny,
deep brown without any changes.
This is one hundred percent fake.
Oh, that's cute!
Chohee is a veteran at this.
She'll do just fine, so don't worry.
Sure, she's a veteran.
A veteran at causing scandals.
Why isn't this fax coming?
You were invited
to that man's house?
Yes. He keeps insisting
that I stay a night at his house...
and I feel bad
repeatedly refusing.
Since I was just going to rest today,
it's okay, right? I'll see you tomorrow.
Let's go.
Um...
I'm sorry if I'm causing
an inconvenience by tagging along.
Not at all.
Women are always welcome.
Is that so?
Goodness. Why does she keep following me? Does she like me that much?
Ah, I almost forgot
to introduce myself.
My name is Ichihiro Tanaka.
Ichihiro Tanaka?
What is your name?
This is Hanako Suzuki.
Hanako Suzuki? An antiques dealer I know is also named Hanako Suzuki.
That Hanako is
an antiques dealer, too?
She's quite famous in that line of work.
You've never heard of her?
Um, you're talking about Hanako
who lives in Kyoto, right?
Oh, you know her?
Yes, I know her.
I've met her a couple of times.
Wasn't she very well known
at the Gogirae auction?
Hanako means "flower child." I think it fits you more than my friend Hanako.
You're very beautiful, Ms. Hanako.
Ah, we're here.
Welcome.
What do you mean
you're at Tanaka's house right now?
It sort of happened.
[What are you going to do if they
catch on that you're not Hanako?]
I fibbed that we just happen to have
the same name, so I think it's okay.
What do you mean, it's okay?
Chohee, I want you out of there now.
Leave Mr. Kim behind
if you must. Now!
I can't leave him behind.
I'll leave with him tomorrow, okay?
Bye, Chief.
Chohee! Chohee!
Chief, what happened?
Change of plans.
Forget the accomplices. We're going to arrest Mr. Kim first thing in the morning.
Officer Cho! Contact Japan and
have them stake out Tanaka's house.
Yes, sir.
Joohyun, sorry but can you find me
the first flight out tomorrow?
You're going to go yourself?
What's your identity?
You've been
deceiving me all this time?
Ha, you may have deceived me,
but you can't deceive this sword.
Mr. Kim?
Mr. Kim, wonderful.
It was like watching a movie.
You've just learned it now,
but your posture is very good.
Not at all.
Thank you for allowing me the honor of touching an authentic Masamune sword.
Now that Ms. Hanako is here,
shall we go take a look?
What?
Ah, Mr. Tanaka offered to show us
the pottery he has collected.
What if he offers to show us the national treasure, the blue vase? What do I do?
I also have in my possession
a very valuable vase.
It's an authentic item hard to find
even in the Korean National Museum.
You also have vases?
What kind of design...
Ms. Hanako!
Are you awake now?
Here, sit up.
I'm sorry.
It seems I've overworked you.
No. I've caused you
a lot of trouble today. I'm sorry.
It's fine. Mr. Tanaka said he'd show us the vase tomorrow, so get some rest tonight.
- Mr. Kim?
- Ms. Hanako?
Please, go ahead.
No, you first.
Ah, the thing is...
I forgot to tell you.
The owner wants to meet you
first thing tomorrow.
Really? What happened
to the business trip?
Ah, I'm sure there's no other reason than that he felt bad about making you wait.
Well, the sooner
I meet him, the better.
What were you going to say?
Ah, it wasn't very important.
Pleasant dreams.
Crazy bastard!
Ah, that last line...
was very cool.
Ha, when we make it
out of here tomorrow, you're dead.
"Pleasant dreams," my butt.
Ugh, this is so stuffy.
I was crazy to put this on. Ugh, ugh.
Isn't that a
Danwon Hongdo Kim original?
What is this?
They're all from Korea.
What are all these
valuable pieces doing here?
Now where is that vase?
Mr. Kim, Mr. Kim!
We found the item.
Yeah? Who has it?
Ichihiro Tanaka. He's a member
of the Tashiokumi yakuza family.
Tanaka?
Where does he live?
Figures, the vase wouldn't be
so carelessly protected.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Dad, don't go.
Dad!
Dad...
Don't go.
Dad!
Don't go, don't go.
Tanaka sure is a piece of work.
Thinking to put this good-luck pole here.
Who is it?
Maybe I shouldn't have said
that last line so soon.
I mean, after all, Hanako followed me
all the way here. Was I too indifferent?
No, no. Sometimes women are
turned off by too much attention.
There's always tomorrow.
Ah, that feels good.
Ack!
I'm sorry, ma'am!
What the heck am I doing?
Where did it go?
Ah, seriously!
What is this? This is crazy.
Oh my!
Ms. Hanako?
M - Mr. Kim?
The Japanese weather
is very hot, no?
Why are you in
the hot springs if it's so hot...
That's what I'm saying.
This is driving me crazy.
And I was going
to let things be tonight.
But if Hanako's going to throw herself at me, it wouldn't be polite to do nothing.
Look here. I know
what it is that you want.
Huh?
I know what you want.
Oh my!
- Are you okay?
- Are you crazy?
What do you want?
What are you trying to pull?
Crazy bastard! Psycho! Pervert!
What a crazy pervert.
Darnit, what's going on?
Wait til you're arrested tomorrow.
That'll be the end of you, Mr. Kim!
Oh my, pervert.
I can't believe it!
What? Pervert? Psycho?
Who's the psycho here?
She's the one who followed me here because she likes me. Darnit.
Hello, thirty-two B cup,
what are you doing here?
Mr. Kim, hand that here.
Ah, what is this...
What bad luck.
And what Japanese woman buys her underwear from Korean infomercials?
Hold on.
Hanako Suzuki? An antiques dealer I know is also named Hanako Suzuki.
I've met her a couple of times. Wasn't she very well known at the Gogirae auction?
Hanako Suzuki.
Something smells fishy.
Right, kitty?
Do you smell it, too?
Chohee?
Yes, I'll get out now. Yes.
Why are you so startled?
I had to borrow some make-up since
I came here empty-handed yesterday.
Yesterday I was quite rude.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's not a big deal.
Let's pretend it never happened.
Thank you for understanding.
Shall we go?
Ah, sure.
Mr. Kim,
not that way. This way.
I should say goodbye
to Mr. Tanaka.
I already asked for his understanding, explaining how we're so busy and all.
Still, he even offered
to show us a very valuable vase.
Mr. Kim, we don't have
much time, so we should hurry.
No matter how busy we are,
shouldn't we at least take a look...
at the blue vase with
the lotus-arabesque design?
What?
What are you talking about?
I suggest you stop pretending
to be a Japanese woman.
Didn't you know?
The real Hanako Suzuki is Korean.
And according to my sources,
she was already arrested.
Then who would you be?
What is your identity?
Oh, Mr. Tanaka!
Trying to run off now, are we?
Did you forget that this is the home of
Tanaka, close friend of the real Hanako?
Mr. Kim! Over here!
I'll be right there!
Let's continue our talk a little later.
Come on, Ms. Fake Hanako.
Can't you go by yourself?
Nice crib.
Here we are.
It's quite an honor
to show the vase to you two.
This is the blue vase
with the lotus-arabesque design.
Isn't it beautiful?
Amazing.
This hue, this pattern,
it couldn't be more perfect.
It's perfect, isn't it?
Yes, perfectly... copied.
What?
This is a replica.
Boys! Your target is the antiques
dealer Tsukimoto in Kyoto.
Go crush him!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Kim, I don't know how to repay you.
If there's anything you need, tell me.
I merely told you a fake was a fake. There's no need for you to thank me.
You've helped me twice so far. If I don't repay you, I can't call myself a real man.
A true samurai repays his debt.
Anything at all I can do for you.
Really?
Of course.
If you want, I can even
assassinate a person for you.
Is there someone you'd like
to have knocked off?
If that's the case...
I'd like to have that.
My Sumire?
What are you up to,
asking for the cat?
Shut your trap, Ms. Fake Hanako.
As you requested, I've packed up
all the items that Sumire uses.
This is Sumire's toothbrush,
hairbrush, and food bowl.
Excuse me.
A guest has been waiting
for quite a while.
A guest? Who?
He says his name is Mr. Kim.
He came here on Hanako Suzuki's introduction to look at an item.
Unfortunately, we'll have
to say our farewells now.
Mr. Kim, Ms. Hanako,
please take care.
Sumire, take care.
Then shall we continue
our conversation from earlier?
This isn't just any item, is it?
Look at that.
You have quite an eye.
Please have a seat.
So you've come to see the blue vase, have you? It's a rare and good item.
I came to buy a different item.
Is this a valuable item?
Well, it's a fairly good porcelain bowl.
Hey!
Mr. Tanaka,
wait a moment, please.
The blue and white porcelain bowl
with a chrysanthemum design.
The rumor that one of the lost treasures was at Mr. Tanaka's house wasn't a lie.
The problem is that it wasn't
the vase. It was this bowl.
So tell me.
Who are you?
Let me ask you one thing.
Are you Mr. Kim from Ryusekai?
What kai?
Ryusekai.
Dunno what that is, but I think the
Mr. Kim you're looking for is inside.
I think you're right.
Hey, where are you going?
Tell me who you are first!
I bet she's an Aries.
Sumire, this bowl is
far too beautiful for you to eat out of.
If you don't want to die, run.
What is she babbling about?
Get them!
Wait!
Stay back.
Stop it!
Stay there.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Darnit, I guess he found out?
What the? Why are
you taking off your clothes?
It's hard for me
to run in this, all right?
Oh my!
What do we do?
You asked for the cat because you knew the bowl was a valuable item, didn't you?
You thief.
How can you just steal someone else's precious property like that?
I thought
you were giving it to me...
So, you think you're justified in trying
to walk out with an item worth millions?
Wasn't it just
the cat's food bowl to you?
Either way, it's mine.
You mean it's your cat's.
What?
Everything is given a value
according to how cherished it is.
But you didn't even value
this bowl as much as the cat.
Isn't that why
you gave it to me for free?
That's because I didn't know
how expensive it was.
Look at it
from my point of view.
That bowl is just
a dollar sign to you, isn't it?
But to us, it isn't.
To us, it's a national treasure.
It signifies the history, the memories and the pride that our ancestors left to us.
Our?
Our...
I'm talking about mankind here!
I thought the bowl was better off in the hands of someone who appreciates it...
not a man who couldn't
even recognize its beauty.
That's why I took it without
saying anything. That's all.
Please cherish it like it deserves to be. After all, it survived hundreds of years.
Wait!
You can't just leave.
Give me back Sumire.
I'm not
taking it back for free.
Everything is given a value according
to how much it's cherished, right?
The amount that
I cherish Sumire is...
equal to this.
Are we nearly there?
Almost.
Chohee, where are you?
What do you mean
it's the wrong Mr. Kim?
If it's not Bumsang Kim,
then who is Mr. Kim?
Tanaka has bad manners.
He has a horrible temper.
I thought we were
heading to an early grave.
Excuse me a moment.
Who here is Mr. Kim?
Um... Run.
What's with the bad karma today?
I'm sorry for everything, Mr. Kim.
Why the sudden polite tone?
What are you
going to do with the bowl?
What do you think? I'm going to
take it home and look at it every day.
I'm going to look at it
again and again until I'm sick of it.
Have you considered
donating it to the country?
Say what?
Do - nate.
Donate?
It's a cultural asset. A national treasure! Shouldn't everyone be allowed to see it?
Look here. I'm as far from
being patriotic as you can get.
I have this philosophy.
One can't share one's lover -
it can't be shared, right?
Likewise, beauty cannot
be shared with others.
And our relationship ends here,
Ms. Hanako. Then, sayonara.
Donate, my butt.
All right, fine. Let's see how far
that crappy philosophy gets you.
What a crappy guy.
And I had just managed
to tie it all together.
I can't go outside
like this. Darnit.
[The number you have called...]
Why isn't he picking up?
Hey, Jonggyu, I'm back.
I picked up something fabulous in Japan.
Come to my house
as soon as you get off work.
Huh, was
Brad Pitt on my flight?
We love you, Bumsang Kim!
Let's protect and
preserve our cultural assets!!
What in the world is going on?
What led to your success
in bringing it back?
Did you have any difficulty
I'm Chohee Heo from the
Cultural Heritage Administration.
I sincerely thank you
for bringing back a national treasure.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America