Episode 4
We were robbed. Robbed!
You think there's some kind of show here for you to watch? Get out of here!
If you have nothing better to do,
go home!
Why's he all pissy at us?
Stop your muttering, you trio.
Anyway, you missed going to
your alumni association.
Who cares about that?
Why'd this cursed thief create
this ruckus by robbing the CHA?
This is driving me up the wall.
What is that fool doing now?
Let's go!
-Do your job already.
- Shouldn't you be working?
Punk...
Chief!
Yeah?
We looked up the license plate number Chohee gave us. It's a stolen car
As expected.
I don't know how she managed to see the number in that kind of situation.
Oh, and here's the list...
...of suspects according to previous convictions of the same crime.
Good. Report the car
as an accessory to robbery...
...and check the surrounding traffic cameras for any possible shots.
Yes, sir.
Officer Cho...
...after getting the witness statements, have a montage of the suspect drawn.
As soon as that's done, call me.
Goodness, the CHA guys are
all screwed. Completely.
Chief Kang.
Yes, Chief Noh.
Sorry you had to come all the way here.
The main office is in an uproar.
The stolen item is
really the “Bihaedangjib?”
Yes, I'm positive since Bumsang is
the one who identified it.
It had occurred to me that it might be
time for that to resurface...
What? You have
prior knowledge about it?
Ah, where's Chohee?
This is definitely breaking news.
What foolhardy fella dared to
steal from the CHA?
Maybe he had an accomplice
on the inside?
What are you thinking about?
Chohee Heo.
She can't be the accomplice.
She helped to chase the thief.
No, not that.
There's something strange about her.
No matter how much
she wants to catch the thief...
how could she risk her life like that?
She's clearly a hardcore patriot,
inside and out.
One out of a hundred
government workers is like her...
...practically sacrificing their lives.
You work for the government. You're telling me you understand that mindset?
You said women should be
experienced, not understood.
Stop trying to understand her. Experience.
Jonggyu Oh!
Yes?
Jonggyu Oh?
That's me.
Mr. Oh, I need your witness statement.
Sure, sure.
Follow me.
Policemen make me so nervous, like
I'm guilty of a crime I didn't commit.
Right, the recording.
I need to take care of that.
Why didn't you tell me about the “Bihaedangjib?”
I'm sorry, Chief.
You thought you'd be troubling me?
Look here, kid,
didn't I tell you not to think that?
How can I not?
You're the one who hired me.
I didn't pull strings to get you in.
You got in based on your skill.
What's the problem?
Chief.
Straighten your shoulders and do your work. Don't worry. Do you understand?
Ack!
What's with the serious convo?
Is he really mad?
No, it's nothing.
Oh, how are your injuries?
Huh? Oh, this is nothing.
Anyway, let's resolve our unfinished business, shall we?
What unfinished business?
Hold on.
Yes, Chief.
The security camera in front of
the Preservation Science Lab is broken?
Yes, I'll check it out right now. Okay.
Where are you going?
Erase the recording already, will you?
Recording. So the unfinished business is erasing the recording?
What else? After all I did for you,
the least you can do is erase it!
Of all the... I can erase it later.
Get your priorities straight. Get out!
Later when? Hey!
I tried to be a gentleman about this, but...
Ah, Mr. Son, it's me. Do a background check on Chohee Heo for me.
No, small stuff, too. Any bribery cases, favors she fulfilled for a cost. All of it.
Why are you asking me
for something like that?
You think I'm a private eye?
I'm sorry about that.
Where were we?
I need you to ask around for
a man skilled in restoring books.
Someone top-notch.
That man would have to be
able to keep secrets, right?
Need you ask?
With an incident of this scale,
I predict a lot of heads will roll.
First, the head of security will have to do more than hand in a written apology.
Same goes for the head of
the Preservation Science Lab, no?
You think Chief Noh might be
forced into early retirement?
Early retirement?
Why should our regulations team
be blamed for anything?
If the book is found it'll be okay,
but what if it's not?
Who else will be the scapegoat?
Then there will be an opening
in the chief's position.
Gosh! You think we'll be safe
when Chief Noh is blamed?
We won't be, will we?
I guess we won't be safe.
I'm not going to take it lying down
if our team is blamed in the least.
What do you plan to do?
Let's think of something
over some coffee.
Coins. Joohyun, I have a ton
for the vending machine.
I'm doing things I've never done before,
all thanks to Chohee.
Now where did she hide it...
Whew. Now how to erase it...
Dear lord, she's doing
all the CHA's work on her own. Okay.
Did you do something wrong? What's your ulterior motive in buying this meal?
Nothing!
I'm buying simply because meals
must be eaten even when busy. Right?
Gosh!
Stop glaring at me when I felt sorry that you obviously pulled an all-nighter.
A thank you would be
the proper response.
Thank you so very much. Happy?
By the way, doesn't your father mind that you stay out all night?
Then again, you're past the age of
being nagged by your father.
I don't want to talk about my father.
So stop.
Yeah?
But he should at least say something about you living with some guy.
I do live with a guy,
but that guy's my younger brother.
Younger brother?
Not a yakuza member?
The only yakuza member I've seen in real life is Mr. Tanaka. Satisfied now?
What about the rumor that you and Chief Noh are more than co-workers?
I knew it, it's a rumor.
Chief Noh is a father figure to me!
Keep saying stuff like that,
and karma will bite you in the butt.
Watch that temper.
The rumors are rampant because of your needlessly fiery temper.
Let me advise you sincerely. Don't live so inflexibly. Slamming on tables and all.
Look here.
Yes?
It's easy to spot the faults of others...
...but even easier to turn
a blind eye to one's own.
Keep that in mind, okay?
Thanks for the meal.
What the? What's her problem now?
How could the CHA of
all places get robbed? How?
How could you let thieves
into our home? Huh?
Find the stolen book before the reporters get a wind of this. Understand?
What are you doing?
Get the meeting started!
Why the hell is he yelling
at the investigations team?
And you think we're here
because we deserve this?
I'm sorry. It took a while
to draw up the suspect montage.
Gyucheol Seo. He's a middle boss
of the Makdae Crime Family...
...with three convictions under his belt.
He's also currently wanted for
charges of violence and larceny.
The Makdae family? Isn't that
Mr. Kim's domestic crime partner?
Mr. Kim again? That bastard.
Excuse my language.
We suspect he played a hand
in the theft, but we have no evidence.
And we lost track of him after his release so looking for him is a problem.
Any ideas?
May I make a suggestion?
At the time of theft, the “Bihaedangjib” was in the middle of being restored.
In other words, if the thieves want to
sell it at a top price...
...they have to prepare the restoration material and hire an expert to do it.
It was printed on paper...
...reserved for palace use, beaten and bleached several times.
There are currently
only two places in the nation...
...that can reproduce this paper.
And there are only a handful of places...
...that can expertly restore it, including the Preservation Science Lab.
This could be a good starting point.
Yes.
Joohyun, I didn't mess up
in front of the director, did I?
Smart, very smart. Super smart!
You had quite the silver tongue in there with the director as your audience.
If this is a fight you're picking,
leave me out. I'm busy today.
Doing what? You don't have any lectures or your TV appearance today.
I have some restoration work of my own.
Remember? How you ruined
my relationship at the TV station?
I can take care of
that restoration work for you.
Instead, help me check out
those private restoration places...
...you were talking about.
Um, no.
C'mon. Why you gotta be like that? Ah, the recording. I'll release it to the world.
Oh, right, the recording.
Speaking of that, go ahead.
I think I've fulfilled my duty
as the advisory member.
Mr. Kim.
Yes, Director Kang.
I'm so proud of you.
You are truly a pillar of the CHA.
Oh, sir, your praise is too grand.
Chief Noh, Mr. Kim will take an active part of the “Bihaedangjib” investigation.
Won't you, Mr. Kim?
Of course, of course I will.
Would you be able to help Chohee check out the different restoration places?
Since you're the expert and all.
Yes, I can. I will go with her.
Don't worry.
Then shall we go, Mr. Kim?
Let's go. We're off.
This is a conspiracy.
You guys are all in on it, aren't you?
Conspiracy? Well, the director is
a closet conspiracy theory nut, I think.
I don't know. Really. I haven't seen Gyucheol is over two months.
You should tell us the truth
while we're asking nicely.
Pissing this man off has led
some men to dire consequences.
So tell us while he's still calm.
Gosh, I can't tell you what I don't know. This is so frustrating.
You're making it hard for me to mediate. Really, you are.
So you won't tell us
when we're asking nicely?
See this? The Bendengee Family's right-hand man gave me this.
You think this is my only scar?
You're gonna tell me the info or not?
That's enough!
Hurry and tell him. Tell him!
I don't know where he is. And I wouldn't tell you even if I knew. He's my son.
Hold on. So can we assume
that you do know where he is?
Well... I could know. Or not.
C'mon. Which is it? It's one or
the another. You can't be both!
You bastard.
Gyucheol, see how these men
mistreat me because of what you did...
Uh, ma'am. Please calm down, ma'am. Calm down.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
So you haven't had any new business lately? No new deliveries?
Yes, that's right.
Can we see your most recent
inventory for deliveries?
The inventory? Sure, here you go.
This is our account book.
Oh! Help! Help!
What the... What are you
going to do about this mess?
Do you know how expensive this stuff is? What are you going to do? Huh?
No matter how much money is offered,
I don't work on books that appear shady.
That's my work ethic.
So you haven't had any new restoration work come up in the past few days?
None. By the way, sir,
I've always wanted to meet you.
If you're free today, how would you
like to go grab some coffee?
My schedule's pretty free today.
Ha ha, you jokester. What about the other date you made for today?
Do you plan to teleport back and forth?
You really can't stand to see me
get any action, can you?
We're in the middle of official business. Come along, we don't have much time.
Do you like me, or something?
What?
I mean, it's weird how you keep ruining my chances with other women.
Oh lord...
Right? You pretend to dislike me,
but secretly you like me, right?
No wonder you keep using the excuse
of work to be with me all the time.
That's right, I like you. No, I love you. So...
Stop screwing around and let's get back to work, Bumsang. All right?
What? We have more places to visit?
Three more.
What? Three more places.
I dug my own grave
when I mentioned restoration experts.
It's been over five years
since I stopped restoring books.
You were quite famous in the frame mounting business. Why did you stop?
You know how things are. It's hard work.
My eyesight was getting worse
and money wasn't great.
I see.
That painting's beautiful.
Yes, I restored that
when I was still working.
That's all, I think.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Scratch this place off the list. Whew,
we still have two more places to go.
There's no need for that.
This is the place.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you smell anything
while you were inside?
Smell what? I'm not sure.
Your nose for decorative purposes only?
I could definitely smell
the boiling amur corktree oil.
Amur corktree oil? What's that?
It's material used when restoring books in the traditional manner.
It dyes the paper
the same color as old books...
...and effectively protects against moths.
You know the “Mugucheong'wang Daedaranikyeong,” right?
It's the oldest book in existence in Korea that was printed with a wooden press.
That managed to last over 1200 years...
...because it used dye
from the amur corktree.
So you're sure you smelled this oil
inside that house?
Yes. Isn't it strange that his house smells of it when he supposedly quit working?
So even if it's not the “Bihaedangjib”...
...he's probably restoring
something illegal.
Exactly.
Man, I'm good. At times like these,
I can't help but pat myself on the back.
What are you doing?
Call Chief Kang already.
Ugh, my arms are sore. Gyucheol Seo's mom is really intimidating, isn't she?
We got no information from her and instead did tons of manual labor.
That's too bad for you. I at least
got a peek at Officer Cho's underwear.
He stripped again? Tell him to wash
his underwear if he's gonna do that.
I have a headache...
Joohyun, didn't you follow Chief Kang so where Bumsang is?
Don't ask. Chief Kang told me
to head back to the office.
Who's he to order me around?
And don't you think he's a bit
guarded against Bumsang?
Guarded? Why would he be?
Oh, there's a reason.
Anyway, good work.
Sit down and rest a bit.
Sit, sit.
If the “Bihaedangjib” is there,
Bumsang will have hit the jackpot.
The mega jackpot.
Yeah.
After all the bad vibes
between him and Chohee...
...they're always together on cases...
Do you think
that maybe they like each other?
Who likes whom!
What I mean is,
that's all one-sided on Chohee's part.
It is?
And Bumsang happens to
like someone else.
He does? Who?
Who does Bumsang like?
Really, do you need me to spell things out for you? You two are so dense.
Sangho.
Yeah?
She needs serious help.
Yes, she does, but she's pretty.
Yeah.
So this is the house?
Is this gate the only exit?
No. There's another exit
on the other side.
Yeah? Good work. Chohee.
We'll take care of things here,
so you can head back.
No, I'll stay...
Chohee, take Bumsang
back to the office.
We have plenty of hands, so don't worry.
Yes, sir.
If we find it today, I'll buy drinks.
No, that's not necessary. You're doing
all the work. I'll buy you a drink.
We'll contact you as soon as
things are confirmed. Go on, Chohee.
Then, we'll leave things to you.
Goodbye.
He might attempt an escape so stand guard in this alley and the one out back.
Officer Park and Officer Cho,
you two accompany me inside.
Yes, sir.
Who is it?
This is the police.
What was that?
You're always snippety with me but docile as a lamb in front of him.
Tch. People think
he's a bit unapproachable...
...because he's serious all the time,
but he's actually a really good person.
And Bumsang. You reap what you sow. Don't you agree?
If we find the “Bihaedangjib”
and we catch Mr. Kim today...
...I promise to play nice.
Like that's so likely.
So who comes up with
these nicknames for the art thieves?
Mr. Kim I understand, though a tad trite. What's his real name, by the way?
Hyukjoong Kim.
Hyukjoong Kim. What an embarrassment to the surname Kim.
What about General Shovel?
What?
Officer Cho mentioned him last time. What's his real name?
Dunno? You're on the regulations team and you don't know his name?
Taesoo Heo. His name is Taesoo Heo.
Taesoo Heo? Is he of
the Yangcheon Heos, I wonder?
Hey, you have the same surname as him.
There are a lot of people
with the surname Heo.
I know. There are a lot of celebrities
with that surname, too.
Why aren't they calling yet? They've had plenty of time to raid the place.
I've been brewing
herbal medicine for my arthritis.
Amur corktree oil does smell
awfully similar to herbal medicine.
I guess that young man from earlier...
...knows a bit about
the restorative process.
I think Chohee secretly enjoys
sending us on wild goose chases.
Why does she keep wasting
our time like this?
Same goes for Bumsang.
I thought he was smart,
but Chohee is rubbing off on him.
That's enough. Half of the leads
we chase are false.
Let's stop pointing fingers and go.
Yes, sir.
They're gone.
I can't believe he correctly
guessed the smell of the oil.
That young man was quite sharp.
The CHA doesn't have anyone like that.
He looked a bit familiar...
That's not important.
You know our deadline, right?
It's too tight.
So...you're saying you can't do it?
No, no. I can get it done.
What? Herbal medicine? Hand me
the phone. Who are you talking to?
Yes, yes, Chief. I understand.
They searched everywhere
but nothing came up.
It was a normal house and
he was brewing herbal medicine.
So you're saying I'm wrong?
Is that so hard to admit?
No way I'm wrong about this.
I smelled that oil every day
until I was positively sick of it.
This isn't right.
I understand that your pride took a blow, but stop it already.
We keep raiding his house, and
he'll file an official complaint.
Just follow me
if you want to catch a thief.
Ugh, what a temper...
Who's he trying to fool?
Hey, tell Chief Kang...
Look who's here.
Hanako of the CHA, right?
Why are you following us?
Ah, this neighborhood has
no public restrooms. Gosh, darnit...
No way Bumsang is wrong. Are you sure you didn't make a mistake?
Dunno, but I wish I had. By the way, why the boundless confidence in Bumsang?
Chief Kang, are you jealous?
What?
Are you jealous of Bumsang's abilities? Or are you jealous of his interest in me?
Hold on, Joohyun.
Hmm.
If it's the prior, you're wasting your time.
And if it's the latter,
you're attempting the impossible.
I'm sure I'm breaking your heart...
...but please understand
that I have no other choice.
Be strong. Good luck!
Chief Kang!
Ah, Chief Noh.
Why are you standing here?
Joohyun gets weirder
the more I get to know her.
I can't get inside her head at all.
Women are impossible to understand.
I still don't get my wife after thirty years.
By the way, how'd things go today?
We checked out a lot of places
but to no avail.
Excuse me.
Yeah, Officer Park? What's up? What? Mr. Kim did what to Chohee?
Oh, long time no see to both chiefs.
You've got a lot of nerve,
voluntarily coming here.
I didn't want to come, but I had to
report a case of illegal tailing.
Illegal tailing?
Ask this little lady here.
Ask her if I'm lying.
You know about double jeopardy, right?
I was acquitted.
So why do you keep tailing me?
And isn't it illegal for a non-police officer, a CHA employee to tail me?
Hey, Bleach head.
The regulations team has special police jurisdiction, so it's not illegal! ...
Get things right
if you're gonna complain.
Oh, it's not illegal? My bad.
I'm sorry, Hanako.
I was just exercising my rights
as a citizen, but I guess I was wrong.
Then I'll be going.
Hyukjoong Kim.
You've been studying, seeing
how you know about double jeopardy.
Then didn't you read up
on zero tolerance?
In layman's terms, it means
that men like you are screwed...
...once we get a conviction.
Don't underestimate the police.
I'll keep that in mind, Chief Kang.
Filed it away in here.
Oh, and Chief Noh. Keep an eye on this girl here. She should be more careful.
What are you gonna do if she meets someone with a nasty temper?
Girlie, take care of yourself, okay?
I'm out.
Chohee, we need to talk.
Are you out of your mind?
If you saw Mr. Kim,
you should've called me or Chief Kang.
Why the hell would you follow him on your own? Why are you so fearless?
Thank goodness
he brought you here to piss us off.
Imagine if he had kidnapped you!
What would have happened then?
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna hear it.
You're off the case.
Chief.
You jumped in front of a car when you were chasing Gyucheol Seo, right?
I can't watch you be
so reckless anymore.
You're off the case!
Chief, I can't do that.
What?
I'm very sorry. I will try my hardest
not to let this happen again.
So please don't take me off the case.
You know how important
this case is to me.
I know. All the more reason
for you to remain uninvolved.
Officer Park, is Chohee inside?
Yes. She's getting an earful
from Chief Noh right now.
Huh... She dare to give me
a fright like that?
You can't because of your father.
For his sake.
Chief.
I've watched you grow up
since you were eight years old.
I've seen it all.
You entering junior high school...
...you trying to survive with little Gyoon...
...never complaining once no matter
how hard life was. I've seen all of it.
I don't know how you think of me,
but to me you're my daughter.
And fathers just want to see
their daughters safe.
And happy.
Your father probably feels the same
as I do. So I can't let you continue.
So Chief Noh was her father's friend? Why is she crying? It's so unlike her.
So is everything cleaned up
at the restoration house?
Everything's cleaned up
at the restoration house.
Tell them to wrap things up.
Wrap things up!
I told them to wrap things up.
Goodbye.
But sir, wasn't it awfully reckless of you to go to the investigations team?
It was, it was. I think
you overdid it with that one.
Not like I'm on the wanted list.
They've got nothing against me.
No need to worry.
But it's so hard to
shake them off each time...
I've got a way to clear them out all
at once, so don't worry.
Gyucheol, you get ready to
lay low for a while.
Yonggu! Go fetch me my passport.
Ugh, that leech.
Chief! Chief, bad news.
Mr. Kim just left for Japan.
What?
I went to the immigration service
to ask for their cooperation...
...and when I checked on Mr. Kim,
he had already left the country.
Call the airport's customs office
at once and...
...check if the “Bihaedangjib” went
with him. If it did, we're done for!
Bribes, favors, none of it. She's clean.
No one's ever bought Chohee anything, not so much as a burger.
Bumsang, are you listening?
I'm listening.
Tsk, tsk. Just how much did she
screw you for you to be so dispirited?
So who's behind the “Bihaedangjib” theft?
And why do you want to know?
Just, you know...
I'm just curious.
Curious? You expect me to believe that?
You know something, don't you?
Nope.
What is it? You can tell me.
Knowing when to keep
one's mouth shut is...
...a basic rule of
a successful businessman.
Ah, so you know nothing.
I'll tell you this. The person who first stole the “Bihaedangjib” was General Shovel.
Who cares who stole it in the first place? How is that important now?
Anyway, don't worry about Chohee. She'll get what's coming to her soon.
What do you mean?
She's public enemy number one
to a lot of guys.
Kkaldagu of Jangan-pyeong, Jjakbal of Insa-dong, Dari Jong of Daegu.
They all wanna teach her a lesson.
She should watch her back,
or she'll get it. Good to hear, isn't it?
Grown men have nothing better to do than pick on a girl? What cowards.
What the. Why is he yelling at me?
What has she been doing with her life, amassing so many enemies?
Oh, Bumsang!
Ah, Joohyun.
Look at those bags under the eyes.
You don't look so hot.
Are you still depressed about being wrong yesterday?
I'm sorry, I should have comforted you. I'm really sorry.
You waited for my call, didn't you?
Huh? Ah, yes, well.
I was dying to call you...
...but I had the tact not to make
matters worse by mentioning it.
That's proper etiquette, I think.
Ah, yes. Thank you. Joohyun, I'm a bit busy right now.
By the way, did you hear
that Chohee was taken off the case?
What? What happened?
Yesterday she was following
Mr. Kim when he caught her.
So Chief Noh has her working
on a different case.
What case?
Just some petty robbery case.
She looked so down earlier
I couldn't help but be a little glee...
I mean, I really felt for her. Deeply.
Hey, get in.
Why?
I heard you were taken off the case?
I'm partly to blame. I hate feeling guilty.
If you want to save on some cab fare,
get in. Before I change my mind.
Ah! Mommy! What the! Dear lord, seatbelt, seatbelt!
According to the airport,
the “Bihaedangjib” wasn't smuggled out.
If that's true, what a relief.
Chief, about Chohee.
Why did you take her off the case?
I owe him a bit.
What?
You wouldn't understand.
If it wasn't smuggled out...
...that means it'll end up at some
rich man's house. What to do...
Our hands are tied either way.
There has to be a distribution channel in which they make deals under the table.
Where do we start looking?
Rich men, you say...
Dear me, Chief Kang,
what brings you here?
How've you been, Hwaja Ji?
Or should I call you Hanako Suzuki?
Ugh, it's hot and I'm bored.
Until when do we have to wait?
I told you to go home.
I already came this far. So, what did this guy steal?
He cleaned out some store in Insa-dong.
We'll ask the family members
about the missing items...
...and if that doesn't pan out, we'll have to take a turn around the streets.
What a tiresome life you lead.
Hey, when you have some free time, learn some combative sport.
Combative sport?
Yeah, like boxing.
Or some self-defense martial arts.
What for?
It's a scary world.
You're always out and about. Who knows what could happen at night?
Just take lessons.
Or find yourself a boyfriend
who can double as your bodyguard.
How inappropriate.
That's unsolicited advice.
Who, who are you?
I don't know nothin'. I haven't seen
my son in months. I really haven't.
Grandma, I'm not asking
if you've seen your son.
I'm asking if you've seen
the items he stole.
I don't know! How would I know that? I don't know nothin'!
Granny, why don't you just ask Daddy? Daddy!
Hey, Bumsang!
Ow, ow...
Daddy! Daddy...
Daddy.
Daddy...
Yes, Officer Cho. Yes, yes. You just need to come up a little bit further. Yes, yes.
Excuse me. I'm really sorry...
...but this is the first time
I've come home in eight months.
This weekend is my daughter's birthday.
Can't I turn myself in
after this weekend?
I'm sorry, the matter is out of my hands. I'm sorry. Let's go.
Daddy! Daddy!
My son, my son! My son!
- Daddy!
- Please don't take Daddy.
Youngshin.
Please let him go.
Please let him go just once.
Let him go, please let Daddy go. Mister, please let Daddy go! Daddy...
Mister, please let him go...
‘I hate this.'
Daddy, please don't go.
Youngshin, I'm sorry.
[Officer Cho]
I'll be home soon, so don't cry.Listen
to your grandmother and study hard.
Don't go.
Why are you crying? I'll be home soon.
Can't you let him go?
You can pretend he got away.
Let's let him go. Okay?
No. I can't do that.
Daddy!
My son!
Yes, Officer Cho. Take a right and keep coming up. Yes.
I'll follow you.
Okay.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- Head on home.
Bumsang, we should have
a drink next time. I'm off then.
Goodbye.
Thanks for today.
Hey! Isn't this a bit much even for you?
He was going to turn himself in?
Why are you so cruel?
Think it's funny that I'm saying this?
You're right. I'm not the nicest guy...
...but the girl was crying and begging. Don't you have a heart?
You think that letting him go
would be any better for them?
At least they wouldn't have to
watch him get dragged away.
Do you understand at all
how much that must hurt for them?
You think that kind of pain is a big deal?
What?
For them, it's a worse pain knowing
that their father is a thief.
And it's better for the kids
if he's in prison.
Letting him go because of
pity won't help anyone.
Would you say the same
if it were your father?
If he were the one
getting dragged away?
Even after all the squabbling we did,
I never hated you or anything.
Watching you always
immersed in your work...
...I thought you had a reason
and I felt bad for you.
But I was wrong about you.
I didn't realize
you were such a heartless woman.
I'd heard that Chohee had a younger brother. It's nice to meet you.
I've heard about you, too,
Chief Shiwan Kang.
Oh, does Chohee talk about me?
Did my sister talk about me?
No, I heard about you from Chief Noh.
Ah, am I being too informal
on our first meeting?
One has to make allowances for age,
so it can't be helped.
I heard you have a kid.
So what brings you here?
What do you mean by that?
Nothing, really. But I will say this.
My sister is extremely lazy and dirty...
...has a horrible temper and
a bad personality, too.
And most importantly,
she really hates kids.
I think I've made my point, right?
So in other words, if I'm interested in your sister, I should just give up now?
So you're actually quite perceptive.
I'm here to talk about work,
so don't worry.
Can you give her another call?
Isn't it about time she arrived?
Should I?
Oh, Chohee, you're home.
Chief?
They're not gonna do any funny business because I'm not there, are they?
They wouldn't, right?
Ah! Ah...
I heard you headed home as soon as handing over Cheoljin Lee.
So why are you so late?
I went for a walk.
You don't look too well.
Officer Cho said the daughter was bawling. Is it because of that?
It is, isn't it?
To tell you the truth, I wanted to
let him go. I could have, you know...
But I thought the kids were better off knowing their father was safe in prison...
...rather than being chased around because he was a wanted man.
Seeing him only on their birthdays...
...and waiting all the time is
too much for them.
At least this way they can go see him when they want...
...and they don't have to worry about him starving or sleeping on the streets.
So I steeled myself and
forced myself to hold onto him.
You did well, it was the right decision.
You don't need to
beat yourself up about it.
I'm sorry, Chief.
Why are you sorry?
I'm actually feeling quite good.
This is the first time you've really
opened up to me, Chohee.
It troubled me that you were always uncomfortable with me.
I'm glad I came here today.
Excuse me. Can I make you guys
some coffee or something?
No, thank you. I have to get going.
Oh, I nearly forgot. I almost left without telling you what I came here to tell you.
I found a possible distribution
channel through Hwaja Ji.
So talk to Chief Noh and
try to get back on the case.
Chief.
You see, I'm a bit on the selfish side.
I can't stand the idea of you
bumming around.
What is this?
An invitation.
To what?
First, put me back on the case.
You've got a lead?
There's a chance
we might recover the “Bihaedangjib.”
And you want to strike a deal with me?
Yes.
I refuse. Take this and leave.
Chief!
I already told you. You're off the case.
Uncle.
Uncle... Uncle, you've looked after me like a daughter since I was eight.
Did you know? The parent always
gives in to the child in a battle of wills.
You'll give in to me. Even if you tell me no, I'm still gonna work on this case.
But I'd rather have your permission.
So what's the lead?
Here's the thing.
Chairman Jang of the Ohsung Group is holding a charity auction this weekend.
It's a charity auction by name...
...but in reality there's going to be
a lot of illegal deals.
There's no guarantee
we'll find the “Bihaedangjib,”...
...but I think it's worth a try.
A charity auction?
And why would I want to go there?
If the “Bihaedangjib” shows up...
...you're the only one
that can verify its authenticity.
Is this my duty as the advisory member?
No, not really...
Are we done here?
Hey, Bumsang.
Come on, at least consider it.
I really need your help, okay?
I'm asking you for a favor.
How unlike you,
the heartless Chohee I know.
I'm not going to change my mind,
so leave.
Is this about what happened last time?
Because I didn't let Cheoljin Lee go?
Is that what this is about?
No, this is about you. I don't like you.
You're heartless and
only care about your work.
So I don't want to help you. Got it?
Sangho! The lobby, the lobby!
The lobby?
- Did you check it?
- The lobby's all clear.
Hurry, hurry!
Joohyun, Joohyun,
must you do that right now?
Did you check up on the vehicle?
Can you do that? Let's do a good job.
Yes, this is Joohyung Wang. How's
the vehicle coming along? Please hurry.
Chohee, what did Mr. Kim say?
Will he help?
I don't think
that's going to work out.
What to do...
We have no other choice.
We'll have to ask someone else.
Sangho, when will Chief Noh arrive?
Five minutes. He says
he'll be here in five minutes.
Then we'll start our preparation
for the auction when he arrives.
How are you? I'm here
from the catering service.
Please sign here.
Sure. It's hot today, isn't it?
Have a good day.
After all those years as a fuzz,
you still can't get it right?
It's working, it's working!
Look, look.
Idiots.
What the, that startled me.
Are they mocking me right now?
Officer Cho.
You're a movie star.
This is an haute couture piece
my mother bought specially in Paris.
If you so much as spill
a drop of wine on it...
Haute what?
You don't know what haute couture is?
Then again, you probably don't have much experience with expensive clothes.
Anyway, this is really expensive,
so please be careful.
Thanks.
So why can't Bumsang come?
Some important business?
Uh...
You're heartless and only care about your work. So I don't want to help you.
I have no idea.
If he were coming, I'd be the one
going into the auction.
Did you hire someone else
to be the appraiser?
What? Oh, Yongcheol Gong of Hanguk University agreed to come.
It's time. Call me when you're ready.
Okay.
Oh my! Dear lord...
Man, I'm not good with
these kinds of situations.
Why'd she have to cry
so heartbreakingly?
Excuse me? Anyone home?
Who are you?
Huh?
Oh, you're the mister
who came the other day.
Yeah, you remember me.
Yes. But why did you come back here?
Today's your birthday, right?
Here. Happy birthday.
Wow, thank you.
How did you know it was my birthday? Oh, did that lady tell you?
Wait, the lady who was with me
last time came by again?
Yes. She bought me this dress.
Oh... I see. It's heavy, isn't it?
You know what? She's not such
a bad person once you get to know her.
She just talks a bit roughly.
So don't hate her, okay?
I don't hate her.
I understand everything now.
And I promised her
I wouldn't cry anymore.
You did? You're a brave little girl.
She said the same thing.
She said when her daddy was
first taken away...
...she cried every day and
beat up her little brother.
I never hit Younghoon.
What did you just say?
Huh?
Her daddy was taken away?
Didn't you know?
She said her daddy was taken away
far more times than my daddy.
For them, it's a worse pain
knowing that their father is a thief.
Would you say the same
if it were your father?
The person who first stole
the “Bihaedangjib” was General Shovel.
A famous art thief well educated in Chinese literature as well as...
...topographic divination.
Thank you for the meal.
You're on the regulations team and
you don't know General Shovel's name?
Taesoo Heo. His name is Taesoo Heo.
Hey, you have
the same surname as him.
So Chohee's father was...
So we're waiting for Chohee Heo?
Yes.
Why isn't she here yet?
She's almost here.
I heard you're a professor in the same department as Bumsang Kim?
The same department, yes...
...but I'm a professor and he's a lecturer. Don't compare us.
Ah... Okay.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Well then, we're off.
Okay.
Let's go.
Looks fabulous, no?
What?
That dress, that purse, those shoes, they're all mine.
The latest haute couture.
You look very beautiful.
I came here to help out my country.
I never expected to meet
such a beautiful woman.
Let's hurry.
Sure, let's go. Let's go find Prince Yangnyeong's “Bihaedangjib.”
Prince Yangnyeong?
You mean Prince Ahnpyeong.
What? Ah, right, right. Prince Ahnpyeong. He was an excellent person.
Do you know anything at all
about the “Bihaedangjib?”
Why is that important?
I'm a professor at Hanguk University.
A professor at Hanguk University!
One quick look, and it'll be obvious, more or less. Let's go.
What do you mean, more or less?
I'm sorry, but I refuse to go in with you.
Why are you being so uptight?
Let's just go in without a fuss.
I refuse to exchange words
with someone...
...who doesn't even know
the “Bihaedangjib.”
Why are you being so bullheaded?
Do you intend to disgrace me?
Let go! I said, let go!
My, my, this is quite shameful for
a professor at Hanguk University.
Bumsang?
You should also consider your father's reputation. Let her go.
You let go!
You haven't been shamed enough?
Yongcheol, Prince Yangnyeong is
King Taejong's son...
...and Prince Ahnpyeong is
King Sejong's son!
We're talking about two completely different reigns here.
Didn't you learn this
in elementary school?
Go brush up on your history, you idiot.
Leave! Idiot.
I thought you weren't coming.
We don't have much time, so let's talk about that later. You have the invitation?
Ah, here.
Where'd you get such an unbefitting dress? Rent it from a rental store?
Huh! Was Joohyun bluffing?
I wouldn't know the difference...
The weather's great.
Perfect weather for a party.
Hey.
What?
Can't you see?
Partners are walking arm in arm.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America