Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
So the restoration will finish
in a couple of days?
Yes, sir.
You don't watch
much television, do you?
Excuse me?
[National treasure no. 238,
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook...
stolen in 2001 has returned to
the museum after seven long years.]
[An anonymous donor
has returned it to the people...]
Why isn't he picking up?
Where are you?
Did you see the news?
Yeah.
I'm driving right now let's talk later.
I'll drop by later or something.
Bumsang! Hey, hey!
Episode 9
A day like today should
be declared a national holiday.
There's nothing better than a stolen
national treasure returning on its own.
The good news is one thing, but do you think we'll have to work late tonight?
How did such a man lacking patriotism
become a government employee?
Hey, jerk, be honest for once.
I heard you muttering to yourself earlier.
Why are you full of patriotism
only when you have an audience?
What did you say?
This is a happy day, remember?
I wonder who
the anonymous donor is?
Based on my fifteen years of experience,
it's the thief who first stole it in 2001.
Why? The “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook is
just too weighty to handle in our country.
He was asking me.
Why are you butting in?
My opinion is that
one of the rich men donated it.
I'm surprised you can say that
with a straight face.
What crazy rich guy would do that?
Maybe he's a kind, rich guy.
A nice guy.
Anyway, whoever it is, the person greatly
served the country and the people.
Definitely.
Kind, rich guy.
Officer Park! Did you get
the employee's witness statement?
Um...
Hey, isn't that Bumsang?
Bumsang, what brings you here?
I was wondering if i could take a look
at the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook.
Of course. I was
just about to contact you.
Please follow me.
Why is he here after
betraying us this morning?
There's something
about him that irks me.
Jinx! I was thinking
the same thing in my head.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
No. It's authentic all right.
That's a relief.
I thought something was wrong.
Bumsang, have you ever seen
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook before?
What?
It's just that you verified it so quickly.
As if you've seen it before.
No, it's just such a famous piece.
Thanks for the coffee.
You're welcome.
Bumsang!
What happened?
My friend. Excuse me.
Sure.
Chief! We're done here.
Should we head back to the office?
Go ahead without me. I'm going to
stop by the hospital first to visit Chohee.
Our poor chief.
I know, right? It's not easy
looking after someone else's woman.
Right.
And he can't ignore her
‘cause she got hurt saving him.
Right.
Chohee won't seek revenge or anything
because we didn't visit her, will she?
Why isn't he calling me?
Bumsang?
You were waiting for Bumsang?
Chief...
I felt weird coming empty-handed.
Have a seat.
Sure.
I saw Bumsang at the museum,
and he met up with a friend.
Ah, I see...
Would you like something to drink?
Let me.
Are you okay, Chohee?
I'm fine.
Are you investigating who sent in
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook?
Yes. We're looking
into the delivery service.
Our guess is it originated
from a rich man's house.
A rich man?
We don't know
who the last owner was.
But since it's a stolen good
and a national treasure...
it won't be taken away with the
good faith excuse like Congressman Lee.
I should get going.
Chohee, where's your brother?
He went to meet a friend.
Did he? Won't it be
inconvenient being here alone?
I'll be fine with
my boyfriend here with me.
It's the least he can do.
Ah, right.
Are you headed home?
No, I have to go back to the office.
I see...
Bumsang, goodbye.
Goodbye.
No, no. Don't come out.
What do you mean, your boyfriend?
Shouldn't you explain things to him
before he misunderstands even more?
I just want him to feel comfortable.
What?
I told him I liked him.
And I got hurt while protecting him.
From his perspective,
I must be quite the burden.
I was hoping he'd feel less pressured
if he thought we were really dating.
What am I, chopped liver?
What?
You used me to lessen
the pressure on the person you like.
At first you were against the idea,
but now you're behaving just like me.
What do you mean I'm behaving
just like you? What an insult...
Anyway, what happened
with Chairman Jang?
What?
He must've seen the news.
Did he contact you?
Yeah, he called me, but he didn't
say anything in particular.
Yeah? No threats or anything?
Nope.
As a well-known man, he wouldn't
heckle me when it's a lost cause.
It's already in the museum.
That's true. He can't even report it to the
police though he must be really upset.
So who did it?
How'd he know that
the scrapbook was at your place?
And why'd he send it to the museum?
So many unanswered questions.
But thank goodness
things ended quietly.
Did you steal it? Then again, if you did,
you wouldn't turn it over to a museum.
No matter who stole it,
the fact that doesn't change is...
that the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook
can never return to me.
And the person who lost it is you.
That fact will also never change.
You should brace yourself.
You will pay dearly for this.
Oh, right!
I forgot to thank him.
Bumsang, I feel sorry for you...
but I'm glad the “Sowonhwagae”
scrapbook is safe.
You're going through a hard time,
so I'm sorry for being happy.
Joohyun, what brings you here?
As your co-worker and as the woman
who loved the same man as you...
I came to have
a heart-to-heart with you.
The last time we went drinking,
you said you weren't interested in him.
About that...
Joohyun, the truth is...
Um, I...
Blocked it.
There's no need to
come up with an excuse.
I'll forgive everything.
I'll give up Bumsang.
Joohyun, thanks, I guess. But maybe
you shouldn't give up so easily.
We could break up
in the near future.
No...
Chohee, that's not how
you comfort someone.
You just have to say that
you'll make him happy.
If he's happy, I'll be happy.
Joohyun, your love is
a very considerate kind of love.
What do you mean?
It just occurred to me that Bumsang
should be grateful for your love.
I'm envious.
What did you say? A change in MCs?
What in the world are you talking about?
The thing is...
We just found out about it today.
Sir, you begged me to stay on for
another season. How could you do this?
I don't want to change MCs. But with the
pressure from above, my hands are tied.
From above?
An order from above...
You should brace yourself.
You will pay dearly for this.
I'm really sorry, Bumsang. Don't
hate me for being powerless, okay?
Then when's my last day? Do I continue
until you find my replacement?
We already found your replacement.
Already? Who...
We record at three.
Three o'clock?
Long time, Bumsang.
So it is. Didn't expect
to run into you like this.
I feel bad about you being cut,
but what can be done?
I can't help it
if the people want me.
I don't know about that, but okay.
At least this time you used someone
else's influence and not your father's.
Nonsense. I got this job
entirely due to my skill and effort!
Again, I don't know
about that, but okay.
You've adopted a very unique sense
of style since I saw you last.
I got a full makeover
at Cheongdam-dong.
Why? Do I look
too intellectual now?
Sure, why not?
Anyway, congratulations.
Bumsang, did you piss off
the president of the university?
Piss him off?
What are you talking about?
I heard all your lectures for next
semester were given to someone else?
What?
I heard they were going to tell you today.
I guess you haven't received the call yet.
Oh, and you're no longer a researcher
at the school's preservation lab.
What in the world did you do?
Anyway, I'll be taking charge of
“Discovering Cultural Assets.”
And it'll be the discovery
of a new Yongcheol Gong.
Chairman Jang,
what a force to be reckoned with.
Yes, Mr. Son?
You guys are here early.
We'll work our butts off, interviewing
witnesses and checking security tapes.
The regulations team will try our best
to uncover the identity of the donor.
Okay. I'm off to talk to someone at the
preservation lab. We'll meet up later.
See you later.
The one form of patriotism we can
perform for the people is...
Sabotage.
Do you have to say shirking our
responsibilities in such a hard way?
If you're uneducated,
at least attempt to study.
Anyway, a case like this
shouldn't be investigated too seriously.
Of course not. We should be grateful
for the donation to the museum.
So we have no choice
but to pretend to work.
Let's all take it easy.
Shall we start shirking our duties
by getting some iced coffee?
You buy!
Seeing how the paper is not very flat,
it seems to have been restored recently.
Recently?
Yes. Only natural dyes
and paper were used.
I think a professional
restoration expert did it.
Restoration expert?
It was probably very damaged before,
but it was done extremely well by hand.
It has the touch
of someone of great skill.
This may sound strange,
but let me ask you something.
Are there many people in our country
with this level of skill in restoration?
There are so few you can
count them on one hand.
Then a person of
Bumsang Kim's caliber -
Would have absolutely no problem.
He's the best there is in book restoration.
What's up?
Did you find out who stole the book?
That's not it. Have a seat first. You must
be going through a hell of a time.
With the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook
being donated. How'd that happen?
Is this why you called me here?
No. Did the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook
belong to Chairman Jang?
News travels fast.
How'd you hear?
Chairman Jang's men
dropped by earlier.
Jeez, he shouldn't be like that.
It's not like you lost it on purpose.
Anyway, be careful. He looks refined
on the outside, but he's a scary man.
There are rumors that he once
buried a middleman alive.
Oh, and is Chohee
still in the hospital?
Why do you ask?
I don't know why
but he asked about her.
I answered truthfully but then it occurred
to me that maybe I shouldn't have.
Pick up, come on...
[Your call has been transferred...]
Why aren't you picking up?
Yes, Chief. I'm a little busy
right now so let's talk later.
Did something happen?
Hey!
Excuse me.
What brings you here -
What are you doing here?
I looked for you everywhere!
Why were you looking for me?
I was just seeing Joohyun off.
At least carry your phone around. Why
would you see her off when you're hurt?
What's up with you?
Let's go in.
What?
Hey! Hey!
Hey. Hey!
When you're alone, don't leave
the room unless absolutely necessary.
And if you don't recognize the number,
don't pick up your phone.
Seriously, what's going on?
No matter.
Just do I as I tell you, okay?
What the? What's with him?
I set an appointment tomorrow with the
head administrative official of the CHA.
We'll recommend Professor Yongcheol
Gong for the advisory member position.
About the young lady...
You can't go in, sir.
Give us a moment.
What brings you here?
Sir, why are you doing this?
What are you talking about?
I distinctly remember you telling me I'd
have to pay. But that's on my shoulders.
Chohee Heo has nothing to do with
what happened. So why in the world...
Who do you think you're talking to?
You come in uninvited, and worse yet,
you raise your voice against me?
And all because of a woman.
Punish me, sir. She's not involved with
what happened. She did nothing wrong.
You're losing your head
over a woman. How interesting.
Is she the woman you like?
You may be right in that
she's not involved in the matter.
But from the brash way
she spoke to me...
isn't it possible that
she's behind the whole thing?
Sir...
Even if she's not, she annoys me.
No matter what you say, I'm gonna keep
doing things my way until I feel better.
So save your breath and leave.
Sir!
Didn't you hear me
telling you to leave?
The cornered mouse
will attack the cat.
What did you say?
Continue doing what you want.
But if you touch a hair on Chohee's
head, I won't just stand back and take it.
Cancel pushing Professor Gong
for the advisory position.
And hands off of Bumsang.
Shouldn't you show him who's boss
after the rude way he just acted?
No. It won't hurt him if we hit him
when he has nothing to lose.
He'll really feel the pain if we hit him
when he has something to protect.
I have a good idea.
According to the
preservation lab employee...
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook was
handled by someone of great expertise.
Do you have any suspects?
I'm not sure yet. I wonder who possessed
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook before?
About that.
There's talk that it belonged to
Chairman Jang of Ohseong Group.
Chairman Jang?
Yeah. It hasn't been confirmed
but it's almost certain.
Oh? Chief Kang!
Hi, Joohyun.
Guess where I'm coming from.
Where?
I just visited Chohee at the hospital.
You did?
As you well know, I've been
suffering a lot these days.
It can't be helped. To alleve the tension
in the office and to build character...
someone had to set out
and put an end to this love triangle.
So you ended it?
Bingo.
I told her to make Bumsang happy.
The strange thing is
she said she was envious of me.
Why?
I'm not sure if she was
envious of me or of Bumsang.
I didn't really catch her drift.
Anyway, it's all over and done.
I see. You did well.
Chief, are you worried about something?
You don't look too well.
Huh? No, no worries.
Jeez, I just told you that
you can stop worrying about me.
I'm back to being the cute
and lively Joohyun I was before.
That's great.
I have to get going.
Where are you going?
To visit Chohee.
It's raining.
Do you have an umbrella?
Nope. It's okay.
But it's pouring outside.
Oh, Sis?
Yeah?
Do you need anything tomorrow
when you leave the hospital?
Nope, nothing. And I'm going
to go straight to work so don't come.
Why? Rest some more at home.
It's okay.
My body and my arm hurt a bit, but
I can't keep troubling the people at work.
I guess if you've already
decided I can't stop you.
But don't overdo yourself, okay?
All right.
Then I'm off.
Oh, and Sis?
What?
Dad stole the “Sowonhwagae”
scrapbook, just like the “Bihaedangjib?”
Yeah, you're right.
Then it coming back to the museum
is a good thing, right?
Of course. It's a good thing.
Then why don't you look happier?
You were so happy when
you found the “Bihaedangjib.”
Ah... that is...
Stop worrying about useless things
and do me a favor.
What is it? Tell me.
Please stop wasting your time here
and go win a scholarship or something.
Sheesh, Sis.
Your brother works
a part-time job every day...
and gets his scholarship through labor.
What more do you want?
I'm really leaving.
Go on then!
Where'd he run off to,
worrying me like this?
Chairman Jang is going too far.
It's not like you lost it intentionally. It was
bad luck. How could he do this to you?
Wouldn't you do the same
if you were him?
It wasn't just any book.
You're in deep trouble.
What if you're blackballed
from this world?
It might happen.
You're talking like
it's not your business.
What are you going to do?
You were awfully reckless. How could
you confront him knowing his temper?
You have your reasons, right?
[Chohee Heo]
Let's leave, I'll grab the check.
Hi.
I'm having a drink with Jonggyu.
No, I'll stop by real quick.
Okay, then let's talk
when you get here. Okay.
He's being so strange today.
Yeah?
Where are you?
Still far away?
Yeah. Still have
a long way to go.
How much longer?
About thirty minutes.
What? Thirty minutes?
Darn, I came out too early.
I'm waiting so get here
as quickly as you can.
Are you outside again?
I told you to stay in your room.
The room was really stuffy. It's pouring.
You don't have an umbrella, do you?
A little rain won't hurt me.
You said you can't stand to see
a woman get wet by the rain.
Well, I can't stand seeing
a guy get wet by the rain.
Is that so?
Um, about earlier. Why were you acting
like that? Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Liar. Then why did
you get so angry earlier?
Hello? Hello!
What happened?
Bumsang!
What's wrong? Hey, let go.
Don't wanna.
I told you to let go.
No. I'm not going to let you go.
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you so flustered by
a simple hug from your boyfriend?
Did you know you're acting
really strangely today?
I know I am.
It's not because
something happened.
You know I haven't been feeling
so well these days. Try to understand.
And I'm quite touched by you
waiting for me with an umbrella.
But just this much. Bye.
Hey! Take the umbrella!
Shouldn't this and this go
to the financial department?
Yeah.
- Check them for me.
- Mr. Nah? Sangho?
Mr. Nah, please write up
the Hahman case report for me.
Sangho, please organize the
briefing material for the Yeoju case.
You want us to do this work for you?
But you always did in the past.
Joohyun, can't you see all this?
We're swamped, too.
So you're saying
you can't do them for me, right?
The thing is...
It's not that...
No one in the regulations
team cares about me.
Bumsang left me,
and now you two, too.
Fine. I'll do it myself.
I'll take care of it.
Joohyun! Joohyun, give it here.
I'll do it for you. Come on.
Finish them by two, please.
When is she going to
get over her broken heart?
When is Chohee getting
discharged from the hospital?
Oh, Chohee!
Hello.
- Chohee!
- Chohee! Are you feeling okay?
Yeah, nothing I can't handle.
Oh, the Hahman case report,
I already turned it in last week.
- You did?
- Yeah.
Let's see.
And I uploaded the briefing material
for the Yeoju case onto our server.
Check it out later.
Okay.
Did you have some coffee already?
I'll buy to celebrate my discharge.
How does morning coffee sound?
Okay.
Chohee, Chohee!
Chohee, congratulations on
being released from the hospital.
Is your hurt shoulder okay?
How's Gyoon doing?
Gyoon's fine.
And the arm is still...
There's something
we're really curious about.
What is it?
Why did Bumsang quit
“Discovering Cultural Assets?”
What are you talking about?
You're full of energy today.
Can't believe you came straight to work.
You were cut from your TV gig?
How'd you find out so quickly?
Was it Chairman Jang?
It was, wasn't it?
What about your other work?
What about the school?
You're not going to be cut from
the advisory position here, are you?
If I'm told to quit, I'll quit.
I came prepared.
That's absolute nonsense.
Don't worry. If I can't avoid
the storm, I'll have to wait it out.
You should have told me all of this
was happening. Why didn't you?
Was that why you were acting
so strangely yesterday? Was it?
It wasn't?
Well, it was, though that
wasn't the whole of it.
What else is there?
Is there more?
Just some things.
Bumsang!
Director, how are you?
Good thing I ran into you.
I have something to discuss with you.
Let's go to my room.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you later.
What's this?
It's my letter of resignation.
Your letter of resignation?
I already know what it is
you want to discuss with me.
Rather than causing you discomfort,
I thought I should bring it up first.
Thank you for all the care
you've shown me.
Bumsang.
Yes, I'm listening, sir.
What in the world
are you talking about?
What?
The reason I wanted to see you
was to ask you to take a look at this.
What?
Were you displeased with
your treatment here at the CHA?
No, that's not it.
I didn't think I had done
anything to upset you.
I see you were feeling differently.
I guess it's true that you can never
really know what someone is thinking.
I never imagined
you were feeling like this.
Sir, how could I possibly?
Ifailed to recognize your great care
and attention. Please forgive me.
Did you really write this yourself?
Yes, I did.
That's weird. What's going on?
I'm so honored that
you called on me again, sir.
You must've been devastated about
losing the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook.
I'm saddened because
I can still remember...
your happy expression when I first
placed it in your hands seven years ago.
Then and now,
you're still as talkative as ever.
Ah, well...
I won't beat around the bush.
Can you guess why I called for you?
Probably because you need me
to do something for you.
You're right.
Do you know Bumsang Kim?
Bumsang Kim?
Of course I do.
I need you to teach him a lesson.
Excuse me?
A penny for your thoughts.
Ah, hello. Have a seat.
Where is everyone?
Ever since the “Sowonhwagae”
scrapbook came back...
everyone's busy pretending to work.
Pretending to work?
No one's really motivated to catch
the anonymous donor here.
Since the person gave it to the museum
instead of lining his own pockets.
That's understandable.
Secretly I felt happy, too.
By the way, did you
find out who restored it?
Yes, well, I have a suspect
so I'm in the middle of investigating him.
Bumsang should know a lot about
that area. You should ask for his help.
Yes, I was planning
to go see him now.
Then as soon as you get
some results, give me a call, okay?
I will.
Why do you think Chairman Jang
left you only your advisory position?
Maybe because a public institution
is harder to influence?
No, that can't be it.
Anyway, it's very strange.
Whatever the reason, it's a relief.
That you kept the advisory position.
It's a relief?
Yeah.
Wow, Chohee, you've changed a lot.
Seems like yesterday you were trying
to kick me out with that recording.
You think you haven't changed?
How did I change?
You, um, you...
Then again,
you haven't changed much.
I wonder who turned
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook in?
Aren't you curious?
I'm more than curious.
If I get my hands on him, he's dead.
I take being able to keep this job
as a sign from God to go catch him.
Watch and see.
I'm going to catch him myself.
Hey, isn't that Chief Kang?
Chief.
Chohee, you're back.
How are you feeling?
Just, you know...
What brings you here?
I wanted to talk to Bumsang.
Do you have a moment?
Sure.
Have a seat.
Okay.
So, what's up?
I wanted to ask you something
about the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook.
I heard something
interesting at the museum.
Apparently it was recently restored.
What's your take on this?
You saw it up close, too.
It was more of a passing glance.
According to the lab employee,
someone of great skill restored it.
Can you think of any suspects?
Is there anyone you know
who could have restored the scrapbook?
Is there a reason
you're asking me this?
It seems to me
you already have a suspect.
Sometimes questions
aren't asked for the answers.
Do you suspect me?
I won't deny it.
Do you have any evidence?
All investigations begin with a hunch.
A hunch...
When appraising, sometimes one's
intuition rather than evidence is correct.
Or it could be wrong.
It seems your line of work and
my line of work aren't very different.
Let's cut to the chase. Did you restore
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook?
I remember telling you before that a
cultural asset is simply a cultural asset.
If a doctor refuses to treat a dying
patient, he doesn't deserve to be one.
Can I take that to mean
you did do the restoration?
You said some questions
weren't asked for the answers?
Finding the answer to your question
isn't my job. It's yours.
What are they talking about?
I'm sorry I couldn't be
of any service to you.
Not at all.
You've helped me quite a bit.
That's good to hear.
Bumsang, before I leave
I want to make one thing clear.
I believe you're a good person.
I sincerely hope
this belief doesn't change.
Chohee!
Chief.
Are you guys done talking?
What did you talk about?
It was nothing important.
I'll be going then. Goodbye.
Chief! Thank goodness you're here.
What is it?
Another item was
delivered to the museum.
Please move out of the way.
There you are, sir.
Please come this way.
Is it this painting?
Yes.
Who received it?
I signed for the delivery but there was
no sender's name or address on it.
Sir, please take a look at it.
Looking at the composition
and the brushstrokes...
it appears to be Shin Saimdang's
“Chochung” paintings. I'm sure of it.
“Chochung” paintings...
Shin Saimdang's “Chochung” paintings?
Let me see. I can't seem to recall.
Uncle, think about it carefully.
Dad stole a lot of paintings, too.
Were the “Chochung” paintings
really not stolen by him?
With so many
“Chochung” paintings around...
If it's Shin Saimdang's,
it should be a collection.
Yes, with eight pictures.
[A collection? A collection...]
A collection...
I don't think it was one of his.
Is that so?
Why are you suddenly asking
about the “Chochung” paintings?
I have my reasons.
Okay, thank you, Uncle. Goodbye.
Oh my!
Why so startled?
Who did you talk with
to end up with such a long face?
Just someone I know.
Are you done confirming the piece?
More or less.
You know what? The more I think about
it, the more I can't understand this thief.
The “Chochung” collection
was definitely stolen, too.
So why send it to the museum?
I simply don't get it.
How in the world am I supposed
to catch him if I don't understand him?
Do you really want him to be caught?
You're asking that knowing
all that happened to me?
I'm planning to join the
investigations team tomorrow.
I'll check out the investigation and
nag them to hurry up and catch him.
Still the long face.
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I have to get going.
Hold on a sec.
I'll give you a ride.
No, I'm just going to take the buss.
Hey!
Shouldn't she be
the happiest person right now?
Did she think it was another one
of her father's stolen items?
So, in other words, you want
to help us out with the investigation.
Is that what you're saying?
Yes, that's exactly what I'm saying.
Bumsang, I still remember clearly
how last time you offered to help us...
and instead snuck away like a fox
that robbed the hen house.
And I remember how you
went back on your word.
I'm sincerely sorry about last time.
I had something urgent come up.
But today I will do my best to help you
and familiarize myself with on-site work.
In that case...
Thank you.
Then shall we go?
Where?
We have office duty today.
Excuse me?
Gosh, darnit.
Something just came up.
Bumsang!
What are you doing?
You're supposed to help us on-site.
These are the past year's
records of natives...
who entered and exited the country...
through the Busan and
Incheon ports. Go through these.
Check when Mr. Kim, Gyucheol, Yonggu
or Yongpal came in and went out.
Officers, aren't you investigating
the anonymous donor today?
The anonymous donor?
Why would we want to catch him?
He deserves a medal.
But you still have to investigate -
No, no.
We're tools of the people, so why would
we want to go against the people?
Rightly said. Not that
we're not going to investigate.
We'll do it later.
Take our time.
Work hard.
How do you expect me
to do this all by myself?
Bumsang, we need to catch Mr. Kim
so that you can sleep peacefully at night.
Right? Then...
Thank you!
Jeez...
Chohee, who do you think
Robin Hood is?
Who?
The anonymous donor. People
nicknamed him after Robin Hood.
Robin Hood?
Who do you think it is?
Let me see...
Did you hear?
Hear what?
The office ladies all think
that Bumsang is Robin Hood.
Bumsang?
Why would they think that?
‘Cause he's the national hero who brought back a national treasure.
No way.
So how are things
going with Bumsang?
What?
Are you two really dating?
No, not exactly.
But I'm planning
to keep up the act for a while.
What are you talking about?
It's complicated. Weren't you
on your way to eat? Hurry up. Go!
Bumsang is Robin Hood?
What?
People think I'm Robin Hood?
So now I'm suspected
of being that thief?
Dear Lord...
Who started that rumor?
How would I know?
Anyway, how's the Robin Hood
investigation going?
Don't get me started. I've been working
for five hours straight without food.
Working on what?
Don't ask.
Shouldn't you at least eat?
You wanna go eat then?
Right now?
Yeah, right now.
Sure. Let's go eat.
Okay, then I'll head over there.
Wait for me at that bench, okay?
Yeah, I did as much as I could.
[Taesoo Heo]
Why in the world is he so late?
Hey! Bumsang!
Why are you so late?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Chohee, listen to me carefully.
Don't be too shocked
and listen carefully.
What is it?
Your father...
He's alive.
What are you talking about?
Your father isn't dead. He's alive.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America