Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Episode 2
Chohee, good job.
You must be bushed.
Not at all.
I didn't expect you to come
all the way to Japan.
How could I not when I sent you
into the battlefield completely unarmed?
So you're saying you
didn't think I could handle it.
Why are you twisting my words around? I meant that I was worried about you.
I was very worried, so I'm very relieved that you're safe and sound.
You're going straight home, right?
Nope. I still have some
unfinished business to take care of.
Unfinished business?
Chief Kang!
Chief Noh,
what are you doing here?
Where is it?
Where's the item?
What item?
The porcelain bowl!
Where is it?
It'll be arriving real soon.
What in the world is going on?
Bumsang Kim! Over here!
What led to your success
in bringing it back?
How do you feel about
finding the national treasure?
I'm Chohee Heo from the
Cultural Heritage Administration.
I sincerely thank you
for restoring a national treasure.
Restoring?
What the - you little!
Sir, let me take
the national treasure.
H - hold on a sec.
Sir.
Sir, everyone's watching you.
- Sir.
- I'll give it, hold on.
Excuse me!
Mr. Kim, a word, please.
One moment.
National treasure. Like the name implies, it belongs to the country.
As a citizen of this country,
I did what I had to do.
Can you look over here, sir?
Amazing, Bumsang.
You're truly amazing.
Smiling when you're clearly pissed.
Not anyone can pull this off.
This is art in its own right.
Ugh, my head hurts.
You know how much it costs?
How much - ugh, my head...
What can you do?
The train has left the station.
Hey, forget about it.
I'll put it on display in a special room
at my museum, so come visit it.
You're pouring salt on the wound!
Ugh, my head.
I knew that Chohee Heo woman was trouble the moment I set eyes on her.
And this is how she screws me over?
Do you know how much it's worth?
Ugh, my head. My poor head.
Bumsang,
my grandmother used to say...
“Eating the easy piece of cake
causes indigestion.”
Things that come along too easily are nothing but trouble, so forget about it.
You think that's
as easily done as said?
Yes, sir.
You've accomplished quite a feat.
I thought you were coming back empty-handed. I should've known better.
I never imagined you'd come back
with such a priceless item.
Sir, let me explain what happened.
I don't know how you
ended up with the bowl...
but it was a smart choice
to donate it to the country.
But the smarter choice
would have been to bring it to me.
Then I could have done more than appoint you as a professor. What a pity.
Sir, the thing is...
We're done.
Yes, sir.
It's all Chohee Heo's fault!
I'll get her back, I will.
What about it?
Why is it my fault?
You think it's okay to wash
the lights and the darks together?
Take a look!
Everything's mottled!
You never do the laundry,
so what gives you the right to complain?
Just wear them.
You think that's your only offense?
Now what?
How could you make the front page,
and not say a word to me about it?
Let me see. It's not such
a big deal to make the front page.
How is it not? You were photographed together with Bumsang Kim.
This is a crowning moment
for our family.
What?
Whenever I watched
“"Discovering Cultural Assets"...
I knew he'd create
quite a stir someday.
Bumsang Kim,
you are the man.
Now that's a true patriot
for you. Definitely.
Patriot, my butt. Do you know
what this man's really like?
He's two-faced and a total pervert,
and he's extremely pathetic.
You don't know anything.
Who isn't pathetic to you?
Of course,
I'm the most pathetic of all.
Totally two-faced...
Yes, Chief?
The director's going to give you
a letter of commendation tomorrow.
A letter of commendation? Why not a cash bonus? It'll help with the rent.
You went on a paid trip and got to see Japan. What more do you want?
It wasn't a vacation. I nearly died
in a yakuza member's house.
How did it feel to go back
to Japan after all this time? Good?
No, not really.
I think things were a lot better
when I used to live in Japan.
I don't doubt it.
You had your father then.
Let's take another shot, Chief.
- Chief! I'm here.
- There you are. Have a seat.
What were you talking about?
Nothing in particular.
Let me pour you a drink.
Sure.
I didn't know you
invited Chief Kang, too.
Yeah, I'm creating an opportunity
for you young singles to mingle.
- What?
Chohee, I know you're
secretly interested in Chief Kang.
You weren't going to dip your feet
in the water, so I'm throwing you in.
Chief! What are you saying?
Who's interested in whom?
I never...
Don't assume things, sir.
Hey, kid, where are you going?
The bathroom.
Oh my god, so humiliating. Chief must be getting senile, completely senile.
So embarrassing.
I was just joking, but her reaction
is a little too exaggerated.
Maybe she was really
secretly interested in you.
How can you say that when
you saw how offended she was?
Why would she be offended?
You're quite the catch.
Chief, I'm a widower with a kid
and she's a single woman.
You're going to
make me the bad guy here.
Since we're on the topic, do you
want me to play matchmaker seriously?
It's about time you met someone.
Until when are you going
to leave Jiyoon to your mother?
It hasn't been very long
since my wife passed away.
I feel bad for Jiyoon, but as of yet
I still feel worse for my wife.
Yes, sir, I turned it in.
Don't worry.
Lucky Chohee.
She caught Mr. Kim and
retrieved the national treasure.
On top of that, she's receiving
a letter of commendation.
I envy her. I really do.
So what? She didn't solve
the Mr. Kim case on her own.
Why aren't we getting something?
Did we do nothing? Did you? Did you?
Now that you mention it. It was unfair the way she was chosen to go to Japan.
Joohyun should've gone, but Chief Noh used his influence to send her instead.
Joohyun, aren't you upset?
Since she supposedly lived for a while in Japan, it makes sense that she went.
More importantly, at this rate don't you think she might become the next chief?
What? Chief?
I mean, Chief Noh's retirement isn't far off, and if she continues scoring honors.
Mr. Nah, you may be older, but Chohee is your match in years of experience.
Right! On top of that,
she's Chief Noh's mistress –
I mean,
he completely adores her.
That's nonsense! She can't upset
the natural order of things.
In this land of upright citizens,
such a thing mustn't happen!
Whatever others may say,
the next chief should be...
How about discussing changes in political power later and getting to work?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Are you all right?
By any chance...
are you Mr. Bumsang Kim?
That would be me.
I get why you're getting an award,
but I don't see why I'm getting one.
Ditto. I couldn't even retrieve the items Mr. Kim smuggled, so why celebrate?
I know. If we don't get those items, the prosecution against him won't stand.
This uniform is uncomfortable.
It's been so long since I wore it last.
Here.
Let me do it for you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Bumsang Kim?
What's he doing here?
Didn't you hear? He's getting
a letter of appreciation with us.
What?
Why do you think
the reporters are here?
We're more like the garnish
to his steak. He's the man of the hour.
Hello, Chief.
Let me introduce you to Chief Shiwan Kang of the investigations team.
He constantly works hand in hand with the Cultural Heritage Administration.
Ah, we've met previously.
Congratulations.
And you already
know Chohee, right?
I know her extremely well.
So we meet again, Ms. Hanako Shizuki.
I mean, Ms. Chohee Heo.
“Chohee Heo.”
Seeing how you're named
after a historically famous artist,
your father must be
quite the scholar.
I guess sometimes the apple
does fall far from the tree.
If you're here to accept an award,
just accept it quietly.
Why are you
picking a fight? Huh?
Hey, government underling.
You really don't know why?
How can you
be so self-righteous...
after robbing a citizen
of his personal property?
I made you into a national hero.
Isn't that enough?
Begging on your knees wouldn't
get you forgiven at this point.
You're not really in a position
to be so self-righteous yourself.
Why? And what did I do?
- What did you do?
- Yes, what?
Was it the chairman of
Dongsang Group or Hyunjae Group?
Or maybe it was
the chairman of Ohsung Group?
Wh - what in the world
are you babbling about?
Who in this small country is capable of sending you to retrieve a priceless item?
It definitely has to be
one of those three men.
You shouldn't be so proud
of playing lackey a filthy rich man...
only to trick someone
out of his cat's food bowl.
There's a limit to
how much I'll take.
What about you?
You accused an upright citizen
of being a thief and tricked him...
spied on him and covertly
investigated him against his rights.
How are you going
to compensate for that? How?
Do you feel wronged?
Of course I do.
Then sue me.
What?
Where are you going?
We're not done talking yet.
Let go.
No way.
I said, let go!
And I said, no way!
Let go.
I already got hit once,
I'm not about to turn the other cheek.
Let go already!
Why so startled?
I do, after all..
have extremely high standards.
Mr. Kim! It's time!
I'm coming.
The crazy look fits you.
The flower looks good.
What's about his get-up?
Decked out in white. Who does
he think he is, a pimp? Crazy bastard.
Letter of appreciation, awarded to Bumsang Kim of Hanguk University.
In recognition of instilling
within our citizens an interest...
in our beautiful cultural heritage
and for retrieving a lost cultural relic.
On behalf of the entire nation, we award this letter of appreciation to you.
June 20, 2008. Signed by
Director Changhyun Kang of the CHA.
They're popping my eardrums. He looks like a total fop. What's the big deal?
Why were we told
to show up today?
Isn't it obvious?
We're the garnish!
In recognition of
instilling within our citizens...
an interest in
our beautiful cultural heritage...
What's with him?
Leave him be.
Hey, if dinner tonight isn't
choice meat, I'm skipping out.
No one's stopping you.
I'm staying to eat!
If Chohee really becomes chief,
I'm resigning! Resigning, I tell you!
Excuse me,
may I ask you something?
And so we conclude
the ceremony. Thank you.
Director Changhyun Kang of
the Cultural Heritage Administration.
Good work.
‘The director of the CHA...'
This is Namyoung Ko, head curator
of the National Central Museum.
Good job.
‘Head curator of the
National Central Museum...'
Congressman Junpil Lee,
three-time Congressman...
and chairman of the National Assembly's Cultural Assets Bureau.
‘Three-time Congressman...'
Lastly, Joongho Hyun,
president of Hanguk University.
Ah, sir.
You're Bumsang Kim of our Department of Art History and Archeology, right?
Yes, sir.
I've heard a lot
about you from the dean.
It's an honor
to finally meet you.
Same here.
Let's head over to my office
to talk over tea.
Sure.
Let's go.
Come on.
Oh man, I have to impress them.
What was the title
of the TV show you're on?
“Discovering Cultural Assets.”
“Discovering Cultural Assets,” huh?
I watch it quite regularly. You've accomplished quite a feat this time.
Please stop it, sir! I've already told you I'm a member of the regulations teams.
I'm not an
appraiser of old books.
Tsk, tsk. That man doesn't even know how to properly treat an old man.
There's something strange
about this book!
I think you're the strange one here.
Just leave already.
Please go on ahead.
Is something wrong?
I want to take a look at the book.
I'll be right there.
Will you leave already?
He's quite courteous, unlike
most young people these days.
So he is.
- Leave, please!
- Wait.
One moment, please.
Sir, may I take a look?
Here you are.
Where is the
Preservation Science Laboratory?
Preservation...?
Please wrap everything up.
Yes, ma'am.
Can't believe they gave a letter of appreciation to that loser. Unbelievable.
Joohyun, what's going on?
Something big is going on at the Preservation Science Lab! C'mon!
How awesome.
So handsome.
He looks like a celebrity.
So cool.
He's really skilled.
We'll begin the cleaning process
after taking some pictures first.
But isn't the cellulose
damage too extreme?
We'll have to separate the sheets
using a reinforcing agent.
Please prepare the reinforcing agent and material necessary for cleaning.
Yes, sir.
Let's begin.
Okay, take the picture.
We can't be sure
until further examination...
but seeing how the sheets were stuck
so meticulously into the binding...
it appears to be a banned book
from the Joseon Era.
If that's true, it's a rare book that's priceless, historically speaking.
Yes, I'd say there's
a good chance it is.
And to find it like this.
I'm amazed by your ability.
You flatter me, sir.
Luck was on my side.
Mr. Kim, may I make a request?
Of course, anything at all.
Right now the world is overrun by thieves who are better appraisers than experts.
We need a man of your untainted patriotism and natural caliber...
in order to purge our society
of the crimes against cultural assets.
I'm not quite so qualified,
but I'll help in any way I can.
Please become an advisory member
of our regulations team.
Excuse me?
With the CHA's intelligence capabilities and the investigations team's mobility...
we have nothing to fear
if we add the expert ability...
of an academic like yourself.
What do you say?
Will you become an advisory member?
That's impossible!
Absolutely impossible!
Chohee, what did you say?
(What are you doing?)
She said it was impossible.
Are you out of your mind?
What do you have against Bumsang Kim to say something like that?
I said it before
I could stop myself...
Do you think it's easy
to recruit a man of that caliber?
Think a little before you act!
He may have the ability, but he doesn't have the constitution to do our work.
And how do you know that?
Besides, did you think that was
the time and place for you to speak up?
How could you do that
in front of the director?
I'm sorry.
Fine, get back to work.
She won't get away with that ridiculous behavior in front of the director.
A written apology is a given
and a salary reduction is a possibility.
Even Chief Noh's coddling
won't save her butt this time.
Why does Chohee deem
Bumsang Kim to be so unworthy?
Does she consider anyone worthy?
Nope.
I'm sorry for all
the dissension I caused.
What do you mean?
I should be the one apologizing.
Don't pay any attention
to what she said.
And could you reconsider my offer?
I would love to become
an advisory member...
but I don't want to cause
discord within the CHA.
Harmony in the organization
is critical, isn't it?
Mr. Kim...
You offered me a chance to work for the country, so it breaks my heart to refuse.
Please take care, Director.
I never thought she'd do me a service, but that Chohee Heo woman saved me.
If it wasn't for her, I would
have been helpless to refuse.
Just the thought of it
gives me the chills.
Of course I can't forgive her for cutting me down in front of all those people.
But everyone already knew of my noble character so they didn't believe a word.
She probably got quite
an earful from her superiors.
So the director offered you
the advisory position, but you refused?
Right.
I refused quite graciously.
Why would I want to work for the Man? It's a thankless job with little pay.
You idiot!
Why?
Know what you just refused? That's the highway to the CHA committee position.
And it pays a lot. The lecturer job and that TV show gig don't even compare.
You go in as a committee member,
rub elbows with the influential...
and who's to say you won't be
the director someday?
Director of the CHA?
Yes, idiot. If you were so clueless,
you should have asked me for advice.
You're still on your high horse
even after losing the professorship.
It doesn't make sense to lose someone like Bumsang Kim because of Chohee.
Shouldn't we apologize
to him and bring him in?
Do you think she'll apologize?
I'll go in her stead. I'll go apologize sincerely and ask him once more.
Think that'll convince him?
He doesn't need us.
We need an advisory member immediately, so find some candidates.
Professors or section chiefs
at museums are good.
That Chohee screws up everything.
Chief, an accomplice of Mr. Kim's just confessed what the smuggled item is.
Really?
Yes.
What's the item?
I'm not sure.
Let's go.
All right.
Joohyun, you, too.
This is the “Naegeumgang,”
painted by Kyeomjae Jeongsun...
the authority of real-life landscape paintings of the later Joseon era.
The owner was Mr. Park of Namwon
in the Northern Cholla Province.
In July of 2005, after it was designated a national cultural asset, it was stolen.
It was smuggled into Japan by Mr. Kim, but the yen currency dropped in value.
We suspect it was smuggled back
when its value skyrocketed here.
So we don't know
who received it from Mr. Kim?
Officer Cho.
Yes, the thing is, that is everything
the accomplice Piljoong Park knew.
With Mr. Kim refusing to acknowledge all this, it'll be hard to get a confession.
Still so incompetent at your work
after how many years as a fuzz?
Well, about fifteen...
Hey!
So we have no choice other
than to sniff around here and there.
We'll take
Insa-dong and Jangan-pyeong.
We'll investigate the smuggling
routes within the country.
Then let's go to our respective
areas and scope things out.
- Yes, sir.
- Good work.
Don't call me a fuzz.
That's what you are.
Go ahead.
You fuzz!
I'm sorry.
Go first.
No, you first.
[Briefing Room]
Lady Luck's on your side today.
Still under sixteen.
Hit me, hit me.
I'm almost out.
Let's stop.
Hit me!
Don't you think
you're pushing your luck?
After all those black jacks,
you still want to risk it all?
Stop while you're ahead!
Hit me, hit me!
What?
Behind you...
We're under attack!
Hello.
You startled me!
I was more startled. Why did
you start running? C'mon.
Did you eat?
I'm starving.
How much did you make?
This is all? Pathetic.
Stop, stop.
You should've called first.
I nearly had a heart attack.
And how would
I know your latest number?
If people find out we're close, that'll
be the end of me in this line of work.
Then quit.
Thievery's all I'm good at,
so how can I quit?
You're the one who should quit.
You're the daughter of an art thief.
It's ridiculous that you work for the man who always stuffed your dad into prison.
Uncle...
I know you joined that regulations team to find your dad, but it's time to stop.
Seven years of no news
means he's a dead man.
If he were alive, that jerk Noh would've stuffed him into prison a long time ago.
So...
If he's alive,
I'll be the one to catch him.
Before Chief Noh can catch him,
I'll catch him and lock him up myself.
That is, if he's alive...
You impertinent punk.
Oh, by the way, there's a new item
on the market these days, right?
Dunno.
Kyeomjae's “Naegeumgang.”
Who has it?
I seriously don't know.
You're the regulations team,
I'm a middleman.
If we share information, that's an infraction of the unspoken rules.
We have to uphold the codes
of our respective spheres.
Shut up and foot the bill.
How come I paid everything?
This is my number for the time being,
so tell Gyoon I want to drink with him.
- This number?
- Yeah.
All right.
Oh, by the way...
What is it?
This.
What is that?
What do you
think you're doing?
- Take it!
- What are you doing?
Please, take it.
Soyeon's starting school, right?
Buy her a new backpack.
And don't work too hard. I don't
want to be the one to catch you, okay?
Then I'm off.
I don't want to get
caught by you, either.
Do you know
what you just refused?
That position is the highway to becoming a CHA commissioner. And it pays a lot.
You go in as a committee member,
rub elbows with the powerful...
and who's to say you won't
be the director someday?
Argh, I'm such an idiot. It was a golden opportunity to enter into public office.
Ow, my head...
Wait a moment. Should I
just go and say I reconsidered?
No, no. I have to
save face. Can't do that.
You don't have to submit
curricula for these two courses.
Why? I can't just recycle last semester's. I bulked it up so submit this copy.
That's not it. Um.
Professor Yongchul Gong
will explain things to you.
I'm teaching those courses.
What?
I have to fulfill some mandatory credits as professor. I'm incredibly sorry.
Don't be. I was gonna cut back on some lectures since I'm so busy these days.
That's a relief.
Ah, I heard you were checking out professorship positions at other schools.
How's that going?
Something'll come up.
I'm sure. But do you think other
schools will be easier to penetrate?
After all, most professors hate
TV personalities like yourself.
And you're a graduate
from a different school.
Isn't that enough to get you
dropped in the initial interview?
Oh man, look at the time.
I need to attend a professors' meeting.
If you look in the countryside, I'm sure someone will take you. Good luck.
What? Ugh,
I wanna just kick his -
Hello, this is Bumsang Kim.
Who?
Joohyun Wang of the CHA?
‘Here about
the advisory position?'
'Of course it's their loss
to lose a talent like me.'
‘Give it your all to convince me.
I'll pretend to give in reluctantly.'
You were offended by
Chohee yesterday, weren't you?
Don't worry about it.
No, I know you were offended.
Reputation and pride are crucial
for an academic like yourself.
That slanderous attack
must've been hurtful.
Thank you for your
sincere consideration.
I spent all night wondering...
if I was right in refusing
the position for the sake of my pride.
Perhaps it was a narrow-minded decision on my part...
Narrow-minded!
It's not narrow-minded at all.
I feel bad for making you
come all this way.
Though of course
I'm glad to see you again.
There's no need to feel bad.
Everything worked out for the best.
Really?
The newly instated Professor Yongchul Gong agreed to take the position.
Wh - what?
At first I thought it absolutely had
to be you. But I realized I was wrong.
Someone of your caliber
shouldn't be tied down to the CHA.
You should do bigger
and better things than that.
Wait, so, Joohyun...
Of course there will be people at the CHA who will resent you for refusing.
But they're small fry that don't know the importance of pride, so ignore them.
Look here, Ms. Joohyun Wang... Then why did you come to see me today?
What?
Oh, of course to apologize
for yesterday's occurrence.
I sincerely apologize on behalf
of Chohee Heo and the CHA. I'm sorry.
Drink up. You must
be thirsty. You talked a lot.
So why isn't
Chohee Heo here herself?
Of course she should be here,
but she's not the type to apologize.
She's so into scoring honors...
she's probably sweeping the streets
for the item this very moment.
What item?
I trust you, but it's
a matter of strict confidentiality.
Then, I should get going.
I'll see you again sometime.
Yes, see you again.
Thank you for that.
Why are all the CHA women weird?
Are they all jinxed?
So Chohee Heo is looking
for an item, eh?
I really don't know.
Really.
I gave up that life
a long time ago, so don't ask me.
I know it hasn't been that long
since you were released from prison.
The CHA's information network
is slower than I thought.
I went in for adultery. Got into
a bit of trouble thanks to the wife.
Sorry I'm not much help.
I sincerely thank you
for cooperating.
If you have any information,
please contact me at the CHA.
I really don't know!
Hey, it's the national hero!
What brings you here?
Cut the crap. What item
was that woman looking for?
The regulations team is looking for it, which means it's tainted.
There's no point
in fishing for it now.
I have my reasons.
What's the item?
Kyeomjae's “Naegeumgang,”
I think she said?
“Naegeumgang?”
So, who's the specialist
fisherman these days?
Jongtae Lee of Cheongyecheon.
Third-time offender of trafficking stolen goods. And he's an expert of paintings.
Can't be him. He doesn't have the funds. How about Chulyong Uhm of Daegu?
Chulyong Uhm? Probably not him. He repented and attends church religiously.
Dari Jong of Daegu.
Didn't he stow away to China?
Jongtaek Go of Insa-dong.
He followed Dari Jong.
What the...
Jichul Kim of Hwanghak-dong.
Right! Kim's good
at fishing the big ones.
He's in prison right now.
Giljin Nah of Dapship-ri.
Inchool Park of Andong.
Jongtaek Go of Insa-dong.
We already
mentioned Jongtaek Go!
Yonggu Lee of Uijongbu.
Old habits die hard, right?
That also goes for dancing, right?
Welcome.
Sis, some well-mannered and good-looking guys are interested in you.
I don't see any.
You have high standards.
All right, I'll make sure you
have love and pleasure tonight.
Tell me what type
of man you want.
There is a type...
Who, who?
I'll set it up right away.
Let me see...
Am I seeing things? You're not the type to grace these halls, yet here you are.
I heard you're fishing for something different these days, not your usual item.
News travels fast.
How'd you hear?
If you're dipping your feet into
a new pond, keep it on the down low.
Why are you
trailing dirt everywhere?
Aw, man.
If you're interested, just say so.
Lord, no. Why would I want
something that already stinks?
What the...
What do you mean it stinks?
See that over there?
She already caught scent of the stink.
Ah, there he is.
Oh, excuse me.
Look who it is.
It's Chohee Heo from the CHA.
Bumsang Kim?
I never imagined
I'd meet you in a place like this.
I don't want to deal with you
right now, so get out of the way.
We should have a drink together
when we met so coincidentally.
Get out of the way!
You shouldn't be so rude
to someone who's being considerate.
Let go!
Wait, wait. If you don't feel like
drinking, shall we dance instead?
Oh my!
Let go already!
It common courtesy
to dance at least one song.
Oh yeah?
What a complete weirdo!
Excuse me.
Where did he go?
What was
Bumsang Kim's problem?
Is she gone?
Whew, that was a close shave.
Mr. Kim, thanks a lot.
No need to thank me.
See how it stinks? The “Naegeumgang.” What are you going to do with it?
Oh, Gyoon? What's up?
What do you mean, “What's up?”
Do you know what time it is?
Are you coming home or not?
Um, I'll be home soon. Yeah.
Hello, this is
Chohee Heo of the CHA.
Hello?
What did you say?
[Office]
Honey, it's your phone.
Who is it?
Chief, the item is on the move.
What?
Where's the location?
The entrance to
Mt. Jangyong in Okcheon.
And the investigations team?
Did you call them?
Yes, we agreed
to meet at the tollgate.
All right. Let's meet up
at the Okcheon tollgate.
Yes, sir.
Why can't the item move
during broad daylight?
Why in the middle of the night?
That's what I'm saying.
Joohyun, what's wrong?
Yes?
Nothing. Go, go.
Chief?
Yes?
My gut tells me
something's wrong.
Night runs like this
always have a bad feel.
Did you ever even have a good
feeling about anything before?
Chief, that's not fair at all.
It sounded like you were dismissing
my intuition, am I wrong?
Yes, you heard wrong.
Okay, we're off!
By the way, what is the item?
Mt. Jangyong
Hey, do you have kimchi on you?
Why would I have kimchi?
Mr. Nah! Mr. Nah!
Is the item safe?
We know that
you're just a delivery boy.
We won't arrest you,
so just hand the item over.
Hey, stop!
Take me with you!
There's a car! Careful!
Hey, look!
Chohee!
Where's the item? Stand up!
Where's the item? Where is it?
I don't know.
Where is it?
Where's the item, you punk?
I really don't know.
All I did was ride the motorcycle.
Ah, it's beautiful.
The “Naegeumgang.”
I wonder if Chohee Heo
enjoys the butt of the joke?
Tell Chairman Jang that I want twenty smackers. Then I'll hand it over.
A tainted piece like this
is hard to handle.
The regulations team
is already on your tail.
Aw, man.
Then what should I do?
If there's no use in holding onto it,
isn't there just one possibility?
Darnit.
Chohee, did you get
the location and time right?
Yes.
Are you sure
it wasn't a prank call?
It wasn't. The person
knew the “Naegeumgang” well.
So what? If he wasn't planning to
move it, it was essentially a prank call.
My car... darnit, Chohee!
Let's call it a night.
What? What are we doing
here in the middle of the night?
I knew this mission
had a bad feeling.
Next time you wanna go on a
wild goose chase, go by yourself, okay?
I understand that you want to earn
more honors, but go a little easy.
Haven't you considered the idea that something like this is a nuisance to all?
Then again...
if you were the type to consider that,
this would've never happened. Goodbye.
Don't worry about it, Chohee.
It could happen to anyone.
Come on, let's grab some breakfast.
I'll buy you some hot soup.
You're going to send me
to an early grave, I swear.
What woman says she'll come right home and doesn't show up ‘til dawn?
Was your finger broken? Why couldn't you call me? It's common courtesy...
Then again, there are times
when you just can't call.
I'm not curious at all.
Gyoon, there's
this person on my team.
Thanks to him, we spent the entire night driving around a mountain on a fake tip.
That jerk! So did
he apologize to everyone?
No.
How could he not?
It's obvious he's apologetic.
Does he have to put it into words?
He should say it all the more
because it's obvious.
If you don't put things into words,
people will never know.
Sis, when you get to work tomorrow, advise him to apologize to everyone.
You do the dishes today.
Thanks for the food.
Ah, what am I
going to do with her?
I'm really sorry about
what happened last night.
I'm sincerely sorry.
I'm sorry about
yesterday. I'm sorry.
My bad.
Darnit.
What are you looking for?
Mr. Nah, where is everyone?
Didn't you hear?
Joohyun found the “Naegeumgang.”
What?
Sucks to be her. Ow.
“Naegeumgang.”
I knew you'd make us proud.
Joohyun, how did you find it?
You've got
your priorities all wrong.
Having caused all of us so much trouble yesterday, you should apologize first.
I don't even expect an apology.
Take some lessons from Joohyun.
She finds things without
causing us trouble. Isn't it great?
What are you all doing here?
Let's start the morning meeting.
Yes, sir.
Does it really matter
who found it and how?
What matters is this valuable cultural asset is back in our country's care.
Ah, but since you're
dying of curiosity, I'll tell you.
Mr. Kim helped me.
Bumsang Kim.
“Bumsang Kim?”
Bumsang Kim helped her?
Hold on.
It's Chohee Heo.
I never imagined
I'd run into you here.
Bumsang Kim!
What is the busy government
employee doing here?
Ah, you want to thank me for helping
to find the “Naegeumgang,” right?
Hey.
Was it you?
Did you plan the whole thing?
Isn't this a bit
rough for a thank you?
Your innocent act
isn't fooling anyone!
You hid the “Naegeumgang”
to screw me over!
Got proof? Do you?
Ms. Heo, let me give you some advice.
Get rid of that bad habit of accusing people without evidence. Bye.
How immature.
Was it fun playing
a joke like that? Was it?
If you're going to play a joke,
you should've just done it to me.
Why does my entire team have to stay up all night and suffer on your whim?
Why?
I found an item you guys couldn't. Shouldn't you be thanking me?
You're pretty darn transparent, you know?
We nearly had it, and so it was useless
to get a hold of it. So you gave it up.
Otherwise, after your joke, you would've handed it over to some chairman.
Am I wrong?
Think what you will.
But you think people will believe you?
I don't care if they don't.
Because I'll remember it.
And let me give you some advice.
Keep your nose clean.
If I so much as get a whiff of stolen goods near you, I'll bring you down.
If you don't want any regrets, then don't get your hands dirty, all right? Got it?
You're the one who's going
to have regrets, not me.
That jerk. If I catch another toe
out of line, I won't restrain myself.
The following items were retrieved from the Hayeon Gallery robbery of April 21st.
This book is the single item
we couldn't retrieve.
According to the Cultural Properties Research Facility the book title is...
Ah, excuse me for a moment.
The title is “Tonggamjeolyo.”
That's the “Tonggamjeolyo?”
The “Tonggamjeolyo” was printed
by a wooden press...
but this was definitely
printed by a metal one.
Bumsang Kim?
That's not “Tonggamjeolyo.”
It's “Songjopyojeonchongryu,”
which was printed...
during Taejong's rule
with the gyemi print type.
Mr. Kim, I'm not sure why you're here, but this is none of your business.
Chohee, you're being rude.
How can you disregard
the opinion of our advisory member?
Committee member?
Please be the bigger person.
Let me make a formal introduction.
It took a lot of effort to recruit him.
This is the new advisory member of
our regulations team, Bumsang Kim.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America