Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Episode 5
Hey! Isn't that Bumsang?
So it is.
Chief Kang, didn't you say
he wasn't coming?
I thought so, too.
I wonder what happened.
Weren't you unsure
about that Professor Gong?
I guess things
worked out for the best.
Aw man, I should have
volunteered for this mission...
Why did you suddenly change your mind? You said you weren't coming.
It's an ideal chance for me score
brownie points with the director.
I can't miss that chance
just because I don't like you.
Yeah, I should have known.
Hold on a sec.
Yes, Chief.
I'm with Bumsang. Yes.
She said her daddy was taken away
far more times than my daddy.
For them, it's a worse pain
knowing that their father is a thief.
Would you say the same
if it were your father?
Yes, sir.
Chief Kang saw us together.
He thinks it's for the better.
Of course it is.
Yongchul is no match for me at all.
Why, do you want me
to bring him back?
No, not at all.
Ah, see that dude with the red tie?
Remember him.
Why?
You think the filthy rich
handle deals on their own?
That's the guy who handles business
for Chairman Kim of Dongwan Group.
Ah, the woman in the lavender works
for Chairman Oh of Hyunjae Group.
I heard she also deals for
Chairman Jang these days as well.
Ah, is she your substitute?
Bingo.
Isn't it a little risky for you to be here? You might run into Chairman Jang.
Don't worry. He has no interest
in attending parties like these.
A lot of guests attended
upon hearing that you'd be here.
You should make a speech...
No. A simple
greeting should suffice.
Have you been well,
Chairman Jang?
It's been a while.
It's been seven years.
What brings you here?
Thought I'd thank you
for getting me out of prison.
How do you like
the “Bihaedangjib?”
I have no interest in books. I accepted it because my friends would enjoy it.
Then I'll be visiting you soon
with an item you'd appreciate.
There's no need.
Don't cause any trouble
while you're here.
Let's go.
The old man still
has a fiery temper.
Ow, my feet.
You borrowed those shoes, too?
What was I supposed to do?
I don't have any of my own.
Can you get any more pathetic?
You're how old and you still
don't have a pair of heels?
I don't see why it's any of your business. Man, when are the deals gonna start?
That's what I'm saying.
They're stalling today for some reason.
Ow, my feet.
What are you doing?
Quiet. It's Chairman Jang.
Chairman Jang!
Oh my god!
The bag, the bag...
What are you doing?
Joohyun is gonna have a fit...
Shut up!
Ugh, really!
What are you doing?
I nearly had a heart attack!
Why is he here today?
You shooting a movie?
You've clearly watched too many.
Of all the things to imitate...
What are you gonna do about the bag? Joohyun emphasized it was from Paris.
Ort court or something like that!
It's fine. It's totally fine.
If she says anything,
you're taking the blame, got it?
And how dare
you try to choke me?
Hey, I didn't try to choke you.
I merely grabbed your neck.
That was grabbing?
That was not grabbing!
That wasn't how I did it.
I did it lightly, like this.
Thank you for attending this charity auction despite your busy schedules.
We invite you to create a beautiful world by helping our less fortunate neighbors.
Please watch the screen.
Okay. As soon as the item
is identified, give us a call.
It seems the illegal auction will
begin soon. They're on the move.
Yeah?
Are the riot police standing by?
Yes, sir.
What if the “Bihaedangjib”
doesn't show today?
Don't jinx the mission.
It was hard enough getting here.
We have to get something out of all this.
As soon as we confirm there is
an illegal auction, we'll raid the place.
What the hell?
This isn't good.
The eagle is set to fly. When the sparrow appears, we'll swoop in, so give us a call.
Seriously, where's the creativity?
Of all the possible codenames, “sparrow?” How trite.
Shut it!
It's just been used so many times.
Did I choose the codenames?
We're gonna settle this later.
Dude, why are you
so sensitive these days?
Everyone look sharp. Let's score
some big points today, okay?
Yes, sir!
Why is Yonggu so late?
Are you sure he made it to the hotel?
He said he was almost here.
Hey, isn't that
the girl from the CHA?
Look at that.
Who's the sucker beside her?
This party has a lot of
unexpected guests.
Sir!
Oh, Yonggu. I have something
you need to take care of.
Wait, sir. There's trouble.
I was coming into the hotel
when I saw the fuzz everywhere.
What?
I think they're onto us.
Everywhere?
All around!
Since everyone here is already well informed, I won't give any explanations.
Previewing time is over.
Let's begin the bidding.
The chicken has flown the coop.
Here we go.
First we'll reveal the highest written bid. It is 2.5 million dollars. We'll start there.
I'm sorry, today's auction is cancelled. I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Sir!
Yonggu Lee?
Let's go!
Mr. Kim!
Hey!
What is the meaning of this?
Police.
We're here about an illegal auction and a violation of protected cultural assets.
We ask that you cooperate.
We can't let you.
- Search the premises.
- You can't do this.
What the...
What happened?
They took everything and ran.
Chohee, where are you?
Yes, Mr. Kim is back in Korea.
I'm telling the truth.
We're following him right now
so please send backup. Yes.
Hey! What took you so long?
One, two, three!
There's no time. I'll go ahead,
follow me when you can.
Excuse me, Chief.
Can I go with you?
It might be dangerous
so stay here.
No. Bumsang's out there,
so I have to go. I want to go.
Do what you want, then.
Tch! Think I can't guess
what you're thinking?
Planning to keep Bumsang and me apart? No~ that's not gonna happen.
Chief, wait for me. Chief!
Oh my god.
How could you lose them?
Who knew he was
going to make that turn?
That's why I told you to stay in that lane. Why did you suddenly change lanes?
I'm not exactly experienced in these kinds of situations. I'm not a cop, yanno.
I'm disappointed we lost the chance to catch Mr. Kim and Yonggu Lee together.
Oh yeah. Yonggu.
Ah, it's beautiful.
The “Naegeumgang.”
I think I have an idea
where their hideout is.
What?
The hideout?
How did he find that out?
Not sure, I didn't
ask him the details.
Anyway, they're headed
to the Incheon Port.
The Incheon Port?
Darnit, they all look the same.
It'll be hard to find.
Ow!
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Ouch...
Did you sprain your ankle?
No, I'm fine. I'm all right.
What do you mean you're
all right? Try and move it.
It's fine.
Geez, you're such a klutz.
I'm fine, I tell you.
Hey, Bumsang!
What?
The thing is,
thanks for coming today.
And when we fought
in front of Cheoljin Lee's house...
you said to let him go
because you felt bad for the kids.
I just want to thank you
for thinking that.
You probably don't understand why,
but I just wanted to say thank you.
Thank me all at once
after we find the book.
Huh.
Did I ask a lot from you?
I just wanted this one job to go right, and you led the stinkin' dogs into the house?
That's not it. I didn't know Bumsang
was chummy with the regulations team.
That's not how he rolls.
Stop your nonsense.
Yonggu, how tall are you?
I'm five-seven.
You're taller than me.
Hey!
Go order me a coffin
that fits a man of five-seven.
- Sir?
- Yes, sir.
What's so funny? Go move
everything before the fuzz get here.
Yes, sir.
You wanna be a bum?
Is that it?
Ugh, you're such a deadweight.
Jeez...
We have no other choice.
We have to grab the book first.
Are you crazy?
What if we get caught?
We just need to creep up there undetected and steal it.
Stop with the ridiculous plan now
and just wait until Chief Kang arrives.
And if we do that we'll lose them
like last time. I'll be right back.
Go wait in the car.
I'll do it.
What?
You think you can run away with that ankle? Go back and call Chief Kang.
Go on!
Use your brain, if you have one.
The fuzz will be here any minute!
Use your heads!
Hurry and move them along.
Darnit, where is she?
I told her to wait in the car.
Chohee's not picking up.
She's not?
That's strange.
Let me try calling Bumsang.
She did say it was
somewhere around here.
I never expected to meet the Bumsang Kim I've been hearing so much about.
Cut the crap. I'll give you
the book, so let the woman go.
First the bowl, then the “Naegeumgang,” and now you've ruined today's party.
Our paths have crossed
one too many times.
I wish I could take this opportunity
to teach you a life lesson...
but I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Hand over the “Bihaedangjib!”
Let her go, and I'll hand it over.
You must be confused.
Who's in the more vulnerable
situation right now? Huh?
You're right. Who is in the more vulnerable situation? Huh?
Hey, hey, stop bluffing
and hand it over.
You think I'm bluffing?
I don't value this thing one bit.
It's not mine, so I don't care
who owns it or if it burns to ashes.
You're not really going
to set it on fire, are you?
You think I won't?
Hey! What are you doing?
How much were you aiming to get for this? How high did you set the price?
Enough so that even the middleman would get hundreds of thousands, right?
Well, there goes
a hundred thousand.
Are you out of your mind?
So let her go already.
A hundred thousand wasn't enough?
There goes a
few hundred thousand.
Let her go!
There, we let her go,
so give the remaining pages to us.
Don't give it to them.
You can't, okay?
We don't have much time.
Hand it over.
You know the saying,
“Pearls before swine?”
If it's gonna end up in your hands,
it's better off as ashes.
Hey!
Darnit!
Go after them!
Yes, sir!
Stop right there, you bastard!
Hey!
Joohyun, the siren.
Chohee, Bumsang,
are you guys all right?
Bumsang, I was so worried about you. Hurry and get in the car.
We're fine. Mr. Kim's probably
still lurking around. You should hurry.
We'll be right back.
- No, wait. Bumsang!
- Joohyun.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
I'm fine, but how could you set
the “Bihaedangjib” on fire like that?
Hey, no matter what, that book
is not important than a human life.
Who cares if a thief owns it?
At least it's safe.
At least that's better than it no longer existing. How could you burn it, huh?
How could I burn what?
You still don't know me at all.
C'mon, follow me.
Come on. I'll take you
to see the “Bihaedangjib.”
Here.
That book from earlier, that was an experimental copy my students made.
It just happened to be in the car.
If Mr. Kim didn't fall for it,
I would've handed the real thing over.
But it seems he has bad eyesight.
Or maybe he's just dumb.
From all the bleaching.
You're speechless
with gratitude, aren't you?
I found Mr. Kim for you. And the “Bihaedangjib.” And I saved your life.
When are you gonna
repay me for all this?
It'll take your entire life...
Oh my!
If you came out to exercise,
don't just stand around staring blankly.
I'll stare if I want.
You're not acting like your usual self.
Did you find yourself a man?
Am I not allowed to?
What's this? You're smiling?
So it must be true.
Who is it?
Who could it be? Who...
By any chance, is it
that Chief Whatchamacallit?
You little punk!
Have some respect.
Why'd you hit me! Stop wasting your time here, and let's go have breakfast.
Gyoon!
What?
I found the “Bihaedangjib.”
Sis...
Aren't you gonna congratulate me?
You found one little thing and
you expect me to congratulate you?
You've got guts.
Dad stole loads of things.
Ms. Heo, you're gonna
have to work even harder, got it?
Ah, what a loss. It was a great chance
to catch both Mr. Kim and Yonggu.
What did you expect from
the investigations team?
At least we found the book.
What if we hadn't even found that?
All of us would've
kicked the bucket...
What a relief.
You're right. And this
is all thanks to Chohee.
I've never been
so grateful to her before.
I know, right?
And she never looked sexier.
You thought so, too?
With that figure, of course.
So true, so true.
You two, get things straight.
Chohee didn't look fabulous.
My dress looked fabulous.
Yeah! That dress
looked awfully expensive.
Right, right! Hey, didn't you say you
were gonna buy coffee this morning?
- I did.
- Let's take Joohyun with us.
I'll buy.
Good morning.
By the way, Chohee.
Yeah?
Don't forget to dry clean the dress.
I'll leave that to you.
I was gonna do that.
“Don't forget
to dry clean the dress.”
What's with the tongue rolling?
Haute couture...
Ah, Joohyun... "Dress"...
If we don't find it, are you going to
give the recording to the press?
Hey, I'm trying my best.
So don't be like that.
I didn't erase it, did I?
[Hey, Chohee! You're too late.
I already erased everything!]
What the heck is this?
[You dare to blackmail me with this pathetic recording? What nonsense.]
[Don't underestimate me. You'll bite off more than you can chew, understand?]
[Since I have an audience, I'll sing you
a little song just for the heck of it.]
[If this a recording you'll have to forget~ Don't pine after it, dry your tears~]
[Dry your tears,
you little kid. Bye, bye.]
Bumsang, what will you do next?
Ugh... ow, it hurts.
Huh?
Jeez, when did I get this stain?
It'll take your entire life...
Was she that happy?
Speak of the devil.
What do you want
so early in the morning?
What do you mean,
early in the morning?
Take a look at the clock.
See know how late it is?
Huh?
Wow, it's already this late?
Bumsang, can we meet up later?
You called me out
and you dare to be late?
You dare to sing
with that level of skill?
What are you
talking about? Sing?
You erased it.
I was gonna erase it for you.
Took you long enough.
Here!
You called me out
to give me this?
No way.
Let's go have a drink.
A drink?
I mean, I want to
thank you, you know.
You said you wanted an official
thank you when we found the book.
You attended the party, found the “Bihaedangjib,” and you saved my life.
Thank you.
What's with the handshake?
Let's put the past behind us
and start anew.
Like we have
a past to put behind.
The slate's clean, right?
Forever!
Yes, forever.
You promised.
Okay.
Haven't seen you around in a while. What brings you here?
Why are you so defensive?
I have good news.
Good news? What?
You're retiring early?
We found the “Bihaedangjib.”
Chohee found it.
That brat, she's good.
It's been seven years
since Taesoo disappeared.
The statute of
limitations is almost up.
More of the items
he stole will surface.
Not like you can even dream
of getting a glance of them.
They're going to pass
from one rich guy to another.
Somehow when you state the obvious,
it pisses me off even more.
You know why? Because Chohee
likes me more, and that irks you.
Think what you will.
I'll be the one to walk her
down the aisle anyway.
Don't even think about it!
I'm going to marry her off.
Like a regulations team member walking in with a middleman isn't weird.
What's it to you
if she walks in with me?
Does she even have a man?
There's a guy I'm nudging her way,
but who knows.
He's not a cop, is he?
How'd you know?
What cop?
It's not Chief Kang, is it?
I don't understand you at all.
Why do you insist on working with me?
I'm the one
who doesn't understand.
What's with that delusion
that I insist on working with you?
Oh my, oh my,
what do you mean delusion?
I'm here,
sitting in your car, aren't I?
You called me here.
And you specifically asked for me.
That's because you're in charge
of the Hahman robbery case.
Chief.
Yes?
Be honest for once.
You think I don't realize that
you're doing this because of Bumsang?
You don't give me any opportunities
to meet up with him, not one...
What are you doing?
Joohyun.
Chief.
What can I do to convince you
that I'm not interested in you?
Would it help if I created an opportunity for you and Bumsang to get together?
You'll set it up?
Okay, call me
when you get near. Okay.
Hey, that was Chief Kang.
He wants to have a drink.
Chief Kang?
So I told him to come here.
Is that okay?
Of course it's okay.
Is he coming alone?
I had no idea
you were going to be here.
And I had no idea
you were coming, too.
The way I see it, that weird rumor started because you chase after Bumsang.
Rumor? What rumor?
Oh my, you didn't hear?
It was quite a rumor.
Apparently Chohee seduced Bumsang
in the hot springs and had a kid...
Hey!
Looks delicious.
Wow, it'll fit right into your mouth, Joohyun. Have some.
Don't want it!
Chief, don't listen to her at all.
Have some of this...
All right, let's just drink.
Okay.
It's not like I'm making things up.
I say she started the rumors herself.
Hey!
Follow me.
Why?
Don't you have
to go to the restroom?
Fine, let's go!
Please continue your meal.
Excuse us.
Continue your meal.
What in the world was that about?
Oh that, it's no big deal.
I think Chohee was interested
in me when we first met.
But that got blown out of proportion
and spread at the CHA.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Isn't that how rumors are?
Mountains are made out of molehills.
Ah, I see.
Chohee must've had a rough time.
Yes, I guess she did.
Let's drink.
Okay.
- She's not gonna wash her hands?
- Ew, how gross.
Stop stalling and say what
you want already. Or let me go.
Joohyun.
Yes?
You like Bumsang, right?
You're worried that
I'm interested in him, right?
Oh, how did you know...
I know, I know everything.
But you know what?
I don't have
a speck of interest in him.
Hold on. Can I take that to mean
that you'll give him up completely?
Fine, I give up. I give up
completely. Satisfied? Right?
Wait.
Can you swear you're gonna
erase him forever from your heart?
Yes.
I swear I erased him forever,
so please just leave me alone. Okay?
Sis! You should've said so from the start. I misunderstood you for no reason.
- We're done. Let's go.
- Okay!
One more hair sweep.
Let's go.
I worry about her.
What's with the hair sweeping?
Careful, Chohee.
What do you say to
another round of drinks?
Sure. Um...
I'll buy the next round.
Sounds great!
Bumsang!
Let's drink another round.
Um, Joohyun? I'm not...
C'mon, Bumsang!
I'm so, so happy to be with you.
Hey... Hey!
I knew this would happen
when she started chugging her drinks.
Chohee, I'll take Joohyun home.
You have another round with Bumsang.
Bumsang, see you next time.
Bumsang, another round.
Sure, let's go, c'mon!
Chief!
Oh my, she's lost it,
completely lost it.
Wow, she's flying away.
In what way are they similar?
Enough for her to mix them up?
Who's similar? To whom?
Jeez...
Hey, aren't you gonna
drink more with me?
Not gonna drink!
Taxi! Taxi. I'm going to Jangchoong-dong!
Man, why is it
so hard to catch a taxi?
I told you I could handle it.
Go home already.
Sit down. You're a girl, after all.
I can't let you go home alone this late.
What's this?
You can't let a girl get wet in the rain or go home by herself at night. What next?
You can't stand to see
a girl cry all alone?
Good guess.
And in case you might misunderstand,
in no way am I hitting on you.
This is a case of philanthropy
based on humanism, okay?
I'm a pretty nice guy
once you get to know me. Got it?
Yeah, you're super nice.
Almost...
Ow!
This much but then you just ruined it.
So get over yourself, okay?
How dare you poke at
your superior's face like that.
Superior, my butt.
Why do I feel lightheaded?
I didn't drink much.
But I feel good.
Oh, there's a taxi.
Then I'm off.
Hey, hey!
Uh, there was
something on your face.
I was trying to remove it
when you opened your eyes.
What?
I know what you want.
You do?
Ack!
Oh dear, I'm so sorry.
That car cut in front of me.
It's okay.
Mister, where are we?
We're almost there.
Just a bit more.
Ah, okay.
What's wrong?
Huh, nothing, nothing at all.
Oh! Mister, please take
a right at the next light.
Okay.
On the surface I appear to be all right, but inside I wanna jump off a cliff.
This was a rare chance for a promotion.
I can't believe Mr. Kim got away.
We just caught
a lot of small fry instead.
This is so humiliating.
Man, cheer up.
We found out Mr. Kim
sent Gyucheol Seo to Japan.
And we retrieved some items
when we raided their hideout.
All thanks to your excellent
questioning of the small fry.
That's not true.
Of course it is. Anything less
and I would've quit my job.
So thank you, Officer Cho.
Oh no, there's
no need to thank me...
Chief Kang!
Oh, hey, Joohyun.
I hope you weren't in the middle of spreading rumors about last night.
Your mother was really bewildered
last night. Did you get into trouble?
Of course I did.
What mother would be okay with
her daughter coming home wasted?
Right? Right?
And I, for one, cannot forgive myself
for my behavior yesterday.
It happens, Joohyun.
No.
I plan to take some time
to reflect back on my behavior.
I came here to make one thing absolutely clear to you.
What's that?
You introduced yourself
to my mother yesterday.
You're more
calculating than I thought.
Keep in mind that yesterday means nothing to me so don't expect anything.
I'm a one-man kind of girl.
Look here, Joohyun. You seem to be greatly misunderstanding something.
No, no, no, no! For exactly one week, please do not attempt to speak to me.
I'm giving you some time
to resolve your feelings for me.
Then, excuse me.
What the...
“No, no, no...”
She talks about not spreading rumors and comes in spilling everything herself.
Mr. Nah says she's not
your normal case of narcissism.
You've got a nutcase
on your hands.
How annoying. How in the world did I confuse Chief Kang with my Bumsang?
I'm usually too smart
to make mistakes like that.
Aw, man, how am I going
to look Bumsang in the face?
Ow, my stomach...
- Joohyun!
- You startled me.
You're just coming to work now?
You're tardy!
I'm sorry. I - ow...
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I've had a serious case
of anemia since I was a kid.
Then you should've stayed home. Why'd you come to work? It's too much trouble.
No, no. The workplace
shouldn't be taken lightly.
I'll endure it for as long as I can.
If it's too much, I can go home early.
Then. Ow...
She should just go home.
No need to endure pain.
Not like they'll pay her more
for staying. Is she gonna be okay?
Hey, does your stomach hurt
when you have anemia?
That's not important!
Joohyun! Joohyun!
Why is he yelling?
Is he taking after Officer Cho? Hey!
I must be losing it.
How could I dream
something like that?
Have I been repressing myself
too much these days?
Yes, too much abstinence is clearly harmful to one's mental health.
Right, gotta release. Gotta release things. It's because I haven't that -
What the!
Why are you so jumpy?
Who's jumpy?
You!
Oh, I see. You did
something bad again, right?
Why am I your usual suspect?
Nothing, I did nothing!
Really?
Yes, really.
How're you feeling?
I didn't drink enough
to be worried about.
What's up?
I'm supposed to meet
the grandfather from the Lee family.
He wants to see you, the man
who found the “Bihaedangjib.”
I want to donate it to the country.
What did you just say?
You want to donate
the “Bihaedangjib?”
Yes.
Really, Grandfather?
Excuse me, sir.
Can I speak with you privately?
Hey, stay here.
- No need for that.
- But this is...
Stop it.
I kept it stuffed in some corner
without realizing its value.
I don't deserve to own it.
If I want to see it,
I can come here.
And it'll be more worthwhile
if lots of people can see it, too.
- Grandfather.
- Grandfather...
This way I can save face
in front of my ancestors.
Thank you for finding
this valuable book, young lady.
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
I mistreated the book
against my ancestors' wishes.
It's under the protection
of the country now.
So please forgive me,
dear ancestors.
He's gonna cry tears of regret.
He's gonna regret it so much it'll hurt.
Does he realize how much money
it's worth? How could he donate it?
How much money? Is that what
a national hero should be saying?
Cultural assets are
essentially private property.
They're part of a cultural heritage, thereby property belonging to all.
Everything you say
is so narrow-minded.
I'm not being narrow-minded. Listen when I say such valuable things to you.
Stop being so twisted.
Valuable, my butt. Valueless...
- Did you just say valueless?
- Nope.
Hey, you think Congressman
Junpil Lee will take this sitting down?
I heard the “Bihaedangjib” made
an appearance at your auction.
How could you do that
when you knew it belonged to me?
Oh, did that happen?
I had no idea.
And the CHA took it away.
Why are you complaining to me?
You're the one who set the stage.
Fine, I guess you could think that.
Three things are needed
in order to acquire priceless items.
A good eye for recognizing items, enough wealth to relocate them...
and the patience to wait
until it comes into one's possession.
If you have these three,
all you need to do is find a way.
Are you saying there's a way for me
to get the “Bihaedangjib” back?
I'll go get the car,
you help her out.
Bumsang!
Joohyun, are you sick?
- Ah...
- Joohyun.
I'm sorry for showing you
such a weak side of me.
Oh no, don't be. You don't have
to apologize to me. Joohyun...
No, no.
Don't speak.
I know how you feel.
I know that
you're hurting for me.
I will be back tomorrow,
bright and healthy.
Um, the car...
- What?
- The car.
- Let's go.
- Bumsang, see you tomorrow.
Oh, Chief. Why are you here
when we don't have a meeting today?
Chief Noh asked me to come.
By the way, did you drink
some more with Bumsang yesterday?
No. We just went home.
I see. Look, I'm sorry about yesterday. For tactlessly crashing your party.
What are you talking about?
I heard you were
interested in Bumsang.
I didn't realize and I was going
to set him and Joohyun up.
I almost made a big mistake.
Chief, what are you saying?
Did Bumsang tell you
that I'm interested in him?
Then you're not?
Of course not. I'm really
not interested in him, Chief. Gosh...
I dunno what nonsense he told you, but I'm not the least bit interested in him.
So please don't misunderstand.
But you guys looked like
you were pretty close.
Give it a chance.
You guys look great together.
Chief!
I have someone that I like.
So please don't say things like that.
Hey, Chohee!
I can't seem to open it...
I'll do it for you.
- Mine, too, please.
- Sure.
Sir, can I see
you for a moment?
Later.
Open that later and come here.
I still have one more to open.
Open it yourself. Follow me.
One sec. Don't open it.
Bumsang! Did you tell
Chief Kang that I like you?
What?
Ah, that? I didn't say you like me.
I said you were initially interested in me.
What?
He asked about the rumor,
so I just said whatever came to mind.
Hey! Why didn't you just tell him
the truth? Why'd you lie? Why, why!
Why are you throwing such a fit
over something so trivial?
Do you like Chief Kang?
What?
Lookee this. What's with the squirm? You do like him, don't you?
I don't like him.
Anyway, why is Chief Kang telling me
to give you and me a chance? Why?
Chief Kang said that?
Yes.
He doesn't look it
but he's quite the gossip.
You... don't you dare
talk about him like that.
He's a way better
person than you are.
Good person, my butt.
How is he a good person when he blabs about things said over some drinks?
You're two-faced,
a player and a total pervert.
You have no right to say that.
Wh - what? Pervert?
Am I wrong? When I think about you coming towards me in that hot spring.
Ugh, it's enough
to give me nightmares.
Are your screws loose? Suffering
from heatstroke? How dare you!
I have one more thing to say.
I'm warning you.
You say one more ridiculous thing
about me and I'll kick your butt. Got it?
Why, you little...
What the? Pervert? The more I think about it, the more it pisses me off.
Fine. Since I'm the better person,
I'll let it slide. I will.
Wait, why should I?
This isn't a matter I should let slide.
Hey, Chohee! I was gonna let it go,
but you went too far. Apologize now.
Apologize? Why should I?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You turned me into a pervert,
and you say you did nothing wrong?
Not like I made it all up. You should be the one apologizing, you shameless jerk.
What?
Cut the crap
and come to my room.
Why should I?
When your superior
orders you to come, you come.
Ms. Chohee Heo,
come to my room at once!
What the heck.
Who is he to order me around?
Fine, I'll be the bigger person and go. We'll settle this once and for all.
Why are you knocking?
Just come in!
Tch, so you want me to open the door
for you? Fine, I'll open the door.
Satisfied?
Doin' dandy, Bumsang?
Bumsang, you bastard.
Yonggu! Let's talk about this.
We don't have this kind of relationship.
“We don't have
this kind of relationship?”
Shut your trap.
I had the crap beaten
out of me because of you.
You're dead.
Hey, do you realize where you are?
What if someone comes in?
Let them!
If I were to write down
everything you put me through...
it'll be longer than the Bible.
See, I told you someone'll come.
Bumsang, open the door.
I'm going to call security.
Hey, open the door!
What the...!
Bumsang, is that you?
Ugh, it hurts.
Whew, I'm tired.
Are you sure you don't
have to go to the hospital?
No way.
This is way too embarrassing.
That was Yonggu Lee, right?
How many times
do I have to tell you no?
I dunno who he was,
but he kept aiming at my face.
Hey, what happened her?
Hurts like hell.
It seems to be torn a bit.
Anyway, consider
today your lucky day.
If it wasn't for that guy who might be Yonggu, I would've kicked your butt.
You should be the one
thanking the faceless attacker.
Turn your face.
Hey, it hurts.
Gently, please.
What's with the vulnerable act?
It doesn't suit you.
Hey.
What?
At least your eyes are
a bit on the pretty side.
What are you babbling about?
Look at that, your eyelashes
are quite long, too. Are they fake?
No way! I don't have
the time to get it done.
So when you look uncharacteristically sad, it's because of your eyelashes.
Can I touch them
to see if they're real?
What are you doing?
So this is how
you hit on women, huh?
You've got a problem, but the women who fall for you are even worse.
Hey, kid.
What, kid?
Let me ask you one thing.
What?
You weren't attracted to me
at all up to now? Not even once?
Did you get hit on the head too hard? Stop talking nonsense.
What are you saying?
Married Chief Kang is better than me?
Hey, didn't I tell you not
to compare yourself to Chief Kang?
Of all people...
And I've never, not even once,
been attracted to you, so don't worry.
You're telling the truth?
Yes, I'm telling the truth.
I swear to God, not even once.
And never in the future either,
so don't worry.
Never in the future either, you say?
Of course.
There, I'm all done. Let's go.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America