Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Boys, why don't we let Bumsang
appraise your punches?
Unfortunately, I don't have
much experience appraising thugs.
Thugs?
That's it, boys. Let's make
mashed potatoes out of him today.
Get him! Get him!
Bumsang!
Bumsang, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hey, you, Bleach Head.
Hey, Bleach Head!
Bleach Head?
You fuzz have no manners.
Hey, run for it.
Bumsang, give us a moment.
We'll be right back.
Hey, Mr. Kim, it's too hot for a chase.
Just give up already.
And if I refuse?
Then we'll probably lose to you.
But we're only gonna go after one guy.
That would be you, Bleach Head.
Boss, let's just turn ourselves in.
Boss, we've got nothing to lose.
Let's give this fight a shot.
Dongpal, you're right.
Chief Kang, we're not going
to get caught so easily.
Boys!
Yes, sir!
Crush ‘em!
Boss! Boss!
Stay safe! Boss...
What's up with
the investigations team?
They should at least give us a call,
telling us if they caught Mr. Kim or not.
What if they haven't found Bumsang yet
and they're just wandering around?
Chohee, don't worry. Chief Kang went,
so he'll save Bumsang for sure.
Yes, Officer Cho. What?
Bumsang was taken to the hospital?
Okay. All right, then we'll head over
there right now. Okay. All right.
They found Bumsang?
Yeah, he was taken to the hospital.
Let's go to show Bumsang
our sense of camaraderie.
Chohee!
How'd you know I was here?
Chohee ran off in such a hurry -
Thank god.
I'm so relieved you're safe.
Did you think I was gonna die?
What do we do?
I'm so jealous.
A lovely Kodak moment,
isn't it, Joohyun?
Hey, guys.
Chief! Where's everyone else?
They'll be here soon.
Let's leave before we interrupt them.
Chief Kang, let's go.
Let's go! Let's go!
Maybe you should stop now.
There are other patients here.
Does it hurt?
Of course it does.
You were really worried
about me, weren't you?
Just a little.
About this much?
Thanks, for even that much.
What about Gyoon and Chief Noh?
Excuse me.
Gyoon.
Sis.
Are you okay?
Are you really okay?
You're back now, right?
Yeah.
You did well.
Chief.
I'm fine.
Chief, are you really okay?
I can leave tomorrow.
Oh, and Bumsang?
Thanks for your help earlier.
No need to thank me.
I'm just glad that you're safe.
I guess I got a little
too ambitious for my age.
Gyoon, don't just sit there.
Get them some refreshments.
It's fine.
I'll step outside with Gyoon.
Why?
I believe Chohee has
something to say to you.
Bro, what's going on?
That's my question. What happened
today? Why were you there?
The thing is, I stole a portable hard drive
full of Chairman Jang's illegal deals
and gave it to Chief Noh.
You robbed his house again?
Yeah, but Chief Noh said that stolen evidence can't be submitted in court
so we tried to set what turned out
to be an unsuccessful trap.
You two are unbelievable.
How could you be so reckless?
If only it had worked.
I'm so ashamed.
Don't say that. We should
be glad you're safe right now.
I guess.
So what are Sis
and Uncle talking about?
I didn't want to believe Chairman Jang,
but truthfully I felt some doubt.
So I felt I had to ask you
once and for all.
What do you want to know?
Did you meet Dad around the time
when he disappeared seven years ago?
I did.
What happened between you two?
I never imagined that would be
the last time I'd see him.
‘I went intending to arrest him.'
All seven national treasures I stole are
in Chairman Jang's hands. Arrest him.
Taesoo!
I'll take the stand.
I'll testify how I stole them and
how Chairman Jang took them away.
So go after him.
How can I with only
your testimony as evidence?
Besides, I came to arrest you, not him.
Chief Noh!
How could you do this to me?
You were always the one
who believed me.
I may be a thief, but you know
as well as I do that I'm not lying.
Enough already. Let's go.
I'll tell them you turned yourself in.
Chief Noh!
Think of your kids.
Until when are you going to live like this?
Think of Chohee and Gyoon. Turn
yourself in! Don't you want to go home?
I can't give up for their sake.
Taesoo!
I have to get those items back
if I want to go back to my kids.
I need to return them to their
rightful places. So don't arrest me now.
Taesoo.
I just ask that
you don't arrest me today.
Taesoo! Taesoo!
Taesoo...
That was the first and last time
I let him walk away.
I should have arrested him then.
Then he would still be alive now.
It was all my fault.
Why is that your fault?
You did nothing wrong.
Chairman Jang has to pay for this.
He's the one who had Dad murdered.
This time I'll arrest him myself.
No. I'll get him.
Chohee.
I'm going to do it, Chief.
I'll be busy starting tomorrow,
gathering evidence against him.
So don't be stingy
with the traveling expenses.
I'll think about it, Chohee.
By the way, Chohee, I recorded
my conversation with Chairman Jang.
Recorded? What?
You mean like a hidden camera?
That's nearly enough evidence.
Chief, where is the recording?
Check for a necktie clip
somewhere among my clothes.
Chief, it's not here.
That can't be.
The vase, the vase!
What in the world does
Bumsang Kim have against me?
It's bad enough I lost the “Bihaedangjib”
to him, but he had to show up right then?
That's what I'm saying.
How did he know to come there?
This is your fault. If you had taken care of
him earlier this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry, Boss.
Sorry?
You think that solves anything?
Look at what happened
to me because of you.
Boss, this isn't the time to be whining.
We have to get far away before
Dongpal tells the fuzz everything.
You're right. We should.
But I'm more scared
of Chairman Jang.
What the?
Who are you guys?
Mr. Kim turned out
to be completely useless.
I thought maybe he could handle
something that didn't require brains.
We captured him like you ordered.
What do we do with him?
Find out through him who handled
Taesoo Heo. Then get rid of the whole lot.
Yes, sir.
What are the cops up to?
I'm afraid they plan
to launch an official investigation.
I'm sorry, sir.
What a bother.
Let Secretary Oh handle things
for a while, and you lay low.
And just in case, tell my team of attorneys
to prepare for all possible scenarios.
Yes, sir. Oh, and Iwazaki is flying in
tomorrow. What shall I do?
With things looking not so good,
should I cancel the appointment?
We can't do that to Iwazaki.
Continue that as is.
Bro, I'm heading to bed.
Okay.
You're turning yourself in tomorrow?
Yeah.
I'll leave you two alone then.
I looked into the matter.
Since no one reported the thefts
and the nature of the crimes wasn't bad
he'll probably just be placed
on probation. Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried.
In fact, I feel at peace now.
Gyoon probably feels the same.
Yeah. You have to be
strong for Gyoon's sake.
Want some tea?
No, I'm fine. I can't intrude on
your sibling time. I'll be going then.
You know what? I'm going
to tell Chief Kang tomorrow.
Tell him what?
That I'm sorry
but I can't accept his feelings.
Not because of everything going on,
but because there's someone I like.
So I can't accept his feelings.
I'm going to tell him that.
Go on then.
Gyoon might come out.
Go home.
Can't sleep?
Bro left?
What are you doing?
Dad didn't carry around much cash.
Twelve bucks. How sad is that?
That's seriously sad.
Why'd he carry this around
when he didn't even smoke?
Sis, this is so interesting.
Look here, at Dad's handwriting.
It looks just like mine.
It does.
It's practically the same.
I know I take after him a lot,
but similar handwriting, too?
I know.
Gyoon, I'm not going
with you tomorrow.
Okay.
When you come back,
let's be happy, okay?
You and me both.
Okay.
We'll be together again soon.
We can charge Chairman Jang
with the following crimes.
The trafficking, possession
and concealment of stolen goods.
The murder of Taesoo Heo.
The attempted murder of Chief Noh.
He'll be locked up
even way past his death.
We took the information from his
hard drive, and after retracing his steps,
we found some evidence supporting
his purchase of stolen goods.
His defense team will flat out deny
all charges and try to hide the evidence.
So we need to hurry.
I will catch Mr. Kim and
Yonggu Lee with my bare hands
for their offense against Chief Noh
and for staining our team's honor.
Your sporadic outbursts
can be seen as signs of illness.
Did I exaggerate a little too much?
We're lacking in manpower, so let's not
divide into teams and all work together.
We'll end the meeting here.
Chief.
Can I have a moment?
Drink up.
Okay.
Um, Chief? I...
I know what it is
you want to say to me.
I saw you and Bumsang together
in the hospital yesterday.
I regret that I didn't accept
your feelings when I had the chance.
I really hope everything works out well
between you two. I really do.
Thank you.
I'll be going then.
It's so hot.
I'm being steamed here.
The investigations team should do
stakeouts. Why are they making us do it?
Don't you agree, Chief?
Who cares who's doing it?
As long as we get something out of it.
Yeah, yeah. I shouldn't have
expected any sympathy from you.
Why did Sangho suddenly go to a training
seminar? When's he coming back?
It'll be a while. I'll stick with you
until he comes back, so don't worry.
You will?
There's no need.
I'm deeply honored that
you're here with me today.
I can handle this on my own.
I'll fly solo.
Isn't that Iwazaki?
He's the Japanese dude
who was with Chairman Jang last time!
Why is he here again?
I can smell the stink from here.
Welcome, Chairman Iwazaki.
“Good afternoon, Chairman Jang.”
Please have a seat.
Forgive me for asking you
to come all the way to my home.
He says it's fine.
I imagine you were very upset because
of the disgraceful affair last time.
I thought maybe you refused my gift
because it was not up to your standards
so I prepared something
more valuable. Show him.
Yes, sir.
The “Geumdongdae” incense burner.
One of my most cherished items.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Thank you so much.
Considering the relationship between
our companies, this gift is not enough.
Chairman Jang, may I ask
an impertinent favor of you?
If it's for you, I will do
everything in my power to help you.
Recently, I bought
a lot of Goryeo celadon.
I need to take it to Japan but Korea's
Cultural Properties Protection Act is...
Ah, there's nothing to worry about.
I happen to know a good way to help you.
God, this is frustrating. I told you I don't
even know what Taesoo Heo looks like.
How can you falsely accuse me of
killing him when I don't even know him?
What?
I'm gonna kick your...
Think you'll get away with spewing lies?
Gyoon already told us everything.
Mr. Kim received orders from Chairman
Jang, and those orders passed onto you.
You gonna keep lying like this?
Hey, Dongpal.
You were part of the Makddae Family
that managed the Hwangjae Nightclub
seven years ago?
Take a good look at this.
Taesoo Heo had this on him.
See this here? Hwangjae Nightclub.
You saw Heo there, didn't you?
Man, I really don't know him.
What does Heo coming to
the nightclub have to do with me?
Stop making wild guesses and
do the interrogation properly, will you?
Come here.
Not coming? Get over here.
Leave the room.
We need to teach
bastards like him a lesson.
You'll get into trouble. The world doesn't
work like that anymore. Calm down.
I'm going to get some water.
- Hey, Chohee.
- Hello.
Hey. You're here to see Gyoon?
I just met him.
It's hot. Here you go.
Dongpal Kim is being uncooperative?
Tell me about it. He's a tough nut
to crack. Keeps denying everything!
Oh, that's refreshing.
This is...
Truthfully, it's a business card
that was found on your father.
We held onto it because we thought
it would help with the investigation.
Sorry we didn't tell you earlier, Chohee.
Don't be. You don't have to
tell me such things.
Excuse me, but I have
to get going. Goodbye.
Chohee.
What's with her?
Dunno.
[Hwangjae Nightclub
Mister Oh]
So we have writing on thin silk paper.
Yes. It's so contaminated we have to
clean it, but we can't use warm water.
In a case like this, the heart of the piece
can be ruined if not done with care.
If possible, the lining paper
should be kept while restoring.
It should be easy if you layer
repeatedly using neutral paper
while watching the
progress with each step.
Nothing's difficult for you, is it?
Glad to be of help. Is that all?
Sir!
Yes?
If you're free this evening,
I'd like to buy you a cup of coffee.
What? Well...
[Chohee Heo]
I'm sorry, but it seems my girlfriend
is already checking up on me.
If I'm caught having coffee,
I won't escape unscathed.
You know how Chohee is.
Yeah?
A nightclub?
Why do you want to go there?
Mister Oh?
Yes.
We heard he worked here
seven years ago.
I'm not sure.
Manager Park! Did a waiter named
Mister Oh work here seven years ago?
Mister Oh?
You're talking about Changsu.
Changsu Oh.
Changsu Oh?
Yes, but he's not here right now.
He went on vacation starting yesterday.
When will he be back?
I have no idea.
What do you mean?
How can you not know?
Truth is, the day before yesterday
some men came looking for him.
He left with them after exchanging words.
Then he went on vacation yesterday.
Why does everyone like Chohee?
You startled me! Chief!
Where's Chief Noh?
What? He'll be in soon.
Yeah?
I don't have time to wait.
Could you give this to Chief Noh?
What is it?
The statement with
Chairman Jang's illegal deals.
Most were done under someone else's
name, so it was hard to sort through.
Chief, why are you so anxious
to arrest Chairman Jang?
What?
Is it because you want to help Chohee?
I see. I knew it.
That's the reason why
our entire team wants to get him.
That's the biggest reason,
but I have another reason.
I made a promise with my daughter.
I'll arrest wrongdoers and
will never lock up the innocent.
But it isn't easy
keeping that simple promise.
If only we had Chief Noh's necktie clip,
things would be easier. What a loss.
A necktie clip?
Yeah. It had a camera
built into it. If we had that...
Chief! You're wearing ties
more and more these days.
Does it look bad?
Then that was a hidden camera?
Dongpal Kim isn't spilling anything.
Mr. Nah, was Iwazaki carrying anything
when he left Chairman Jang's house?
No, I don't think so.
He was all smiles and
in a great mood when he was leaving.
There's definitely something
going on between those two.
Mr. Nah, please
watch Iwazaki a bit longer.
And let's wait a bit on Dongpal.
Hey, Chohee.
[Chief, we have to look for Changsu Oh
from the Hwangjae Nightclub.]
Changsu Oh?
Boss, where do you think
they're taking us?
I think Chairman Jang
wants to knock us off.
Knock us off? Knock?
No, no. I can't die.
I can't die!
I can't die now.
I wanna live.
It's okay, Yonggu.
Get a grip.
We'll figure something out.
You're Changsu Oh, the guy
who took care of Taesoo Heo, right?
We're all in the same boat here,
so why don't you stop staring daggers?
Let's join forces.
Officer Cho.
It seems Chohee hit a mark.
What?
This Changsu Oh character
is extremely suspicious.
Not only did he work alongside
Dongpal in the Makddae Family
they were also buddies
in the army and in prison.
Is that so?
Eat.
Eat up, punk.
This will be the last meal of noodles
you'll have if you go to prison for murder.
What are you talking about?
You know Changsu, right?
Your gang buddy.
He told us that you were
the one who took care of Taesoo Heo.
W-w-what?
Changsu Oh said that?
I can't believe this.
You know that Changsu's not exactly
smart but he's not the type to lie.
So tell me every detail on who, what,
when, where, why and how you did it.
I really didn't do it!
Then spill it.
If it's not you, who?
It's not me.
Was it Mr. Kim?
Yes or no?
It wasn't me and
it wasn't my boss either.
It was Changsu Oh who did it!
He did it?
Drag them out.
Yes, sir.
Where did they go?
Are they gone?
They're gone.
Where are we?
I saw a small amusement park while
running. It seems we're on Wolmi Island.
Wolmi Island? We were in there for
only an hour? I thought we traveled far.
You're quite useful.
I thought our gang only had idiots
like him, but we have someone like you.
How about working for me?
Let's go our separate ways.
Jeez, talk about lack of manners.
He ignored me.
Hey, why are you ignoring Boss,
you jerk! Right, Boss?
Isn't she back from
the investigations team yet?
Please send someone to work with me.
I'm dying here without Sangho.
I'll work on it, so be patient.
Bumsang, when did you get here?
You're back from a stakeout?
I'm dying here trying to tail
Iwazaki or whatever his name is.
Iwazaki is that guy from
the Robin Hood incident.
Yeah, I'm tailing him because him
and Chairman Jang are up to something.
But all they do is golf or eat out
or party with some ladies.
But he went to a pottery
exhibition today, didn't he?
Yeah, yeah. Thanks to that I feel
a little more learned myself.
I'll be going then. Good day.
Yeah, yeah.
Mr. Nah.
Where's Joohyun every day?
Where is it?
Lady, what are you looking for? There's
nothing worth money around here.
The thing is...
Just something.
You're in uniform - you're students -
Why aren't you in school?
Listen to her.
She's asking why we're not in school.
It seems you're a little confused.
Who are you to nag us?
No, I'm not nagging you.
We have stuff to do here.
Find what you're looking for and scram!
Think I'd leave just
‘cause you told me to?
Where is that necktie clip?
There you are.
Were you waiting for me?
Who else would I wait for?
Gyoon is being moved next week,
so I spent some time with him.
How's he doing?
Gyoon?
He gained weight.
That's not what I was asking.
Let's go eat.
Wait up.
In the cafeteria?
Yeah.
There is other food in this world
besides food in the cafeteria.
And who goes on
a date to the cafeteria?
We're going on a date right now?
Of course. Let's go out.
I'll buy you something good.
Sorry, but I'm joining the stakeout
in front of Changsu Oh's house tonight.
Stakeout?
Yeah.
What's with the sudden stakeout?
Let's just eat here today
and eat well next time, okay?
Just for today.
All right.
Hey, are you sulking again?
No, I'm not.
Looks like you are.
Hey, isn't that Chairman Jang?
Don't let them say otherwise.
And don't call them either.
Well, look who it is.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has, sir.
Have you been well?
Of course. What are
you doing here at the CHA?
Advisory member. I forgot.
You're lasting longer than I expected.
Thanks to you. What brings
a busy person like you to the CHA?
You really don't know?
I'm disappointed.
Don't the CHA employees know
I was appointed the chief director
of the Monuments Fund?
I'm here to see the director of the CHA
before I'm inaugurated into office.
Chairman Jang, do you think
you deserve to hold that position?
Hey!
I happen to think that no one loves
cultural assets as much as I do.
Of course you do. Perhaps that's why
you've forgotten how to value human life.
What are you talking about?
Drop the act.
You killed my father.
Chohee.
Do you understand
what she's talking about?
Chairman Jang, you killed my father.
You're quite impertinent.
Or perhaps you're just fearless?
Wait and see.
I'll lock you up myself.
I'll be waiting. But you should
watch your mouth and your back first.
They think they stand a chance
against me. What are the police up to?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
We've managed to plug up the leaks.
And Iwazaki?
Manager Kang is taking care of it.
The exhibition was officially held today
and everything's in order.
Professor Gong even wrote
a dedicatory letter for us.
Make sure no word of this gets out.
Yes, sir.
Maybe we're wasting our time here.
If Chairman Jang's men kidnapped
Changsu Oh, he's probably a dead man.
Dead or alive, it is our officer's code
to continue until we know for sure.
I've followed that code this far.
You know that.
Sure, like the time
you went off to meet Ms. Kim...
Jinguk, what is that?
Isn't that Chohee?
Oh, my poor heart.
Sorry I'm late.
No need for you to come. You have
a too strong sense of responsibility.
Aren't you two sleepy?
Get some shuteye. I'll stand guard.
No, it's okay. Seriously...
Well, if you insist.
Let's take turns.
Chohee, thanks.
Sure.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
If it's proven that Chairman Jang was
behind all that, it'll be a major headline.
Don't say a word until it is proven.
It'll cause big trouble if it leaks out.
All right. Chohee must be in a lot of pain.
Thinking about her dad and all.
Yeah.
By the way, take this.
What is it?
Jeez. Yongcheol wrote the review of some exhibition, and he bragged so much.
He left a copy for you, too.
He did?
This is...
Why? Did you go to this exhibition?
Not me, but the people at the CHA.
Something's off.
Huh?
Hey, I have to go check this out.
Sorry, but I have to go.
Sure.
What was that about?
The exhibition is over?
Yes. It was a special exhibition
held only yesterday.
Why only one day?
I heard it's because the next exhibition
is scheduled to be in Japan.
Could I take a look at the pottery?
Didn't you see them on your way in?
They were being loaded into a truck.
[Ohseong Distributive Services]
Ohseong Distributive Services?
This is the pamphlet of
the exhibition Iwazaki attended.
You can tell that it's all a pretense.
A pretense?
On the outside, they look like regular pottery, but see the brush strokes?
I'm sure they were covered
with mud and disguised as pottery.
Why would someone do this?
To smuggle them abroad.
As you know well, cultural assets are
forbidden by law to leave the country.
With one exception.
Unless the purpose is to be exhibited.
So Chairman Jang set up this exhibition
to help Iwazaki smuggle things out.
If not, why hold a special exhibition
for just a day and invite no one?
They're planning to legally carry things
out under the pretense of this exhibition.
The truck used belonged to Ohseong
Distributive Services. Start there.
No, we'll head straight to the airport.
The airport?
Iwazaki's flight is set to leave today.
Then everyone's headed to the airport?
Oh, okay.
Got it.
Then shouldn't we go back them up?
Right?
Since you have to catch Changsu Oh,
stay here. I'll go to the airport.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Be careful.
I will. Good luck.
It seems Chairman Jang had his guts
botoxed. He started some major stuff.
That man isn't afraid of anything.
Man, where is Changsu Oh?
There are no signs of him anywhere.
I'm sorry.
Changsu Oh?
Okay, I understand. Yes...
Which airport?
I'm not sure, but it seems Iwazaki headed
towards Haneda Airport in Japan.
Then we should head to Kimpo Airport.
Officer Cho, I'm tailing Changsu Oh right
now. Opposite that house. Hurry. Okay...
Hey, Changsu Oh!
Stop right there!
Where did he go?
I'm sure he came this way.
Isn't that him?
It is!
Mister Oh of Hwangjae Nightclub.
Long time no see.
Over here.
Come on. Over here.
Changsu, it's me. Sangcheol.
Don't recognize me?
Why are you putting on
gloves in this heat?
Who are you?
Who do you think?
We're cops here to arrest you.
Chohee, stay back.
Stay back.
Changsu, let's go somewhere cool.
Screw you.
“Screw you?”
You little...
Hey, look at this.
Chief Kang. Over there!
[Ohseong Distributive Services]
Over there...
Police.
We ask for your cooperation.
Let's take a look inside the truck.
Mr. Nah, some water, please.
Water?
Wow, we got him!
What are you doing here? Scram!
This is one too many times. Scram!
Get out!
I told you to leave.
Why are you still here?
Sir, I'm not here to pick up scraps.
I really need to find something.
Seriously, lady. You've been coming
here for days now. Leave already!
Sir, just once. Let me look
just a little more, please?
Excuse me.
Hello? What?
You caught Changsu Oh?
Okay, I'll be right in. Okay.
Darn it...
I wanted to show Chief Kang
that I could be of help.
Things never work out for me.
Are you leaving or not?
I am, I'm leaving.
Then hurry up and leave.
That hurt...
Huh?
[Inaugural Ceremony for the new
Chief Director of the Monuments Fund]
- Chief.
- Yes?
We're ready.
All right. Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time to listen
to Chief Director Jang's inaugural speech.
Sir, please take the stand.
I'm Ohseong Jang.
First, I want to thank
everyone for allowing me
to take this honored
and esteemed position.
Let me ask you.
What is a cultural asset?
It connects our nation's
past, present and future.
It's an inheritance that holds
a great emotional value for us.
Therefore, we all have
the responsibility and right
to share, cherish, protect and love
this valuable cultural inheritance.
Cultural assets are
sacred items that cannot
and should not be
possessed by a sole owner.
The “Geumdongdae” incense burner
and Duryang Kim's “Sansu” painting?
Is it impossible? I think the files are worth
those two items. Are you going to refuse?
I couldn't.
Fine, I'll give them to you.
But keep this in mind.
You'll regret touching
my items someday.
Your items?
Cultural assets belong to the country, no?
Moreover, these are national treasures.
Now you sound like the regulations team
chief. National treasures or stolen goods.
I paid good money for them,
so they belong to me.
Chairman Ohseong Jang,
you're under arrest for attempting
to smuggle abroad cultural assets.
W-what? Smuggle abroad?
What nonsense is this?
Don't even think
about denying everything.
We not only found all the items,
but Iwazaki confessed at the airport.
You guys planned this?
I warned you last time
that you'd better to brace yourself.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America