Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
You're hiding something
from me, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I overheard your call with Chief Kang.
What are they doing at my house?
This was found in Gyoon's room. I think
he used it for his Robin Hood activities.
And...
What else?
We found these, too.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
I'm not.
Why do you keep asking that?
Look at me!
Look me in the face and tell me.
What are you hiding?
What is it you're unable to tell me?
Hello, who is this?
[This is Ohseong Jang.]
Who did you say you are?
Chairman Ohseong Jang
of the Ohseong Group.
Episode 15
Who was that?
Why do you look like that?
Chairman Jang.
Chairman Jang?
Why would he call you?
I don't know. He says he wants to see me
immediately, but I don't know why.
Because of Gyoon.
What about Gyoon?
What did Gyoon do?
Brace yourself for this, Chohee.
The truth is, Gyoon...
Gyoon is Robin Hood.
He acknowledged it.
All right. Let's assume
that he is Robin Hood.
So Chairman Jang wants to see me
because Gyoon stole his things?
I don't think that's the whole of it.
According to Gyoon...
According to Gyoon, Chairman Jang
played a hand in your father's death.
What?
Say that one more time.
Say it one more time.
Chairman Jang had something to do
with my dad's death?
Are you saying that his death
might have been Chairman Jang's doing?
That's what Gyoon said,
but nothing's certain. So -
Since when did you know all this?
That Gyoon was Robin Hood,
that my dad might have been murdered.
When did you find out?
For a while now.
Do both Chief Kang and
Chief Noh know? Do they?
I told Chief Kang, and
I'm assuming Chief Noh knows by now.
How could you do that?
How could you!
How can you keep me in the dark
while all of you knew?
Don't go. You can't go alone when
you don't know what's waiting for you.
Let's evaluate the situation first -
No. I'm going on my own.
I'm going to listen to what he has to say.
Why was this found here?
It might have been left there on purpose,
so let's check thoroughly for fingerprints.
Yes, sir.
If we find nothing, doesn't that just mean
he was behind the museum break-in?
Huh? Bumsang!
- Jinguk, let's go.
- Yeah.
Why are you here alone?
Where's Chohee?
I had something urgent to tell you.
What is it?
Did Chohee...?
Yes, she found out that
Gyoon was Robin Hood.
Where is she right now?
Were you surprised
that I wanted to see you?
What is it you want to say to me?
I heard this Robin Hood character
has been creating quite a buzz.
Did the regulations team
figure out his identity?
I heard it was your brother,
Gyoon Heo. Am I right?
What is it you wish to say?
Your father is the famous
art thief Taesoo Heo.
Your brother is Robin Hood, who steals
from people to donate to the museum.
Things must be rough for you.
Sir, I'm sure you didn't
call me here to tell me that.
I'll cut to the chase.
Chief Kang came to see me.
He implied that I did
something to your father.
I don't even know your father.
The more I think about it,
the more offended I am.
So I did a little investigating myself
on how your father died.
And I found out
something very interesting.
What do you think
Chairman Jang is up to?
I'm not sure. Maybe he was feeling
pressured because I visited him?
He's nervous and wants to find out
how much information we actually have?
I'll be relieved if that's the case.
Chairman Jang is a terrifying man.
I'm on pins and needles because
I have no idea what he intends to do.
What is this interesting thing
you found out?
It's not the fact that you were involved
with my father's death, is it?
Your words are full of accusation.
So you also think I was involved?
Weren't you?
I don't really care what you insist I did.
But I think you'd understand
what it feels like to be falsely accused.
I hear your brother is the main suspect
for the museum break-in.
Imagine he is being falsely accused.
Wouldn't you feel upset?
That's how I feel.
I'm offended that I'm being accused
of killing a man I didn't even know.
If you called me here to tell me you're
being falsely accused, then we're done.
I'll be leaving then.
You're very impatient.
Interesting information should be told
with dramatic pauses to build the effect.
By the way, who's the current chief of the
regulations team? Is it still Jeongpil Noh?
Why do you ask?
I wonder what he was up to around
the time your father disappeared.
That is the interesting information
I found out. Do you find it interesting?
So what you're saying is...
Chief Noh had something to do
with my father's death -
That's for you to find out, isn't it?
[Seoul District Police Department
Fingerprint search system]
Hold on. I think we've got
a match on one of the fingerprints.
[Match]
[Bumsang Kim]
Let's search again,
focusing on the ex-cons.
Chief.
Yes?
Um, Chohee is waiting
for you in the office.
Is she? Call me as soon as
the fingerprint results come out.
Um, Chief?
If we get some unfortunate results,
we have to arrest Chohee's brother, right?
Yes, that would be our only choice.
Why don't we pass
this case onto another team?
The intelligence team has so little work
they're totally bumming around.
I understand how you feel.
I hope we don't have to arrest Gyoon.
Bumsang told me everything.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about the investigation earlier.
I wanted to tell you
when things became more definite.
What's gonna happen to Gyoon now?
His Robin Hood acts can be dealt with
leniently due to mitigating circumstances.
But the museum break-in...
Everyone thinks that Gyoon was framed
for the museum break-in.
I'll do my best to collect evidence,
so try not to worry.
So why did Chairman Jang
want to see you today?
Chief, how much of what
Chairman Jang says is credible?
What do you mean?
I don't know if what he said was true.
But the truth is, he said Chief Noh -
Chohee. I heard you went to Chairman
Jang's house? Did anything happen?
I gave him a call. I thought
you should tell both of us at once.
Thank goodness if nothing happened.
Did Chairman Jang say anything strange?
Nothing happened.
Thank god nothing happened.
Chairman Jang isn't your usual
shrewd man, so be careful around him.
Chohee.
Yes?
Are you really okay?
I'm trying to be, for Gyoon's sake.
I have to be okay.
Yeah. Go home and get some rest.
Um, Chief?
I mean, Uncle.
Yeah?
I...
What is it?
I trust in you.
That's the only way I'll endure.
I'll be going then.
Chohee.
‘Brace yourself for this, Chohee.'
The truth is, Gyoon...
Gyoon is Robin Hood.
Everyone thinks that Gyoon was framed
for the museum break-in.
According to Gyoon, Chairman Jang
played a hand in your father's death.
I wonder what he was up to around
the time your father disappeared.
Hey, Chohee!
What happened to you?
I couldn't reach you at all.
Have you been talking with
Chairman Jang all this time?
This is bad.
We should get you to a hospital.
No, I'm fine.
Hey, you're burning up right now.
It's okay. I've been pushing myself
too hard. I'll be fine after a little rest.
Um... sorry for getting
mad at you earlier.
I know why you did what you did,
that you were just worried about me.
No, I was at fault.
Why are you apologizing?
Why did Gyoon do this?
Because of me?
Or because he found out
Dad was murdered?
Was my dad really murdered?
Did Chairman Jang really kill him?
And how did Gyoon find out?
Where is he?
What is he doing?
What is he thinking?
I don't understand any of it.
Don't worry.
Gyoon will be fine.
He'll be back without any problems.
Understood.
I didn't add the celadon bought
for Iwazaki to the inventory list.
Copy only the expenditure breakdown
of the latest deals and erase the rest.
Yes, sir.
What? The expenditure information
is gone? What was everyone doing?
You know what will happen
if that gets into the wrong hands.
I'm sorry, sir.
I ordered it to be erased,
but before it could be -
Someone must've stolen it.
It didn't just disappear on its own!
Who is it?
Who would come into my house...
Robin Hood.
Robin Hood?
Mr. Kim said that
Gyoon Heo got away, right?
Yeah, it's definitely him.
It has to be him!
Would he?
He already broke in once before.
He can because he already did before.
Go out and find him at once!
Yes, sir.
That slippery weasel.
Man, we have meeting after meeting
because of that Robin Hood jerk.
And the meetings are ridiculous.
Things get repeated over and over again.
They all sound like broken records.
At times like these, it's such a hassle
being higher up on the ladder.
Then quit.
I'll take your place.
What? You, too, now?
Sangho, it's fine that you take always
Joohyun's side, but don't become like her.
I have enough problems with Joohyun
cutting me down all the time.
Mr. Nah!
I'm not a petty person who cuts people
down. I just speak the honest truth.
You do always speak the truth.
You little -
Never mind, I give up.
When I'm chief, the both of you are -
Good morning, Chohee.
Where's Chief Noh?
Chief Noh? He got a phone call as soon
as he got here, and he left soon after.
Did he say where he was going?
No, he didn't. He didn't, right?
See what I mean, Chohee? I told you so.
Our chief is turning so lazy these days.
It's too early for this.
You know you like it.
Gyoon!
Did you wait long?
What is this?
I got it from Chairman Jang's
house last night.
Inside you'll find all the details
of his illegal deals of stolen goods.
How did you...
I should give it to my sister,
but she thinks I'm traveling right now.
She knows everything.
What?
She knows that you're Robin Hood.
What are you going to do?
What else?
I haven't changed my mind.
Gyoon.
Please take care of the investigation.
I know that it won't be easy.
But I can't do nothing when I know
that Chairman Jang had Dad killed.
Who says he had your father killed?
I overheard it. When I was kidnapped,
I overheard the guys talking.
Didn't you know about the relationship
between Dad and Chairman Jang?
You wanna know what kind of
relationship Chief Noh and your dad had?
Yes.
Why are you asking out of the blue?
I was just curious.
Isn't the relationship between a thief
and a regulations team member obvious?
The chaser and the chased. They grew
close out of hatred for each other.
Chief Noh went through a lot of trouble
because of Taesoo and me.
Though they did hit
a rough spot near the end.
But seeing how he took you guys in,
he really is a good person.
Um, Uncle. What rough spot?
What happened between them?
I'm not sure. It's stranger for them to be
on good terms, not the other way around.
By the way, is Gyoon
back from traveling yet?
How did you know he went traveling?
He came to borrow money from me.
So I just gave it to him as allowance.
When?
When did you see him, Uncle?
A few days ago.
Why? Is something wrong?
No, it's just that -
One moment, Uncle.
Yeah, what is it?
Okay. I'll be right there. Yeah.
Uncle, I'm sorry but I have to leave.
Yeah, go on, go on.
Oh, and Uncle? If you meet Gyoon or
get a call from him, please tell me. Okay?
Yeah, sure.
By the way, Chohee.
Hey, Chohee?
How strange.
Did something happen?
Chohee!
Hey.
Ms. Heo, this way.
Yeah, bye.
Mister Kim? He came by
the day before yesterday, I think.
He wanted to look at some digital safes,
so I told him to go ahead.
He had a cup of coffee
and we chatted some. The he left.
He didn't say where he was headed?
No, he didn't mention that.
I told him to stay longer,
but he said he was busy.
Which safe did he look at?
He was looking for
a special fireproof safe.
But we didn't have that model
so I showed him something similar.
That one over there.
The bigger one.
Chief!
Chief Kang. Chief!
Hey, Joohyun.
How could you just ignore me
when I kept calling your name?
Are you going deaf?
Did I do that?
I guess I was thinking too hard.
Where are you coming from?
I picked up some pictures.
Pictures?
Hold on.
Where did they go?
Here you go.
Wait, when did you take this?
When we were in Chinatown.
What do you think?
They came out well, didn't they?
Yeah, they did.
Did you know that sometimes when
you're alone, you're very expressionless?
I am?
Yes. Look at this picture. If you're not
talking to anyone, you look like this.
When you're in your investigative mode,
you frown like this.
You should smile more.
And take more pictures.
You naturally smile more
when you take pictures.
Cheese. Click.
See. You look so much better
when you're smiling.
Upon a closer look, you actually
look decent when you're smiling.
Then I'll be going.
‘To Chief Shiwan Kang.'
‘I don't do the honor of signing things
for just anyone. Be grateful.'
Chief!
Oh, hey.
What are you looking at?
Oh, it's nothing.
What's up?
I wanted to give you
a progress report while I was here.
Oh, what happened to identifying
the prints from Chohee's house?
I thought we'd salvage at least
a few prints, but it was clean.
The only outsider we got was Bumsang.
So it turned into unfavorable
evidence for Gyoon.
Yeah, so far.
What's that?
Oh, this?
Just something.
I'm just copying some files.
Chief Kang, you want a cup of coffee?
Stay here. I'll get it.
Dad...
Sis, I'm sorry.
We got off work early today.
Get some rest.
I will.
What are you thinking about?
Gyoon?
Not just that...
You have something else
troubling you? What is it?
The truth is, Chairman Jang
told me something when we met.
He asked me if I knew what Chief Noh
had been doing when my father died.
Was he implying that Chief Noh had
something to do with your father's death?
I dunno. I don't want to doubt Chief Noh
because of what Chairman Jang said.
But I can't help thinking about it.
Did you ask Chief Noh?
How can I?
I doubt it.
I haven't known him as long as you,
but he's not that type of person.
Trust in him.
That's the right thing to do.
And if you're really curious,
just ask him directly.
It's better to feel bad once
instead of festering doubt in your heart.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Did I ever say anything
that wasn't right?
Yeah.
Bye.
See ya.
Don't get out.
No way...
Gyoon. Gyoon!
Gyoon, where are you going?
Where are you going?
How could you do this to me?
Gyoon, you can't do this to me.
How am I supposed
to live if you do this!
Sis.
Turn yourself in, okay?
I can't watch you do this anymore.
Do you realize what you're doing?
Turn yourself in.
You can't continue this, Gyoon.
No, I can't do that right now.
Why? Why can't you?
Chief Kang said that mitigating
circumstances will be considered.
And I'll do whatever it takes to clear
the false charge of the museum break-in.
I'll clear you for sure, so turn yourself in.
You can't do this. You can't, Gyoon.
Sis, I know that
I'm not doing the right thing.
But Sis, even if I'm wrong,
I don't want to regret things now.
I'll regret it later
when I'm paying for my actions.
Why are you being like this?
Why, Gyoon?
Do you want to see me die?
Do you?
How am I supposed
to live if you do this?
Turn yourself in, Gyoon. Please?
Sorry, Sis.
I have something I need to do.
When I'm done,
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Gyoon.
Turn yourself in!
I'll be back. When I'm done with
what I have to do, I'll come back.
Sorry, Sis.
Gyoon! Gyoon!
Gyoon, Gyoon!
Hey, Chohee.
Chief.
What's wrong?
I met Gyoon.
Bumsang, did you wait long?
No, are you getting off work now?
Think I have an easygoing job like yours?
I'm working late tonight, too.
Easygoing, my butt.
You have something to ask me?
I wanted your opinion on this.
Should we restore it or not?
This is a slave contract
from the Joseon era.
Yeah. A collector from Andong
donated it a few days ago.
In the third year of King Seonjo.
A ten-year-old girl was sold as a slave
to repay her father's debts.
It's so sad. When I first read it,
my heart hurt a bit.
What a filial daughter.
The daughter repays the father's debt.
Times haven't changed, then or now.
What do you mean?
Hey, are families
supposed to be like this?
I don't know much about families.
Parents give up
their lives for their children.
Children sacrifice
their lives for their parents.
Is that how it is?
Weird. Never thought
I'd hear you talk about families.
Maybe it's time for you
to get married, Bumsang.
No way.
Anyway, don't restore it.
Yeah?
Though old and damaged,
restoration isn't always the best choice.
It's not the right time yet.
All right. You're the expert.
Are you headed home?
I wish. I have to
stop by the CHA first.
Hey, isn't that
Chairman Jang's secretary?
Why is he at the museum?
Not sure.
Oh, right! You don't know, do you?
He's going to be the chief director of the
Monuments Fund. That's probably why.
Chief director of the Monuments Fund?
Well, he certainly qualifies with his wealth
and good eye for art. Don't you think so?
Someone who truly loves cultural assets
qualifies, not a man like that.
Anyway, go back to work.
I'll be leaving.
Yeah, bye.
You waited long.
Please get in.
The truth is, Chairman Jang told me
something when we met.
He asked me if I knew what Chief Noh
had been doing when my father died.
I think I did the wrong thing.
Instead of talking to him, I should've
grabbed onto him and called you.
Did you tell him about
the mitigating circumstances defense?
I did. But Chief?
I don't think he's hiding because
he's afraid of being investigated.
Then?
He said he has something to do.
That he'll come back when he's done.
But I have no idea
what it is he feels he needs to do.
Well, what could it be?
I printed just a few pages.
Check if they match with your records.
You should know better than anyone
that you can't do me in with this.
But it's certainly enough
to cause you major discomfort.
It's still a weakness, isn't it?
What is it you want?
I don't expect much. Just enough
to set me up after my retirement.
You've changed over the years.
Time can change
both mountains and men.
So you want to line your pockets
with this opportunity?
An explanation is unnecessary
since you know so well already.
Fine, how much do you want?
I don't need money.
From what I know,
you have a lot of valuable items.
Can I tell you what I want?
What do you want?
Something that Gyoon has to do.
Maybe he wants
to complete Robin Hood?
What do you mean,
complete Robin Hood?
The seven national treasures
your father stole.
Maybe he wants to return
all of them to the museum.
That's possible.
Then the two remaining
national treasures are...
The “Geumdongdae” incense burner
and Duryang Kim's “Sansu” painting?
Is it impossible?
Chief Noh, you're greedier than
I assumed. Not just one, but two.
And you know how valuable both are!
I need at least that much
to enjoy life a little after retirement.
I think the files are worth
those two items. Do you refuse?
I couldn't.
Fine, I'll give them to you.
Quick to decide, as expected.
But keep this in mind.
You'll regret touching my items someday.
Your items?
Cultural assets belong to the country, no?
Moreover, these are national treasures.
Now you sound like
the regulations team chief.
National treasures or stolen goods, I paid
good money for them. They belong to me.
That's your logic.
Thank you for the ride, Chief.
No problem.
By the way,
I had some men stationed here.
They'll patrol the area at night
so you'll be safe. And...
Don't worry about Gyoon.
We'll find him first, for sure.
Thank you.
I'm always burdening you.
When did you ever burden me?
Just, you know, this and that.
I trouble you all the time.
Chohee, are you still
uncomfortable around me?
What?
You said before that you were
always uncomfortable around me.
Are you still?
No. Now I'm not.
I'm not sure when, but I've grown
comfortable with you, Chief.
In the past, I felt nervous talking to you
and was uneasy eating with you.
Hearing that you feel comfortable now
is somehow upsetting.
Why? Isn't it a good thing?
No, I don't think it is.
I liked it better when I was
an uncomfortable person to you.
Uncomfortable because just looking
at that person sends the heart racing.
Because you're that kind
of person for me now.
Chief.
It's true, I like you.
Um, Chief.
I'm sorry, but I don't have the leisure to
think of things other than Gyoon and Dad.
And there's also Bumsang.
I know I'm a bit late.
But I just wanted to tell you, that when
things are difficult, you can lean on me.
So we're even now, aren't we?
I'll try my best to be comfortable with you,
so don't feel pressured by what I said.
Bye.
Hey.
When did you get here?
Just now. I didn't mean to overhear.
It just happened.
Bye.
You can't just leave like this.
The thing is...
Chief Kang was totally cool.
He knows how to confess his feelings.
Much better than an inept boyfriend.
But he always does things
a little awkwardly.
I mean, that was bad timing.
I'll confess my feelings at a totally
fancy place, okay? That I like you.
That I sincerely like you.
Then again, maybe
you don't like fancy things.
I don't know. Go in. Bye.
I like you.
Chief, is something wrong?
Hello.
What's with the heavy sigh?
What? Ah, it's nothing.
It doesn't look like nothing.
By the way, Chief Noh
wanted you to call him.
Chief Noh?
Yes.
Okay, I'll do that.
Yeah, I'll leave it to you.
Yeah, okay.
Chief Noh!
How could you do this to me?
[Chairman Jang]
Did you prepare the items
like I instructed?
I did, but what do you plan to do?
What else?
We have to strike a deal.
If a merchant doesn't make deals,
how will he make a profit?
But this deal is a little...
We won't find out if we made
a profit in this deal until it's done.
Just do as I instructed.
Yes, sir.
And I almost forgot.
Call Mr. Kim and tell him to come.
Yes, sir.
Chohee!
Hey, Joohyun.
Going somewhere?
To the general manager's office
to give him a report.
The general manager? How unlucky.
What a bad way to start the day.
Good l uck.
Thanks.
Did you fight with Chohee again?
What?
It's just that there was
a weird tension between you two.
We didn't fight.
But I did do something wrong.
What did you do?
Chief! You're wearing ties
more and more these days.
Does it look bad?
Not at all.
Looks great with the necktie clip.
I have an appointment right now, so push
back today's meeting to the evening.
Okay.
Bumsang, I'll see you in the evening.
Goodbye.
Our chief is acting weird these days.
I think he's having an affair.
An affair?
He keeps leaving the office
to meet someone. It's suspicious.
Let's check the items first.
Why are you here when it was
Chairman Jang I talked to on the phone?
Did you really think
he'd come out to a place like this?
Of course not.
I just asked because I wondered
if maybe he had health problems.
Why are you stalling?
Jeez, you're impatient.
Is there a reason you're stalling?
Not at all.
Guys.
Yes, Boss?
Let's take this opportunity
to salvage our hurt pride.
Yes, Boss!
It seems to be in order.
Then I should check my items, too.
Go ahead.
About the hard drive. I didn't make
a copy so there's no need to worry.
Doesn't matter if you made a copy.
You'll never get to see it again.
What do you mean?
Uncle!
You're -
We have to run!
What are you doing?
Go after them!
Let's go!
Uncle, why isn't Chief Kang here yet?
I don't know. He said he would be here.
I don't know what happened.
I don't kow if we should run with these.
Uncle!
What the -
It seems Chairman Jang
saw right through our plan.
What do we do?
Let's get out of here first.
Yo, Chief Noh.
Of all the places to run into you.
Hey! It's that weasel!
I was wondering where you had gone.
It seems I can catch
two birds with one stone today.
I don't understand how this happened
but thanks for traveling in a set.
Guys!
Yes?
It's hot. Why don't we take these guys
for a little swim with the fishes?
Crush ‘em!
What's going on?
Bumsang?
Move it!
Don't you guys have any basic manners?
All of you ganging up on two guys!
Bastard!
Bro!
You're -
Mr. Kim! Long time no see.
When are we going to
get cleared for mobilization?
I told you to wait.
Why are you badgering me?
It's been two hours already.
We're in a state of emergency right now!
Why can't we at least take some guys
from the criminal investigations team?
I don't know! How am I supposed
to let you go when the superiors say no?
I'll try again, so wait a bit more.
Sir!
The last time we met, did I fail to mention
I was close with the police commissioner?
You think you'll be safe
after this insolent behavior?
Chief, what happened?
We won't get approved.
Let's go on our own.
Just us?
Gyoon. I'll clear a path for you.
Take Chief Noh and go.
What are you talking about?
Call Chief Kang.
I'll try to hold on as long as I can.
Bro!
You want to all die together?
Bro...
Look at those two.
Are you two dating?
Why are you conversing so intimately
in the middle of a fight?
We were discussing how you are
a disgrace to the surname Kim.
You little!
You mean Gyoon is
with Chief Noh right now?
Yes. I don't know the details
so let's head over there.
This is the regulations team.
Yes.
What? Okay, okay.
Yes, I understand.
What do we do? Bad news!
Chief Noh was taken to the hospital.
What?
What about Gyoon?
Is Gyoon okay?
Gyoon called the hospital himself
so he's fine. The problem is Bumsang.
Bumsang?
Bumsang was there with them?
Why was he there?
Seems he fought with Mr. Kim and
his men to save Chief Noh and Gyoon.
The investigations team
went to save him, but -
Joohyun, what did you just say?
What happened to Bumsang?
Subtitles Provided by MBC America