Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
There was an uproar seven years ago
when General Shovel stole it.
National treasure no. 238,
the “Sowonhwagaecheob.”
General Shovel... Taesoon Heo.
Hey, what brings you
here at this hour?
Let's have
a glass of wine together.
She has impeccable timing.
Episode 8
Coming over to a guy's house later
at night? You're bolder than I thought.
I thought we were dating.
If we're dating, this isn't such a big deal.
You're the one who ignored me
when I suggested a fake relationship.
Have a change of heart?
Not exactly...
If you have something to say,
spit it out. What is it?
You wouldn't come over at this hour just
to drink wine with me. Why'd you come?
If I ask you something,
can you answer me honestly?
That big, huh? Seeing how you're
stalling for dramatic effect and all.
Go ahead. I'll tell you the truth.
I saw you at the museum today.
Why did you meet Chairman Jang?
We're searching for
Mr. Kim and Dongpal Kim.
You guys focus on retrieving
the items from the Yeoju case.
Yes, sir. About Chairman Jang
from the Ohsung Group.
Yes?
Supposedly he visited
the museum today.
Chairman Jang did?
That's strange for a man
who hates being in the public eye.
Joohyun, are you going home?
Chohee left already, so why can't I?
Joohyun, we need to get going.
Okay. I have some business
to take care of. Goodbye.
Oh, they're gearing up for war. Looks like
they'll be pulverizing someone today.
Joohyun isn't that kind of person.
I hope she gets over
her broken heart soon.
You need to get over it first.
By the way, Mr. Nah, why did
Chairman Jang visit the museum?
He thought the “Bihaedangjib” was there
and wanted to see me on the side.
You? Why?
“Bihaedangjib.” Chairman Jang.
Can't you make the connection?
Don't you remember
the charity auction?
It was ruined because
I affirmed the “Bihaedangjib.”
Do you know how much
trouble I got into?
Really?
Yes. I had a hell of a time
trying to calm him down.
Is that so?
What a relief.
What do you mean, a relief?
He totally chewed me out.
Well, that's not
exactly what I meant...
To tell you the truth,
I was worried.
Worried about what?
It was Chairman Jang who sent you
to Japan to get the vase.
Who knows what else
he'd ask you to do?
It isn't easy saying no
to a person like him.
I was afraid you'd get caught up
in something like that again.
That's why I came to see you today.
Since when did you worry
about me like this?
You're right. There's certainly
no need for me to worry about you.
But I felt I needed to get involved so
you'd stop walking down the dark path.
You're a better fit with being
the CHA's advisory member, you know.
Well, I said what I came here for,
so I'll be going then.
Hey, the bottle's open,
you might as well stay and drink.
Drink? No, it's okay.
Don't come out. I'll go on my own.
No, I'll give you
a ride home. Hold on.
It's okay, really.
I told you before, I can't let a woman
go home alone at this hour. One sec.
What's that?
Hey, hey!
Do all women of the regulations team
enjoy snooping around people's houses?
I wasn't snooping. I was just looking.
Are you restoring something?
What else?
Let's go, come on.
I told you, it's okay.
This is it?
So this is her house.
Shouldn't we have called first?
We can't give her
the time to prepare herself.
That's right. It has to be a surprise attack
so we can drive her into a corner.
Dears, thank you.
I won't forget this.
Don't thank us.
We're doing what we have to.
We can't let Bumsang fall into
Chohee's hands. No way, absolutely not.
All right, then, let's go.
Who are you?
Your sister's home, right?
Ah, you came to see my sister?
He's cute.
Oh my, did you see him smiling?
His eyes were twinkling.
We'll do it ourselves.
I'm sorry I don't have anything
good to offer in refreshment.
Oh no, it's okay.
What did you say your name was?
Ah, my name is Gyoon Heo.
Gyoon...
Gyoon Heo who wrote
the “Dongeuibogam?" How cute.
That would be Joon Heo.
Gyoon Heo wrote
“The Tales of Honggildong.”
Why'd you open your big mouth?
Foot in the mouth, I tell you.
Dears, what are you doing?
Did you forget why we came here today?
That's right. What brings
you here to meet my sister?
See, the reason we came here is...
We came to congratulate Bumsang and her about their beautiful relationship...
sincerely from
the bottom of our hearts.
Mmph, mmph, that's not it.
We wish them eternal happiness.
Why would they?
What? They offered you
a part-time job at the CHA?
Have they gone off the deep end?
Gyoon, I'm coming home
so let's talk when I get there.
Why'd they invade your home?
Why else?
You started the rumor that we're dating.
How are you planning to fix this?
A man's word is his honor, and
there's no use crying over spilled milk.
We'll just break up later.
What, a month later?
Because of differences in personality?
Shall we make it men trouble? Chohee's
indecent life, something like that?
Ugh, let's just stop here.
I'm wasting my breath.
Why isn't the bus coming?
I told you I'd give you a ride home.
You drank.
And I don't wanna fall victim to your
humanism sham. Know what I'm sayin'?
That's why you have
a ton of work but no men.
Think what you will.
Chohee!
What?
What if... if...
If what?
If another item that your father stole surfaces, what are you going to do?
I'll try my best to recover it. Why?
I'm just asking.
Just asking?
Yeah, hey, bus number 431, right?
It's here. Go home then.
Okay, I'm going.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Ugh, it's so hot.
Officer Cho?
Yes?
Did you see Chohee?
My guess is she's
somewhere with Bumsang.
You know how it is. This is the most
passionate time of the year for couples.
You think that's all? After all the rumors
surrounding them, they're finally dating.
That's what I'm saying.
It's you.
The person I like is you,
not Bumsang.
Are they really dating?
What was that, Chief?
What? Oh, nothing.
By the way, Officer Cho?
Yes?
If you have some free time, can you look
into Chairman Jang's recent activities?
Chairman Jang?
Yes. You know how we got nothing
out of the charity auction raid.
I heard he showed up
at the museum.
He's not one to do things without reason,
so I want to check up on him.
Understood.
Hey, isn't that Joohyun?
I never expected to see the princess
so down in the dumps like that.
That's what im saying. She's so
lifeless these days, like a sick puppy.
Chohee and Bumsang shouldn't
express their affections so blatantly.
Chief, we'll see you later.
Okay.
Jingoo, let's go.
We'll be back.
Joohyun, have you eaten?
C'mon, I'll buy you lunch.
I want to see you eat some.
Why aren't you eating?
Joohyun?
Chief, I'm so incredibly embarrassed.
I didn't even realize that they were
dating, and I thought he was into me.
Can you imagine how
dumbfounded he must've been?
Joohyun, did you like him for real?
Does anyone pretend
to like someone else?
Then you should've
told him seriously how you felt.
You were always so playful that no one,
including Bumsang, took you seriously.
Chief, what should I do?
First things first, eat up. And go back
to how you were, cute and lively.
Everyone's worried
because you're so depressed.
Joohyun. Joohyun?
Chief, I'm such a bad person.
Now that Bumsang dumped me,
I understand how you must've felt.
You were so into me, yet all I did
was talk about Bumsang in front of you.
How hurt you must've been, Chief.
Um, Joohyun, the thing is...
I am such a cruel person.
Chief, can you ever forgive me?
Yeah. Why don't you eat?
Go on then.
Ah, it's so hot!
Why make us do workshops with
the shopkeepers in this sweltering heat?
It's a bother for both parties.
That's what I'm saying.
Chohee, you don't look tired at all.
Compared to working on-site,
this is nothing.
Why are you two making
such a big fuss over nothing?
Big fuss?
I see.
Now that you're dating Bumsang,
you've got nothing to fear?
Chohee, I'm Mr. Nah.
Your superior!
How dare you say
I'm making a big fuss over nothing!
Stealing Bumsang
from Joohyun is one thing.
Now you say whatever you want to your
elders? How can you change overnight?
What did I do wrong?
Excuse me.
I have somewhere I have to stop by first.
You two can handle the last place, right?
Wh - what?
I did most of the work until now.
So I'll leave the last one to you, okay?
She's definitely going off on
a secret date with Bumsang, isn't she?
How could they go on a date
during working hours? She's changed.
She's a different person.
- Uncle.
- Oh, hey.
Isn't it hot?
Thanks.
Snap it off, like this.
I thought you'd be all sullen,
but I was wrong.
Why would I be?
Congressman Lee took
the “Bihaedangjib,” didn't he?
When I heard,
I was angry enough to chew nails.
You must've felt terrible.
There's nothing I can do about it.
This is the line of work I chose.
By the way, I told Gyoon to meet us here.
I wanted us to have lunch together.
Gyoon, too? Man, I can't stay. I have
an important meeting I have to attend.
That's too bad.
Oh, Chohee?
Yes?
More of Taesoo's items are surfacing
now the statute of limitations is ending.
Which items?
You know the “Sowonhwagaecheob?”
I think it's gonna make an appearance.
“Sowonhwagaecheob?”
Do you know who has it?
A guy who deals with the filthy rich says
that Chairman Jang seems to have it.
It seems it's a bit damaged so
he's looking for someone to restore it.
He's looking for
someone to restore it?
But it won't be easy. After all, it may
be a rare item, but it's also stolen.
I think I know who's doing it.
I'm sorry, I have to get going.
Hey, Chohee! Chohee!
[Chohee Heo]
Don't we have a meeting later?
Why in such a hurry to meet me?
Why did you lie to me last night?
What are you talking about?
“Sowonhwagaecheob.”
You're still going to play dumb?
The item you're restoring,
it's the “Sowonhwagaecheob,” right?
And that's the real reason you met
Chairman Jang at the museum. Isn't it?
Fine, you're right.
Let's not beat around the bush.
Report it to the police.
Restoring a stolen item is a felony.
I can't turn a blind eye when I know.
If you report it yourself,
you won't get into too much trouble.
What if I can't?
No, what if I don't want to?
Bumsang!
I know that the “Sowonhwagaecheob”
is an item your father stole.
I know you want to get it back
like the “Bihaedangjib.”
That's why I didn't feel comfortable
with Chairman Jang's request.
Then you should have refused.
Did he offer you a professorship?
Is that why you couldn't say no?
Why do you live your life like that?
You don't have to live the way you do.
What's wrong with the way I live my life?
Turn me in if you want to.
But keep this in mind. I'm not living my
life by cheating or trampling on others.
I'm just working with people
who realize and need my abilities.
I never once thought
that was so incredibly wrong.
I'm leaving.
Bumsang, remember this.
I don't intend to turn you in.
But you shouldn't live like this.
I think that you absolutely shouldn't.
It's true that no one can live life without
dirtying their hands at least once.
Compromising oneself to get what
one wants isn't necessarily a bad thing.
But you know what?
A sin is still a sin.
No matter what anyone says,
that's what I think.
Ugh, so hot.
What are we eating later?
Let's eat cow intestine, okay?
How can you be thinking about dinner?
Joohyun's in so much pain...
Why didn't Chohee
make it to the meeting?
It's strange. She never misses
a meeting if she can help it.
- Did something happen?
- Do you think...
They already got into a couple's tiff?
You're being a little too blunt.
Come on, let's go.
Definitely too blunt.
What did I say?
They're always like that. Just let
their comments slide off your back.
Don't worry about me.
Bumsang, I'm sorry we couldn't
provide protective custody for you.
What?
We should have used
a couple of men to protect you.
But the procedure for approval is very
particular and its options are limited.
It's fine. No need to worry.
Thank you for being so understanding.
You're going to dinner, right?
I have something
to take care of at home.
Then let's have a drink next time.
Sure. Goodbye then.
What is it you wish to say to me?
The “Sowonhwagaecheob”
is a stolen national treasure.
As I'm sure you already know.
I'm sure it's not easy for you
to own a stolen good...
so why don't you take this
opportunity to do something good?
You want me to
donate it to the country?
Yes.
You're quite a bold woman.
What if I refuse?
Then I have no other option but to take
care of the matter according to the law.
You'll be charged for possession of
a stolen good, Bumsang for restoration.
And since it's a national treasure,
it won't be a light sentence.
So the reason you came to me first
is out of consideration for Bumsang?
As I'm sure you already know,
he's a person with a valuable talent.
If you make the right decision,
everything can end without a fuss.
Sir, please cherish people as much
as you cherish your possessions.
I entreat you.
I'm sorry, but I'll have to refuse. If things
go public, he'll be the one hurt, not me.
It seems you're the one
who has to make a decision.
Did I leave the cover open?
What the...
What in the world?
How could this happen?
What now?
What do I do?
Shouldn't you tell Chairman Jang?
You don't know what he's like?
He won't believe that it was stolen
and he won't just let this slide.
Did you call the police?
The “Sowonhwagaecheob” is a national
treasure. A stolen national treasure!
You don't know what'll happen
if I involve the police?
What are you going to do? Who could have taken it? Have any theories?
None.
Ah, I don't know.
Chohee Heo.
The item you're restoring,
it's the “Sowonhwagaecheob,” right?
Let's not beat around the bush.
Report it to the police.
Why didn't Chohee
make it to the meeting?
She never misses
a meeting if she can help it.
Hey! What are you saying?
What about Chohee?
Hey!
It's you, isn't it?
You took it?
You're the only one it could be.
Where did you hide it?
Bumsang, what are you
talking about? I took what?
You're going to play dumb?
Fine.
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
Bumsang!
Hey!
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
The “Sowonhwagaecheob.”
You really don't know?
What?
Only you and Chairman Jang knew
I had it. Where did you hide it?
You lost it?
Lost it?
Fine, where were you during
the meeting? After fighting with me?
Can't tell me?
I was...
Anyway, it wasn't me.
I didn't steal it.
Don't lie. It has to be you.
You're the only one!
Sis, I...
Oh wow, sorry. Sis, I'm sorry.
Sir, I'm sorry.
This house really needs a doorbell.
Please continue.
I'll give you until tomorrow
to put it back. If not, I'll...
I don't know what I'll do.
Sis, I'm really sorry.
I ruined the mood, didn't I?
But he's quite the indiscreet person.
Sis, did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
That bastard!
Man... Now she's
haunting me in my dreams.
[Chairman Jang]
Yes, sir.
Good work.
Chohee, why are you so out of it?
Should I move this?
First check the inventory
to see if we're missing anything.
Hey, Sangho!
Who made this pile? Did you?
Do it again, okay?
Chohee!
Chief.
You were avoiding me
just now, weren't you?
No. I have to
organize the things here.
If you avoid me like that,
I'll feel apologetic towards you.
Can't we try to be more
comfortable with each other?
Frankly speaking,
I think that'll be a little hard.
I was never fully comfortable
with you in the past either.
And the reason I'm avoiding you is
I end up lying to you against my wishes.
So I'm ashamed of myself...
But there's no need
for you to feel sorry.
Man, after seeing your expression,
I'll take back everything I said.
Let's try to be more
comfortable with each other.
I practically twisted your arm.
It's okay if you do.
Chohee, don't bum around
and help us out here.
I should get back to work...
You're not done with the restoration?
You said you could do it quickly.
It seems I'll need
a little more time.
I guess it can't be helped.
Is a week enough time?
Yes.
By the way, it seems you know
a very interesting woman.
Excuse me?
Yesterday afternoon Chohee Heo
from the CHA came to see me.
She asked me to donate the
“Sowonhwagaecheob” to the country.
And she advised me to cherish you
and not just my possessions.
She was a very bold woman.
'Anyway, it wasn't me.
I didn't steal it.'
It really wasn't her.
Then who in the world...
Yes, Mr. Nah. What's up?
What? Chohee got hurt?
Which hospital is it?
Okay, I'm headed there.
For Chohee of all people to be in the
hospital, it certainly doesn't feel right.
I know what you mean. She's most like
herself when she's working her butt off.
With the up comes the down.
She found herself a boyfriend
and was going on dates.
Then something like this happens.
It's so sad, it really is.
Did you contact Bumsang?
Yeah.
But I don't think he'll be happy that
she hurt herself saving another man.
He'll be pissed.
Chief!
I'm worried that Chohee's
hurt worse than we presumed.
She'll have to stay
in the hospital for a while.
This isn't good.
For the time being, you two
will have to juggle her duties. Okay?
Yes, sir.
Then let's go home.
Get Joohyun to do some of the work.
I'm not doing anymore.
I can't tell Joohyun to do more work.
Then you do it.
Fine, I'll do it.
Chief.
Oh, how are you feeling?
Lie back down.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
That's a relief.
I'm sorry you're hurt
because of me, Chohee.
Please don't be.
At a time like this just say,
“Thanks, Chohee.”
Thanks, Chohee.
I'll stop by whenever I have time
tomorrow, so take care of your body.
Take care of her body? Sounds like he's
talking to a woman who just had a baby.
Maybe I'm biased
because he has a kid already?
I'm fine. Please
don't worry about me, Chief.
“Please don't worry about me, Chief.” What's with her?
I'll be leaving then. Lil' bro, you're going
to stay here with her, right?
Of course. Do you realize you've been
saying you'd leave for thirty minutes?
Gyoon, why are you being so rude?
No, it's okay.
I'm really leaving. Get some rest.
Okay, goodbye, Chief.
Yeah.
Are you really leaving?
Yup.
Then I'll walk you out.
Sis, I'll be right back.
Let's go.
Bumsang.
- Hey.
- The “Sowonhwagae...”
You first.
No, you first.
Is your arm all right?
It hurts a little,
but nothing I can't handle.
Did you find
the “Sowonhwagaecheob?”
No, not yet.
What are you going to do?
Won't youl get into big trouble
if Chairman Jang finds out?
Probably.
I wonder who took it.
Why didn't you tell me
you went to see Chairman Jang?
How could you say nothing
when I was making you out to be thief?
Have you ever been
accused of being a thief?
When I was younger, whenever
something disappeared at school...
they pointed fingers at me.
All because of my father.
No matter how much I said
I didn't do it, no one believed me...
until they could see
the missing item for themselves.
If the person is not ready to believe,
it's no use defending myself.
Do you believe me now?
I'm sorry.
You know how to apologize.
Yeah, and I also know how to
slice apples. Where's the knife?
How rude!
I'll accept your apology.
Hey, you need to wash it first!
A little dirt won't kill me.
Chief, we'll be back later.
Okay, but where are you going?
We're definitely
not going to the sauna.
We're on our way to Madam Oh's bar
to track Dongpal Kim down.
We're definitely not going there to see
Ms. Kim who works there. So he says.
Please call me as soon as
you find out anything.
Yes, sir. By the way, Chief,
about Chairman Jang.
Yes?
He cleaned up after the charity auction
so well that there are no scraps at all.
Yeah, the tracks
are completely spotless.
There's a rumor he'll release an item,
but the underlings won't spill anything.
Let's keep an eye on him.
He'll make a mistake one day.
Is that all?
Oh, and it's not very important,
but about the vase at Tanaka's house.
Yes, what about it?
I don't know what got into Chairman
Jang, but apparently he really wants it.
He even sent someone
to Japan to get it for him.
Officer Cho, wasn't that vase
determined to be a fake?
Was it?
Anyway, we'll be off then.
Okay.
Jingoo, let's go to see Ms. Kim.
We'll be back later.
So Chairman Jang
sent someone to Japan?
I know it's not an easy thing to ask,
but please look into it, okay?
I'll try, but I can't
guarantee anything.
That's why I'm asking you.
I'm counting on you, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
The food doesn't look too appetizing.
There you go, finding fault
in everything. Did you eat?
Not hungry.
Did Chief Kang stop by?
Yeah. He came yesterday.
The least he can do is nurse you all
night, and he didn't even drop by today?
Hey, Chief Kang's a busy person.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
You like him that much?
There you go again. Goodness...
How's the search for
the “Sowonhwagaecheob” going?
I understand you're anxious about it, but
consider my feelings and stop asking.
Bumsang, that's hurtful.
What is?
It's true that I'm curious about it
since it's an item my father stole.
But I'm also worried about you.
I'm not trying to take credit
or anything, but I do feel upset.
Hey, hey, there's no reason to feel upset.
Here, have a quail egg and cheer up.
I'm being nice so take it already.
Why are you acting out
of character? I don't want it.
Let me ask you something.
What?
Is there another reason behind your
quest to retrieve all your father's items?
It's because I'm
self-conscious and selfish.
The last time I saw him, I told him
that if he doesn't return everything...
I'll never see him again.
That I'll never forgive him. To go plead
forgiveness to my dead mother.
And I haven't seen him since.
Sometimes I can't help but think that he
can't come home because I said all that.
If I put everything back where they
belong, maybe he'll come home then.
Something like that.
That's nonsense, you know.
It is, isn't it?
It's complete nonsense.
I'm not repaying my father's debts.
I'm not so filial or patriotic.
I want my conscience to be at peace.
I'm looking for them to live in peace.
Man, you're being complicated.
Bottom line is you miss your father.
You hope that he's alive.
He's alive. If you get all the items back,
he'll come back. Believe in that.
Here's some grilled beef.
Bumsang.
Oh, hello.
Hi. How's Chohee?
She just fell asleep.
I guess I came too late.
Go on in. She was
waiting for you all day.
I'll be going then.
Bumsang, you want to
go grab a drink with me?
Let me pour you a drink.
This line of work usually runs
in the family. Is that your reason?
Close enough.
My grandfather is a potter.
I see.
He must be proud of you. To be a
famous art expert at such a young age.
That's not necessarily true.
What about you? Did you start off
in the cultural assets unit?
No, I started off in
the violent crimes unit.
But I haven't left since I joined the
investigations team seven years ago.
You have an aptitude for it?
Not necessarily, but I do like it.
I'm lucky to be doing work that I enjoy.
Of course, it's a great blessing
to be able to do work that you enjoy.
But sometimes in this line of work,
there are unfortunate situations.
Young and talented people like you
deal with stolen goods or restore them.
I hope you don't do
anything illegal like that.
I don't really like
the phrase “stolen goods.”
What do you mean?
To someone with your job, it's important
whether or not an item is stolen.
But to someone who does
restoration work like me...
cultural assets are patients
in need of a doctor's care.
A doctor shouldn't discriminate against
patients dying in front of their very eyes.
My work is the same.
When there's a cultural asset before me,
it's not that important if it's stolen or not.
Am I right to assume that you'll do
restoration work for stolen goods?
A cultural asset is just that.
I'm saying that theoretically using
“stolen goods” to describe it is wrong.
That's an extremely
sophistic take on things.
Please consider it the worthless
philosophy that a man has of his job.
Bumsang, the more I get to know you,
the more intriguing you are.
The same goes for you. Cheers!
Thank you for the meal, Chief.
You're welcome. I want to go for
another round, but I have to hurry home.
I heard you have a daughter.
Her name is...
Jiyoon.
Jiyoon. Jiyoon Kang.
What a pretty name.
The girl is prettier than the name.
I'm a fool when it comes to my kid.
By the way, is the investigations team
still investigating General Shovel?
General Shovel?
I told you before that he hasn't been
active in years. Most consider him dead.
So you're saying he could be alive.
I guess. But why bring up
General Shovel all of a sudden?
I was just curious because
he's such a legendary art thief.
You should get going.
Jiyoon must be waiting.
Okay. Bumsang, let's have
another drink next time.
Sure.
Jeez, I forgot...
Goodness, something will
fly right into her mouth.
'You said that a fake with memories
is the same as being authentic...
but this art expert thinks otherwise.'
'The line remains drawn between
what's fake and what's authentic.'
'This is an authentic Goryeo
celadon porcelain set...
though it's only worth thirty bucks.'
'I give this as a gift to you, your brother and the father you believe will return.'
I've asked all my superiors to look
around, but I've come up with nothing.
You didn't mention me, did you?
Of course not. I'm searching in roundabout ways so don't worry.
Okay, thanks.
No problem.
Hey, is Chohee still in the hospital?
She has to stay a few more days.
Oh yeah? Maybe I'll go visit her later
with a bouquet of flowers.
Hey, why would you go visit her?
And why are you calling her
by her first name? It's insulting.
What the? You're being weird.
I'm calling her Chohee ‘cause that's her
name. So why do you feel insulted?
That was quite a curious reaction.
What's curious?
I'm saying Chohee will feel insulted.
Hey, I have to get going.
Where are you going today?
I'm following the
investigations team today.
The art thief Mr. Kim is after me so
I want to be there when they catch him.
Bumsang, how have you been behaving
at the CHA to be targeted already?
That's what I'm saying.
There must be something huge
happening if they didn't even notice you.
Call me if you hear anything, okay?
Okay.
Do we really have to go out
when it's this hot?
Stop talking if you're clueless.
Stop fighting, stop fighting.
I'm sorry. Did you wait long?
You have your hands full with your love
life. Why do you want to come with us?
Oh, I enjoy on-site work very much.
Officer Cho, you know, right?
And how can I sit out
when you're going after Mr. Kim?
This is odd.
We thought you forgot us all since
you're always nursing your girlfriend.
There's a rumor that you set up
a living at the hospital.
Bumsang, you're really
planning on going with us?
We might not make it back
to Seoul tonight.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
A man can't go back on his word.
One moment, please.
Yes, yes, sir.
I'm sorry. Something came up,
and I have to get going.
Look here.
What the.
He totally went back on his word.
If he weren't so glib, I wouldn't feel
so insulted. He is way too slick.
That's what I'm saying.
He's definitely running off to Chohee.
Let them be. It's the best time of their
relationship, so cut them some slack.
Poor Joohyun is the one left in the dust. My poor Joohyun...
Yes, Chief.
What did you say?
At the museum?
Were you surprised that
I suddenly asked you to come?
No.
I can tell that you were
considerably surprised.
Why did you call me?
How much longer do I have to wait
for the “Sowonhwagaecheob?”
Just a couple more days,
and you can see it again.
A couple of days, you say?
Why are you sitting up?
I told you to rest at home. Why are
you here so early in the morning?
Why else? My only sister is laid up in the
hospital, so how can I enjoy being alone?
What is this?
This? A Goryeo celadon porcelain set.
It's authentic?
Where did you get it?
Was it Bro?
Who are you calling “Bro?” I'd better
not catch you saying that again.
To not be able to call my brother-in-law
by his proper title... What a sad fate.
Oh ho, now you're ducking my hits?
You wanna die?
So Bro is...
“Bro” again!
Mr. Bumsang Kim is
our nation's best art expert.
So this must be incredibly rare.
How much is it worth?
Thirty bucks.
Thirty bucks?
There's a Goryeo celadon
porcelain set worth thirty bucks?
Oh, I nearly forgot. I was going
to watch some baseball today.
So the restoration will be
complete in a couple of days?
Yes, sir.
You don't watch
much television, do you?
Excuse me?
Everyone's in a frenzy today about it,
but apparently you missed it?
National treasure no. 238, the
“Sowonhwagaecheob,” stolen in 2001...
has returned to the museum
after seven long years.
An anonymous donor has returned
the “Sowonhwagaecheob” to the people.
[The unidentified donor
used a delivery service...]
Hey, Gyoon.
Go back to that just now.
What?
[...Prince Ahnpyeong's handwriting.]
[With a width of 16.5cm
and a length of 26.5cm...]
Subtitles Provided by MBC America