Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Bumsang isn't Robin Hood.
The real Robin Hood is...
General Shovel Taesoo Heo.
My father is Robin Hood.
Fine. Let's assume your father is alive.
Can you prove that he's Robin Hood?
Sowonhwagae scrapbook, "Chochung"
collection and "Maejukmun" vase.
All the items that were sent to the museum were items my father stole.
But that alone could be
mere coincidence, not evidence.
Logically speaking, yes,
but I just know that it's my father.
That he's stealing those items
in order to come back to Gyoon and me.
That's what I can't help thinking.
What do you want to do?
Please reopen the
official investigation of my father.
No, we can't do that.
Chief.
Chohee! There's no need for that.
If his case is reopened, everyone
will find out you're his daughter.
Things will become difficult for you.
I can deal with that, Chief.
Chohee!
My only concern is causing trouble
for Chief Noh. I don't care about myself.
So please begin
the official investigation.
Chief Kang, can you give us a moment?
I want to talk to Chohee privately.
Chohee.
Yes, Uncle.
Don't make me say it twice.
Let's lay this case to rest.
No more talk about
an official investigation.
No, Uncle. I can't do that.
Chief Kang is right. If the truth
comes out, you'll have a difficult time.
I can handle that.
It's okay even if I'm forced to quit
the regulations team because of Dad.
I've prepared myself for at least
that much. So please do as I wish.
Why are you rushing things? Matters like
these should be approached carefully.
Dad's in danger.
What do you mean?
Think about it. Only Chairman Jang's
most valued items have been stolen.
What do you think will happen
if his side catches Robin Hood first?
Dad's alive.
I know he is. And he's targeting
another one of Chairman Jang's items.
We have to find him before it's too late.
Or something bad might really happen.
I don't want to lose him again
while I stand by and do nothing.
Chief, you'll help me, won't you?
It's like the chiefs are working
in a different time zone today.
The meeting should've started a
long time ago. Why aren't they here yet?
What are you muttering about now?
Bumsang, weren't you
with Chief Kang earlier?
Yes. They'll be here soon.
What could be taking them so long?
Well...
Big news, big news! Really big news!
Joohyun, what's wrong?
About Robin Hood!
They found out who Robin Hood is!
What?
Who is it?
Who did they say?
That... Shove...
Right! The Shoveling General!
They said it's the Shoveling General.
Who the heck is the Shoveling General?
General Shovel?
General Shovel? Taesoo Heo?
Yes.
And here's the shocker.
Chohee is that person's daughter.
What in the world? You can't assume that
because they have the same surname.
Joohyun, let's stop getting
caught up in nonsensical gossip.
It's the truth. I overheard Chief Noh
and the others talking in the office.
Joohyun is speaking the truth.
We do think Taesoo Heo is Robin Hood,
and I am his daughter.
My father was missing for seven years.
I really want to find him.
So please lend me a hand.
Who is it? Who dares to come
into my bedroom and rob me?
And the “Maejukmun”vase was a gift to
Iwazaki. How could you let this happen?
I'm sorry, sir.
What did the police say?
Well, this is not a situation
we can report to the police.
They were all national treasures,
so we can't claim good faith purchases.
So you want me to take
the hits sitting down?
I'm sorry.
I don't need your apologies.
Go and find out who the thief is!
Do whatever it takes and find out!
When she was young, she used to cry
every time I took her dad away.
Then one day she stopped crying.
She would silently look at me, and I thought, “Am I sinning against her?”
I tried to excuse myself
that I was just doing my job.
But I couldn't stop
the overwhelming regret and guilt.
I'm a father, too.
I never imagined this was
the debt you mentioned.
I cluelessly spoke lightly about
General Shovel in front of her.
Imagine how hurt
she must've been each time.
Why didn't you tip me off beforehand?
I considered it.
But why didn't you?
The loss of Jiyoon's mother
seemed too great for you.
That's why I didn't tell you. But seeing
you now, it seems I made a mistake.
Excuse me?
If I knew you liked Chohee
so much, I would've told you.
Chief.
Here, let's drink.
Chief Kang, let me give you
a piece of information.
In my opinion Chohee
and Bumsang are not dating.
If you let go of the hand of the person
you like, it's hard to grab on again.
So go grab her hand.
It's okay for you to do so.
That's my opinion.
Don't involve yourself
anymore in this case.
What? Why do you say that
out of the blue?
Because I feel bad.
How can I ask for your help
when I know what you went through...
because my dad stole
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook?
What if I don't care?
What?
Things are fine if I don't care whether or
not your dad stole it or something worse.
Thanks for trying to make me feel better,
but that'll only make me feel worse.
I want to at least maintain a certain level
of courtesy with you. You understand.
Understand what? Since when
did you worry about courtesy?
There you go again.
Fine! If you don't need my help,
it's all the better for me.
Hey, are you pissed again?
I'm not. Bye.
Hey! Are you really not pissed?
I said I'm not!
I'm not pissed, I'm hurt.
You dense woman.
Now I feel bad again. But it wouldn't
be right for me to ask for his help.
Chohee!
Chief.
You're late.
Yes. Did you wait long?
No, I just got here.
What brings you here?
Just.
What?
Just wanted to see your face.
Did you drink?
You did, didn't you?
Chohee.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Until now I didn't know
anything about you at all.
Chief, the reason I didn't tell you
about my father is I lacked courage.
So if you apologize to me,
I'll be ashamed.
Just like you couldn't tell me about your
father, I I couldn't tell you something, too.
What is it?
I'll tell you later.
You can't mention it
and not tell me. What is it?
Later. I'll tell you
after we find your father.
I'm good now that
I've seen your face. Bye, then.
Goodbye.
I wonder what it is?
The items returned are designated
cultural assets and national treasures.
So you want me to single out
stolen national treasures...
that can't be good faith purchases?
Right.
Taesoo stole seven national treasures.
Take out the returned “Sowonhwagae”
scrapbook, the “Chochung” collection...
and the “Maejukmun” vase,
and there are four remaining.
They are Duryang Kim's “Sansu” painting,
the “Gimainmul” double goblets...
the “Geumdongdae” incense burner, and the “Geumdongyeorae” standing Buddha.
Do you know who
gained possession of them?
It's strange, actually.
Most of Taesoo's items passed through
me, but he sold these seven on his own.
But you were in charge of distribution.
For the most part, yes. But once
in a while, he sold items directly.
And that's what he did
with these seven.
If we find the four items, we can
figure out Robin Hood's next move.
All three at the museum came from
Chairman Jang. Maybe he had all seven?
That's possible.
Chairman Jang might've sold some.
So let's find out his dealers first
and if any were sold separately.
Yes, sir.
Uncle, I should buy you dinner
but I have somewhere to go.
It's okay. Go on. I'm sure
you'll buy me dinner later.
Of course. Thank you
for coming today, Uncle.
At least she's smiling.
Chief Noh, do you think
Taesoo really is alive?
I hope so.
For Chohee's sake, I hope he is.
I'm sure it wasn't easy coming here.
Thanks for acknowledging.
By the way, who was that in the
conference room? The guy from TV?
Something Kim. Bumsang Kim, right?
He's the perfect husband for Chohee.
What's your problem?
I told you I have someone in mind!
Who? Chief Kang? Jeez, that widower
with a kid and our single girl?
Who says a widower
can't marry a single woman?
You want to ruin Chohee's future?
Who's ruining her future?
Your suggestion itself
is ruining her future!
You...
Chohee!
Why are you running
in this sweltering heat?
Where are you headed?
Why do you ask?
Why else? I'm going with you.
No, you're not.
I thought about it, and I think it works out
better for me if you're indebted to me.
What?
And I promised to help you find
your father. A man should keep his word.
You don't need to.
Where are we headed?
Chohee!
The “Sansu” painting was seen
at a gallery in Pyeongchang-dong.
Let's go.
Oh, Bumsang, I heard you've
been helping Chohee out a lot.
Since the investigations team is in charge
of the case now, you don't have to worry.
And I'm sorry for accusing you of
being Robin Hood yesterday.
No problem.
Chohee, let's hurry.
Director Kang,
what are you saying?
They may be national treasures,
but thieves must still be arrested.
Isn't that a given?
I'll talk to you again soon.
The CHA is a pathetic institution
full of incompetent fools.
What did you find out?
I found out who
the CHA thinks is Robin Hood.
Yeah? Who is it?
They think it's Taesoo Heo.
Taesoo Heo? Who's that?
General Shovel Taesoo Heo?
Oh, your hands...
Your hands are so pretty for a guy.
You have great skin.
Do you want to eat?
Lil' Bro, why are you
holding up these busy ladies?
Hello, Bro!
Stop bothering these charming ladies
and let's go. Excuse us.
He called us charming!
Once they get a hold of you,
it's hard to get away.
You came here for nothing.
Your sister's not here.
I didn't come to see her.
I promised to meet Uncle Hwang here.
And I remembered
you were here, too, Bro.
I'm starting to get used to
you calling me that.
Is the Robin Hood
investigation going well?
What?
Who does the regulations team
think is Robin Hood?
Your sister didn't tell you? The truth is,
everyone thinks it might be your father.
My dad as Robin Hood?
I think she didn't want you to worry,
so maybe I shouldn't have told you.
My sister's like that. She still
thinks I'm a kid in grade school.
She probably didn't tell me
because she thought I'd worry.
Robin Hood is still a thief, after all.
But I worry more about her.
You do?
She's searching so hard for Dad,
so what if...
I mean, I desperately want him
to be alive, too, but if he isn't...
I don't think
I can watch her get hurt.
You care for her a lot, don't you?
She raised me from when I was kid,
acting as both my mother and father.
Dad might be the most
important person to her...
but she's my most important person.
She's all I have.
You're all grown up. I'll tell her to stop
treating you like a kid when I see her.
Excuse me.
Hey, Jonggyu.
Yeah, of course. I'll go.
All right, see you later.
I wish I could have dinner with you,
but I have to attend an alumni reunion.
An alumni reunion?
The “Sansu” painting at the gallery was
Jung Lee's, not Duryang Kim's. Your turn.
Chairman Jang is suspected
of dealing stolen goods...
but I'm not sure if it's
one of the four national treasures.
So we're going to stakeout
Chairman Jang's house.
Straightaway? Right now?
Of course now.
Let's hurry, we have no time.
Chief, we'll see you later.
Have a good day.
It's hard running around
doing legwork, right?
No, I'm just doing my job.
Um, Chohee?
Excuse me.
Hey, Gyoon.
You're with Chief Noh?
And Uncle Hwang?
Okay, I'll be right there. Yeah.
Chief, I'm so sorry.
I think I have to head out first.
No, no. You have to go.
Go on then.
Have a good day.
I'm leaving.
Chief!
Joohyun.
I brought the documents
you requested.
Thanks.
He doesn't look so good.
Is it because I didn't ask him to dinner?
Jeez, how bothersome.
Chief!
Your sister's coming right away?
No.
She has a lot of work to do
at the investigations office?
No, that's not it.
Uncles, I've decided
to marry off my sister.
So I sent Sis into
Bumsang Kim's arms tonight.
What?
How strange of Chief Noh
to want to eat at a place like this.
Where are they?
You skipped the last grad school alumni
reunion. What brings you out here today?
I told you I was sick last time! And I'm
leaving after greeting the professors.
The great Bumsang graced
our presence without a date?
Did you ever see me with a woman
after I joined the CHA?
Why didn't you bring Chohee?
She's busy.
Why? Chasing Robin Hood?
Still, you should've asked her.
Why bring it up at all?
She's too busy to come.
But Bumsang, are you saying
you wanted to bring Chohee?
Didn't I tell you not to call her by
her first name? You hardly know her.
What else would I call her
if not by her given name?
Heo.
Ms.
Maybe I should've
just mentioned it to her.
Isn't that Chohee?
[Sis, you've probably arrived by now.
Have a good time with Bro.]
What is he talking about?
Hey.
Huh? What are you doing here?
Isn't it obvious? An alumni reunion.
What are you doing here?
Gyoon wanted me to meet him here.
Gyoon did?
Yeah.
So he planned this.
What's that?
I met him briefly at the CHA today.
I told him I was dateless, and he kept
asking me where it was being held.
I didn't expect this.
He did something
completely uncalled for.
Have a good time at your reunion.
I'll be going then.
You're leaving?
Of course I'm leaving. Why would I stay?
I don't have the peace of mind to stay.
There seems to be a lot of
beautiful women inside. Have fun.
Hey.
What?
You should at least eat
before you leave.
Huh?
I mean, you have to eat anyway.
And I'm leaving soon, too.
Let's eat and leave together.
Let go for a sec.
Okay.
If you come alone, they don't
discount the membership fee, right?
Of course they don't.
Yeah? Then we should eat.
Let's sit here.
Bumsang! Bumsang Kim!
Stay here while I go say hello.
All right.
Look who it is.
It's Bumsang Kim.
It's been a while.
Bumsang, I thought you'd be too
embarrassed to show your face tonight.
Why would I be embarrassed?
Ah, getting cut from my lectures
and the TV show? I'm fine with it.
Liar. Aren't you mad jealous right now
because I took over everything you had?
Whatever, good for you.
Hey Yongcheol, you do know
how scary netizens are these days, right?
Study some before you make a fool
of yourself by saying something stupid.
What? How rude.
Stop it already. Why do
you guys fight whenever you meet?
Did you hear? Chairman Jang
is majorly investing in me these days.
I doubt that. He's probably
investing in your father, Minister Gong.
Whatever! He wants to put me in charge
of the school and his private art gallery.
He even sent us a gift recently.
A gift? What kind of gift?
Let me just say
that it's very valuable.
Anyway, I pity you
for floundering around...
like a fish out of water
after Chairman Jang cut you loose.
My date is waiting for me, so...
That laugh,
I swear I'm gonna kill him.
Leave him be. Him being
an ass is nothing new.
Why don't us dateless people
share a drink?
Jonggyu, you can enjoy drinking.
What?
Hey, isn't that Chohee?
How did that happen?
So Chief, why is it that
you're always buying me food?
You always come at mealtimes.
That's totally an excuse, isn't it?
Why else?
Aren't you trying to build up our
relationshipthrough shared meals?
How can eating a meal together
add anything to a relationship?
Chief, loads of couples strengthen
their relationship by eating together.
You seem indifferent
but you're secretly pretty sly.
What? Sly?
You're the one
who asked me to dinner.
I did, didn't I?
Fine. I won't ever eat
with you again. Satisfied?
What?
You can eat with me...
Jealous?
Yeah right.
They do look good together, though.
Why don't you go up
and perform a song for us?
Only couples are allowed.
Want to go up?
No, thank you.
You can do it by yourself.
You said they looked good up there.
Singing one song is no big deal.
Look at them, they're just belting it.
I can't sing. Gyoon takes after
my dad so he's good.
Your father was good at singing?
Yeah. He was really good.
The funny thing was that he only
sang hymns when he was drunk.
Hymns?
Yeah. Said he liked hymns because they're “nice” songs. Isn't that hilarious?
You'll find him soon.
I hope so.
Stay put.
Hello, fellow alumni.
I'm Bumsang Kim from the class of 97.
There's a person I really want to sing with,
so I came up despite the embarrassment.
I hope that she can forget her troubles
today and be happy, if only momentarily.
Hey, where are you going? Huh?
Everyone, I think she's shy,
so please give her a hand.
You're dead after this is over.
It's okay.
I'll die with no regrets.
I hope I'm the first person you think of
when you wake up in the morning
The way I think of you
I hope I'm also the person you want
to share the good things with
Though you'll probably leave me
Yes, I know that right now
love is a fear you need to avoid
You asked me uneasily if I knew that
when love deepens, it becomes sadness
But what you don't know is inexplicable sadness can give us the strength to live
Yes, I know that right now
love is a fear you need to avoid
You asked me uneasily if I knew that
when love deepens, it becomes sadness
But what you don't know is inexplicable sadness can give us the strength to live
Hey, why are you out here?
Are you buzzed?
No, I'm just a little embarrassed.
You're pretty good at singing.
I thought you were someone else.
What aren't I good at?
When I first saw you in Japan,
I really thought you were a thief.
And when I saw you again at the CHA,
I thought you were a crook.
A crook?
To put in your terms,
you looked like a fake.
Now do you realize how bad
you are at evaluating men?
My realization hasn't reached that far yet.
But I do know one thing.
You're not a fake
to carelessly throw out.
You know what? For the most part,
the fakes tend to look more authentic.
Treasures are like that.
Authentic items can still be
authentic with a piece missing...
but fakes are imitations
no matter how beautiful.
The problem is that people don't
realize the value of their treasures.
I'm talking about you.
You should definitely find your father,
but value yourself more.
If you wait for him with an untroubled
heart, you'll meet him for sure.
Do you really think so?
Of course. Those fated
to meet will surely reunite.
Those tied together by the string
of fate will surely meet again..
If not in this life, then the next.
If it's impossible in this life,
then I hope it happens in my next life.
Why are you worried?
You still have a long life to live.
Don't worry. I'll do everything
in my power to help you.
Let's go in and have another drink.
Hey.
I got to sing in public thanks to you.
I'd forgotten all about feeling happy,
but I was able to momentarily remember.
So thanks.
Chohee.
Yeah?
This time, I'm asking you
formally beforehand.
Lend me your lips.
What?
I'll be going then.
I'll take you home.
No, I'm more comfortable
going on my own.
Bye.
Oh, how sad my life is.
Is that you, Sis?
How was your date with Bro?
Sis! How was your date?
What's up with her?
How strange.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Why did I do that?
She thinks I'll miss
seeing her at her size?
Oh my god.
What do I do?
Oh! Chief.
Look forward while you're walking.
I'm sorry.
Did you have fun
with Chief Noh yesterday?
Yeah...
I found a middleman who met your dad
right after his release from prison.
I'm going now to meet him.
Want to come?
Is it okay if I tag along?
Of course. Let's go.
He came to borrow money.
He needed two grand. I didn't have
enough so I lent him twelve hundred.
Did he say anything else?
I asked him why he needed
the money, but he wouldn't answer.
I stopped asking, but he looked
strangely nervous about something.
What do you mean?
He'd fidget and keep looking around.
It seemed like he was being chased.
Chased? By whom?
Since he was just released,
I doubt it was the police.
He just kept saying he was all right,
so I'm not sure what was going on.
We bury some Goryeo celadon
that Bumsang's grandfather made.
Then later we distribute them
with a fake appraisal by Bumsang.
He'll get into trouble with the police.
We'll make money and get him good.
That's not our priority right now.
Stop with the nonsense.
What?
Didn't you tell me seven years ago
that Taesoo Heo was definitely dead?
Yes, I did.
Then why is he stealing my things? How
is the dead Taesoo stealing from me?
Did you see his dead body?
Did you see it with your own eyes?
Um, the thing is...
What happened was...
What else would I expect from you?
Go find him immediately.
If you don't, you're a dead man. Got it?
Yes, sir.
- Go.
- Yes, sir.
That imbecile.
Was Minister Gong
satisfied with the gift?
Yes. But I wonder
if it will do any good.
The world can change, but people
and money will never change.
What gift should I prepare for when you
meet Chairman Iwazaki this weekend?
Find a celadon on par
with the “Maejukmun” vase.
If that old fogey doesn't like it,
all our efforts will have been for naught.
Search out only the best.
- Officer Cho!
- What, what? What?
What?
Nothing, go back to sleep.
Hey, who's that?
Isn't that the secretary?
Why did you leave so early yesterday?
And Chohee, too. Did something happen?
Hey!
Huh?
Did you drink until late?
Don't even ask.
Yongcheol boasted about his father
so much that he ruined the mood.
Why's he like that?
Let him be.
Despite everything, we all know
how great his love is for his father.
The problem is he goes around
hurting his father's reputation.
Like how he mentioned the gift from
Chairman Jang. That's a bribe, not a gift.
A bribe from Chairman Jang?
It's obvious. You know well that Chairman
Jang doesn't give gifts without reason.
What was the gift?
How would I know? I'm assuming
some expensive pottery or painting.
Yongcheol's father is quite the collector
himself, so it's probably something big.
Chairman Jang gave
Minister Gong a bribe.
Jonggyu.
Yeah?
Can you subtly try asking
Yongcheol what the gift was?
‘It seemed like he was being chased.'
Chohee, let's go in.
What's wrong, Chohee?
Are you okay?
You're thinking about what we heard
earlier regarding your father.
I can't help being uneasy.
There's nothing to worry about.
That news was from seven years ago.
Someone might've chased
him then, but not anymore.
I hope so, Chief.
But I don't know why
I feel so apprehensive.
If something happened to him...
It's okay.
Everything's going to be all right.
Chief, excuse me.
Bumsang.
Hey, Bumsang!
Bumsang, can we talk?
About what?
You seem to be misunderstanding
something. Chief and I were...
Stop. I don't want to hear it.
Are you mad at me?
No. I'm not mad.
But I am a bit dumbfounded.
Bumsang.
Yesterday you were in my arms,
and today you're in his.
Don't you think
it's a little ridiculous?
What? Ridiculous?
You don't even care to listen
to what I have to say.
Fine, think what you want.
But know this, Bumsang. I...
Let's just stop.
Why did you say that?
Why did you say that to Chohee?
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
Don't misunderstand.
Now I have to explain
my feelings to you, too?
Chohee was in shock after hearing
that someone was chasing her father.
She was struggling to
handle that, so I hugged her.
You saw that and misunderstood.
What exactly are
your feelings towards her?
If neither of you is serious,
then you should drop the act...
What if I am serious?
What if I do sincerely like her?
I fully understand why you're saying
all this and how you feel towards Chohee.
Please keep in mind
that I, too, am serious about her.
Bumsang!
You're here early today.
Yeah.
Why aren't you two saying anything?
Did you have a lovers' spat?
Joohyun, I'm going ahead.
Hey, we need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Bumsang, what happened? People
like her are scary when they're mad.
Good luck.
Chohee! Wait up!
‘If neither of you is serious...'
‘What if I am serious?
What if I do sincerely like her?'
Chief.
Yes, Officer Cho?
I think Chairman Jang will be
on the move tonight with an item.
What item?
We're not sure,
but Officer Park says it's pottery.
He saw the secretary holding
a box designed for pottery.
Did you verify whom he's meeting?
We found out it's a Japanese person
after tailing the secretary yesterday.
So he's attempting
to smuggle it abroad?
I guess we'll find out
if we raid them tonight.
Robin Hood probably
knows about tonight, right?
Of course he knows.
He managed to steal all those items
because he's in Chairman Jang's vicinity.
What should we do?
Should we set the ball rolling?
Chief, they're on the move.
Got it. We're on our way.
Everyone, let's go!
Yes, sir.
Daegil!
The plan to arrest Robin Hood is in
motion? All right, we're on our way.
We're going on a mission
with Chief Noh absent?
Don't worry. I will fill
his shoes while he's gone.
Come on, let's go catch Robin Hood.
Why are you so tactless?
Isn't it better for you not to go, Chohee?
It'll be weird if you meet your father there.
Chohee, sit out on the mission today.
No, I'm fine. I'm going, too.
Let's go.
‘We need to talk.'
‘I have nothing to say to you.'
Jonggyu, did you find out anything?
[Yongcheol wouldn't get specific,
but I think it's a statue of Buddha.]
A statue of Buddha?
[I think you should meet him
and verify things yourself.]
Okay, thanks.
A statue of Buddha...
Oh, Bumsang, are you headed home?
Yes, did something happen?
We're on our way
to arrest Robin Hood.
Hey, we're busy! Hurry, hurry!
He thinks he's chief.
Bumsang, see you tomorrow.
Chief, Chairman Jang's in sight.
And the item?
The secretary has it.
He's carrying it in right now.
I wonder if Robin Hood
will show up today.
Who knows?
We'll find out, I guess.
Forgive me for making you wait.
It's okay. It's been a long time
since we met, Chairman Jang.
Can I help...
We had a tip about an illegal trade today.
We ask for your cooperation.
Thank you sparing the time
to meet me, Chairman Iwazaki.
I hope for boundless growth
between our two companies.
If we were to join forces, we could
conquer the Asian market easily.
I've been keeping an eye on the Ohseong
Group. I'm here hoping for good results.
Thank you, Chairman Iwazaki.
Goodness, we were so busy talking
business that I forgot about the gift.
Kim, the gift.
I'm always receiving gifts from you...
Since you're well known
for your interest in Goryeo celadon...
it was extremely hard choosing
an appropriate gift for you.
What is it? What is it?
Maybe it's Robin Hood?
Shh!
What the!
I'm Chief Shiwan Kang
of the investigations team.
We ask for your cooperation.
The item's still here.
I'm sorry. There was an outage
due to a power overload.
Then it was a real power outage?
What about Robin Hood?
What a nice house Yongcheol lives in.
Robin Hood?
Are you Taesoo Heo?
Subtitles Provided by MBC America