Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Episode 13
Chief Kang.
Chief.
What happened?Was it really
Taesoo's remains found at the site?
Is it Taesoo?
Yes, it seems certain.
We'll need further examination
to figure out the cause or time of death.
How... could this happen...
Did you call Chohee?
No, I couldn't.
I should call her now,
but I'm not sure how to tell her.
You're meeting your father for the first
time in seven years with a band-aid?
How clumsy.
You're that excited?
I'm a bit antsy and nervous and stuff.
Everything will be fine, right?
Of course. Congratulations.
You're congratulating me
when I haven't even met him yet?
What should I do?
The food's getting cold.
Should I clear the table?
Yes, Chief.
Daddy, don't leave. Daddy!
This is the last time.
It really is.
Dad! Dad!
Give these back!
Hey, Chohee. Chohee,
this is the last time, okay?
I'm serious. So won't you
forgive me this once?
I don't want to find him at all.
I don't care if he's dead or alive.
If he's alive, I'll catch him myself.
Chohee, don't worry.
I'll come back. I promise I will.
‘I have a wish that
I cannot speak aloud to anyone.'
‘It's okay if he never
comes back to see us.'
‘Please, I just want him to be alive.'
‘Please just let him be alive.'
Chief, where's Dad?
Chohee.
Chief, it's not true, right?
Dad's not dead. Right?
Chief... Please tell me
that Dad isn't dead. Please?
Chohee, I know you don't want
to believe it, but Taesoo is dead.
It's not true, Chief. It can't be true.
Why would he be dead?
Bumsang, you tell me.
My dad isn't dead.
You said he wasn't dead.
He's not dead.
Chief, he's not.
Dad, how could you leave like this?
Are you and Gyoon okay
with going on your own?
Of course. That's why I didn't let
Uncle Hwang or Chief come.
Is that why Bumsang isn't here?
I'm not sure.
I haven't seen him all day.
I see.
Um, Chief? Stop worrying
about me and go home.
Chohee.
It's enough that you stayed up
with me for several nights.
I want us three to be together for
the last time. Just Dad, Gyoon and me.
Chief, we'll be going then.
Chohee, don't forget that
everyone's worried about you.
Thank you.
Let's go, Gyoon.
Dad, are you at peace now?
How could you do this?
Didn't you miss us?
How could you just leave like this?
We waited for you for so long.
Dad. Gyoon and I will live
with smiles on our faces. Okay?
We'll come visit again, Dad.
[Taesoo Heo.]
Don't cry...
Should we have forcibly tagged long?
How could we intrude when they want
to say goodbye to their father?
So what's the cause of death?
Nothing particular.
Basically, no signs of foul play could
be determined from the remains.
I heard he was at the site
of the Paekche kingdom ruins?
The end of a thief's life is obvious.
He was buried alive while digging.
It's possible.
I can't help thinking this is all a relief.
What is?
Knowing for certain instead of
wondering whether he's dead or alive.
There's closure.
I guess.
If we consider Chohee, I agree.
You're right, but...
I wish he could've been alive.
Hello.
When did you get here?
Just now. I didn't wait long.
Did you say your farewell?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Really?
Yeah.
You know what? I thought I had
no good memories of my father.
After all the fighting
and crying and resenting...
I thought we shared no memories,
but I was wrong.
After sending my father away
after looking for him so long...
I remember even the trivial details.
How my dad helped me
to paint my nails when I was six.
How he breathed on my hands
to keep them warm during the winter.
How he cooked noodles for
Gyoon and me late in the night.
They're really trivial things,
but I remembered all of them at once.
I see.
I wonder what you would've said
if you got to meet him again.
I would've asked him to forgive me.
To forgive me for saying
I never wanted to see him again.
Though those words
mean nothing now.
I really wanted to tell him that.
He forgave you a long time ago.
You really think so?
Yeah, of course.
He was your father, after all.
You're probably tired.
Why aren't you resting?
Because of this.
What is this?
Chief Kang gave it to me
at the funeral home.
Dad's possessions found at the site.
[Chohee, Gyoon. I don't know why
it's so hard for me to go back to you.]
[A few days ago, I missed you so much
I found myself wandering near home.]
[And I saw you guys from afar.]
[Seeing how bright and healthy you guys
turned out to be, I felt so sorry to you.]
[And I was grateful to you as well.]
[When will I be able to return to you?]
[I'll be able to go back when I'm done
with the work I must complete.]
[Until then, don't forgive me.]
[And I don't know when it will be,
but I will surely return to you.]
[Until then... Until then, wait for me.]
Are you okay?
Why are you back at work?
You should've taken a few days off.
I agree. We'd be fine
even if you're gone longer.
You're making me sad.
What?
It sounds like you're saying
our team doesn't need me.
No, that's not what I meant -
Mr. Nah! I understand that you're
rivals for becoming the next chief...
but how could you say that?
What did I say that's so wrong
that you're all riled up like this?
Just imagine how much pain Chohee
must be in after sending her father away.
Shouldn't we be working hard together
in order to help her forget her sadness?
Yet you want her to not come in?
Joohyun, that's not what Mr. Nah meant.
Joohyun, he's right. If you're so hard on Mr. Nah, it'll make me feel bad.
No, it's fine.
Joohyun, I realize how much you care
about Chohee, so cut the sermon short.
I'll just shut up on my own.
Mr. Nah!
I'm grateful and slightly taken aback
by your efforts to comfort me...
but can you take things
down just a notch?
Sure, I'll consider it.
Chohee, are you really okay?
I'm trying to be.
Wow, you're definitely
in a class of your own.
If I found out my father
passed away like that, I'd...
What do you mean, “like that?”
You know what I mean.
I'd feel so weird if it were my father.
Like a heavy rock were
pressing down on my chest.
The next chief should definitely be
a solid person like you!
Hwangjae Nightclub, Mr. Oh
532-0472
What is this?
It was inside Taesoo Heo's wallet.
I was uneasy about it so I took it before
returning everything else to Chohee.
It's in the 500s. We're looking at Seocho
or Kangnam, or even Songpa. But why?
Are you thinking it was murder?
Yes.
And you have a reason to think so?
The middleman Heo met immediately
after his prison release told us...
someone was chasing Heo.
And to create the false cell phone account and the counterfeit passport...
the person must've known for a fact
that Taesoo Heo was dead to do so.
You know we found
no signs of foul play.
But the possibility is there.
What do you plan to do?
I'm supposed to go meet the thief
who worked with Taesoo Heo last.
A thief? Who?
Is it someone I know?
No. I heard about him
through a middleman.
Apparently he went clean
and lives a normal life now.
I'm not sure I'll get the information
I want, but it won't hurt to try.
And Officer Cho
is looking up that number.
Taesoo Heo was found dead?
From the state of his remains,
he seems to have died a long time ago.
So Mr. Kim was telling the truth.
Then who the hell is Robin Hood?
Um, sir. About that CHA employee
who came last time. Chohee Heo.
She's Taesoo Heo's daughter.
Are you sure?
Yes, we verified it at the funeral.
I want more information about her.
'If I found out my father
passed away like that, I'd...'
It seemed like he was being chased.
Why are you standing there?
I completely forgot with everything
that's been happening...
but supposedly Dad was
being chased by someone.
I heard about that from Chief Kang.
You heard?
What about it?
I keep thinking uneasy thoughts.
What if Dad's death
was caused by someone -
I told you about
the cause of death, didn't I?
Yes, I know.
Chohee.
Yes?
Frankly speaking, it'll be hard to find
someone in your father's line of work...
who was never chased by someone.
At one time, Hwang had all kinds of
suspicious characters tailing him.
So what you're saying is...
Yeah, don't think thoughts like that.
Okay, I'll try to think
more positive thoughts, Chief.
Celadon porcelain was created
because jade was so rare.
How wonderful it would be
if one could make jade out of clay.
Just like how the alchemists of the west
sought to create gold from lead...
the effort and passion people put in
led to the creation of this new treasure.
Rather, something more valuable
than jade was created.
The Goryeo celadon before you.
I have a question.
Shoot.
What's the most expensive item here?
Don't ask what's the most expensive.
Ask what's the most valuable.
What's the most expen -
I mean, most valuable item here?
Let me see, the most valuable treasure.
What's your most valued treasure?
Sorry for making you take around
such an amateur group.
Not at all. It was relaxing. I'm tired of
debating with the people of our trade.
Hey, while you're at it, why don't you
lead our preservation lab as well?
You're determined to use me since
I was cut from most of my gigs, right?
It's better than bumming around.
You're right, I'll do it.
By the way, did you
hear about Yongcheol?
Why? Did he cause trouble again?
He insisted seriously to the investigations
team that you were Robin Hood.
What?
I hope the real Robin Hood is caught soon
so Yongcheol will stop causing problems.
He won't keep his trap shut.
- Hey, I gotta go. I'll call you later.
- Okay.
Excuse me, can I have
some plums? These here.
- You want plums?
- Yes.
- How many do you want?
- However much is written here.
- As written?
- Yes.
Hello, how are you?
We're the police.
We ask for your cooperation.
The current user is a Juhyeon Kim.
Seeing how there's no business name,
it's a personal account.
It was used by your average family until
August of 2006. Used by a Hojun Lee.
Until November of 2003...
it was used by the construction site office
of the Ohseong Parkville apartments.
Before that -
Hold on.
Did you just say Ohseong Parkville?
Ohseong Parkville,
as in the Ohseong Group?
It was built by Ohseong Construction,
so I'm assuming yes.
What connection does Heo have with
the Ohseong construction site office?
Why did he have this number?
It seems certain that
Chairman Jang is involved.
Yes, I'm here to meet the person
who worked with Heo last.
Okay, then we'll talk in detail
back at the office.
I'll take them for you.
You don't need to...
Okay, one, two...
Three.
Satisfied?
Yes.
Do you want to take a picture?
No, I'm fine.
I don't take pictures.
Why not?
Well, I just stopped
taking them one day.
Don't you have to go
to the Incheon museum?
Go on. I have to work, too.
I have plenty of time.
I can go after I help you.
You don't need to help me.
You think I'm not onto you?
If I don't help you, later you'll definitely -
Fine, let's go.
Okay. Lead the way.
He's quite photogenic.
Remind the president
of the Tokyo office...
not to show that we're disappointed
until Iwazaki broaches the subject first.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
It seems to be the information
you requested on Taesoo Heo.
Chohee Heo and Gyoon Heo.
They're brother and sister.
Sir! This boy. He was helping
with the landscaping until recently.
What?
Careful, careful.
Why are we always moving boxes
instead of regulating?
Chohee, don't push yourself too hard.
This is the last of it.
Yeah, take things easy.
We have a meeting tomorrow,
so I wanted to wrap things up.
Hurry, hurry.
She's really straining, isn't she?
You should physically exert yourself
when things are complicated in the mind.
Hey, why is Joohyun so overprotective
of Chohee all of a sudden?
I'm not sure.
There's something up her sleeve.
After losing Bumsang, it's definitely
not in character for her to be so friendly.
I think the extreme strain of her broken
heart threw her into an identity crisis.
Extreme... identity crisis?
You suddenly sound so smart these days.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Chohee.
How'd you know to find me here?
Eunju told me where you were.
Is that so?
Um...
I'm almost done here.
Did you eat lunch?
Yeah, I did.
Oh, you did.
So what's Gyoon up to today?
Gyoon? He should be home today.
Why?
No reason. Just curious.
Work hard, and I'll see you later.
Okay.
He's only curious about Gyoon?
Who is it?
What the! Who are you guys?
Grab him!
Let go!
Bro! Run!
It's dangerous! Hurry!
Stop right there!
When I get my hands on you!
Bro!
Go that way. Hurry!
I think we lost them.
Who were those men?
What?
Why were they chasing you?
Dunno. I have no idea.
How can you not know?
They clearly have a problem with you.
I wouldn't cause any problems.
Let's go. Let's grab something
to drink since you're here.
Stop right there, Robin Hood.
I know that you're Robin Hood.
Now, answer me.
What have you been up to?
Who were those men,
and why are you stealing?
Those men were probably
Chairman Jang's men.
What?
They probably figured out that I worked
part-time at his house to get information.
You went into his house?
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you so fearless? Do you know
what kind of person he really is?
Do you have any idea
how dangerous your actions are?
I prepared for this when I started.
Gyoon.
My sister hated our father.
Yet at the same time, she missed him.
And she always felt sorry to him.
That's how she lived her entire life.
I can't watch her live
trapped in his shadow anymore.
I wanted her to lead a normal life,
the kind where she dates and marries.
And eventually makes me an uncle.
I wanted to give her that kind of life.
You idiot.
That doesn't mean you should...
I'm sorry about stealing
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook.
You might think I'm being shameless,
but I don't want to regret doing it.
Yeah, it's me.
Your car's in front of my house,
so I was wondering if you were here.
Yeah, I'm nearby with Gyoon.
You're with Gyoon?
Yeah. We'll be there soon.
Okay, sure.
Gyoon.
Yes?
Promise me one thing.
Don't steal again.
You said your sister was all you had.
The same goes for her.
You're everything to her.
As of this moment, I'm forgetting that
you're Robin Hood. So you do the same.
And don't ever do it again.
For you and for your sister's sake.
Can you promise me this?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you that Taesoo Heo
was taken care of seven years ago?
And I've been proven correct.
So please put your trust in me now.
It's not difficult to trust you
if you do things well.
Since Taesoo is dead,
who do you think this Robin Hood is?
I'm not sure.
Who could it be?
It's Taesoo's son, Gyoon Heo.
His older sister is Chohee Heo of the CHA.
Ch - Chohee is Taesoo's daughter?
Tsk, tsk. You're so slow.
How can I entrust anything to you?
What? Three men couldn't catch one kid?
How could you flub up like that!
Incompetent fools. Leave me!
Um, sir?
What?
I have a good idea
that'll make you feel better.
Would you trust me this once?
Did your talk with
Chairman Jang go well?
We're going to be busy for awhile.
Yonggu, go round up all the boys.
Why, why, why?
Stop trying to know everything.
Every time you know too much,
things screw up.
So stop it, okay?
I just want to be loved by you.
Dongpal.
Yes?
Let's go already.
Yes, sir.
It was a man
who spoke Japanese well.
Fluent in Japanese. Do you remember
anything about his appearance?
Not sure. I don't really remember
since it was seven years ago.
So seven years ago this man and Heo got
into a fight at the construction site office.
Right.
Then do you remember
why Heo was being chased?
Taesoo was originally going to sell the
seven national treasures to a rich man.
But he suddenly had a change of heart.
When he refused to sell, things got ugly.
But I didn't understand why he insisted
on returning them to the museum.
The man who fought with Heo.
Do you know whom he worked for?
Well, he was probably
working for some rich guy.
Was it Chairman Jang
of the Ohseong Group?
I have no idea.
Chief! Would this look
better on me, or would this one?
Don't tell me you're about to say
that both would look great on me.
How did you know? I don't know
how you read my mind so well.
Was he teasing me? No way.
Then again, both would look good on me.
Chief! What did you talk about
with the shop owner?
Just this and that.
Don't you have to go to the museum?
The thing is, it's already closed. This is because you keep dragging me around.
When did I drag you around?
You kept following me.
Oh my, Chief!
When did I follow you around?
Jeez, if you say things like that,
people will call you shameless.
Even in the past
you always dragged me around.
Fine. Let's go.
Chief, we're just gonna leave?
Then what else?
“I'm hungry.
Let's have some noodles first.”
It's your cue to say this.
How strange.
I'm hungry.
Let's have some noodles first.
Chief, I'll buy the sweet and sour pork!
I didn't prepare much,
but help yourself. Eat.
Wow.
I should come over every day. It's really
good. I was getting sick of eating out.
Is it really good?
Yup.
By the way, Gyoon, why was the house
so messy? Did someone come over?
About that, I was trying to clean
the house, but it ended up like that.
That was the result
of attempted cleaning?
Gyoon's definitely special. What younger
brother cleans the house? Right, Gyoon?
Absolutely, Bro.
What's this? You're totally on the same
wavelength. What are you two up to?
We're not up to anything.
Nothing up these sleeves.
Chohee, why don't you
let Gyoon travel a little?
Travel? That was out of the blue.
When we were talking earlier, I sensed
that he wanted to get some fresh air.
But he's too worried about you. So you
take the first step and tell him to go.
Gyoon, is that how you feel?
What? Um, well, not exactly, but...
Silly boy, why didn't you tell me?
Don't worry about me and go.
Go and get some rest, okay?
Sis.
Don't mind me in this sibling moment.
I'm just going to eat quietly.
Go on, eat.
Don't come out. Go in.
It's okay.
Really, don't come out.
I know about your philanthropic mindset,
but it's fine. I want to see you off.
Hey.
What?
Thanks for today.
For what?
For treating Gyoon like a brother.
I'm so busy taking care of myself that
I can't give him the attention he needs.
But you listen to him and
take care of him. So thank you.
If you're that grateful,
do me a favor.
What favor?
While Gyoon's on his trip,
stay over at my house.
What?
I won't be at peace
knowing you're home alone.
I won't make you uncomfortable in
any way, so just until Gyoon comes back.
Man, you call that a joke?
I'm not joking.
That's so ridiculous. Why would I go
to your place when I can stay here?
And nothing's going to happen
to me if I stay home alone.
Thanks for the concern,
but no more silly jokes.
Go home.
Aren't you leaving?
I'm leaving.
Leave then.
Why aren't you leaving?
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Why is he joking
with such a serious face?
‘Promise me one thing.
Don't steal again.'
‘You said your sister was all you had.
The same goes for her.'
‘You're everything to her.'
“To be or not to be.
That is the question!”
Do you know what this means?
Idiots.
To die or to live,
that is the question.
Written by Brother Shakespeare,
the greatest writer born to England.
How silly of Brother Shakespeare.
He calls that a question?
Of course you should live.
I give up on you.
Anyway, your lives are
gonna change starting today.
We come into the world
butt naked and leave butt naked!
Let's give it our all
and not hold back!
When the boys gather later,
train them well.
Our first priority is to find the man who fought with Heo at the construction office
but it's difficult since we don't
have any specific information.
It seems clear that Chairman Jang
has something to do with Taesoo's death.
I think we can assume that.
So we plan to find out the relationship
between Heo and Chairman Jang.
And one more person. Robin Hood.
What?
Only Hwang, Chairman Jang and Robin
Hood knew about Taesoo's seven items.
Are you saying Robin Hood had
something to do with Heo's death?
We can't say he was
related to Taesoo's death, but...
Chohee.
Chief.
Chief, what brings you here?
Um, I just came to talk with Chief Noh.
Chief Kang, isn't there
a security training exercise today?
- Yes.
- You should go prep for that.
- Yeah, I have to go.
- Okay.
Um, Chief? What did you
discuss with Chief Kang?
Oh, it's nothing important.
We're getting major pressure from
above about the Robin Hood situation.
Gyoon, where are you?
The bus terminal?
Yeah, I told my grandfather about you,
so don't worry. Yeah, we'll talk again.
Bumsang, can we talk for a moment?
There's something I want to ask you.
I want to ask you about Robin Hood.
If Chohee's father is not Robin Hood,
you're the only witness to see him.
So I wanted to ask you
for some specific details.
I believe I already
told you everything I know.
Last time you just said
it was a young man.
If you can give me a physical description,
it'll really help with the investigation.
He was masked and wearing a hat
so I can't tell you his physical description.
But you can probably tell me
his body size and height, things like that.
Average height, average size.
And now in retrospect, I may have been
hasty to assume it was a young man.
What do you mean?
The thing is...
Chief! Chief!
Bumsang, Bumsang!
What is it?
Robin Hood is back.
What was it this time?
The “Gimainmul” shaped double goblets?
The “Gimainmul” double goblets?
Hwang mentioned it...
So you mean another one of Heo's
items were sent to the museum?
I don't know who Robin Hood is,
but what a hassle. Anyway, let's go. Hurry.
Bumsang, what are you doing?
Let's hurry up and go.
I'll meet you at the museum.
How could he just walk off?
- Let's go.
- Let's hurry.
A two dollar ticket, please.
Gyoon!
Bro!
Why, what's wrong?
Is it you?
Did you do it again?
What?
Another one of your father's items
came to the museum. Did you steal it?
Someone who knows Heo?
Who's returning these items
when Taesoo Heo is dead?
What a humdrum.
Don't you mean conundrum?
Um, Chohee?
Yes?
I've thought about it, and I think Robin
Hood is someone related to your father.
Does anyone pop into mind?
Why are you so curious?
We've already covered all the grounds.
C'mon, let's go to the meeting.
What meeting? What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so tactless? Why do
you keep asking her about her father?
It's fishy.
What is?
Look, the darkest place
is under the candlestick.
It has to be someone Heo knows -
Let me see.
Maybe!
Maybe?
- Hwang?
- Chief Noh?
Darn...
- Hwang?
Who is Robin Hood?
You really didn't do it?
It really wasn't me. Why would I
after promising I wouldn't yesterday?
Please believe me.
Then who in the world is it?
I have no clue what's going on,
but I'm not getting good vibes about it.
Lay low at my grandfather's place and
don't tell anywhere where you are, okay?
Okay, I'll do as you say.
Get on, the bus is about to leave.
Okay.
Um, Bro?
Yeah?
I don't have to worry about my sister,
right? You'll take care of her?
Of course, that's a given.
Then I'll leave her
in your care until I return.
Okay, and taking care of her will always
be my responsibility, so don't worry.
Go on then.
Bye, Bumsang.
Thank you.
Bumsang, really thank you.
“Bumsang?”
I definitely like “Bro” better.
Why are we having a security
training exercise on this hot day?
No matter how hard I try to find the
positive aspect of this, I end up so angry.
What if Chohee makes fools
of us all again like last time?
Everyone'll hate on
our regulations team.
If she does, I'm gonna
let her have it. I swear, I will.
Mr. Nah, that's not a good attitude.
Why are you hating and ostracizing the
diligent Chohee? You shouldn't do that.
Joohyun, I'm already steamed as it is,
so let's stop right here.
What will you be doing?
Are you joining the training exercise?
I was given a very important responsibility. Preparing refreshments.
Dressed all in black on this hot day.
What are we doing? We look like crows.
That's what I'm saying. Why can't we just
sorta pretend to do it instead of all this?
Yes, this is Officer Cho.
Yes. Yes, sir.
Hey, Jinguk, we have to
head over to the security office.
What now?
If they beckon, we must go.
Chohee, wait for us.
Okay, I'll be here.
Bumsang, how are you?
Wow, you look cool. What are you
doing in all black in this sweltering heat?
Right? We have a security
training exercise today.
What brings you here?
I came to take a look
at the item Robin Hood sent in.
Yeah? I wonder who that Robin Hood is.
Seeing how he only sends in Dad's items,
he definitely has some connection to Dad.
I have no idea who he is
and why he's doing it.
By the way, Gyoon left on his trip today.
Oh, did he?
But he wouldn't even tell me
where he was headed.
Traveling is like that.
You go where your feet take you.
I guess so.
This is the “Gimainmul” double goblets
Robin Hood sent today.
Can we use the X-ray room right now?
Why? Is there a problem?
I don't think it's authentic.
No way. All of the items Robin Hood
sent in so far were national treasures.
I'm sorry, but you need to leave
because of the training exercise.
You can't leave once the exercise begins.
Sure.
Okay.
What should we do, sir?
We have no choice. Let's take
a look at it tomorrow. Good work.
Chohee, please take it easy this time.
Yeah, let's make things easier for
everyone and not overexert ourselves.
Then I'll just turn myself in
as soon as the exercise starts.
Why so extreme?
You know that we have to
start over from the beginning then.
Then I'll stay uncaught until the end.
Extreme!
Too extreme.
It was a joke. Your reactions...
Even her jokes are extreme.
Everyone, focus.
We'll start the exercise
at precisely 2100 hours.
Doing your best is great, but don't cause
physical harm to one another.
Now, now, there are only ten minutes left
so let's hurry things along.
A fake Robin Hood.
Why are you so serious?
No, it's nothing.
I get to leave early thanks to the training
exercise. C'mon. I'll buy you a beer.
Sure.
Okay then, the twenty-third security
training exercise will begin now.
Start!
Yes, sir!
Excuse me?
Subtitles Provided by MBC America