Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Cultural assets cannot and should not
be owned by a single person.
They are sacred.
The “Geumdongdae” incense burner
and Duryang Kim's “Sansu” painting?
Is it too much?
I think it's quite a bargain.
Are you going to refuse?
Of course not.
Fine, I'll give them to you.
But keep in mind that you'll regret
touching my things someday.
Your things?
Cultural assets, moreover national
treasures, belong to the country, no?
That sounds more like you.
Who cares if they're
national treasures or stolen goods?
I paid good money for them,
so they belong to me.
Chairman Ohseong Jang,
you're under arrest for attempting
to smuggle abroad cultural assets.
W - what? Smuggle abroad?
This is ridiculous.
Don't bother denying it.
We not only found all the items,
but Iwazaki confessed at the airport.
You guys are behind all this?
I warned you last time
that you'd better brace yourself.
Just one picture.
One shot, that's it.
Final Episode
Hold on!
Please leave.
How's Chairman Jang doing?
We're in the middle of investigating.
We don't know anything yet.
Please wait for
the official press release.
Later. Leave.
Just one comment, please!
Chairman Jang is a big catch, isn't he?
The reporters are gathering
like a pack of hungry wolves.
I know. It's going to be
a hassle dealing with them.
I wonder how Chief's
handling things in there.
He needs to get a full confession
and get promoted.
I dunno.
Chairman Jang won't give in easily.
Iwazaki testified you were very eager
to help smuggle the celadon abroad.
Nonsense.
All I did was
lend him a truck to use.
I didn't know he disguised
the celadon as plain pottery.
Fine, we can always confirm
the details with Iwazaki later.
Another major charge against you
is the murder of Taesoo Heo.
Can you prove it?
A case can be made against you
with just indirect evidence.
The fact that Mr. Kim
worked for you seven years ago,
and that you had all seven
national treasures Taesoo Heo stole.
Still gonna plead innocent?
As I said before,
I know nothing about Taesoo Heo.
You think you'll get off easy
as long as Mr. Kim isn't caught?
You're not listening.
I told you I know nothing.
I know your defense attorneys
are quite impressive.
But let me tell you that
this time it won't be so easy.
Then let me tell you
something as well.
Keep in mind that libel and
defamation are serious charges.
Not as serious as murder.
Chairman Jang must be
sweating it right now.
How humiliating for him.
I'm worried because
he won't be easy to interrogate.
Leave that to the investigations team. This is your cue to step away.
Step away?
It's time for you to fulfill
your duties as my girlfriend.
We've got a full schedule,
watching movies and eating good food.
So you wanna go for a drive?
Right now?
I can't.
I'm working late tonight.
Again?
Yeah.
Then let's eat before
you start working late.
Sorry, but I have to go
research some material.
Why is work always your first priority?
I'm really sorry.
Don't sulk, please.
I'll call you later, okay?
Hey!
You want me to eat alone?
Man, I can't believe her.
Mr. Nah, check the distribution routes
to find where Iwazaki bought the celadon.
All by myself?
We have no choice.
The investigations team
is busy with Chairman Jang.
Yes, sir.
Orders are orders.
Chief, what should I do?
Joohyun, what got into you?
Since when do you volunteer for work?
Mr. Nah!
That's offensive.
Who found the hidden camera,
the key to Chairman Jang's arrest?
It was me.
Did you forget?
How could I?
You found it by dumb luck.
What did you say?
Both of you stop.
Joohyun, help Chohee find evidence
for Chairman Jang's illegal deals.
Okay.
Now, let's turn in for the night.
You guys must be tired.
Yes, sir.
[Your call has been transferred...]
Why isn't he picking up?
Chohee!
Hey, Joohyun.
Where were you?
You even skipped the meeting.
Oh, Chief didn't say anything?
I was preparing some material
to give to Chief Kang.
You have to give
what to Chief Kang?
This material. Why?
Nothing, just asking.
Chohee, what do you
think of Chief Kang?
Chief Kang?
I think he's a great person.
That's it?
What do you mean,
“that's it?”
Never mind.
Oh, right.
I forgot you have Bumsang.
I'll give this to Chief Kang for you.
Sure.
And Chohee, treat Bumsang well.
You were busy chasing Chairman Jang,
and now you're busy indicting him.
He's probably frustrated
because you're so busy.
Why are you suddenly so concerned
about our relationship?
Just ‘cause.
Anyway, I'll take this
to the investigations team.
Have fun with Bumsang. Bye.
Okay.
Anyway, why isn't he picking up?
[If you don't pick up,
I'm never talking to you again.]
What do you want?
You found the time to call me?
What?
I realized that yesterday
we agreed to eat something good.
I'm here to keep my promise.
Try some.
I didn't even eat anything
because I wanted to eat with you.
Then knock yourself out.
I'll get indigestion eating
with a busy person like yourself.
Are you still sulking?
At least try some
since I bought them anyway.
Don't wanna.
Don't be like this.
I came all the way over here.
What does that make me?
Then give me a piece.
What?
You want me to handfeed you?
Not if you don't wanna.
Not gonna eat then.
Fine, I can feed you one.
Here.
Is it good?
I can't tell after one piece.
Give me some of the sausage.
Jeez. Fine.
Here!
It's good.
That's a good boy.
Ow, my neck.
Man, it hurts.
There's nothing worth
anything in these files.
By the way,
I saw on the news earlier
that Chairman Jang's defense team set
up camp in the hotel across the street.
They're going to prepare
their defense all night.
Of course they're going
to pull all the stops.
We have to catch Mr. Kim.
He's irrefutable evidence.
Right.
Chief!
Joohyun, what brings
you here at this late hour?
Chohee wanted me
to give this to you.
Thanks.
And, tada!
Have some of this.
Hey, it's sushi rolls.
You bought these for us?
You guys are working late,
so I specifically bought eel rolls.
Enjoy.
I've been craving eel these days.
You really know how to hit the spot.
Totally.
Thanks a lot, Joohyun.
Chief, please have some.
I don't really like eel.
And I'm not very hungry.
I went out of my way to buy it.
Can't you eat just a little?
Thanks.
It's as good as eaten.
Officer Cho, prep for another
interrogation at midnight.
Yes, sir.
Chief!
Joohyun, it's so good.
Have a seat and have some.
I'm fine.
Please help yourselves.
Joohyun!
It's delicious.
Hey, how'd it feel
to arrest Chairman Jang?
How'd it feel?
Well, a little strange.
I thought I'd feel
completely relieved.
But strangely I feel empty
and mixed up inside.
Maybe because Gyoon isn't here?
Yeah, that could be it.
Speaking of Gyoon, I miss him.
Why do you miss my brother?
He's practically my brother.
You really think that?
Of course.
I was always envious of you guys.
And since he always called me bro,
it felt like I was family.
It felt good.
It feels good to hear you say that.
Here, cheers.
Yeah.
Chairman Jang arrested
for illegal smuggling
Yonggu, we're saved.
What?
The investigations team
arrested Chairman Jang.
Then can we go home now?
Idiot.
How can you be so clueless?
The only way we'll survive is
by leaving the motherland.
Leave the motherland?
And go where?
Let's go to China.
Let's start from scratch
on the plains of Manchuria.
China?
How are we gonna get there?
The fuzz are everywhere.
I've got a plan.
But first we need some dough.
Dough?
How? How?
Are your eyes for
decorative purposes only?
Follow me.
I got it.
I got it, so let go.
Jeez.
Let go. It hurts.
Hurry up already.
This white and blue porcelain...
This'll bring in some cash.
Boss, how are we gonna steal it?
The security looks loose.
The “Sosangpalgyeong” painting,
the “Bukgwandaecheopbi” copy,
the “Pyeongyangseong” painting,
and the commemorative
photo album of King Kojong's family.
Let's wrap them all
in newspapers and walk out.
Boss!
Is he onto us?
He's coming this way.
They can never stand
to cut us a little slack.
Let's retreat for now.
Excuse me, but are you...
[Wanted]
So Mr. Kim used Taesoo Heo's
counterfeit passport?
Then Gyucheol Seo probably
used a counterfeit passport, too.
Pretty much.
That's awfully bold.
Fine, it's obvious that Mr. Kim and
Yonggu Lee's only option is to stow away.
Where will they go?
China? Japan? Hong Kong?
The Philippines? Taiwan? Where?
I - I - I have no idea.
If you don't,
you'll take the fall.
Where?
Officer Cho!
We have a tip from
the Incheon City Museum.
Two men suspected to be
Mr. Kim and Yonggu Lee were spotted.
Yeah?
Then we should go.
Let's hurry.
I'll see you later.
I hope Boss isn't caught.
Come in.
What's up?
Here are the items to appraise.
Report to Mr. Nah when you're done.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Bye.
Hey, Chohee!
Yeah?
Don't you have anything to say?
Say what?
You really don't?
I think you do.
I don't.
I'm busy so let's talk later.
Hey, hold up.
What?
I have something to say.
What is it?
What do you think?
Hey!
Bumsang, excuse me -
I didn't see anything.
Oh dear...
Chief!
What are you doing here?
Mr. Nah, do Chohee and Bumsang
really like each other?
Did you think they didn't?
How strange.
Oh my god, what are you doing?
Chief Noh saw everything!
Why so embarrassed?
It's natural for us to kiss.
He'll understand.
This is the workplace.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'd kiss you on a crowded
street if you wanted.
I'm wasting my breath here.
And it's natural for lovers to want
to touch each other and stuff.
Sorry if I embarrassed you.
Go back to work.
Are you mad again?
Hello, Chief Noh.
Tired?
You don't look too good.
Is Chairman Jang giving you hell?
A bit.
What brings you here?
The prosecution informed me
that Iwazaki recanted his confession.
Initially he blamed
Chairman Jang for everything.
Now he claims he didn't know
the pottery was really celadon.
They matched their stories.
What if we end up losing both?
The warrant has to be
issued by tomorrow afternoon,
but we have no other way
besides catching Mr. Kim.
Think we can catch him?
Officers Park and Cho went to Incheon,
so let's keep our fingers crossed.
Jeez, it's hot.
I'm back.
So was it
Mr. Kim and Yonggu Lee?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
What were they doing at a museum?
Punk, why else
would a thief go in there?
They couldn't have left the area
because of the search we set up,
so they're somewhere
here in Incheon.
Then let's scour the harbors first.
If we poke around,
they're bound to show up.
Let's go.
Man, we're in trouble
if they stow away.
Because of Chairman Jang,
no one's willing to talk.
Looks like Insa-dong won't pan out,
so let's go find private owners.
It's really too much.
It is, isn't it?
How could this happen?
This is unheard of!
You're going a little overboard here.
I went there with eel sushi rolls.
But he said
he didn't like eel and left.
He didn't even acknowledge
that I found the necktie clip.
How could Chief Kang do this to me?
Chief Kang?
Ah, you were talking
about him all this time?
Whom did you think
I was talking about?
Oh!
Joohyun, where are you going?
Oh, oh!
This color and design
are totally his style.
Chohee, let's go in for a sec.
Joohyun!
Jeez, she's driving me nuts.
I like this one and this one.
What to do?
Don't just stand there.
Pick out something for
your brother and Bumsang.
A lot of clothes here
would look good on Bumsang.
He's picky, so he won't
wear something I pick out.
No, no~
You're wrong.
No one dislikes a gift.
He'll like whatever you give him.
Are you picking out men's clothes?
For whom?
Chief Kang?
You're as perceptive as ever.
I was picking out clothes
for not only Chief Kang,
but also Officers Cho and Park.
The three men who are working hard
to lock up Chairman Jang.
Yeah, sounds like a good idea.
They'll really like it.
I agree.
Choose something for Bumsang.
I'll be choosing for the officers.
Okay.
Oh, cute, totally cute.
We have motorboats and freighters.
We even have fishing boats.
Yonggu, choose one.
Which one do you like?
A passenger ship like the Titanic.
I wish I could send you off
on a shrimping boat.
You said I could choose.
I'm hungry.
How much you got?
Can I take your order?
Two bowls of rice.
Excuse me?
Give us two bowls of rice.
We'll eat it with water.
You can't just order rice.
So you're refusing to serve us?
Coming right up.
Boss, I'm so embarrassed.
It's so hot.
Where is Mr. Kim?
There's not a hair in sight.
That's what I'm saying.
If he wants to stow away, he has
to use this harbor or the docks.
Let's hurry up and eat,
and give it another go.
Okay.
Can I take your order?
What shall we have?
Give us the lunch set.
Sure.
Isn't that an article
about Chairman Jang?
So it is.
I wonder what nonsense
the reporters wrote this time.
Excuse me, sir!
Can I borrow your newspaper?
What do we do?
Shut up.
No.
Just lend me the outer page.
Jeez.
What a cheapskate.
Leave him be.
He doesn't want to give it.
With what right?
Looks like it belongs to the restaurant.
Hold on.
Sir?
Lower the newspaper for a sec.
No.
Then lift it up.
Long time no see, Officer Cho.
Run!
Bastard, stop right there.
Boss, why are we
always running away?
It's the downside of being a thief!
Bleach Head!
Bleach Head.
Come over here.
Boss.
All for one and one for all.
Stop the bluff
and just let me go.
You have an innocent man locked up
without evidence or witnesses.
You're wasting my time here.
This isn't right.
Until your forty-eight hours are over, you're still a suspect for murder.
Why don't you just sit tight
until three o'clock tomorrow?
You've got a lot of nerve for
someone on pins and needles.
Not bad.
By the way, didn't you
receive a call from above?
He said he'd call you.
Not yet, huh?
Go ahead.
No need to be polite.
Just answer it.
Hello, this is he.
What?
I understand.
I guess I have no other choice.
Okay.
Why the heavy sigh?
Sir.
Mr. Kim was arrested.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
What?
On the way here, he confessed
that you were behind everything.
I think getting a warrant
will be no problem.
[Chairman Ohseong Jang
was arrested today for murder
and for violating the
Cultural Properties Protection Act...]
Well, that's a wish fulfilled.
You wanted to catch that guy.
I did.
It turned out for the bestl.
For Chohee and for Gyoon,
and I have no more regrets.
Yeah, Taesoo can rest in peace now.
Probably.
That poor bastard.
All that's left is your retirement.
What's after that?
Why?
You have something in mind?
Yeah.
Wanna be my driver?
If an ex-middleman and an ex-regulations
chief joined forces, we'd be invincible.
Shouldn't we marry Chohee off first?
With whom?
That Chief Kang dude?
That was my original plan,
but she already has a guy.
Bumsang Kim.
You saw him before.
That guy?
Chohee has great taste in men.
I liked him from the moment
I laid eyes on him.
Let me make it clear that
I'm going to walk her down the aisle.
Don't even think otherwise.
We'll see when the time comes.
It's nearly over.
You just need to come home.
Sis.
When you come home,
let's go see Dad first.
And then we'll move Mom
so that she's by Dad's side, okay?
Okay, let's do that.
And let's go to Yongin, too.
Why there?
I think we were happiest
when we lived there.
That was the best time
for you, me and Dad.
You're right, it was.
It was fun back then,
burying a time capsule with Dad.
Time capsule?
What's that?
You don't remember?
I'm not sure.
You can't remember
when it was your idea?
You saw it on TV and
suggested that we try it.
We put in our treasures and
vowed to open it in the 21st century.
What's your treasure, Chohee?
Oh, right.
I remember now.
I had forgotten all about it.
Now you remember?
Do you think it's still there?
No way.
It's been over twenty years.
You're probably right.
I don't remember exactly
but I think I put in a doll.
I'm not sure.
I don't remember either.
Go look for it with Bro.
With Bumsang?
And if you find it,
tell me what my treasure was.
Okay, I'll do that.
So you're giving us
each a shirt, but why?
You know what?
It's the first time I've received
a pretty shirt in my five years as a cop.
It's not such a big deal.
You guys don't go home much
and don't get to change much either.
So they're for the sake
of your personal hygiene.
Everyone knows about
the sad state of our hygiene
and that we don't go home much.
But thanks anyway.
I'll wear it well.
Thanks so much.
I'll wear it well, Joohyun.
What about you, Chief?
Why so quiet?
This is just so unexpected.
I guess it is unexpected
from a beauty like myself.
You've got a point.
Anyway, Joohyun, thank you.
I knew you'd look better in
a V-neck collar than a rounded collar.
No one has my good taste.
Then please enjoy the shirts,
and I'll be going then.
I assume you know that you must
dry clean it on the first wash.
Then, bye.
What's up with her?
Who knows what
goes on in her head?
Anyway, it feels good.
Don't you agree, Chief?
Yes.
Joohyun!
Yes, Chief?
Going back to the office?
Yes, why?
I have an engagement,
but I can stop by the CHA first.
What engagement?
A date with my favorite
person in the world.
Is that so?
Thank you for the offer,
but that sounds important.
It's okay.
I'll go on my own.
Um, it's my daughter.
I promised to play with her.
Your daughter?
Yup.
I have to get back on her good side
by playing with her today.
Where are you going?
I didn't think about it yet.
Maybe the children's museum.
You know what?
I was gonna go to the museum, too.
Then shall we go together?
Sure, let's go together.
How old is your daughter?
Jiyoon is six.
Her name is Jiyoon?
Jiyoon.
Jiyoon Kang.
Is this Jiyoon?
She's so adorable.
Is this the first time
you've seen her picture?
Yeah, it is.
That's strange. You've ridden
in my car loads of times.
This picture was always here.
Was it?
I guess it's because back then
I was too focused on work.
I focus so well that
I hardly notice anything else.
Is that so?
You're similar to Jiyoon.
I am?
In what way?
She focuses so well that once she grabs onto a mirror, she doesn't let go.
You like mirrors, too.
Chief!
Just kidding.
Jonggyu, are you that bored?
Why do you keep coming by -
Tada!
What's this?
This? A bribe.
A bribe to make you feel better
since you're mad at me.
When was I mad?
Man, I was all worried for nothing.
But at least you're not sulking.
It's not much, so try it on later.
Okay, thanks.
I'm almost done.
It's an iron sword.
Yeah.
My dad stole a ton of these
back in the day.
Your father ended up a really
dark cloud in your life, didn't he?
I understand how you feel,
but isn't it time to let him go?
I know my line of work
is restoring cultural assets,
but sometimes the rotting
and aging state can be beautiful.
Restoration isn't always
the best way to love cultural assets.
Watching them fade away
is another form of love.
What's your point?
That sometimes
what's natural is the best.
Whether we're talking
about relics or people.
That was longwinded.
Hold on, I'll wrap things up.
Um, there's somewhere I want to go.
Can you go with me?
So this is where you used to live?
I think so, but I'm not sure
because it changed a lot.
No way it would stay
the same for twenty years.
Still, I feel disappointed.
There should be a good-luck pole
my father made somewhere nearby.
A good-luck pole?
Yeah.
Every time we moved, Dad set up
a good-luck pole at the entrance.
But it's gone.
Hey, there's one over there.
Where?
It's still here.
I'm so proud for
finding it in one try.
I don't know if the treasures
are still here, like Gyoon said.
Treasures?
Yeah.
A long time ago, we buried
our treasures in a time capsule.
So you came here
on a treasure hunt.
You brought me
here to dig, didn't you?
Aw man, I knew it.
Hurry up and dig.
Whereabouts?
You have to point out
the general area.
I think it's over there.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Put more power into it.
Hey, it's really here.
What's your treasure, Chohee?
I'm not gonna show you.
Let me have a peek.
I shouldn't...
Wow, is this me?
You drew it well.
Don't you have a treasure?
Treasure?
Of course I do.
What is it?
What is it!
Well, my treasure is...
A secret.
No fair.
Well, too bad.
Let's put them in.
Now let's put on the cover.
Cover it with plastic.
Daddy, when are we
gonna open this up?
When do you think we should?
How about when Chohee's
about to get married?
But I'm not gonna get married.
You're really not going to marry?
But a wonderful prince will come
sweep you off your feet.
I drew this a long time ago.
Wanna see?
This was my treasure.
Your taste then
was as bad as it is now.
Hey.
What is it?
[Dear Chohee and Gyoon.]
[You'll probably be all grown up
by the time you open this up.]
[How beautiful did
Chohee turn out to be?]
[How handsome did
Gyoon turn out to be?]
[And how old have I grown?]
[But Chohee and Gyoon,
no matter how much time passes,
you will always be
my dearest treasure.]
I miss him so much.
Hello.
Chief Kang!
Hey, Joohyun.
Did you get home
all right last night?
Chief, that fantastic shirt
looks strangely familiar.
You bought this for me.
Don't you remember?
Of course I do.
How could I forget?
I'll wear it well.
Thanks.
It's not a big deal.
If you're so grateful,
you should buy dinner.
Not in the cafeteria,
but in some fancy restaurant.
Okay, I'll buy you dinner
in a fancy restaurant.
Satisfied?
Really?
You promised.
Chief Kang, Joohyun.
Did you hear the news?
What's up?
Chief Noh's retirement
date has been set.
Really?
Hey, where did everyone go?
Chief!
This is not good at all.
Just because I'm retiring,
am I already a lame duck?
Why are you already retiring, Chief?
You said it would be in the fall.
September first is in the fall.
Still.
I did all that I could.
And it's time for me to relax
with my annual pension.
Out with the old
and in with the new.
I know that you're sorry to go.
I do have a lot of regrets.
I really regretted letting
you join the regulations team.
But that was also the best decision
in the past thirty years of my life.
Chief.
You started this work
because of your father,
but if you keep going,
you'll find a greater objective.
That's how life works.
Go find everyone
for the morning meeting.
Tell them I'm not cutting them
any slack until the very last day.
Yes, sir.
We acknowledge your contribution
to the Cultural Heritage Administration.
From Director Changhyun Kang.
Chief Noh, thank you
for all your hard work.
Thank you.
Now we'll listen to Chief
Jeongpil Noh's farewell speech.
I'm not really good with words.
It has been exactly thirty years
since I began protecting cultural assets.
I cannot tell you that I've never
once been shaken in my resolve.
There were times I wanted to quit
and times the dark side tempted me.
But I plowed forward because of
the pride I had in protecting our history.
Our work is not simply
protecting cultural assets.
We are protecting the history, pride and
memories that our children will inherit.
Memories become history, and
a history full of pride becomes the future.
Cultural assets are not just antiques,
but our memories, history and future.
I will now pass on this serious
responsibility to you guys.
But I will always
be here with you in spirit.
Thank you for listening to me,
though I am not good with words.
When it comes time for me to officiate
Chohee and Bumsang's marriage,
I will be better prepared
for public speaking.
Thank you very much.
(Excuse me a sec.)
Is this an international number?
Hello, this is Bumsang Kim.
Hello, who is this?
Thank you for all your hard work.
Chief, I am so sad.
Chief, I already feel empty inside.
Thanks.
Chief, the last silver dust I'll give you.
You're going to come visit us, right?
Why would I when
I'm not even getting paid?
Chief Kang, you did well.
Chief...
Take care of your health.
I'll leave the regulations team
in your hands, Chief Nah.
What?
Didn't I tell you?
You're being promoted to chief.
Are you serious, Chief?
Oh no!
I will do my very best.
Thank you.
I didn't want to see
Hwang walk you down the aisle,
but I'd rather officiate
than have him do it.
Uncle...
Hey, where did Bumsang go?
Yes, yes.
What are you doing?
Chief is waiting for you -
I understand. Goodbye.
A Japanese person?
Who was it?
It was Tanaka.
Ichihiro Tanaka.
Tanaka?
The yakuza Ichihiro Tanaka?
Why would he call you?
Who stopped Chairman Jang
from smuggling items abroad?
It was me, Daegil Nah.
After I unveiled our country's
richest man to be the filth he really is,
it was obvious
I would become chief.
Where are we eating dinner?
We have to have at least sirloin.
Let's all have some silver dust...
I can only take this to mean
you're all green with envy.
Fine.
At times like these,
I need Sangho by my side.
Sangho!
Mr. Nah, I have something
urgent to discuss with you.
Chief Kang!
No, no~
I'm Chief Nah now.
That's my catchphrase.
No, no~ That's how you do it.
Chohee, what's taking you so long?
Mr. Nah -
That's not important right now.
I just learned the Makddae Family
is contacting Daishokumi clan.
Dai -
I've heard that name somewhere.
Th - th - that's the clan of that dude
in Japan, what's his name?
Tanaka!
He's the boss, right?
Right.
Why is Tanaka coming here?
Okay, I'll tell them.
Chohee wanted me to tell you.
He's coming to buy the “Geumsagyeong”
through the Makddae Family.
And how does Chohee know?
Tanaka asked Bumsang
to appraise the “Geumsagyeong.”
They're meeting this weekend.
What do we do?
What do you think?
It's time to show them what
Chief Daegil Nah of the CHA is made of.
Where is the meeting place?
Man, they're fast.
Of course they should be.
Be ready!
This is Eagle.
Everything's in place.
All we need is for Turtle to appear.
Roger.
Gotcha.
Come in, Sparrow.
This is Sparrow.
Nothing unusual here.
Call me when Turtle crawls into view.
Do not get distracted
and do your very best, over.
Stop overdoing your job, over.
Are you messing around?
At this important time?
Stop messing around
and stay sharp, over.
Chief Nah's spirit
is poking at the clouds.
Just like this tower.
Why can't anyone
do their job right?
Hey, Chief Kang!
Are we set?
Yes, just in case,
the riot police is standing by.
Good.
Chohee and Bumsang?
Chohee's here,
but I haven't seen Bumsang.
How can he be late
on this important day?
I swear,
there's no one I can trust.
Okay, so we'll stay hidden and wait
until Bumsang and Chohee meet Tanaka.
Then we'll close in on them, okay?
Did you get it or not?
What are you doing?
Move, move.
Okay...
Mr. Nah - I mean, Chief Nah
is too inflated today.
Since when did he work so hard?
You know he always
has to be in charge.
And the seat really
does change the man.
Oh, by the way,
will Chohee be all right?
She's the only one experienced
enough to handle this job.
And she's also fluent in Japanese.
Chief, I happen to be
quite good at Japanese.
Oh, right. I forgot.
How can you be so indifferent?
I'm disappointed in you.
Joohyun!
Chief.
I know you want to tell me
you're actually interested in me,
but this isn't right.
We need to go this way.
Let's go.
J - Joohyun.
Chohee said the key to going
undercover is a believeable front.
If we act like lovers, we'll do our part
without getting discovered.
Now, let's go.
Tanaka already knows her by sight.
Why does she insist on doing this?
Yo.
Hey!
You...
Why?
Is it too much?
It's okay, it's a little
conspicuous as a disguise.
It is conspicuous, isn't it?
I was thinking that, but...
Hey, did you get
another call from Tanaka?
Yeah, he's waiting near the tower.
The thought of meeting Tanaka
is making me nervous.
You? Nervous?
Remember Japan? What if
he brought all his yakuza cronies?
I never thought I'd see
the great Bumsang all nervous.
I'll give you a present
to ease your nerves.
A present?
What is it?
Now don't be nervous.
I'm off.
Yeah, let's do this.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America