Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Your father...
He's alive.
What are you talking about?
Your father isn't dead. He's alive.
Hey.
You shouldn't make jokes like that.
Here, take a look.
I found this while looking up records
of Mr. Kim at the investigations office.
January 23rd of 2008.
Taesoo Heo is on the list of people
who came in from Dandong, China.
Your father's name is here.
It could be someone
with the same name.
So I looked up the criminal record,
and there was only one match.
This is your father, isn't it?
Is this real? Is it?
This is real?
No matter what others said,
I always believed my father was alive.
It didn't matter what they said,
I believed he was alive.
And he really is alive.
Episode 10
Where did everyone go?
Hey, Chief.
Officer Cho, about
the documents I asked for...
I submitted them for approval.
Hey, where did Bumsang go?
He's long gone by now.
Bumsang was here?
Yes.
For what reason?
To help with the “Sowonhwagae”
and “Chochung” cases.
You know how he can get
pretty nosy sometimes.
Claiming to want to familiarize
himself with on-site work.
I asked him to look over
the records for Mr. Kim's name.
He probably left
after a half-hearted attempt.
I think we bought too much food.
Chief, you want some?
I'm fine.
Huh, why is this document open?
The sushi rolls taste good.
It was a good buy.
Are you done crying?
Yeah.
Why are you bawling
over good news?
Seriously, what's wrong with me?
Shouldn't you tell Chief Noh about this?
He'll help you find your father.
You'll want to find him
as soon as possible.
I'm going to find him on my own.
I thought Chief Noh knew all about you.
He'd definitely help you out.
That's exactly why.
Dad's statute of limitations
still has two months remaining.
I always felt indebted to Chief Noh.
But turns out he always
felt indebted to me.
‘Cause I'd always bawl when
he'd come to take my dad away.
So I don't want to make
Chief Noh arrest my dad again.
Then I'll help you look for him.
It's okay, I can do it on my own.
Don't worry. Hey, I gotta go.
I'm serious. I'll help you.
Why?
Aren't I your boyfriend? I have to
fulfill my boyfriend duties for a month.
And wasn't he famous enough to change
our country's archeological history?
I want to meet him, since we're more
or less in the same professional sphere.
Let's go. I'll give you a ride.
Sis! Bro, hi!
Gyoon... Gyoon...
Why are you being weird?
Gyoon.
What is it?
Dad... I think he's alive.
Sis...
I'm serious, Uncle.
So can you collect all the information
you have and give it to me tomorrow?
Yes. Yes...
What did Uncle Hwang say?
Same as you. Asked if I was sure.
Said he couldn't believe it.
Do you think Dad's really alive?
Not sure. I'll look into things
starting tomorrow, so don't you worry.
Sis, I'm thrilled that Dad might be alive,
yet at the same time I'm not.
What do you mean?
If he were alive,
why didn't he come to see us?
You and I went through
some really hard times.
Wasn't he worried about us?
I can forgive a dead father.
But I dunno if I can forgive a father who
didn't come to see us when he was alive.
Your pent-up feelings against Dad
are nothing compared to mine.
I resent him a hundred times, no,
a thousand times more than you.
I hated how Mom had to die, how
people called me a thief's daughter...
worrying about him getting caught
and not being able to go to college.
I really resent him for it all.
But I still want him to be alive.
I want him to be alive...
so I can tell him exactly how much
I hate and can't forgive him.
Sis.
So let's find him this time.
Of the items
returned to the museum...
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook
was stolen from Chairman Jang...
and the “Chochung” collection from Congressman Lee. So we suspect.
Congressman Lee? Serves him right
for what he did with the “Bihaedangjib.”
So who is it that
avenged us in my stead?
That would be Robin Hood.
They must be pissed that they can't
report it since they're national treasures.
Can we convict them for the possession
and harboring of stolen goods?
But all we have is a hunch about them
with no real hard evidence.
So it's impossible to motion
for a subpoena as of yet.
So our plan is to focus on arresting
the anonymous donor, said Robin Hood.
What's that?
We're going to arrest Robin Hood?
Why would we do that?
He's a good thief.
If we go against the public's wishes,
wouldn't we get hated on?
What better opportunity
for a promotion?
You have to become a sergeant. You
planning on staying an officer forever?
Chief, we should work for the public,
but we have to get promoted, too.
This is a serial theft case of designated
cultural assets. We have to investigate.
You two please cover the legwork for Chairman Jang and Congressman Lee.
Sangho and Mr. Nah, please look into
the delivery service Robin Hood used.
Robin Hood...
Bumsang!
Are you really gonna be like this?
Gonna be like what?
Are you going to keep avoiding me?
I wasn't avoiding you.
I was just trying to walk this way.
Don't lie. The look in your eyes
told me you were avoiding me. Right?
I never did that.
I know that you feel like
you sinned against me.
But if you keep this up,
you'll only be making me uncomfortable.
Joohyun.
I gave you up completely.
So please treat me with ease.
No, no~
I know that you fear that your feelings
will waver when you see me.
But please treat me
the way you used to. Please.
What a guilt trip.
Joohyun.
Joohyun!
Chief, we'll be on our way.
Okay. Where are you going first?
We'll mapquest the two men
and go the closer location first.
Congressman Lee, what are you saying?
I sent you the “Chochung” collection.
I should be asking you the same thing.
I never even got to see it.
It isn't my problem
that it's in the museum.
I did my part so I expect
the promised payment.
Let me make myself clear.
I never received it.
Your driver was the one
who got robbed in front of my house.
I can't be held responsible for that.
I advised you on the good faith purchase
matter and even lent you my lawyer.
I think I've done all that I can for you.
So how can you do this to me?
This is a bigger problem for me.
I never even got to see the collection
yet the police are already pestering me.
Anyway, I have nothing
to do with the matter.
I came to tell you that I won't give you
a penny since I never even got to see it.
A fitting house for a man
like Chairman Jang.
Think they'll open the gate for us?
Based on my fifteen years of experience,
they'll just make us stand in this rain.
That's obvious even with
fifteen days of experience.
- Go on then.
- That's what I'm saying.
Where have I seen him before?
Hey, isn't that Congressman Lee?
Junpil Lee!
But...
Why's he here?
Chohee, Bumsang and I agreed
to treat each other comfortably.
That would be
better for you and me...
Chohee?
Yeah?
Chohee, you don't look so good.
Did something bad happen?
Me? No, no. Only good things
have been happening to me.
Good things?
What kinds of good things?
Did Bumsang propose to you?
Dear Lord, no, that's not it.
No? Then what could it be?
Good things...
- How strange...
- Excuse me.
Yes, Uncle?
I compiled a list of people
who used to be close with your father.
A lot of the numbers have changed. And
there are people who might be dead.
[I'll just send it over.]
Thank you, Uncle.
[No need to thank me, you punk.]
Check those people out first.
I'll check out the people still in business.
Okay. If anything comes up,
we'll call each other. Yeah. Okay, bye.
So Taesoo is alive, is he?
- Can you fax this for me?
- Sure thing.
Is it really okay for you
to be helping me like this?
I said I would, didn't I?
I'm not going back on my word.
Shouldn't you be out looking for
Robin Hood instead of helping me?
Where would I look for him?
At Chairman Jang's house?
Don't ask so many questions
when I'm offering. Where to first?
First Sadang-dong.
Let's go there first.
You saw Congressman Lee
in front of Chairman Jang's house?
- Yes!
- It's true, I tell you.
It was pouring and we rang the bell, worried that they wouldn't open up...
when the gate opened and
Congressman Lee came striding out.
He was greatly agitated
like a mad bull.
It looked like he had a major
showdown with Chairman Jang.
Definitely. And something
was definitely fishy, right?
Those two would never meet
unless something big was going on.
Chief, it seems to me that...
this has something to do
with the “Chochung” collection.
Good work.
- Officer Cho.
- Yes?
I need to ask you a favor.
Can you look into Bumsang's
surroundings for me?
Is there some kind
of problem with Bumsang?
No, it's not like that.
I'll look into the university.
Can you find out if he has
bad relationships with anyone?
Yes, sir.
And this is a secret
between you and me.
That goes without saying!
[Taesoo? It's been a while since
I saw him. More than ten years.]
You can't hit a homer
on the first pitch. Where next?
Shillim-dong and then Anyang.
Okay.
Have you seen him recently?
It's been a while
since we lost contact.
Do you know anyone
we could possibly contact?
Well...
It's been a while since I saw him.
Around seven years I'd say.
There are good-luck poles.
So your father's friend is here?
Not a friend but someone who shared
a prison cell with him seven years ago.
Hope we pick up some news here.
How can I help you?
So that was...
Hold on, when was that?
It was 2000 or 2001. I shared a prison
cell with him for about five months.
I see...
He was so nice and sympathetic that
a lot of people treated him with respect.
What is this about
losing contact with him?
Um, the thing is...
He's been missing
for seven years now.
Inadvertently we came across some
records showing that he is still alive.
So now we're trying to
find out what we can.
Did you meet him after
you were released from prison?
No, I didn't meet him.
So you haven't
seen him in seven years?
Yes.
That's strange. I definitely thought he'd
head straight home after his release.
He said he'd return the stolen items and
go to his kids with a clear conscience.
Dad said that?
Your name's Chohee, isn't it?
He always talked about you and Gyoon.
He missed you and
regretted what he did.
Sorry I'm not of much help.
I don't have much information on him.
I'm sorry.
Not at all. You've been
a great help. Thank you.
I made this in prison
after learning how from your father.
Truthfully, he made half of it.
I'll give it to you in hopes that
he returns to you. Please take it.
Thank you, sir.
Then, take care.
You okay?
Of course.
Let's go.
All his lectures were cancelled?
Were there problems with his lectures?
Not at all. If anything,
his lectures were too popular.
I don't understand why this happened.
Where's the book
I asked you to borrow for me?
Here it is.
Professor Yongcheol Gong?
Bumsang?
He had loads of problems.
There was more than one.
First, he seduces women and students
with his looks and his silver tongue.
Second, he hatches plots to slander me
due to his jealousy of me. And third!
Do you know why
his lectures were cancelled?
Oh, that?
My opinion is that
it's because of Chairman Jang.
Chairman Jang?
I don't know about their relationship, but
Bumsang definitely rankled the old man.
The old man had his lectures cancelled
and had him cut from his TV show.
From “Discovering Cultural Assets?”
Ah, I'm hosting that now.
I was supposed to get the advisory
member position at the CHA, too.
But that one remained
untouched for some reason.
Anyway, Bumsang probably has
a major grudge against Chairman Jang.
He's probably
already plotting his revenge.
But what can he do?
It's Chairman Jang he's up against.
Revenge...
Joohyun, what's up?
What the hell?
You ruined my car!
Learn how to drive!
Look at my car!
It's because of middle-aged women like
you that there are so many accidents.
Look here.
Who are you calling middle-aged?
I'm not middle-aged. How dare...
You look middle-aged so I'm
calling you middle-aged! So what?
Joohyun, what happened?
Chief!
Oh, is this your husband? Good.
What are you going to do about my car? I'm not even done making payments yet!
Look here, sir! Watch what you say.
Do you know who this is?
This person is Chief Shiwan Kang of
the district PD's investigations team!
How dare you raise your voice!
I'm not middle-aged!
Joohyun?
Yes?
Investigations team?
Then you're a cop?
Did you call your insurance company?
What?
I'm sure you know that even if you were
rear-ended, you bear part of the blame.
Let's take a look.
Why'd you drive when
you hardly know how to?
I'm supposed to pick up the the Hahman
case items but no one could help me.
I can't bring them all back with a taxi,
so I brought out my dad's car in secret.
So you do work after all.
Chief! That's an insult.
Can't you see all the liver spots and dark
circles I gained from working so hard?
Oh, right. Where are you coming from?
Investigating Robin Hood?
More or less...
Who do you think Robin Hood is?
I'm not sure.
What about you?
I think it's Bum -
I'm not sure either.
Who could it be?
You think it's Bumsang, right?
How'd you guess?
Just a wild guess.
You're practically clairvoyant.
Chief.
Chief, why aren't you
brushing me off?
What?
“Joohyun, Bumsang
can't be Robin Hood.
You think that makes
any sense? Go home!”
Isn't that the normal reaction?
I think that maybe
it isn't entirely unlikely.
Really?
So you also think that Bumsang is
Robin Hood. Right, right. It could be true.
Why aren't you eating?
What? Oh, right.
Don't be picky with your food and eat
everything. Chief, have some of this, too.
I thought we were going to eat?
Where are we?
The place with the
best food for miles. Come on.
This isn't a restaurant.
You should've called before coming.
We were in the neighborhood.
You should've at least
told me ahead of time.
We're just eating.
No need to get all worked up.
Much easier said than done.
Grandpa says it's all right.
Here you go, here's the chicken.
Doesn't it look delicious?
There you go.
Bumsang, have all you want.
You, too.
Thank you.
There you go. Go on.
You're so pretty and with nice skin.
So pretty, isn't she?
See, he agrees.
You're not too thin. And your hips
look just right for childbearing. Right?
See, he agrees with me.
Grandma, we're not dating.
She's just a co-worker of mine.
Yeah, sure, okay.
That's how things are.
You start off working together
and eventually live together.
Right?
See, he agrees.
Right...
The rest corresponds to
what you found out.
And how should I put this?
He seems to have a lot of girl problems.
Chohee's in for some heartache.
Anything else?
That's it for information about Bumsang.
Oh, about the “Chochung” collection.
Yes?
The regulations team says it belonged to
Chairman Jang not Congressman Lee.
The “Chochung” collection
belonged to Chairman Jang?
Yes. The moment Chairman Jang
tried to sell it to Congressman Lee...
Robin Hood came swooping in,
stole it and sent it to the museum.
Based on my fifteen years of experience,
we should switch our focus...
from grudges against Bumsang
to grudges against Chairman Jang.
Ah, Chief Kang, sorry I'm late.
Good work.
Hello, Chief Noh.
So what you're saying is
Bumsang is Robin Hood?
It seems very likely
looking at the circumstances.
How is that possible?
It's just office gossip of the ladies.
But considering the relationship
between Bumsang and Chairman Jang...
he's the most likely suspect.
The second possibility is that
this is all an act by Chairman Jang.
An act?
In other words, he's just trying
to make things difficult for Bumsang.
Of course, it doesn't
make much sense.
Of course.
A rich man like Chairman Jang wouldn't
give up his possessions for that reason.
But considering his pride and how he
hates to lose, it isn't completely unlikely.
He's a man who values his pride
above monetary losses.
And finally, we can't disregard the
possibility of a third party involvement.
A third party? Who?
Not sure. If I knew that,
I wouldn't be here right now.
Jeez, this is difficult.
Should we stick a man on Bumsang?
Isn't the glaze too thick on this one?
Who's the woman?
Is she the woman you like?
What do you think about her?
I like the expression in her eyes.
So you like her.
But there's also
gloom in her expression.
So you don't like her?
Are you saying you like her or not?
This is the first place certificate he got
in a national composition competition.
And this is the second place certificate
he got for a sketching competition.
The winner had connections
according to Bumsang.
And he got innumerous awards for
perfect attendance and excellence.
You're very proud of him,
aren't you, Grandmother?
Of course. He's such a great kid.
He never caused me any trouble.
And he never showed it when
he was going through a hard time.
Really?
Yeah. He's such a considerate kid.
Bumsang is very considerate.
I'm so out of it. It's time for
Grandpa's medicine. Give me a sec.
Sure.
- Look at these while I'm gone.
- Okay.
You were one of a kind
since you were young, Bumsang.
Studied much?
A pink notebook?
How unconventional.
What is this?
'May 12, 1988. Thursday.'
'Today, the prettiest girl
in class gave me chocolates.'
'I think she likes me.
She has good taste.'
'August 5, 1988. Friday.
The weather is sunny.'
'I went to the Bomun Shrine for the anniversary of Mom and Dad's deaths.'
'The priest told me before that if I climb
the stairs, my wish will be granted.'
'So I went up the stairs
again this year.'
'It was so hard but I made it
and stood in front of Buddha.'
'But when I tried to make my wish,
I couldn't remember it.'
'Instead, I just kept crying.'
'After standing there for a while,
I finally thought of a wish.'
'I didn't make the wish to go
to Mom and Dad like I did last year.'
'I didn't make the wish
to meet Mom and Dad again.'
'Will Buddha grant my wish this year?
The wish I made today was...'
'Mom, be happy.
Dad, be happy.'
Bumsang?
Hey. I'm almost done. We can
leave after I'm done with these.
I finally understand why
you took me to the Bomun Shrine.
What? How would you know that?
That's none of your business.
Wrap things up here then.
Sit, sit.
If I knew you were coming, I would
have made the radish kimchi you like.
It's okay, Grandma.
I'm coming back next week, anyway.
You're coming next week?
Are you coming with him?
Oh, no, I'm not coming.
Yeah, you must be busy.
Next time, we'll go up to Seoul
so we'll see each other then.
Okay, Grandmother.
It's late. Go on home.
Bye, Grandma.
- Thank you for the meal.
- You're welcome.
No matter how the public feels,
we need to catch Robin Hood.
Why suddenly the change in heart?
We're continuously working
late hours because of him!
Yeah. We'll have
to catch him, eventually.
Chief.
You two haven't gone home yet?
We can't go home when there's
so much work to do for the country.
There aren't enough hours in the day for
all the worrying we do about the country.
What brings you here?
What? Ah, I had
something to ask Chohee.
Chohee?
Chohee left early in the morning with
Bumsang. We haven't heard from her.
Ah, is that so?
Why don't you give her a call?
No, I can ask
her tomorrow. Goodbye.
Yes, sir.
Doesn't it seem like Chief Kang
takes care of Chohee a lot?
He doesn't do nearly
as much as I do for Joohyun.
I miss her, suddenly.
Joohyun...
Though they tried not to show it, your
grandparents seemed kind of lonely.
Go visit them more often. After all,
you're the only family they have.
You should go visit them.
My grandma seemed to like you
since she thinks you look prolific.
You must be the fecund type.
You wanna die?
Hold that thought.
Hey, why are you calling me?
Chief Kang did what?
He asked questions about me?
[You know how I can't tell lies.
So I told him the truth about you.]
[But I was worried and decided to give
you a call since we are friends, after all.]
Yeah. Thanks.
Chief Kang did something?
No, it's nothing.
Did he figure out that you restored
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook?
Is that it? It is, isn't it?
You shouldn't have restored a stolen
good in the first place. Why'd you do it?
Stop already. Before it was
a stolen good, it was a cultural asset.
It was my fault for being unable
to refuse Chairman Jang's request.
but I've never once regretted restoring
the “Sowonhwagae” scrapbook.
And I know Chief Kang
is just doing his job...
but it's insulting to hear that
he's checking up on me like that.
He probably wasn't
comfortable doing it either.
It's not like you guys are strangers.
It probably took a lot of deliberation
on his part. So don't feel so insulted.
I can't believe you.
What?
You understand Chief Kang so well,
but did you ever try to understand me?
But... that's not what I meant...
Enough.
I forgot that you like him.
Look here, Bumsang.
Never mind,
let's talk about this later.
Bye.
Hi, Sis.
Hey.
Did you find out anything about Dad?
No.
Oh, just one. Hold on.
You know what this is?
It's a good-luck pole.
How do you know that?
Of course I do. It was at the entrance
of the village when we lived in Buyeo.
Wow, you remember that?
Of course. I even remember
the day he whittled it.
You have a good memory,
remembering all that.
You think that's all?
I remember the day he set up
the good-luck pole in the village...
the day we played
hide-and-seek under it...
and the day you chased after him
crying when he was being arrested.
Why remember all that?
Where did you get this?
I met someone who shared a prison cell
with him and he gave it to me.
He made it together with Dad.
They made it together?
I see.
Hey, aren't you hungry?
I'm starved.
Let's eat.
Come on.
I can't believe you.
What?
You understand Chief Kang so well,
but did you ever try to understand me?
Was I being unfair?
Doesn't it seem like Robin Hood
is awfully quiet these days?
He must've heard our complaints.
I've been continuously thinking
about who Robin Hood could be.
There you go again!
Talking about Bumsang.
No. At first I really believed
that Bumsang was Robin Hood.
But then it occurred to me
that maybe he's not.
Then who do you
think Robin Hood is?
I think that it's...
Chohee.
What?
You know I'm quite insightful
about the future.
The time has come for
the appearance of a female thief.
A prepared female thief.
By far, Chohee seems most likely.
Please spread the rumor far and wide
whenever you get the chance.
Why do her conclusions always
end up nonsensical like that?
So what? How could you possibly
understand the pain of a broken heart?
[Testing, testing. Hey, Bumsang.]
[If you were hurt by my words
yesterday, I'm really sorry.]
[But I wasn't trying
to take Chief Kang's side.]
[I was just trying to comfort you in my own way. So don't be angry anymore.]
[I'm on my way to meet my dad's friend.
Pray for some good news. Okay?]
This weekend I'm going to try
going to where we used to live.
Are you sure he's alive?
I showed you the records.
You want to see them again?
You think he's alive because of a sheet
of paper? After seven years of no news?
Uncle.
Gyoon asked me why your father
didn't look for you two if he were alive.
He said he couldn't believe
your father would do that.
Still, I...
I agree with Gyoon. If he were alive,
he wouldn't have kept quiet for so long.
He would've done something.
Stolen something. Anything.
Think about it. I'm one of the people
who desperately hope he's alive.
But no matter how much I think about it, I don't think you're doing the right thing.
You're only going to end up
with an even more bruised heart.
It's me.
Come to my room right now.
What?
Apologies should be made in person.
So come to my room.
I'm outside right now.
Who said you could go by yourself?
Come back then. I'll be waiting so hurry.
Hey.
Who's he to tell me what to do?
Didn't he hear the recording?
[Your call has been transferred...]
What in the world? What's going on?
She's taking too long.
Did something happen?
[Chohee Heo]
Hey! Where are you?
Hey! What are you doing here?
Bumsang, you're here!
Come, come, sit down.
Chohee!
Why are you yelling? Excuse me,
can we get another shot glass?
No, don't bring it.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I'm drinking. Have a drink.
Here, here.
What's with you?
Do you know how worried I was?
You should've called me or something.
Ah! I plumb forgot to call you.
You forgot?
Jeez...
Come on, drink already.
You're not gonna drink?
Then I'll drink.
Hey, hey! Get up.
What?
Why? I just got here.
Get up already!
- What's your problem?
- Come out!
Hey, let go!
What's your problem?
I'll forgive you for worrying me,
so just go home. Okay?
Who are you to boss me around? Go
home yourself. I'm going to drink. Let go!
Hey. Hey!
What's up with the drunk behavior?
This is so unlike you.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Stop lying.
What is it? Huh?
Come on, tell me.
Really. Nothing happened.
Chohee!
I said nothing happened!
Why do you keep asking
when I said nothing happened?
Nothing happened, okay?
I saw my dad.
I saw him, but...
He wasn't my dad.
I really thought it was my dad,
but it wasn't him.
[I got angry and you cried.
Let's consider ourselves even.]
[Don't cry when you wake up, okay?
It's not like you. You're the fecund type.]
[Now that I think about it,
you were kind of cute while drunk.]
[Don't be too hard on yourself. Bye.]
What's this?
Ugh, my head. I didn't even
wash up before sleeping.
What?
Buy me something to eat.
What? How more
shameless can you get?
Can't you just buy me something?
No. Buy it yourself.
Yes, Chief.
Okay, I'll be right in.
Another item came to the museum.
It was delivered again?
It's a vase with a plum tree
and bamboo design.
Bumsang, please take a look at it.
It's...
The “Cheongjasamgang
Maejukmun” vase.
Yes, Officer Cho.
Officer Cho!
Chief.
I looked into the matter.
The vase that came in was stolen
last night from Chairman Jang's house.
Again from Chairman Jang's house?
Yes. Last night.
News travels so fast that all the
rich men and middlemen already know.
This is definitely a plot against Chairman
Jang. What do you think, Chief?
Chief!
Uncle, the “Cheongjasamgang
Maejukmun” vase. Dad stole it, right?
[The "Maejukmun" vase?
I'm sure your dad stole it.]
Why do you ask?
Did it show up at the museum, too?
Yes.
That's so strange. Why do your dad's
items keep showing up? Three of them!
Three? It's two. You said the “Chochung”
collection wasn't one of dad's items.
[Oh, didn't I tell you?]
I was searching through my records for
you, and I found out he stole it in 2000.
[So all three items sent to the museum
were all your dad's stolen items.]
[Who in the world is doing this?
I don't understand.]
He said he'd return the stolen items and go to his kids with a clear conscience.
Bumsang.
Can I have a private word with you?
What is this regarding?
Please excuse me for asking,
but where were you yesterday?
And why do I have to answer that?
Because you're in need of an alibi.
Why would I need an alibi?
Do you know what common factors
connect the items sent to the museum?
They're all stolen goods and they were
all in Chairman Jang's possession.
So what?
Bumsang, are you Robin Hood?
What?
If you can't give me an alibi,
I'll have no choice but to investigate you.
Where were you last night?
I believe the investigation
has already begun.
Please answer my question. Where were
you last night and with whom?
He was with me.
We were together until about midnight,
and he was probably home after that.
Then you just need to provide
an alibi for after midnight.
There's no need for that, Chief.
Bumsang isn't Robin Hood.
The real Robin Hood is...
General Shovel Taesoo Heo.
My father is Robin Hood.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America