Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Is this where we're having dinner?
Episode 3
I should've skipped lunch
for this grand dinner!
Though I'm undeserving, thank you
for giving me this opportunity.
I will do my best to protect
our nation's cultural assets.
And dinner's on me,
so please enjoy yourselves.
Whoa!
He's as generous
as the affluent air he exudes.
And he looks like he has a frank
and straightforward personality.
He looks better in person than on TV.
I thought
you said he looked like a fop.
Since when is a fop a bad thing?
Work isn't easy, is it?
Please enjoy yourself.
Please help yourself to more.
Joohyun,
let me pour you a drink.
Oh no,
I can't drink very well,
Just a little?
Just a little.
Just a bit more. More, more.
Oh, it's overflowing.
Thank you.
Chohee, would you like a drink?
If you insist. I really want just a little.
So, how did you manage to find
Kyeomjae's “Naegeumgang”?
What?
I mean, we couldn't even find it,
yet you found it so easily.
He did, didn't he?
Why are you asking... Oh, that's true.
What happened was...
A few days ago a man came to me
with a painting to appraise.
But something seemed
awfully fishy about it.
Is this a stolen painting?
Gosh, darnit. How'd you know?
And that's when I called
Ms. Joohyun Wang here.
And that's why I insisted that...
...he absolutely must be
our committee member.
Good job.
Good work, good work!
Oh, you're done with your drink.
Yes.
Then you must've seen the thief's face.
Right.
Can you describe
his physical attributes to us?
Was he tall or short?
How was his build?
Was he, by any chance, bald?
The thing is,
he seemed to be in disguise...
So he must be the jerk that led us on
that wild goose chase at Mt. Jangyong.
Then we have to catch him!
I'll do more than catch him!
I'll break his little legs.
I'll cooperate with your investigation...
...so please don't worry
and have another drink.
Yes, another drink.
Let me fill you up.
So what ulterior motive do you have to becoming the committee member?
Why, are you nervous?
If you are, you're welcome to act as rudely as you did before.
“Bumsang Kim doesn't
deserve that position.”
I considered it but..
...why stop you when you volunteered to protect the cultural assets?
I should help you any way I can. Right?
Bumsang Kim, I welcome you to the Cultural Heritage Administration.
I don't know what you have up your sleeve, but I advise you to brace yourself.
Look here, about that...
why don't you listen to your own advice?
Stop picking petty fights with me.
You little...
Sir.
Oh my my,
look at the uncouth way she speaks.
Why does Chohee dislike you so much?
The truth is, in Japan...
Well, something happened.
What happened?
No, no. I don't think
I should be telling you.
Sir, it's okay.
You can tell me anything.
I can, right? The truth is...
What? She tried to seduce him
while completely naked?
She's totally crazy!
Is she out of her mind?
Do you realize whom we're talking about?
Chohee Heo,
the woman who does everything...
...and anything she can
to achieve her goals.
That's chump change to her.
No wonder.
After being rebuffed, she took it out on him in the Preservation Science Lab.
Still, how could she do that when she already lives together with a man?
Seriously!
What? Chohee lives with a man?
You didn't know? I heard he was yakuza.
Yakuza...
Somehow that doesn't seem to fit.
The rumors are
probably everywhere by now.
I hope she's thoroughly embarrassed.
You jerk. What's wrong with you?
There were already a ton of rumors about her anyway.
And I had to do it in order to
survive at the CHA.
I bet. Wow, this is a great room. Yongchul's probably green with envy.
Don't even mention that jerk.
If I think about how I lost the professorship to him...
I have to succeed here
if only to squash his ego.
I'm going to become the director, no,...
...the Minister of Culture,
and exact my revenge on him.
Bumsang...
Why? Don't think I can do it?
Look, the director of the CHA is...
calling me?
Yes, sir?
Chief, I seriously think he's the one who hid away the “Naegeumgang.”
You saw him yesterday,
all the crap he was spewing.
Everyone has skeletons in the closet.
One foot in heaven, one in hell.
That's how everyone is.
Chief!
Don't go around accusing a superior without any evidence, okay? Got it?
The director is here from the main office, and he wants to see you. Let's go.
What about?
Probably about the main family of the Kangheung branch of Lees.
We won't find out ‘til we go.
Your handwriting is amazing.
You balance the discipline of the Chinese print and the independence of...
...the Chinese cursive handwriting well in your brush strokes.
Did you really write this yourself?
I'm embarrassed to admit yes.
It's wonderful.
Really?
Come in.
This is the head investigator...
...for the robbery case of the main family of the Kangheung branch of Lees.
Wait, aren't you the employee
who caused trouble last time?
Since it's a family matter of mine, I was going to personally ask for help, but...
Chief Noh, can't you go
instead of this employee?
But I have to prep for the National Assembly's inspection...
...of our administration with you.
Then whom can I trust with this endeavor?
I will help you.
You will?
If I can help in any way with my lacking
services, I will try my best.
I'm impressed, Mr. Kim. Then I will entrust the matter to you.
But someone should still go with you...
I will go with him.
It's only natural that I should since we've already worked together in Japan.
And I would like this opportunity to make up for my mistake last time.
It's impressive that you are going
to the crime scene yourself.
We've never had a committee member like you before.
Please, you flatter me too much.
I need to familiarize myself...
...with crime scenes as well as
learn the ropes of the trade.
Will you be okay going with Chohee?
Yes, that worries me a bit. It would be great if I were going with you instead.
Should I request a change in partners?
What are you saying?
We have to go check out the robbery at Congressman Junpil Lee's house.
Congressman Junpil Lee?
Congressman Junpil Lee,
three-time Congressman...
...and chairman of the National
Assembly's Cultural Assets Bureau.
‘It would be great if I could make an appearance there as well.'
Too bad you can't go.
You should chase
just one rabbit at a time.
She speaks absolute rubbish sometimes.
Shall we?
We shall. I'll see you later.
What an impressive fellow.
Doesn't it look like
Chohee hasn't given up on him yet?
That's what I'm saying.
I should have gone with him.
Did you see how he wanted me?
Jiyoung, how can you say that?
Of course I miss you, too.
Yes, let's meet up next week.
I'll call you. Okay.
Hello, Yeonju. How have you been?
I waited for your call.
Hello? Hello? Ah, my battery
died at this critical moment.
Let me borrow your phone for one call.
Never mind.
You're so busy. What with Jungeun, Minju, Youngju, Soyoung...
I never knew you were an expert appraiser of women as well.
Why, are you interested in being appraised by me?
Heck no.
Why refuse? You're the one who's following me around.
Think what you want...
...but I want to make sure you don't dupe anyone like with the cat's food bowl.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I forgot to tell you.
I'm not the expert women appraiser.
My car is.
He does this whenever
a wretched woman rides.
He bucks like a wild bronco.
What did you say?
What's important in pottery
is the base of the piece...
...and in paintings the artist's seal.
When it comes to women, they should be kind or at least not speak crudely.
You are impossible to appraise.
You should to work on that.
Maybe pay the doctor a visit.
What? In my opinion, you should be
the one seeing a doctor.
What's your mental age?
You're such a schoolboy. So immature.
Let's stop the bickering,
you schoolgirl...
Say what?
Over here, too, please.
Okay.
He has a lot of old books.
At 08:47. I'll give you a call
as soon as it's verified. Okay.
Chief Kang.
Yes?
Chief, about the main family
of the Kangheung Lees..
Seeing how Bumsang was sent down, the losses must be serious.
Shouldn't we go, too?
We can't go anywhere...
...until the Congressman shows up to confirm his losses.
We have to wait.
How long do you think
we'll have to wait?
He'll be here soon, right? He has to.
Joohyun, what's up? Are you interested in Bumsang Kim?
What?
Oh, I'm not the one who's interested. He's interested in me.
Why else would he agree to be
the committee member...
...after refusing multiple times?
I should have known when he called me about the “Naegeumgang.”
He said earlier that he really wanted to go with me.
I hope the Congressman shows up before lunchtime.
Is she being cute or
is she really that clueless?
Congressman, sir.
What items did you lose...
What do you mean nothing was stolen?
In other words, all the important
cultural assets are still here.
The rest we'll have to sort out,
one by one.
What an unfortunate thief. It's not an easy feat to steal only useless things.
That's strange. Let's compile a list of the damages.
The furniture and pottery are intact...
...but what do we do about the old books? There are tons.
Are there?
I'm not sorting through them. Looking at Chinese characters gives me headaches.
There's nothing to fear.
Bumsang Kim is here.
Sir?
You want me to sort through
all these books?
What happened to familiarizing yourself with crime scenes...
...as well as learning the ropes of the trade?
I think this is
a great opportunity for just that.
And if you filch anything, you're dead.
We're so incompetent
in Chinese characters...
...that it'll take us months to do it.
We sure are glad you're here with us, sir.
God's going to bless you.
For sure.
He's gonna do more than bless him.
So she's gonna pull one over me like this? How am I going to finish all this?
Something like this has never happened in our village before.
You must be in shock.
I can't even begin to describe
how I feel...
...but thankfully I won't be ashamed in front of our ancestors.
Yes, we should be glad that
no one was hurt. Then we'll be going.
Hold on.
Are you by any chance
Mr. Bumsang Kim?
Yes, I am.
It is you! Don't you remember me?
You took a look at my book at the CHA.
Ah, yes, yes. I remember.
It's you, it's you.
Fellas, this is the amazing guy
I was telling you about. Come here.
Sirs, may I ask you a question?
Shoot.
Ask anything you want.
Testing, testing.
As descendants of Hyunro Lee of
the Kangheung branch...
...there's no way the thief is one of us.
I sincerely beseech you,
as village leader,...
...to find that disgraceful thief and restore our good name.
Ah, so you didn't witness the crime?
If I saw him, I would've done something about it. Beat him down with a stick.
Ah, yes. Have you seen any strangers around the village?
Strangers? There's a stranger now.
Chief.
Huh.
What's with the sudden rain?
Beats me.
What brings you here?
Oh, Joohyun insisted persistently
that we come.
Don't you have an umbrella?
No umbrella.
Ack, it's cold.
Where's Bumsang...
Why would she want to come here?
I think she's interested in Bumsang.
What?
Where is he, by the way?
He's probably sweating it right now, cataloging the old books.
Look here.
That is the character for “uniform.”
No, it's not. Use your bifocal glasses.
This character means “to cross.”
You need another brush stroke here for it to mean “to cross.”
Adding that brush stroke would give you “to resume.”
You're back. They're almost done,
wait just a bit more.
Then is it “to resume?”
It is, I tell you.
It shouldn't have that brush stroke.
Listen, listen.
Here, here.
We're leaving.
It's is indeed difficult to determine who's superior. You're all so knowledgeable.
Please take care.
That's a great talent of yours.
You were born wily, weren't you?
I'm not wily.
I have wisdom from experience.
Anyway, was anything missing?
Just one.
The “Myungshimbogam.”
What I don't understand is...
...why steal a common book like
the “Myungshimbogam?”
Exactly.
The dead dog was probably worth more. He should have just taken the dog.
Maybe it's an amateur who knows little about cultural assets?
But isn't it strange? He tore off the door and killed the dog.
It seems awfully premeditated,
doesn't it?
By the way, what was missing from Congressman Lee's house?
He's a famous collector.
That's the funny part. A thief came in, but apparently nothing's missing.
Maybe the Congressman purchased
a stolen good and had that stolen?
He is, after all, a politician.
It wouldn't be worth the trouble...
...being charged with the concealment
of stolen goods.
That's probably why he claimed
that nothing was missing.
I'm on the same page as you, but what can we do? He insists nothing is missing.
We can't go looking for an item
when we don't know what it is.
Would you happen to know?
What? How would I...
You're quite familiar with this kind
of thing, the back alley stuff.
Me? Dear no, I'm an appraiser.
How would I know about
the circulation of stolen items?
Is that so?
Excuse me.
Please enjoy yourselves.
He's a gem all right.
It must be quite a hassle to be a thief.
You'd have to study up on
what's valuable.
Just be glad that thieves these days
are stupid.
If we had more men like Mr. Kim and “General Shovel,” we'd be in trouble.
I've heard of Mr. Kim,
but who is this “General Shovel?”
A famous art thief well educated in Chinese literature...
...as well as topographic divination.
It was said that if his trail of conquests had been followed properly...
...our country's archeological history would have turned out differently.
Oh, the man who cleaned out Kyungju, Buyeo and even Gongju?
Yes, him.
Chief Noh caught him
a couple of times...
...but he dropped off the radar
for the past few years.
There's a rumor that he's dead,
but no one's sure.
Thank you for the meal.
Why aren't you eating more?
I ate plenty. Excuse me.
Is it morning sickness?
Why isn't she eating?
Is Chohee pregnant?
Dad, Dad! Dad,
where are you going? Where?
Oh, Chohee.
You're not going to steal again, are you?
Are you?
You told me you quit. You said
you were never going to steal again!
This is the last run. The last one.
Dad, you can't. You can't do this.
I don't need to go to college.
I'll work more part-time jobs. So please don't go, Dad. Please don't go.
I'll be back.
Dad, Dad!
Dad!
What is she doing? Why'd she wander into that isolated area?
Sir, won't you be bored while driving back? I was thinking of riding with you...
Well, then I'm saved from boredom, aren't I?
Right?
Let's go.
Okay.
No, Jiyoon, I really will be home
early today.
Ice cream? Want me to buy some? Strawberry?
Huh? Okay.
All right. I really, really love you, too.
Okay.
Chohee, when did you get here?
Just now. Chief, you're a great dad.
Me? Far from it. I always go home late,
I don't play with her. I fail as a dad.
So what brings you here?
Ah, I was told Mr. Kim's trial is today.
Oh, didn't you hear?
The trial was moved to eleven.
What?
Aw, man.
You're already late,
nothing you can do.
Let's go, I'll buy you something to eat. What do you want?
I... Anything's fine with me.
Anything's fine?
I can't just buy you anything.
What shall we eat?
Hold on.
Yeah, Officer Park. What?
What?
What happened?
Due to insufficient evidence.
No doubt the filthy rich men who deal with Mr. Kim pulled some strings.
Chief, there he comes.
Sir, congratulations on being acquitted.
I enjoyed my stay in jail, thanks for that.
But unfortunately for you,
I'm already out.
Enjoy your freedom
while you can, Mr. Hyukjoong Kim.
You'll be back in there
before you know it.
And who is this lady?
Oh, the famous Ms. Fake Hanako?
So the CHA's hiring based on looks now?
I don't know
who's pulling strings for you...
...but it'll be in your best interest
to lay low.
I'll keep that in mind.
Sir, we've got a shadow on our tail.
Leave them be. Let them waste some more gas. We'll shake them off later.
They gave you a hard time.
Should we go teach them a lesson?
No good, it might affect the big deal.
We can always take care of
the small fry later.
So who's the guy who tricked Yonggu Lee into giving up the “Naegeumgang?”
A pretty famous guy
named Bumsang Kim.
Bumsang Kim? It was him, you say?
The national hero. You're quite popular. Just like a celebrity.
Not you, too. You know
I don't care about that sort of thing.
I don't like it when other women
throw themselves at you.
So what? You know
that you're the only one for me...
Really?
No.
Meanie.
Come here.
Bumsang, hey.
That was the host of “Discovering Cultural Assets,” right?
She's as plastic as the rumors say she is.
What were you two up to?
Nothing. Is this it?
Yeah.
By the way, don't you think
you're being awfully shameless?
How can you become
a CHA committee member...
...after pulling that stunt with
the “Naegeumgang?”
Hey, watch what you say.
Someone'll hear you.
You know Congressman Lee, right?
Congressman Junpil Lee?
Ever hear of an item that went into
that house on the down-low?
Tons. He practically feeds everyone in the black market. What's up?
He had a huge catch stolen, but he denies it. Got any ideas?
A huge catch, you say?
There is a pretty tremendous catch
that comes to mind.
What is it?
Can't tell you for free.
Free? I set up
your television appearance.
Fine, fine. The item is...
Really? That exists in real life?
Yup. Congressman Lee's
a real fanatic of Prince Ahnpyeong.
I'm sure about this one.
Please standby.
Recording will start soon.
Oh, I'm nervous. ‘Cause this is
my first TV appearance.
I should have gone to
the congressman's home yesterday.
I chased the wrong rabbit.
That's my seat. You're over here.
Someone from the investigations team is tailing Mr. Kim.
As for the Kangheung family case...
...we're planning to sort through well-known thieves...
...of rare books for suspects.
And I'm going to go to Congressman Lee's house later.
Hey! The congressman recanted his theft report. Why are you going there?
Shouldn't we be investigating him
for the concealment of stolen goods?
Don't you know what that man's
capable of? Drop that case.
Chief...
You wanna turn the CHA upside down?
Digging around with no evidence
will get us all fired.
I know something's fishy, but there's nothing we can do. Back off.
Fine.
Big news, big news! Chohee, Chohee...
What about her?
She's pregnant.
Shut up! Shut up!
Who's the father?
Apparently, she doesn't even know.
Shut up! Shut up!
You don't think it might be
Bumsang Kim, do you?
No way. What do you take him for?
Didn't you hear that he rejected her even when she was seducing him butt-naked?
You think that's true? He is a guy
after all. It's probably true, right?
I did what to whom?
Oh, Chohee.
I wanna hear everything you know.
All of it.
What can we say?
Bumsang Kim, you're dead meat.
I'm gonna kill you...
And I'm the art expert Bumsang Kim. Good night.
Cut. Good job.
Exit slowly. Starting from the back.
Honey, you're leaving?
Huh?
We should finish our conversation
from earlier.
What were we talking about?
Yoo-hoo. Bumsang?
Hey, what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
What are you doing with this woman after you knocked me up?
Wh ? what? Knocked up whom?
What are you babbling about?
Darling, who's this woman?
Didn't I tell you?
Is this Soyoung? Jungeun?
Fine, darling. I don't care.
But don't throw away
your child for this woman.
Hey, what the hell are you talking about?
You don't know? Don't you remember that hot, steamy night in Japan?
I'm pregnant due to that night.
What do you expect me to do
if you ignore me like this?
It's not true.
Honey...
Hey, it's really not true. Really.
You jerk. you dare to two-time me?
No, no, I tell you it's not true.
Are you insane? Why are you doing
this to me? What did I do to you?
Drop the innocent act.
I did what? I threw myself at you
while completely naked?
You're the insane one. How could you start a rumor like that?
It's not like it was a complete lie.
You did jump into the hot spring completely naked. Am I wrong?
What?
It's not my fault you have such a loose reputation that everyone believed it.
Rumors about you and Chief Noh and that you live with a man are...
...already rampant.
I can't believe this.
Fine, let's assume I do live loosely.
Why are you so self-righteous?
You tricked a man
out of his cat's food bowl.
Why are you drudging up the past? Fine, so it wasn't just a cat's food bowl.
Was it such a sin
that I tried to sneak it out?
And you snuck
the “Naegeumgang” away, too.
Speaking of which...
...you had one long night in the mountains but eventually got it.
What are you so upset about? It's not like I sold it on the black market.
You were going to.
To Chairman Kim of the Dongsan Group.
That's not even funny.
I've never even met Chairman Kim.
Who do you think you're fooling?
Chairman Kim sent you
to Japan to get the vase.
You don't know anything.
It was Chairman Jang...
Oh yeah? Chairman Ohsung Jang
of the Ohsung Group?
Yeah, he did. So what?
I recorded the conversation.
What?
If you had just apologized,
I would have let bygones be bygones.
But it's too late.
Make sure to check out the front page
of the newspaper tomorrow.
What the... Are you threatening me?
You think I'd shake in my boots?
It really made the front page.
Dear lord, how could he
be so shameless?
I know. And we hated on
Chohee for nothing.
I didn't know this was your true nature.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Me, too.
So you were the one who screwed us over with the “Naegeumgang?”
And you still agreed to
be the committee member?
How shameless.
Shall we teach him a lesson?
How about we start by snapping
his legs into two?
Whoa, that's bad.
Thank you. Bumsang, you're dead.
- Hey, wait! Let's talk about this.
- What are you doing?
I have nothing to discuss with you.
Let's compromise. I have
an incredible bit of information.
Don't need it, so back off.
Aren't you curious about the item Congressman Lee lost?
Not in the least, so will you stop already? Got it?
“Bihaedangjib.”
Written by Prince Ahnpyeong...
...one of the three great calligraphers
of the Joseon Era.
Aren't you intrigued?
Other than the “Mongyoodowondo” currently at Japan's Tenri University...
...and national treasure no. 238, “Sowon-
hwagyecheob,” which was stolen...
...there are no other intact authentic works written by Prince Ahnpyeong.
...You know this.
That means if this “Bihaedangjib” is authentic... Hey, hey!
Uncle. Uncle, where are you right now?
Was the “Bihaedangjib”
info a little too much for her?
Shoot, that's not the problem right now. What do I do about that recording...
There's no way she already
sold it to the press.
No, she's totally capable of doing that. And more.
“Bihaedangjib?”
The “Bihaedangjib” really surfaced?
Dad stole that, right? Tell me, Uncle.
Chief Noh. Does he know about this?
No. The theft report was recanted...
...so it's not even being investigated.
I didn't want to cause him any trouble.
So Uncle, you have to help me.
You're going to look for it by yourself?
I have to find it. Whatever it takes,
I have to find it.
Why?
‘Cause Dad stole it. The wrongs my thief father committed, I have to set right.
I have to be the one who finds it.
Do you think you'll find
some traces of your father...
...if you find the “Bihaedangjib?”
You're barking up the wrong tree, Uncle.
I don't want to find him at all. I don't care if he's dead or alive.
So stop worrying over nothing.
Chohee.
I'm sorry, I have to leave first.
Ah...
Huh, you're home? I cooked some noodles, want some?
No, you eat it all.
It's all overcooked.
Thanks. I was asking just to be polite.
Gyoon.
Yeah?
What if Dad... Dad...
Dad...
If you're asking if I miss him, then yes.
If you're asking if I think he's alive,
then the answer is no.
Uncle Hwang called.
An item Dad stole surfaced, right?
You know what?
I don't think...
...Dad's such a terrible person that he'd sever contact with us for seven years...
...if he were alive.
So don't go looking for him, okay?
Gyoon.
Instead, search out the items
that he stole.
After all, you're a member of
the regulations team. Right?
Do you want to find the “Bihaedangjib,” or do you want to find your father?
The wrongs my thief father committed...
...I have to set right.
I have to be the one who finds it.
[Bumsang Kim]
Why is she ignoring my calls?
Wait, I mustn't show her
how desperate I am right now.
Be patient. Be patient.
Darnit, I can't! I'm going crazy.
[Bumsang Kim]
Bumsang Kim...
She ignored all my calls.
What is this woman up to?
Mr. Kim?
Ah...
Ah, Sunyoung. How are you?
How could you not visit me
at the Preservation Science Lab?
Of course I have to visit. I was planning to go see how you were doing.
So did you find out what the mysterious book we restored was?
Not yet. But the book it was in is the “Myungshimbogam.”
“Myungshimbogam?”
Please call me anytime
when you find out what it is. I'm curious.
I can call you anytime?
Even late at night?
Of course.
But wouldn't Ms. Heo mind?
What?
I heard you two were getting married.
Married?
I probably shouldn't be saying this,
but I think you're being hasty.
Marriage is not something
you decide on a whim. Then, bye...
Wait...
This is absolutely preposterous.
So basically I just fell into the trap
that I dug for Chohee, right?
[Chohee Heo]
Hey, where are you!
Recording, where's the recording?
I can't just give it to you.
I have a condition.
What kind of condition?
Help me find the “Bihaedangjib.”
Then I'll give it to you.
Dude, I practically handed it to you on
a silver platter. No way I'm helping you
No?
No.
Oh yeah? Too bad.
I wasn't going to call them...
Hello, is this the broadcasting station?
Fine, I'll help you.
What do you need me to do?
I want you to contact
all the middlemen...
...that you know
who specialize in rare books.
Why do you want me to do that?
You probably know more people.
What middleman would willingly
help out the regulations team?
So you have to help.
I would if I knew any middlemen.
You don't know any?
None.
Really?
Of course not really.
I know lots. Put that away.
Prince Ahnpyeong's “Bihaedangjib.” Who filched it?
Put a pile of greens in my hand,
and I'll tell you.
Don't try to play me.
We both know how this game works.
Fine. Mr. Son in Insa-dong
can probably help you out.
I just came from him! You're useless.
Absolutely useless.
How am I supposed to know something that Mr. Son doesn't?
So the “Bihaedangjip” is in the open again, is it? Thanks for the tip.
What the... Hey, do I have to
continue this charade?
Of course. Next.
“Bihaedangjib?”
Never heard of it. While you're here,
can you appraise this for me?
Aw, man. Mr. Park.
That looks real familiar.
Why do you have that when you said
you quit this business?
Goodness...
Long time no see, Ms. Heo.
I have another engagement,
so gotta run. See you next time.
You pay for the coffee.
All right, onto the next player.
I'm serious.
That's the bottom of the barrel.
Quit lying through your teeth.
I'll release the recording.
Seriously... I really don't have any more. Why do you have to be like that?
Why do I have to be like what?
So, you absolutely refuse to dip into your secret stash?
Who gave you the tip about the “Bihaedangjib?” Was it Mr. Son?
Fine, we'll meet him tomorrow.
For now let's go eat. I'm starving. Okay?
Then we're going to do
this tomorrow, too?
Here are the files on Mr. Kim
that you requested.
Sorry for making you
come out all this way.
Why should you be sorry?
Chohee should be for dumping it to me instead of doing it herself.
I wonder why she's so busy every day?
It's awfully suspicious.
This is your first stake-out, isn't it?
Stake-outs and spying are
Chohee's specialties.
Are you really mad that you had to
come here instead of Chohee?
Oh my, of course not.
It's all part of my job.
So how long do you have to do this?
It must be terribly boring.
Yeah, so how about a little drive?
What?
Ch-chief. How about
dropping me off first?
There's no time.
It's time to lose the shadow.
That persistent bastard.
Yes, sir.
Oh, gonna burn some rubber, huh?
Ch-chief?
What the! Why are you screaming?
Sl-slowly! Fifty miles per hour. You should keep the speed limit.
Ack, oh my god.
Joohyun, lift your head.
I can't see the sideview mirror.
Mommy!
Joohyun.
Hey, Joohyun.
Those suckers must be pissed about losing me. But the real game starts now.
What happened to the “Bihaedangjib?”
The first volume is already packaged...
...and we're still looking for
the second one.
If you screw up this time, you're done for. Life's too long to spend in pain.
Yes, sir.
D-day's almost here. Find the other volume as soon as possible, okay?
Don't worry, sir.
The “Bihaedangjib” has two volumes?
It was originally one.
But according to the book “Seollo Ilgi,”...
...Prince Ahnpyeong's tactician Hyunro Lee split it into two volumes...
...and hid them before his death.
Then there's another volume aside...
...from the one stolen from
Congressman Lee? Where's that one?
How should I know?
So why are you so hung up over this?
Do I need a reason
to search for a cultural asset?
Yes, if you're going to be hung up over something that's not an official mission.
Wasn't this case closed?
So why are you working your butt off?
Everyone at the CHA knows.
My goal is to be the next chief.
Chief?
If I want to up my performance rating...
...this is the kind of thing
I have to suffer through.
It's a reasonably persuasive reason. But why can't I believe a word of it? Huh?
Believe it. Stop talking nonsense
and eat. It's on me.
In case you've forgotten...
...I'm an expert appraiser. I separate
the real from the fake for a living.
And I say that everything you said just now is a complete lie. Not that I care.
Hey, hey.
What?
Say cheese.
What for?
You've got a whopper stuck in there.
What?
Ah, there's nothing there...
Ugh, why's it raining?
Hey, if we don't find the “Bihaedangjib,”...
...are you going to give
the recording to the press?
Need you ask?
Hey, at least I'm trying. Aren't I?
I'm trying my best. So don't be like that.
Ugh, you're creeping me out, Bumsang.
Hey!
So it's like that, huh?
You don't want to get fired?
So that's your goal? To get me fired?
I won't while we're looking for
the “Bihaedangjib,” so relax.
Let's meet up tomorrow at
Mr. Son's store at 10 am. Got it?
Don't be late. I'm off.
Hey...
What?
I can't stand seeing
a woman get wet in the rain.
Here, use this. See you tomorrow.
What's up with him? Is this his chivalrous act?
I should have known
you'd give me something like this.
Hello, Chief.
The Kangheung Lee family's village was robbed again? What's missing?
The “Myungshimbogam.”
That's it for today.
Thank you for your effort.
It's pretty clear that's the only book missing, so let's head back.
Yes, let's. We shouldn't be wasting time here when we've lost track of Mr. Kim.
It's so strange how the same book
keeps getting stolen.
Let's leave after we find out if any other household still has their copy.
You pouring salt on the wound?
How can you be so tactless...
...when you know
he's in a foul mood about Mr. Kim?
I'm in a foul mood, too.
I thought we'd be able to
kick back without Chief Noh...
...but here we are toiling away.
So how did he manage to lose Mr. Kim?
What?
It's weird. Chief Kang's not
the type to easily lose a suspect.
That's what I'm saying.
The thing is...
That Mr. Kim is a slippery fella.
You know how he is, how fast he is.
I'm sorry I can't join you, Chief. Yes, yes. Call me when you get back. Okay.
That's so strange.
Why does the “Myungshimbogam”
keep getting stolen?
[I'm already here. If you're even
a minute later, you're dead!]
Did I exploit the recording too much?
As descendants of Hyunro Lee
of the Kangheung family branch...
Prince Ahnpyeong's tactician
Hyunro Lee split it into two volumes...
...and hid them before his death.
Hyunro Lee. Hyunro Lee?
Are you sure I'm not going to
end up a scapegoat?
Don't worry, I tell you. I've got your back.
Hey! Why are you so late?
Hey, Bumsang. You said that Hyunro Lee split the “Bihaedangjib” into two, right?
He did, right? You're absolutely sure?
Yes. Why do you want to know?
Hyunro Lee split
the “Bihaedangjib” into two.
The “Myungshimbogam” keeps going missing in the village...
...where Lee's descendants live.
What do you think this means?
Then the men who are stealing
the “Myungshimbogam” are after...
We have to hurry down
to the Kangheung village.
I have to check something.
There's no need.
We have to go to the CHA.
What are you talking about?
Remember the book
I restored last time?
The day you got
the letter of appreciation?
The pages were hidden in a copy of
the “Myungshimbogam.” Get in.
Chief, this is the only house
that wasn't robbed.
Sir, may we ask you some questions?
Why are you CHA fellas here again?
How did you know
we were from the CHA?
I distinctly rememberly
how you mistreated me.
Have you forgotten already?
Mistreated?
So what do you want? Is this about
the “Myungshimbogam” again?
And how did you know that?
How many times do I have to
repeat myself? It's at the CHA.
I keep telling you that it wasn't robbed...
...because it's safe at the CHA,
thanks to Mr. Bumsang Kim.
This is the first time we've heard this. What do you mean you keep telling us?
Goodness, are you pulling
an old man's leg?
You sent some men this morning, and they asked me questions about my copy.
So why do you keep showing up
and asking the same questions?
Sir, wait a moment. A CHA employee came by? This morning?
Yes.
They're not picking up at the Preservation Science Lab?
Yah, maybe they're out for lunch.
Yes, Chief. I was going to call you
and tell you something.
What? The men who stolen the books are targeting the CHA?
I'll give you the specifics later.
First check up on the book.
Hurry. Go to the CHA. Hurry.
Bumsang, how long
until we reach the CHA?
Ten minutes if you're willing to
pay the speeding ticket.
Okay, step on it.
No one's in?
Let's call security.
What's going on?
Yes, yes, I understand.
The museum sent someone.
Security at the museum will be tighter, so it'll be safe there.
Is this really an authentic work by Prince Ahnpyeong?
See this seal that reads “Cheongji?”
It's the penname
that Prince Ahnpyeong used.
It's definitely the “Bihaedangjib.”
Oh my, then it'll be designated
a national treasure in no time.
To think I was the one who restored it...
Now that we've seen it,
we should get going.
Excuse me?
How can I help you?
I'm from the museum.
Ah, yes.
Then, we'll be off.
Is the “Bihaedangjib” a family heirloom of yours? Why are you so deeply moved?
I'm not.
I saw everything.
You were on the verge of tears.
Where does this bottomless affection
for cultural assets come from?
What? Are you picking a fight again? Huh?
You're so clearly overreacting,
that's why.
Yo, Jonggyu.
Hey, Bumsang.
What are you doing here?
I heard the “Bihaedangjib” was found. The museum sent me.
What?
I'm from the museum.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America
All cultural assets and individuals
that appear in this program have been altered to fit fictional situations.
Said cultural assets and organizations have no real-life associations
with this drama.
Hey!
Are you crazy? How could you jump
in front of a moving car?
Ah, are you okay?
Say what?
The license plate was 4885. 4885.
Huh, she's perfectly fine.