Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Let me ask you one thing.
What?
You weren't attracted to me
at all up to now? Not even once?
I've never, not even once,
been attracted to you, so don't worry.
You're telling the truth?
Yes, I'm telling the truth.
I swear to God, not even once.
And never in the future either,
so don't worry.
Never in the future either, you say?
Of course.
There, I'm all done. Let's go.
How about now?
Feel anything towards me now?
What do you
think you're doing?
Well, I did expect a slap in return.
So go ahead and hit me.
Take your best shot.
I've already readied myself for it.
Hey! Hey, kid!
What's taking Joohyun
so long? I'm worried.
Why are you asking me?
I don't get why I'm stuck here.
Maybe we should
take her to the hospital?
What the...
Joohyun, are you okay?
Are you really done?
Nothing more to push out, right?
Mr. Nah!
It's bad manners to say
something like that to a lady.
Let's go.
- Joohyun!
- Oh my god, are you serious?
Joohyun!
What if it's serious?
Darnit...
Where are you going? Hey!
C'mon, let's talk about this.
Did I look that easy to you?
What?
Did I look so easy that
you would kiss me as a joke?
I don't know what you think of me,
but take your nonsense elsewhere.
Hey, hold on.
Don't you dare lay a finger on me
from now on. I won't take it sitting down.
Why couldn't she hit me
when I was ready for it?
Hey, isn't that Chohee?
Chohee! Chohee!
That was a total diss.
When I become chief, I'm going to
make sure she learns her manners.
Hey, isn't that Bumsang?
Bumsang! Bumsang!
Another diss.
How long is Joohyun planning to take? We'll be here all night, I tell you.
Think about how much pain
she's in. You're so inconsiderate.
[This blue and white porcelain piece was drawn with paints made with cobalt...]
Oh? Sis, you're home.
[...covered to create the special
blue design of this porcelain piece.]
[And there's another reason this blue
and white porcelain piece is so valuable.]
That crazy bastard...
Isn't Mr. Kim cool? Even guys think that, so imagine what the ladies must think.
Sis, is he really
that good-looking in real life?
Good-looking, my butt.
Why are you watching that crap?
What are you doing?
I was enjoying the show.
Did something happen?
She's acting weird.
Anyway, he's not as good-looking as me, but he holds his own pretty well.
Crazy bastard. Evil jerk.
She didn't even
bother to listen to me.
Ow, it split open even more.
Dude, why in the world
did you do that?
The weather totally sucks.
Jingook?
Yeah?
If I could, I would send
all the art thieves a memo.
Saying what?
To take a break from stealing in the second and fourth quarters of each year.
Every time it feels like we can take a breather, they cause trouble again.
Look at the bright side. The more they steal, the more chances for a promotion.
What an optimist you are.
So who's coming from the CHA today?
Chohee and Joohyun.
Ms. Joohyun?
Coming to keep an eye on Chohee ‘cause Bumsang is coming, eh?
Your deductive reasoning skills
are exceptional.
How long have I been a cop?
Fifteen years.
What's he talking about, fifteen years? It's too early in the morning to be lying.
Wait up.
Look what
happened to the shovel.
Looks like they drank alcohol, too.
Hi, Chohee.
You startled me.
When is Bumsang coming?
How would I know?
Why are you snapping at me?
Did something happen between you two again? Oh, oh, your expression changed.
Didn't you say last time that you gave up on him? So how could you do this?
I feel insulted.
Bumsang!
Considering the excavation site
and the Gobe fragments...
it seems likely earthenware from the early Paekche period were excavated.
I have a question.
Shoot.
How'd you get so beat up?
Excuse me?
Last night some punks were picking on
a student. I couldn't just do nothing.
Oh my, oh my, so in other words you fought seventeen of them by yourself?
What?
I mean, otherwise there's no way you would've gotten so beaten up, right?
Yes, right. It was too dark to count ‘em, but I knew instinctively there were a lot.
You're so amazing.
With your crusade for a just society, you'll run the cops here out of a job.
Just accept it.
Can I speak to you
privately for a moment?
Sure, why not?
Seventeen? Why didn't you just tell them that Yonggu beat the crap out of you?
Oh right, you don't want them to know that you have history with Yonggu, right?
Hey, aren't you the one who
wanted to put the past behind us?
I did say that, but everything
you do reminds me of the past.
Yeah, so what
do you want me to do?
First thing we do at an excavation theft site is dig up the hole the thieves filled.
I already know that.
So start digging.
Say what?
Repent while you dig. Repent the atrocity you committed against me.
Here.
Work hard.
No, wait...
Where did that woman go?
- Bumsang.
Ah, yes?
You offered to dig instead of us?
Don't worry about it.
And last time you offered to go
through the old books by yourself.
It's no big deal.
You're such an admirable person.
I agree.
Drink this while you work.
Thank you!
When compared to the crime scene photo, the hole's about the right size.
That means one person
dug it at a time.
Officer Cho, how long
do you think it took?
For how long did Bumsang dig?
Around three hours?
So if we assume he took turns with the lookout, it was done by more or less...
Three men.
Three men? At most.
Excellent. Let's go.
Good work.
Hey, Bumsang, good job.
Now fill the hole back up.
What?
Don't you understand Korean?
Fill it back up with dirt.
Hey, no way, I can't do it.
I'm climbing out now.
Finish up the job
before coming out.
Hey, my hand... Ease up.
Then I'll let you finish up.
Hey, hey!
What the! Argh!
Bumsang, you must be so tired.
Your clothes are all ruined.
It was hard work, but worthwhile.
Bumsang, thank you for
all the shoveling you did today.
Ah, would you like a soda?
Or do you not drink sodas?
I'll take that.
Bumsang!
Chohee, why does it break my heart
to watch him walk away?
It breaks your heart?
Well, it gives me a headache.
Chohee, you just came in?
And Joohyun, too.
Chief, did you forget that
I asked you not to speak to me?
Why must you
always bother me so?
Chohee, I'm going in first.
Joohyun's under
the impression that I like her.
I'm not sure how I should
act around her. What should I do?
Hmm, from what
I know about Joohyun...
Yeah?
There's no solution.
What?
Until she runs out of steam, she won't listen to a single word anyone tells her.
Gosh...
Why does she think I like her?
It's so troublesome.
By the way, didn't you say
there's someone you like?
Excuse me?
Who is it? It can't be Bumsang.
Is it someone I know?
Oh, no.
You don't know him at all.
Yeah? What's he like?
What's he like...
He's a strong and
very warmhearted person.
But he has so much sadness in
his heart that there's no room for me.
I don't know who he is,
but he's a fool.
Not being able to recognize you
for the genuine person you are.
He is a fool. A real fool.
Chief, what are you doing?
Oh, hold on.
I've never won a doll
at this game before.
You've played it a lot, huh?
Yeah... hold on, hold on.
Oh wow.
Here! This is for the dinner
you just bought. Here, take it.
No, it's okay.
Give it to Jiyoon.
My daughter's doll is right there.
The bigger one?
Yeah, the brown one.
Jiyoon loves teddy bears. So take it.
Okay.
I'm very good at this.
The store in my neighborhood
went bankrupt because of me.
Look. All right!
Ugh, it's freezing...
Jonggyu?
Was the alumni association
gathering today?
Hey, I can't make it. I'm suffering from fatigue after digging all day yesterday.
No, I'm serious.
I really did dig.
With a shovel! Don't you know what a shovel is? A shovel, you jerk! Hang up.
Aw man, there's nothing to eat.
Except anchovies.
So the donation ceremony for the “Bihaedangjib” is going to be held here?
Yes. It'll be exhibited at the museum
as soon as the ceremony's over.
All your hard work paid off,
didn't it, Chohee?
I didn't do much...
When you're happy,
it's okay to express it, kid.
You're right, I'm thrilled.
I'm heading out then.
She looks pretty happy.
She should be, considering her father.
Chohee!
Chohee, is it true that
Bumsang is out sick today?
He didn't make it to work?
He didn't.
I heard he's really si...
You didn't know?
Nope, this is news to me.
Thank you.
Hey, how could you come the emergency room for a petty thing like a cold?
I had chills earlier and really
thought I was going to die.
You know me.
Once I'm sick, I really suffer.
I don't know about that, but I do know that no one exaggerates like you do.
Get a shot of nutrients
before you leave.
Hey, go easy on me.
[Chohee Heo]
Chohee?
Hey, you're faking it
right now, aren't you?
Faking it?
You can't fool me. Come to work before
I embarrass you in front of everyone.
Hey, Chohee,
I'm in the ER right now.
The ER?
Yes, and I have to go in for an examination now so I'll talk to you later.
Hello? Hey!
Hey!
Hey, if you have some bandages,
wrap up my hand, will you?
Why do you need bandages?
Stop asking questions
and just do it.
Whew, what are you up to now?
What a total kid he is.
Chohee, hey.
Bumsang.
What's wrong with your hand?
How could you ask when
you're the one who stepped on it?
What?
The cold is one thing, but apparently
you fractured my finger.
Fractured your finger?
The hand is vital to a person
who does restoration work.
How will I make a living now?
That's strange.
I swear I didn't step on it that hard.
A fracture...
I'm really sorry.
What's done is done.
I'm going to go home
and get some rest.
Yeah, hurry home and rest.
But who knows if I can
drive with this hand.
Me?
Can you?
I'm so dizzy, all of a sudden.
Whoa, the room's totally spinning.
Hey, are you okay?
Your fever seems to be gone.
Hey, hey. Why are you
pretending to be nice now?
Did you eat something?
Eat what? I didn't eat
anything since last night.
You have nothing to eat here?
You should eat something.
There's nothing to eat
in a bachelor's pad.
And with this hand...
I'm not hungry.
You need to eat to regain your strength. You want me to order something?
No, doesn't sound very appetizing.
If you really want me to eat,
maybe we should cook something?
Cook?
Yeah, maybe some kimchi stew
or something. And make it spicy.
Hey, are you saying you want me
to cook kimchi stew for you?
I think my appetite
is coming back at the thought.
Fine, I'll cook kimchi stew for you.
Hey, hey, there's pork in the freezer.
Put that in and make it spicy.
All right, I'll cook.
You get some shut-eye.
Chief Kang, thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- No problem.
The food here at the CHA
is always so good.
Why are you so unproductive
when you eat such delicious food?
Aren't you ashamed?
So you let Mr. Kim get away because
you eat bad food at your office?
What did you say?
What's up with you two?
You always argue when you meet.
Let's all calm down.
Yeah, stop it, you two.
Can you guys head back and write up those reports about the Yeoju case?
I'll head back later.
Okay.
- I'm warning you...
- Whatever...
- Have you had lunch?
- Oh, I'm on a diet.
Oh.
Whew, it's better
not to run into her.
Oh hey, Joohyun.
Why did you ignore me
when you saw me?
Because last time you
told me not to speak to you.
I said not to speak to me.
When did I tell you to ignore me?
Are you looking down on me?
No. No, why would I do that?
The thing is...
Okay! Fine.
If that's not the case,
then can I ask for a favor?
A favor?
What is it?
Hey, why are you snooping around
in someone else's house?
I'm just looking around.
Hey, are these your grandparents?
Yeah. My grandfather
made all the pottery here.
Oh... your grandfather is a potter?
He's a vigorous old man who spent
his entire life immersed in clay.
Hey, why did you stuff
this one down here?
It's a fake.
It's a fake?
There was an antique store
I frequented when I was in college.
The owner's daughter was really pretty. So I bought one to impress her.
I think I paid around
eight hundred dollars for it.
Eight hundred dollars? You're crazy.
You were reckless, weren't you?
But it turned out that, ha,
she was a married woman.
For real?
Yeah.
And I really liked her, too.
I told you it's a fake.
Why are you putting it up there?
So what if it's a fake?
I think that if an item holds a special memory, it's no longer a fake.
Isn't that why you kept it?
Hey, the food's all ready.
Let's go. Let's eat.
Here.
Oh!
There, I cooked and here's
your stew. Can I leave now?
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
I can't eat with this hand. Feed me first.
You can eat with your left hand.
Here!
Tch... Fine.
I'll feed you. Here!
Open your mouth wider. Ah.
Hey!
“Ah!”
Fine. It's fine, I tell you.
I'll eat on my own.
Look at you.
Here!
Listen to me as you eat.
I admit I was wrong in doing that to your hand. But you did something wrong, too.
It isn't right to kiss
someone you don't even like.
Hey, are you lecturing me
in my vulnerable state?
I'm being serious here.
I wanted to tell you this.
I understand what you're trying to say, but I'm not the type to kiss just anyone.
Then why did you kiss me?
You don't like me in that way.
Of course I don't.
Think I've lost my marbles?
The reason I kissed you was...
Yeah?
- Isn't that Chief Kang and Joohyun?
- What?
Oh no! What's going on?
You think I'd know?
What brings them here?
Chief Kang can't know that I'm here.
He absolutely can't know, okay?
Why “absolutely” can't he know?
Just know that he can't.
Isn't there anywhere to hide? No?
Why isn't he opening the door?
Oh no!
Do you think he's unconscious?
Is he that sick?
So I heard.
Anyway, thank you
for coming with me, Chief.
No problem. I should have come
anyway since Bumsang's sick.
But why did you want me
to come with you?
Why do you ask?
You didn't want to come with me?
That's not what I mean.
You like Bumsang.
This is a good opportunity for you two
to be alone. I don't want to ruin things.
No, no.
You're thinking about it all wrong.
Bumsang is a man, after all.
A very passionate man, at that.
I'm here to pay him a visit,
not to stir up his feelings for me.
Hello, Bumsang!
Here, flowers!
I'm relieved you're not that sick.
I was so worried about you.
You must be very uncomfortable.
The weather's hot, too.
Oh, this? Don't worry.
I'm taking it off tomorrow.
Why did you do
all that shoveling yesterday?
Someone like you who needs
to protect the hands shouldn't shovel.
Definitely shouldn't shovel.
Joohyun, do you realize how many
times you said the word “shovel?”
Oh, I didn't mean to babble on.
Don't worry. I did do
a lot of shoveling, after all.
If I knew we were coming, I would've asked Chohee to join us. It's too bad.
I'll tell her to come
visit you sometime.
Sure...
Why is Chief Kang here?
Darnit, what to do?
Why is it so hot in here?
Ugh, I'm so hot.
What the! Bumsang, you pervert.
This is a padded bra...
Jeez...
I knew it, the perv.
Bumsang, I think
your phone is ringing?
Um, I don't think so.
No, I heard a phone ring.
From that direction.
No.
You heard wrong.
Ah, it must be the neighbor's.
The walls are terribly thin here.
That's not it. I definitely
heard it from over there...
No, no. Please stay seated.
I'll bring out some refreshments.
No, Bumsang. I'll do it.
I'm the host.
No, please stay here.
You have a hurt hand.
Then...
How did he cook with a hurt hand?
Two sets of chopsticks. Two cups.
Was he with a woman?
Hey...
Joohyun,
what are you looking for?
What? Oh, I'm just checking out
your home. It's so nicely decorated.
Checking out my home?
Yes.
Uh, wait...
Aren't you being rude?
You're the one being rude.
Stop coming between Bumsang and me.
I think you're way out of line here. Bumsang, we'll be leaving now.
What?
So soon?
Yes, you seem to be perfectly well.
Joohyun, we should let
Bumsang get some rest.
Joohyun, leaving already?
Please take care of yourself,
and we'll see you tomorrow.
Bumsang?
Take care. See you later.
Okay. It's a pity
you can't stay longer.
Hey, they're gone.
They left?
That was a close one.
What in the world was that?
You were in such a panic that you made me nervous, too. Come out, already.
I swear there was
a woman in there.
Let's assume there was. Why cause embarrassment for everyone?
She'd be the only one embarrassed.
It was a good chance to reform Bumsang's loose ways.
Look here, Joohyun.
Chief Kang, you're quite
an interesting character.
You act like you gave up on me, yet
here you are showing your true colors.
Are we talking about this again?
I mean, why else would you grab
my hand like that in front of Bumsang?
I knew I shouldn't have asked
you to come with me.
Enough already. I'm headed back
to the CHA. You want a ride or not?
No way. You think I'd ride your car after what just happened? I'm cabbing it.
Hey, do you like
Chief Kang that much?
What?
What are you talking about?
It's practically written on your face.
“I like him so much.”
Stop talking total nonsense.
Why else would you hide like that?
You could've told him you were visiting.
That was just...
Hey, you shouldn't be ashamed to
like someone. It's a natural emotion.
Then again, I would have never
expected you to be like this.
What?
I thought you didn't give guys the time
of day. So you are a woman after all.
Eh, whatever. I'm leaving.
What was it?
Hey, how do you open this?
I'll do it for you.
Yeah, you do it.
Okay.
Bumsang, I left my car keys here.
Chohee?
Chief!
Chief, the truth is,
what really happened is...
It's okay, you don't have to explain.
But I admit I'm a little taken aback.
You could've just told me honestly
last time that you really do like him.
No, that's not it. I came
because it's my fault he's hurt.
Anyway, it's not what you think,
so please believe me, Chief.
Okay, I believe you. I believe you,
but isn't this how love starts?
You cook for him,
worry about him when he's sick...
hold his hand, check his forehead
for a fever, things like that.
I remember that's
how things started for me.
Liking someone is an exhilarating feeling. So don't be embarrassed.
No matter whom you like,
whether it's Bumsang or someone else.
It's you.
The person I like is you,
not Bumsang. It's you.
Oh my god.
Oh god, what did I just do?
Oh god, what am I going to do?
Oh no! Oh no...
[Your call has been transferred...]
Argh, she's not picking up again.
This is so frustrating!
Whatever. It's not like I wanted
the whole thing to happen.
Hey, it's pretty good.
Argh, this is so uncomfortable.
Daddy!
Hey, it's my little girl!
Come here!
Did you have fun
at kindergarten today?
Yup.
Aren't you going to give
me a kiss? Once more.
Ah, scratchy.
You're home.
Hello, Mother. Why are you
outside at this late hour?
Jiyoon couldn't sleep so we were playing at the playground. Did you have dinner?
Of course.
Let's go in, Mother.
Daddy, this is Cinderella, these are the stepsisters and this is the glass slipper.
And the prince will announce that he'll marry the owner of the slipper, right?
Right.
- Is that so?
- Jiyoon.
Time for bed. Come on,
Grandma will tuck you in. Let's go.
Don't wanna.
I wanna play with Daddy.
Daddy, can we play
just a little bit more? Please?
Sure, let's do that.
Mother, you can go to bed.
I'll tuck Jiyoon in later.
Daddy's the best.
Jiyoon, Daddy's tired so don't
keep him up too late, okay?
Okay, Grandma.
Don't worry.
Good night.
Ah, I almost forgot, Daddy.
I drew you today.
You did?
Yup.
Let's have a look.
Wow, you drew this?
Yup.
And this is me?
And...
This is Mommy.
Looks just like her, doesn't it?
Wow, it really looks like her.
Why does the investigations team lack such basics? Especially Officer Cho.
What did they do to claim
“All for one and one for all.”
And insist on attending
the donation ceremony?
That's what I'm saying. After all, we're the ones who found the “Bihaedangjib.”
Right.
Joohyun, what do you think
about Officer Cho's motto?
Joohyun?
Yes?
(All for one and one for all.)
Ah, you're talking about that?
Let me take Chief Kang
and Bumsang for example.
They love the same woman, so how can we talk about all for one and one for all?
It's impossible.
Yup, totally impossible.
When is the museum bringing over
the “Bihaedangjib” tomorrow?
Oh, Chohee's in charge of that.
Hey, where did
she disappear to now?
Um, Chief? What I said
yesterday shocked you, right?
I don't know why I said that to you.
I shouldn't have said it.
You don't have to worry about it.
So just forget all about it.
Yes, please forget
I ever said anything.
When I was dating Jiyoon's mom,
she always used to say something to me.
She said I was tactless, slow
and never understood how she felt.
I'm like that.
I admit I was shocked to hear
what you said yesterday.
And I felt really sorry to you.
And truthfully, I was a little happy.
Being loved by someone
is an exhilarating feeling.
And you're such a good person.
But I don't think I'm ready
to start a new love, not yet.
I'm sorry, Chohee, to have
to refuse your feelings like this.
No, please don't be.
Why should you be?
I shouldn't have said
all that in the first place.
Like I said earlier,
please don't worry about it.
I have to attend the morning
meeting so I'll be going first.
Sir!
We heard you were very sick.
Are you okay now?
Yes, I'm fine.
And we heard that
you hurt your hand?
It's this hand.
Are you okay?
Sir, if you have any trouble
typing or anything like that...
Um, my hand... Ow...
Oh, I'm sorry.
You can come to me anytime.
I will help you.
Thank you.
No, sir. I will help you.
Quiet. Sir,
I'm the best at typing.
Let me show you.
I'm typing now.
Sir, this is what I call
the “eagle typing” technique.
I can type a thousand
characters a minute.
Then who is the best?
I am!
Hey! What happened yesterday?
You didn't pick up your phone.
Things didn't work out well
with Chief Kang?
Guys should be more
understanding than that...
Should I explain things to him? That there's nothing going on between us?
It's fine.
There's no need for that.
Something really
did happen, didn't it?
By any chance did
he reject you? Is that it?
That's not it.
Hey, you realize
this is not my fault, right?
He already felt like that, so I don't
have to feel sorry to you, right?
Yeah, why should you be apologetic?
I should be thanking you.
For bringing my pathetic one-sided
crush to an end. I should be grateful.
I'll see you later.
She really liked him, didn't she?
I thought she'd be all over me for faking my injury. But she doesn't even care.
[Chairman Jang]
You work for the CHA these days?
I heard you were the one who verified the “Bihaedangjib” at my party.
Yes, it's true. I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't call you here
to scold you, so relax.
I called you here because of this.
I couldn't find another person
quite as talented as you are.
Did this piece come into Korea
through Dandong, China?
How did you know?
It's now a public fact that North Korea's authentic items come through Dandong.
So there tends to be
a lot of well-made pieces.
Are you absolutely sure?
Didn't you call me here because
you were already suspicious?
Yes, that's true.
I've valued this item for a long time. What a pity. Should I just break it?
Is it really necessary to do that?
I might be speaking out of place...
but are are people who value
fake items suffused with memories...
as highly as authentic items.
It's actually quite well made. If you used to value it, then I suggest keeping it.
As a person
who values only the best...
I never thought I'd hear
you say something like that.
Don't feel I was unjust in calling you here simply because there was no one else.
Not at all. Please call me
whenever you need me.
I'll keep that in mind.
By the way, about Congressman Lee's “Bihaedangjib.” Is it authentic?
Yes, I'm sure of it. It'll probably be designated a national treasure soon.
A national treasure.
I wonder if it will come to that?
What did he mean by that?
But I don't think I'm ready
to start a new love, not yet.
I'm sorry, Chohee, to have
to refuse your feelings like this.
[Bumsang Kim]
What do you want?
[Whatcha doing?]
Just lying here.
Hey, it's not the end of the world.
Why are you so listless?
If you're trying to pick
a fight with me, I'm hanging up.
Do you want me
to buy you a drink?
No.
Fine, then.
I'm just trying to comfort you.
Hey, if you want to comfort me,
sing me a song.
Sing a song?
Your singing amuses me.
Sing that song. What was it?
“If~” that song.
It'll help me laugh a bit. Yeah?
Fine, I'll sing.
If it's a person you
have to forget, then...
Hey, blockhead, you really sang
'cause I told you to?
You're the one who asked me to. Who cares if you're listless? I'm hanging up.
What?
What is it now?
No, it's just that...
That did comfort me a lot.
[Good night.]
Hey, wait up.
What?
About the “Bihaedangjib.”
What about it?
Never mind. I'll see you tomorrow
at the ceremony. I'm hanging up.
Nothing will happen, right?
Jingook?
Yeah?
Why do the CHA boys
lack the basics?
What now?
I repeatedly taught them the mindset of “All for one and one for all.”
Yet there's not a single call
wondering where we are...
how we're getting there
and if we're even coming.
Who cares if they're not calling us? They'll probably buy dinner after, right?
If they buy pork ribs again,
I'm going to turn the CHA upside down.
It's time to go.
Hey, can the two of you
go without me?
Why? You're not going?
I have some things to take care of.
You're acting strangely.
Did someone at the CHA offend you?
What?
Who is it?
Was it the delusional Joohyun?
The rude Mr. Nah?
Sangho Lee? Who?
Officer Cho, why did
you leave Chohee out?
Hey, punk. You think Chohee
would offend Chief Kang?
Dogs will bite
the hand that feed them.
Punk, what do you mean by that?
Am I wrong? Am I?
That's enough. Let's head over
as soon as I take care of some things.
Did you just say “bonus?”
And extra vacation time,
on top of that?
And the director will also give us
enough for a grand dinner tonight.
Wow, this isn't a dream, is it?
Okay.
Now, now, we don't have
much time so let's hurry.
Yes, sir. Hurry!
Where's Chohee?
Chohee? She's working on the program for the ceremony. Should I go get her?
No. I'll call her.
Get back to work.
Yes, sir!
Hello, this is Jeongpil Noh.
Congressman Lee, what brings
you here without prior notice?
It's not because...
Joohyun, can you look
through these for me?
You're leaving now?
You begged to be on the guest list
and you're going to be tardy?
Bad news, bad news.
Congressman Lee is here
to take "The “Bihaedangjib" away.
What are you talking about?
How can he take it away?
He's claiming a good faith purchase.
A good faith purchase.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America