Cultural assets and individuals in this
program have been altered fictionally.
They have no real-life
associations with this drama.
Joohyun, can you
look through these for me?
You're leaving now?
You begged to be on the guest list
and you're going to be tardy?
Bad news, bad news.
The “Bihaedangjib.”
Congressman Lee is here
to take it away.
What are you talking about?
How can he take it away?
He's claiming a good faith purchase.
A good faith purchase.
So what exactly
is a good faith purchase?
And you call yourself
a CHA employee?
For items bought without prior knowledge of it being a stolen item...
the sale is considered valid.
But why is he allowed to take it?
He didn't even report it stolen.
Congressman, please
reconsider what you're doing.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Chief. Is he really taking it?
Please hold on.
Please give back the “Bihaedangjib.”
You can't take it.
What did you say?
You don't deserve to take it back.
What in the world are you saying?
It was mine in the first place,
so who are you to tell what I deserve?
You bought it knowing
it was an illegal book.
Isn't that the reason you didn't
report it when it was stolen?
What? How dare you,
you impudent woman!
Sir, please just leave.
Let go.
Do you know who I am?
Of course I do.
You're Congressman Junpil Lee.
As a congressman chosen by the people, do you realize what you're doing?
Enough of your cheek,
and go mind your own business.
Of all the bad luck,
I have people like you attacking me.
If you step out of line one more time,
I won't just let it go. Understand?
And you call yourself
a congressman?
What did you say?
You should be embarrassed.
You should be ashamed.
You little...
I won't stand here and take this!
Congressman Lee,
I suggest you leave quietly.
How dare you!
Your conscience isn't clear either. We'll let you go, so take good care of the book.
Chief Oh.
I'll remember this.
I'll take care to remember
today's events as well.
This isn't right, Chief.
This isn't why we found the book.
I understand how you feel.
But what can we do?
You know our hands are tied.
No. I don't know.
I don't know any of that, Chief.
He can't do this, Chief.
Chohee.
I'm sorry, sir.
If it's a person
you have to forget...
Wait, why is this song
stuck in my head? Jeez...
Chohee!
Hey, Chohee!
Did he really take it away?
The “Bihaedangjib”...
Bumsang, bad news,
major bad news!
Joohyun, what happened?
Congressman Lee came by and
took the “Bihaedangjib” with him.
What?
What are we going to do? You went through so much trouble to get it.
What about Chohee?
What? I'm not sure.
I heard she went against Congressman Lee, but I'm not sure where she is.
Help me find the “Bihaedangjib.”
I found Mr. Kim for you. And the “Bihaedangjib.” And I saved your life.
How are you gonna
repay me for all this?
It'll take your entire life...
Why are you crying?
You didn't do anything wrong,
so stop being a fool.
It's none of your business.
Butt out!
I'm going to get it back.
No matter what, I'll get it back.
How are you going to do that?
What's your plan?
Gonna steal it, like those scum?
Yeah. Whatever it takes,
I'll get it back.
Stop it already! Just stop!
You already did enough, so stop it, okay? It can't be helped, so just give up.
Bumsang, you don't
understand how I feel.
You don't know why I'm acting like this,
and what that book means to me.
You'll never understand.
I do, I understand!
Your father is “General Shovel.”
Taesoo Heo.
How do you know that?
I understand that you want to return
the items he stole to their rightful places.
But if I were your father,
I wouldn't want you living like this.
That was your father's life,
and your life is your own.
You did the best you could.
Does he think he's a untouchable?
He dares to claim a good faith purchase!
How dare they rip the book into two like mere tissue? It was so hard finding it.
We can't let him get away with this, for the sake of the country and our future.
What region voted that bastard into office? I'll set them on fire, I will!
He was elected by
proportional representation.
What...
a total bastard.
We should be grateful
he's keeping it safe in the country.
At least he didn't take it abroad.
But this is just too much.
I've lost all motivation to work.
This isn't the first time
this happened, so let it go.
Chief, are you leaving?
Yeah, don't drink too much
and go home early.
Yes, sir. Goodbye!
Darnit...
Chief! Will you be okay?
You drank a lot.
I must be getting old.
I'm not even angry.
I know that you're
the most upset out of all of us.
No, that would be Chohee.
She's probably very depressed.
You seem to take a special interest
in Chohee and her matters.
I told you.
I have a bit of a debt.
Go on in.
Sangho, go get some water.
Get it yourself.
Punk, I'm your senior...
Ow, my head.
Ugh, I drank way too much.
Ow, my head is spinning.
I really hate the defeatist
attitude in this office!
While you were drinking and whining last night, I made an important decision.
A decision?
I will have my revenge against Congressman Lee.
Revenge?
For the sake of the lost bonus,
the lost extra vacation time...
and Bumsang's trampled honor.
I absolutely must do something.
I will avenge everyone.
- Joohyun.
- What?
Your necklce is beautiful.
So is the bracelet.
You guys have good taste.
This and this,
they're part of a set.
Oh my, I don't have
time to waste time here.
I have to get the investigations team's
consent. Then, I'll be on my way...
A set, she says.
The bigger problem is that
we're part of a set with her.
General Shovel?
He went missing seven years ago.
Some say he stowed away to China or that he was buried alive while digging.
Everyone has his own opinion.
But he's most likely dead and gone.
Bumsang!
Hey, Joohyun.
Are you okay? I was so upset that
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
You couldn't?
By the way, is Chohee in yet?
Ah, Chohee...
Wait, why do you ask?
What?
Why do you keep asking about her,
both yesterday and today?
Did I?
By any chance...
No, no.
She's in charge of the “Bihaedangjib” case. I'm just worried as a colleague.
A colleague?
That's it, right?
I forgot about your strong sense
of camaraderie and philanthropy.
Chohee took a leave
of absence today.
A leave of absence?
Yes.
She's a bit disloyal for taking time off while everyone's under so much duress.
But what can you do?
Wow, wow!
Sis, what's all this?
Is today a special day?
No, it's not. I just woke up early and decided to do a little cooking. Try it.
You're acting strangely.
Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
Then what's up?
You take a day off though you usually never do, and then you cook a feast.
You don't want to eat?
You want me to clear the table?
No, who said
I didn't want to eat?
Thank you for the meal.
Is it good?
By the way, Sis, did the ceremony for
the “Bihaedangjib” go well yesterday?
Yeah, of course it went well.
Then it'll be exhibited at the museum soon? I'm going to go see it then.
Hey, didn't you say you had
a morning class? Hurry up and eat.
I'm so full.
Who could it be?
Who is it?
Bumsang!
As expected you live in squalor.
Hey, what brings you here?
You think you have the time
to take a day off and bum around?
What?
A big case happens and you're
stuffed up in your house. C'mon, hurry!
What case?
Ah, you talk too much.
Hurry up and come out.
Hey, hey.
Come on out first.
Goodness!
Tell me what case it is!
Gosh, you're noisy.
Just come with me.
Hey, Bumsang!
Jeez, pipe down, will you?
Get in the car.
Get it, come on.
- You...
- Get in already.
- You're really not going to tell...
- Quiet, please.
Hey!
I'm not in the mood for your jokes today. Why did you bring me here?
To get some fresh air.
What?
What good is being stuffed up in the house? It's better to get a little sun.
Well, I never...
Hey, I brought you here for some fresh air, so don't get any other ideas.
Huh? Chief Kang!
Oh, hey!
What brings you here?
I heard Chohee took a leave of absence, but I couldn't get in contact with her.
That's strange. She's not home?
She went out without
even clearing the table?
She left her phone, too.
This is so strange. Sis!
Man, she's really
acting strangely today.
She was really upset, wasn't she?
Excuse me?
She would be.
I knew she'd be upset.
Did something happen to my sister?
What is it?
Your sister went through a lot to find
something called the “Bihaedangjib”...
but someone took it away, claiming
it to be a good faith purchase.
She must be going through a hard time, both yesterday and today.
So that's what happened.
That's why she was acting strangely.
Have you been well, sir?
Thanks to you.
There are a lot
of priests here today.
Sir, I'll be right back.
World Peace. I hope
everyone's wishes come true.
Please help me hit the jackpot.
Daddy, please stay healthy...
Did you say this was
the Bomun Shrine? It's a great place.
Do you come here often?
Once in a while.
When I've got a lot on my mind.
Since when did you know
about my father?
Ah, remember the day
you wore that rented black dress?
The day of the party?
No wonder. I was curious as to
why you decided to show up.
Hey, Chohee?
Yeah?
Aren't you curious
as to why I brought you here?
I guess.
Look over there. I brought you here
for some extreme training.
You want me to climb those stairs? What's at the top?
Buddha.
A very benevolent
looking Buddha is there.
He'll grant you one wish
for climbing the stairs.
What's your wish?
A wish?
I don't know.
I don't have any.
Everyone has at least one wish.
Did you ever go up there?
Of course.
Did your wish come true?
No. He apparently
discriminates against people.
Maybe because I'm Catholic?
What was your wish?
My wish?
My wish was...
The unification of the Koreas.
Uh huh...
If you choose to ascend the stairs, I will contribute a bottle of water to the cause.
Here. I must go have a meaningful
talk with with the head priest.
Oh, and when you reach the top,
you'll see the surprise I prepared for you.
Look forward to it. It's big.
You know how generous I am.
You need to go greet your parents.
Yes.
Let's go.
I understand that you want to return
the items he stole to their rightful places.
But if I were your father,
I wouldn't want you living like this.
Don't look for Dad anymore.
I know you joined the regulations team to find your father, but stop that now.
No news from him in seven years means he's no longer a man of this world.
- Chohee.
- What is all this?
Give them back.
Give them back to their owners!
Chohee, this is
the last time. Really.
So forgive me
just this once, okay?
You always say that it's the last time. You always want me to forgive you.
I won't forgive you. Go plead
forgiveness to my dead mother.
And put everything you stole back in their rightful places. Take it all back!
Or I'll never see your face again.
Never, I tell you!
You think you'll find traces of your father while looking for the “Bihaedangjib?”
Is that why you're trying to find it?
You're barking up
the wrong tree, Uncle.
I don't want to find him at all.
I don't care if he's dead or alive.
Daddy, don't leave!
Daddy, don't leave. Daddy!
Chohee, don't worry.
I'll come back home.
I promise to come back.
Daddy, don't leave.
‘I have a wish that
I cannot speak aloud to anyone.'
‘It's okay if he never
comes back to see us.'
‘Please, just let him be alive.'
What? Congressman Lee
took back the “Bihaedangjib?”
Those CHA jerks must
be pissed out of their minds.
I can practically hear
their unhappy cries from here.
Ah, sir, didn't you say that Bumsang Kim's leg was snapped into two?
I did.
That's strange. He was on TV yesterday and he was walking around just fine.
What?
What happened?
See, the thing is...
That Bumsang Kim is
one hell of a lucky guy.
I was about to really give it to him
when that Chohee Heo appeared.
So I gave him a double
nosebleed, like bam!
Why did I expect
any better from you?
Aw, man. How can I have my revenge
on Bumsang Kim and Chohee Heo?
If I ever run into them again,
I'll make mashed potatoes out of them.
By the way, Dongpal, did you
prepare what I asked for?
Of course. This is me you're talking to.
Dongpal Kim does things right.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Money doesn't exactly grow on trees...
I know, I know.
I won't forget this.
I won't forget your loyalty.
Yonggu.
Yes, sir?
Let's go.
Sir, are you leaving?
Sir, please take care.
Goodbye.
You got that much money to spare?
How dare you use that money?
It's bad enough I have to pick up
after your sorry butt at my age...
but now I have to help
fund a thief's escape?
Who are you calling a thief?
Do you have a death wish?
This is important business. I'm
working on behalf of the entire nation!
You want a medal?
How dare you
call my boss a thief?
I'm not going to be home today.
Lock up well, all right?
What?
You want to have revenge?
I can't just stand by
and do nothing.
If we take this opportunity to teach
Congressman Lee a lesson...
it'll be the perfect opportunity to warn
thieves against cultural asset thefts...
as well as stop this
good faith purchase nonsense.
So how do you plan on
going about this revenge?
I did some research on some incidents
Congressman Lee was involved in.
The Daegu
hostess bar case of 1999.
The Haeundae Japanese
restaurant lobby case of 2002.
The casino rebate case of 2004
and the Landa Kim case of 2007.
Do you know what's the
common factor of these cases?
In the heart of this decadent power
was a beautiful woman.
So the strategy of this plan
is the badger game.
The badger game?
So in other words, you will use your beauty to approach Congressman Lee.
Then you'll exact
your revenge somehow, right?
Precisely.
Then rather than a traditional Korean dress, you should prepare a gown.
I already did. This time it's
an original prêt-a-porter piece!
Pret...a-potty?
You don't know
what prêt-a-porter is?
Anyway, Chief, I'm ready to
dedicate everything to this mission.
Joohyun.
Do you think that plan
makes any sense at all?
Chief...
Stop wasting our time
and go back to your office! Now!
Why are you so angry?
You startled me. What did I do?
Hello, this is the investigations team. What? You saw Mr. Kim?
We're almost there.
Chief, please okay my plan.
Please!
Joohyun, stop following us
around and leave already.
If this is about my safety,
Bumsang will save me, so don't worry.
Please, let's just try.
Let's have our revenge, okay?
C'mon, Chief!
When did Mr. Kim come?
About an hour ago.
I wasn't going to say anything for my husband's sake, but he went too far.
Did he mention things like where he was going or whom he was going to meet?
No, I don't think
I heard anything like that.
What did he say?
He said he was gonna make
mashed potatoes out of someone.
Mashed potatoes?
It was someone Kim, I think?
The name ended with “Sang.”
Bumsang Kim?
That's it!
He said Bumsang Kim.
And he mentioned
some woman, too.
Something Heo, maybe?
Could it be... Chohee Heo?
Yup, that was it! Chohee Heo.
Mr. Kim said he was going to get them.
The tolling of the temple bell calls forth
a piety of proud loneliness...
You are so incredibly good-looking.
You look much better in real life
than on television.
And you're so knowledgeable.
You really do look better in real life.
I'm sorry. Please excuse me.
Can I please have a hug?
You're quite popular with
the middle-aged women.
Like that's anything new.
Did you make a wish?
I hope you didn't wish
to become my girlfriend.
Are you suffering from heatstroke?
I should say that to you, seeing how you're sweating like a pig. Let's go eat.
You're buying.
Cheapskate.
How could you leave
your wallet at home?
Hey, kid, that's your fault. I left my phone, wallet and bag all at home.
Excuses, excuses.
Instead, I'll take care of dessert.
How are you going to do that
when you don't have a penny on you?
The restaurant gives out
free ice cream. I'll be right back.
Tch!
It's good to see you smile, you kid.
Sweetie!
Oh, wow. I can't believe we ran
into each other here, of all places.
What brings you here?
Huh?
Oh, I heard you were filming here today. I came to cheer you on, why else?
Oh wow, really?
You didn't come
with a woman, did you?
No way, I don't have
a woman I'd bring with me.
What about that woman
who claimed to be pregnant?
Why are you drudging up the past -
Didn't I explain everything to you?
That woman has nothing to do with me.
Oh, right.
You said she was a stalker.
I did?
I told you she was a stalker?
No wonder. I knew
you wouldn't cheat on me.
Anyway, it's so great to meet you
here in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, I knew you'd be happy.
Sweetie, who was that?
Just now?
Don't you get those calls from annoying telecommunicators many times a day?
I should just turn off the phone.
Shall we walk a bit?
We are at the beach, after all.
He hung up. He would never
hang up on me. What's going on?
Do you think something
happened, Chief?
What's this I hear about not being able
to contact either Chohee or Bumsang?
What are we going to do, Chief?
What if Mr. Kim kidnapped them?
What?
Joohyun, how could you
say such a thing?
It's called a woman's intuition. What if something happened to my Bumsang?
Chief Kang, what do you think?
Chohee left her phone at home,
and Bumsang's was just disconnected.
It's possible that
nothing happened...
but we can't disregard the
possibility that Mr. Kim is involved.
Oh no, Chohee must've been kidnapped.
What are we going to do?
Hey, nothing's been confirmed yet.
Anyway, this is entirely the responsibility
of the investigations team!
They should've been properly protected
after the “Bihaedangjib” was found!
Why is that our fault?
It's not like we knew
this was going to happen.
Look, stop all the pessimistic thinking
and let's be levelheaded about this.
Officer Cho, check if Bumsang has been
to the university or the TV station.
Officer Park, find out if we can
locate him by tracing his cell phone.
Yes, sir.
Joohyun, try calling
Chohee's house one more time.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Where did Bumsang go?
Darnit, the ice cream is melting.
Where is he?
Yup, that's more like him.
It's all melted. Darn...
Sweetie.
Yeah?
I'm sorry, but I still
have a lot left to film.
Don't worry about me.
I have to head back soon, too. I'll just look around by myself before leaving.
But then I'll feel bad.
There's no need to feel bad.
It's good enough that I got to see you.
Sweetie...
That's it. I'm going
to cancel the rest of the shoot.
What?
You came all the way here for me.
It's the least I can do.
You can't do that.
Where's your professionalism?
And I happen to think that you look the most beautiful when you're working.
Really? Then how about I hurry
things up instead of canceling?
Hurry?
Hwayoung, we have
to start filming again!
Ah, you have to work.
Go on then.
I'll be back.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Wait for me, sweetie.
Okay, but I might leave
so don't pay any attention to me.
I'll hurry back.
Yeah, yeah, but I might leave.
Go on. Yeah, yeah. All right.
Why are you empty-handed?
Where's the ice cream?
It all melted
while you were here.
Hey, if you were planning on going
on a date, why'd you bring me along?
What are you talking about?
It's not like that.
But I saw everything.
Saw what? I was standing over there
when I coincidentally ran into her.
And I coincidentally saw you
on the beach with her.
Fine, it was a date.
I have no plans of ruining your restored
love life, so have fun on your date.
My legs are killing me, thanks to you.
I'll be going home, then.
Hey, where are you going? How are you
going to back on your own? Hey, kid!
Why talk big in the first place?
Hey, can you
lend me twenty bucks?
Twenty bucks?
I don't have money
for transportation.
And yet you were all ready to leave?
Go on, then. I'm not giving you a penny.
Then how am
I supposed to get back?
You were walking away just fine.
Or maybe you can swim back. Whatever.
Hey! Lend me twenty bucks.
Don't cling to me... Fighting!
Good luck on getting home, all right?
C'mon, lend me twenty bucks.
Don't have it.
Stop bothering me.
Then ten bucks.
Don't have ten bucks.
C'mon, lend me twenty bucks!
My dress shoes are ruined.
So what?
Just get them cleaned.
Gosh, darnit!
Hey, come here.
Kid. Come here for a sec.
This is the famous salted shrimp
from Kanghwa Island.
Lady, this is all you have?
Don't you have it in
a different color in the least?
That's all we have left.
You guys look like a couple.
Why not just dress alike?
- Who?
- What?
There's a couple here? Where?
Excuse me, is there a couple here?
What time is it?
This is an expensive shirt, darnit.
Excuse me,
can I make a phone call?
Sure.
Thank you.
Is there a way we can find out?
Officer Cho,
what did the university say?
He had no classes today.
And the TV station?
No show today, either.
What about
the trace on the phone?
Since the phone's off,
it'll take some time.
Sir, my sister will be all right, won't she?
Nothing happened to her, right?
She'll be fine.
Call Bumsang again.
Okay.
Hello?
Sis!
Is that Chohee?
Let me talk to her.
Chohee.
Oh, Chief.
Hello? Joohyun?
What? You thought I was
kidnapped along with Bumsang?
Dragged away with Chohee?
Everyone was so worried.
Chohee, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Bumsang, you're okay, right?
You're safe, right?
Of course I'm okay.
Where are you?
Bumsang, where are you?
I had some things to think about...
I came out to get some fresh air...
You're really okay?
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Of course.
Chief, I'm so sorry.
Please tell my brother
to wait for me at home.
Of course!
There's nothing wrong.
Yes, don't worry. Yes...
What do they mean they thought
we were kidnapped by Mr. Kim?
That's what I'm saying.
We should apologize to everyone.
Why should we apologize?
They caused this ruckus on their own.
Gyoon must've been so worried.
Instead of worrying,
let's just head back.
Ah, what about
that announcer of yours.
Why are you worried about that? I'll take
care of it. Mind your own business!
And yet you never
take care of anything.
Through this event, I finally realized
how important Chohee is to our team.
And I need to treat Bumsang better.
I was too indifferent to him when he joined the CHA simply to be with me.
What doesn't kill us will only make
our team stronger. With that in mind...
Let's go eat.
Yes, let's.
Shall we?
Did they all forget
to take their medicine today?
They must've forgotten as a group.
Let's go eat, too.
Yes, sir.
My fifteen years of experience
tells me that something ain't right.
Are you referring to how we talked to
Bumsang and Chohee simultaneously?
Yeah.
Yeah, it didn't sit well
with me either...
What if they were together...
No way.
If they were...
Then they were lying...
Then we'll make mashed potatoes
out of them in Mr. Kim's stead.
For sure.
Let's go.
Hey, thanks for today.
You're welcome. Go on in.
No, you go first.
About the announcer from earlier.
That really was a coincide...
What?
Never mind. I'll be going then.
Bye!
Sis!
Gyoon.
Where have you been all this time?
Do you know how worried I was?
Aren't you Bumsang Kim?
Ah, yes.
Your brother?
Yeah.
I am her brother Gyoon Heo.
Nice to meet you.
Gyoon Heo?
Author of "The Tales of Honggildong?”
“Chohee Heo” and “Gyoon Heo.”
The greatest literary
siblings of the Joseon Era, eh?
As expected,
you're very knowledgeable.
But why are
you two here together?
Ah, we met coincidentally
over there. Right?
Right. You should get going.
Yeah.
You can't just leave like that.
Come in for a cup of coffee.
He has some coffee already.
Go on then.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
- All right, bye.
- See you next time, lil' bro.
Don't look a thing alike.
You're handsome.
Go already!
“See you tomorrow?”
He definitely has good taste.
He knows that I'm better looking.
Punk!
Let's go in, c'mon.
Why didn't you tell me
you work with Bumsang Kim?
Why do I have to tell you that?
I didn't have the chance to tell you.
Do you know how
worried everyone was?
I told you, I'm sorry.
Where were you?
What did you do all day?
I just went out for some fresh air.
I felt so stifled inside the house.
Sis.
Yeah?
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Why didn't you tell me?
About what?
About what happened to
the “Bihaedangjib.”
You knew?
Fool. Do you know how
foolish you are sometimes?
What am I to you? Why can't
you tell me this stuff honestly?
You're worried I'll be sad?
That I might worry?
Gyoon.
Sis, I'm an adult now.
Until now, you protected me,
but it's my turn to protect you.
So from now on,
tell me everything.
When you're sad or angry,
you can tell me.
Understand?
Look at you, you're
all grown up, aren't you?
You realize that now?
Oh, and since when did
you start dating Bumsang Kim?
What? I'm not dating him!
Who are you trying to fool?
You guys were dressed like a couple.
Why didn't you say anything?
What are you talking about?
Hey, go brush your teeth and get to bed.
And stop with all the nonsense.
Go to bed!
Think I'll believe you?
Shut up!
Such a famous person will become
my brother-in-law. How awesome.
Man... Bumsang,
you're one of a kind.
Dressing in couple tee shirts, how
unfashionable. Ugh, how unsightly.
Here, Mr. Daegil Nah.
Officer Cho.
By the way, about our revenge
on Congressman Lee.
Are you still talking about that?
Man, you're persistent.
Didn't you know that Joohyun
has a very stubborn side to her?
Yeah.
What is this?
Didn't you all agree with me earlier?
And we can't just rest on our laurels. Speaking of which, Chief.
Why don't we just watch some TV?
I'll turn it on.
Mr. Daegil Nah.
- Chief, try some of this.
- This is the famous salted shrimp...
Oh, look at this. Look.
Huh?
Isn't that Chohee and Bumsang?
What the!
What's going on?
Bumsang!
You're going to
become mashed potatoes.
Hey, you have to keep
what happened yesterday a secret.
Watch your own tongue.
- But...
- What?
Hey, watch the hand.
Isn't this the tee shirt
from yesterday?
Oh, this? Yeah, it is...
How could you wear this?
What if I had worn mine?
See, something went wrong
with the laundry.
That's another matter.
Like you'd ever wear this.
That's true, I wouldn't be
caught dead in that...
Yeah, so don't ever wear it.
I'm going to keep wearing it.
You're going to keep wearing that?
We paid good money for it.
Anyway, thanks for the shirt.
Well, it does look good on you.
I'm sincerely sorry for making
everyone worry yesterday.
I'm sorry, too.
Why are you two apologizing?
Perhaps for going to Kanghwa Island...
eating salted shrimp
and playing around in the mud?
No, they're probably apologizing for
lying to us and going on a secret date.
If you feel so sorry, you should
have gone somewhere secret...
instead broadcasting yourselves
live across the nation.
That's enough. We should be glad that they're back safe and sound.
I'm sorry for going against you, Chief.
But I can't just let it go.
I agree. I can't forgive them
for hurting Joohyun and making her cry.
Everyone in the CHA knows
that Bumsang was chasing Joohyun!
Wait, chasing?
I was chasing whom?
Everyone knows, you jerk.
I can't let this matter slide.
Don't do that. I'm really okay.
Please don't be like this.
Joohyun.
Bumsang, you're
a total player, aren't you?
The one thing I can't forgive is a man
who goes around making women cry!
How could you toy with two women of
the same household? At the same time!
Officer Park, what do
you mean, “toy?” This is...
Bumsang. You should be clearer in
your actions. If it was all a joke to you...
I won't let you get away with this!
You player, you!
Should we just
post this on the internet?
Let me explain everything.
The truth his...
We're dating.
Hey!
Chohee, let's not hide it anymore.
I don't care
what you say against me.
But Chohee's only sin was loving me.
Please attack only me.
I guess Chohee was too embarrassed
to admit everything. You understand.
Chief, excuse us for a moment.
Look at them.
They really were dating.
No wonder they were...
Like, no wonder...
Don't you agree, Chief?
Yeah...
Are you crazy? Completely off
your rocker? I'm not dating you!
Hey, pipe down.
You think I liked saying all that?
Then why did you do it? What would
Chief Kang have thought of me?
Oh, right. Chief Kang.
I totally forgot.
Why'd you tell such a lie
and make me into a fool?
Even if we insisted we weren't dating,
no one would have believed us.
If we can't avoid the tornado,
we should face it straight on.
And the damage on my side
is greater than yours.
So just do as I tell you.
Let's just date for a month.
What?
Oh, that was a slip of the tongue. Pretend to date.
And after a month,
we'll have a public break-up.
What should the reason be? Let's just
go with “differences in personality.”
All right, let's take this opportunity to
quiet all the rumors about us in the CHA.
Um, okay. Continue.
I'm done.
By the way, is it safe for me to walk
around when Mr. Kim is after me?
Shouldn't the investigations team
put me in protective custody?
Protective custody, my butt.
Hey, get a grip.
Can you talk to them for me?
I'm scared. Hey, kid!
Ah, I see.
So when will the second volume of
the “Bihaedangjib” go on exhibit?
At the end of this month?
It would've been great if we could have
exhibited both volumes. What a pity.
Can you help me?
Sure.
How do I get to this art gallery?
Ah, you have to go down to the second
floor and turn left. It'll be right there.
Thank you.
Chairman Jang of the Ohsung Group?
What brings you
all the way to the museum, sir?
I thought I'd take a look
at the “Bihaedangjib.”
But I heard Congressman Lee
took it back.
I was just lamenting the loss.
What do you think?
About Congressman Lee's actions.
Like you once said, properties
should always be in circulation.
They could be ruined in a single moment
or they could last a thousand years.
It's not that important
whose possession they're in.
I was worried you had changed
after working for the government.
I see my worries were unfounded.
I want to give you a second chance.
I have an item
I need for you to restore.
There was an uproar seven years ago
when General Shovel stole it.
National treasure no. 238,
the “Sowonhwagaecheob.”
General Shovel... Taesoon Heo.
Hey, what brings you
here at this hour?
Let's have
a glass of wine together.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America