Une coupe de champagne
s'il vous plaît.
Garçon, un café s'il vous plaît.
T'as de très beaux yeux,
je peux t'acheter un verre?
Bonjour, Giles.
Ça va?
You're late.
Ça va bien, merci.
So how's my girl?
Serviced and ready to go.
Papers are in the glove box.
I got you something.
Just a little bon voyage.
You open it.
So you don't get lost.
Maybe I want to.
I'll miss you, Holly.
Come here.
Ladies, I'd like
to introduce you to Giles.
As you can see,
he's a real peach.
He's quick to learn
and eager to please.
He doesn't get tired,
and he goes off
like a firecracker.
What more could a girl want?
You looking for a lay?
Oi.
You shopping?
How much?
What are you after,
handsome?
A handjob.
How much?
50?
Without a condom,
and dirty talk.
Well, don't just sit there.
Don't you have any lube?
What?
Lube.
KY.
Um...
- Out.
- What?
I'm not paying top dollar
for amateur hour.
I'll be good.
I promise.
Fuck that.
You can do anything.
20 bucks.
Show me your tits.
Gonna be a good girl?
Give me your hand.
Oh, that's better.
Now, what's a sweet face like
you doing hawking your fork?
I'm broke.
That's not what
I'm paying you for.
Come on.
Now, what's a sweet thing
like you doing on the streets?
I love sex.
Yes.
Um, I'm a slut.
I just can't get enough.
Yeah, you fucking whore.
You're all the same.
Oh, baby, I can feel
you getting hot.
That's better.
How old are you?
17.
You like us young?
Young and tight.
Come on, dirtier.
Ah, my tight, young pussy's
aching for your big juicy cock.
Take it, you bitch.
Make me beg.
I'll teach you.
Teach me a lesson.
Oh, you fucking whore.
Oh, make me scream.
Come on, come on.
That's better.
Yes.
Harder!
No!
Where did you get this?
Freedom of Information.
Got mine as well.
Look at you.
The prick made me suck him off
then arrested me anyway.
Ligurian arrested me.
His kid had just been born.
Does he know?
I'm meeting him for dinner.
Don't you tell him, Holly.
He'll stop you if he finds out.
I can't just disappear.
Forget the past.
In Paris,
it'll be all future.
To the end.
To the beginning.
Show it to me.
First class.
I'm proud of you, Holly.
A little something
to help you stay retired.
Happy birthday.
I don't know what to say.
Say a prayer for me
in that hunchback's church.
I never thanked you.
What for?
Giving me a chance.
Why did you pick me?
I needed a blonde.
You looked tough.
You looked like a survivor.
I wasn't wrong.
Be careful, Holly.
Don't forget what he is.
Say something to me in French.
Don't say what it means.
What are you after?
A hand job would be good.
50, up front.
- Hi.
Got a spare ciggie?
Don't smoke.
Nobody smokes anymore.
It's feral, eh?
Stunts your growth.
Puts you in an early grave.
What's your name?
Shay.
I'm Cindy.
Buy me a soft serve, Shay?
I'll pay you back.
Okay.
Can I get a soft serve,
small fries, and a Coke?
Don't flash your money around.
There's a lot of eyes,
and they're always watching.
You must be starving, eh?
You want some?
This'll fill me up.
I'm a real sweet tooth.
Haven't seen you
around here before.
I just got here.
Can you lend me a dollar?
I'll pay you back.
I can get a smoke for a dollar.
You're a real friend.
Don't keep your cash
in your pocket either.
Happy birthday, Holly.
Come here.
Ever felt like running away?
Ever felt like
changing your life?
What's your dream, Holly?
If you could do anything,
go anywhere, what would it be?
Before my mum died,
she took me to Paris.
That's what I remember
about her.
She was happy.
I've always wanted to go back.
Let's do it.
Let's go to Paris.
I'm getting out.
I'm gonna disappear,
and I want you to come with me.
Money won't be a problem.
What about your family?
I don't love them.
Open it.
Put it on.
You have to.
It's bad luck otherwise.
What?
Let's go.
Sorry.
It's all right.
Look me in the eyes
and say that.
It's all right, Michael.
Pack your bags.
Tomorrow I'll be rich enough
to set us free.
Monkey, be quiet.
Fuck.
I'll give you
the group discount.
100 a hole, 50 a hand,
that's 350.
That's right boys.
It's real too.
Fuck.
Rocky.
Rock.
I got her.
You fuckin' tryin' to avoid me?
No.
What the fuck
you runnin' from, then?
You fuckin' scrote.
Where's my money?
I seen her, Rock,
stealin' Karlene's trade.
It's my stretch,
you fuckin' slut.
No, no, no, I wasn't.
That's fuckin' bullshit!
Shut up, Karlene.
Thinks she's so fuckin' good.
Do somethin'.
Do somethin'!
- Give us the money.
- I don't have any.
What the fuck did you say?
I spent it.
See that?
See fuckin' that?
Fuckin' lying bitch.
Listen, you fuckin' slut.
Next time, it's a hot shot.
Stay off our fuckin' street,
or you're dead, cunt.
You fuckin' bitch.
Bel, hey, it's Holly.
Hi, are you working?
Yeah, now.
No, no, no,
just a couple of hours.
Okay.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
Bye.
Um, well I'm swinging by yours,
like, in two minutes.
I can come get you.
It's good money.
Yeah, no, that's not
gonna help me, so...
No, it's all right.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Monique, it's Holly.
You working?
It's good money.
Come on, Mon,
you're my last hope.
Yeah, thanks anyway.
Dramas?
It's the night for it.
Full moon.
Everyone's a little crazy.
Great.
Maybe I can help.
Can you find me a brunette
who can fuck and suck?
Look out!
Fuckin' asshole!
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
You could've fuckin' killed me!
You fuckin' idiot!
She's perfect.
Wait up.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Fuck off!
Want a job?
I said piss off, lady.
Don't you understand English?
I need a girl right now,
and you're perfect.
Threesome at the Hyatt.
Couple of hours, tops.
It's 300.
When was the last time
you made that much?
Nothing weird?
Nothing weird.
Just one bloke?
Just me and the guy.
$400.
Wait.
I need the money.
Just give me a chance.
How old are you?
19.
Don't bullshit me.
17.
You got anything else
to wear?
Just this.
Put it on.
What's your name?
Shay.
It's $300, Shay.
Okay.
I'm Holly.
Let's go.
You okay?
Yeah.
Nervous?
No.
Just follow my lead, okay?
Better out than in.
Present company excepted.
You like that?
When I fuck you,
when I make you come,
I know it's all an act,
an illusion.
It doesn't matter.
I want the illusion.
That's what I'm paying for.
Just for an hour,
I've got the biggest dick...
The magic touch.
I can make you come
in under a minute.
Prove it.
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
Yeah?
No, no.
You're early.
No problem.
Come up.
Fuck!
I got business.
Get in the bathroom
and shut up.
Take your clothes.
Come on, move!
Move!
Hello, Willie.
Lovely night for it.
Yes, top night, Mr. Bennett.
Things went great,
I'm happy to say.
Fine.
Well, come on.
Make me happy.
They loved the gear.
You too?
Did you love it too?
Yeah.
I had a taste, Mr. Bennett.
I'm not gonna deny it.
Of course you did, Willie.
Yeah.
A good salesman's
got to know his product.
Here.
You better count that.
Do you like bowling, Willie?
Dunno.
Why?
Because now you're
a bowling ball.
Drive!
You've rung Holly.
I'm tied up right now,
but if you leave your name
and number, I'll call you back
to arrange an appointment.
Gotcha.
Fuck.
Calm down.
- He's dead, isn't he?
- Shh.
- He shot him in the head!
- Shut up!
I saw it!
Just calm down, all right?
All right?
Oh, shit.
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Where to?
Just drive.
He knew we were there.
He didn't see us.
How do you know?
You're safe.
Oh, fuck.
Stop.
Stop!
You don't know me.
I don't know you.
Hey.
Wait!
Where to?
Where can I take you?
Look, give me a destination
or get out.
You all right?
Everyone's crazy tonight.
What's that?
Don't worry.
Shh.
Can't leave him at home.
He's part of my act.
Look, can I take you somewhere?
I'm hungry.
How about your favorite
restaurant?
Vegas is the place
for any serious magician.
My old man used to say
that if you conquer Vegas,
the world will follow.
If you could work
at any casino,
which one would it be?
Caesar's.
How come?
It's the coolest.
And he played there once
on the same bill as Tom Jones.
Who?
Tom Jones?
The singer.
Forget it.
Your Dad sounds cool.
Yeah, he was.
I used to watch his shows
over and over.
My dad was magic too.
He disappeared when I was born.
What, you never saw him?
I got a stepdad.
Aren't you cold?
I left my coat at the hotel.
Here.
So what did you want to be
when you grew up?
I never had a dream
or anything.
Not like you.
Maybe I could be your...
Your lovely assistant.
Hello, Holly.
I'm Willie's friend.
You going somewhere?
Where's your friend?
Willie was a greedy turd.
He always got a double act.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
That was foreplay.
Do you want to fuck with me?
Your friend
with the pink lipstick.
She was from the street.
I don't know her name.
Wrong answer.
Look into my eyes and listen
to the sound of my voice.
There is nothing
but the sound of my voice
and my eyes.
I will count backwards
from five.
When I reach one,
you will be under my spell.
Five.
I want you to completely
free your mind.
Four.
All tension flows
from your body.
Three.
You feel totally relaxed.
Two.
You're light as a feather.
One.
A deep sleep envelopes you.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Tell me your name.
Shay Maree Ryan.
How old are you, Shay?
17.
Tell me something
about yourself.
I never forget a face.
Where are you from?
Up north.
Why are you here?
Mum died, so I ran away.
Sorry.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
Look at me.
You're beautiful.
Don't.
Can I see you again?
Do you want to see me
or see me?
I want to see you.
"Harry the Impossible."
Will you call?
I don't just hypnotize anyone,
you know.
It wouldn't work out.
How do you know if you don't
take a chance?
What's in the bag, bitch?
Hand it over,
and you won't get hurt.
You're the one'll get hurt.
Aww teach her
some manners, Rock.
I'll teach her some fuckin'
manners, all right.
Oh, fuck!
My fuckin' eyes!
My fucking head!
You bitch!
I fuckin' hate you people.
Open your mouth!
I want a room.
$25 the half,
$30 the hour.
Five bucks for the towel.
No, for the...
for the night.
80 bucks for the night.
Room three, first floor,
end of the corridor.
Thanks.
Whoo, oh, my God!
Hey.
Hey, Mum.
Don't you ever be afraid
to take a chance, Shay,
you know?
We're looking for your friend.
I don't know her.
Yeah, but you know what she
looks like, though, don't you?
Huh?
Don't ya?
No.
Ah!
Don't you?
Stop, stop.
All right.
All right!
She didn't see you.
She can't hurt you.
You can't trust women.
Shit just fuckin' flies
out of their mouth
without them even thinking.
It's biological.
It's because they got
a cunt hidden away.
It's natural they're gonna
be hiding something.
With a bloke,
it's all just there, isn't it?
What you see is what you get.
But women are fuckin' liars.
I fuckin' hate women.
Start looking.
Where's Rose?
Don't know.
Who are you?
I heard you from next door.
Have you got anything?
No.
Got a smoke?
Sorry.
Fuck.
What time is it?
It's late.
Where the fuck is she?
I'll get you some water.
Okay?
Sweet.
Here I am, baby.
Who the fuck are you?
She's the girl from next door.
Well, she can fuck off,
because we're fuckin' busy.
I was just seeing
if your friend was all right.
He's not my friend.
Hurry.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Come on. Come on.
Come on!
Half.
Half!
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck.
The back of your hand.
Shut up, bitch!
Shut up.
Fuck!
Ooh.
You got any money?
No.
Bullshit.
Cutie like you.
Come on.
Give us some money.
I don't have any.
Fuck you.
Hey, open the fucking door.
Come on, sweetheart.
Open the fucking door.
The welcome wagon.
Cunts.
That's the way it is.
They fucked me.
Now it's your turn.
I could tell 'em you're here.
They'd pay me for it.
Thanks.
Get fucked.
Hey.
Pink lipstick.
Run!
Gotcha.
Get in!
Are you all right?
What did he do to you?
Police radio.
What?
He's a cop.
Fuck.
You should go home.
I can't.
Somewhere else, then.
There's nowhere else.
I could stay with you.
I'm going to the airport
to get on a plane out of here.
That guy'll come after me.
I offered you a job.
No one forced you.
You don't give a shit.
I just saved you.
I don't owe you anything.
You can have the car.
I can't drive.
Get out.
Get out!
Hey.
Fuck off!
It's Shay.
Fully didn't recognize you.
Where you going?
Nowhere.
Can I come?
I saw a guy get killed.
You okay?
I think someone's after me.
Who's lookin' out for you?
Rocky will help.
He looks after me.
He'll love you.
Yeah.
I'll go get him.
Lend me some ciggie money?
I'll pay you back.
You're a real friend.
Don't move.
Get in.
I'm waiting for someone.
Shay, get in.
I met my first trick
on this street.
I was so scared.
This big old man.
I thought he was gonna
have a heart attack on me.
I promised myself,
before I turned 30, I'd quit,
move to Paris,
reinvent myself.
It's my birthday today.
I've been fucking for money
since I was 15.
I want a new life.
There's this guy.
He doesn't know
that I'm leaving,
and I don't want him to.
He can help us.
Who is he?
He's a cop.
Don't worry, ladies.
Safe as houses here.
Take a load off.
This is Bob's place.
No secrets between him and me.
Except where the bodies
are buried.
Good one.
- Who's this?
- Shay.
We were on the job together.
You see what happened?
- He shot him in the head.
- Who shot him?
A cop named Bennett.
He tried to kill us.
He's after us, Michael.
Where'd you park
his car darlin'?
We didn't say anything
about a car.
Gotcha.
Mate, you got more bruises
than a Queensland banana.
I reckon your nose looks better
on this side.
Fonzie got busted!
Laugh now, you fuckin' dog!
Where's my car, cunt?
Settle down.
Get out of my way.
You made enough mistakes
tonight.
Fuckin' settle down.
Look at my suit.
That bitch broke
my fuckin' nose.
- You can have the girl.
- What do you care?
Holly's mine.
Oh, mate.
She's a fuckin' whore.
She's pissing off.
Her place was empty.
She's coming with me.
No, no, look at her bag.
I saw the ticket.
Whores only love money.
Everything else is an act.
Back to the car.
He was lying, Michael.
I remember the first time
I saw you.
I arrested you just so
I could hear your voice.
I'm gonna believe you, Holly.
We're rich enough to disappear.
What about Shay?
It's just you and me now.
She's my friend.
Look in my eyes and say yes.
No.
I can't.
Tell me it wasn't all an act.
Police!
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
Move!
Drop the gun!
Drop the fucking gun!
Drive,
or I'll fucking kill you!
Come on!
Step on the fucking peddle.
Faster!
Come on!
Holly.
Okay.
The case.
It's just a scratch.
You're still beautiful.
What time's your flight?
I'll never make it now.
You've got to try.
I'll call Harry.
Who?
The taxi driver.
He's also an escape artist.
It's ringing.
Oh my God.
Holly?
Holly, lie down.
Lie down.
Just lie down.
Tenir moi.
Holly?
Somebody help me!
Help me!
I usually
pull him out of a hat.
You like me, don't you?
Yeah.
I want you
to make me disappear.