on the side of her lips?Yes.
So until that gets better, she should probably rest.
There MAY be some people that do not know of the BBF story.
because due to its popularity rising, people may have just started watching.
For those viewers, I have prepared a summary of episodes 1-16 so far.
Let's watch!
The new transfer student to the luxury high school, ShinHwa, Geum JanDi.
Geum JanDi, fighting!
School life wasn't exactly comfortable for her.
Lick it.
Can't you stop?
Who is she?
What?Then you lick it instead of her.
If you lick it, I'll let it go.
What's wrong with you?!
It's up, it's up! The sophomore in class B, Geum JanDi, got the red card!
Hey, you keep chuckling to yourself, what's wrong with you?
Around this time, her lids probably popped.
Goo JoonPyo gradually began to fall for Geum JanDi.
What?
Stop . . . stop now . . . help me.
You still don't believe me.
I believe..i believe in you.
In the name of ShinHwa F4, I have an announcement to make.
From this day forward, second year Geum JanDi will officially be the girlfriend of F4's Goo JoonPyo.
Where are we going?
I have something to show you..
Alright, look outside.
Wow, it's a heart! It's really in the shape of a heart!
If I found a girl I liked, I promised myself that I would bring her here.
Do you see it? My heart.
It's wrong, right? It's all wrong, isn't it?
I guess that you know her better than me.
Sunbae.
Please, be happy.
Tell me you will be.
If sunbae's sad, I'm sad too.
They felt each other's pain in love.
So, it was like this?
Goo JoonPyo! Stop, don't do this, this is . . .This is what? Is this something you don't know about either?
I'm sorry.Geum JanDi, don't ever act like you know me from now on.
Due to JiHoo, JanDi and JoonPyo's love was over.
Yoon JiHoo is no longer a member of F4.
What?JunPyo . . .
Also, in a week from now, Yoon JiHoo and Geum JanDi will be expelled from this school.
But, then his heart couldn't easily forget Geum JanDi.
Why did it have to be JiHoo out of all people.If only it wasn't JiHoo . . .
Goo JoonPyo . . .
Say that you like me once.
However, their thoughts were messed up about each other.
Yes? What did you say?
JoonPyo. Goo JoonPyo . . .
Get up! Geum JanDi's here!
Get up man!
Goo JoonPyo.Please wake up. Why are you doing this?
The words you wanted me to say, I think I can say them now.But if you're like this, what am I supposed to do?
Wake up!
Are you telling the truth?
With F4's help, they confirmed the love between Geum JanDi and Goo JoonPyo.
Ya, Geum JanDi must have been really shocked. Look at her shoes, shoes!
JoonPyo, lucky you!
If it were me, I could die happy right now!Sunbae!Sorry.We had to do something about it because both of you are so stubborn.
Meanwhile, Kang Hye Jang (JoonPyo's mom) finds out that they're dating.
Her dad's a dry cleaner, her mom works at a bath house.
Yes, that's right.
Stop the car.We don't need to stop the car.Don't you hear me?! STOP THE CAR!
Goo JunPyo./br Geum JanDi. Stand still,
please stand still.
But Goo JoonPyo shows his love in front of Kang Hye Jang.
Find JoonPyo right now. He needs to go somewhere with me.
Okay.
I didn't get to thank him.
I couldn't even tell him I like him.
And thus a long time of separation comes between the two.
I'll be back soon. Don't go anywhere, just wait . . .
I love you, Geum JanDi.
In this section, or entirely?
Uhm, entirely I'd have to say the first kiss with JanDi was most tender . . .
on the swings in the playground.
I'm good looking, I'm tall, I have a lot of money.
NG.. (laugh).
Again!
I'm good looking.I'm smart, I'm rich. How could you hate me?
Wow! It's really good! How could you hate him?
Please say that to . . .
Which one?"Geum JanDi, 2year (of high school) Class B, is my girlfriend."?
No, not that.Ahh, "kkuhjuh" (meaning go away).
Oh, I don't think I can do it.Then please look at me and do it.
If I look at him, I can't do it even more!Then please look at the middle and do it.
Kkuhjuh.That "kkuhjuh" is cool.
I didn't need that many lines.
It was mostly, "Yo! What's up?".
Then please show us the real way to say it.
It's not very friendly.
When I met my friends, I would say, "Yo! What's up?"
It's awkward, right?
Get lost!
What about "kkujuh"?
"Hurry up and get lost", sorry.
The conversation between Goo JoonPyo and his older sister,
You remember, right?You, know, "What kind of guys I hate the most?".Here's his sister.
What kind of guys do I hate the most?
The guy who is lying.
the guy which i don't like most?
Wait, no, I'm sorry, I didn't catch the feeling in time.
Sorry, please thing that your sister got really sick
So now her nose is stuffy and her voice sounds different
A.. a unfair man.
A person who keeps a grudge?
Oh, what kind of man was that again?
And Goo JunPyo is what kind of man? Your older sister's favorite man!
The second section of the summary, let's watch together!
Yoon JiHoo had JanDi's back during hard times.
You're gonna catch a cold.
I'm okay though.
Thank you.
It's really warm!
I hoped you wouldn't need it, but oh, well.
See?Sunbae.
Whenever my heart rings the emergency bell, you appear.
Fine, command me.
What?
To be Geum JanDi's emergency car.
Hmm, it's my first time riding one of these.
In the end, JanDi goes to find JoonPyo in Macau.
H-hi. I came.
Yeah, so what brings you here?
Just so you know, I'm doing fine. And as you can see, I'm busy.
You can go now. You don't need to worry about me.
So to you, I'm like . . .A stain I would like to erase./br
This is so cruel, Goo JoonPyo.
I was always like this.
Once again, JiHoo helps JanDi's broken heart.
It's the first time in my life, earning money with my own hands.
When I'm with you, there's a lot of new things I do.
So because of that, thanks.
Young master, should we go now?
Wait just a little bit.
Why did you come?
I don't have anything to say to you.
Speaking of which, what are you doing ?
You think you have the right to ask that kind of question?
Yoon JiHoo!
I forgave you because you were my friend, and I tried to stay away from her because she was my friend's girl.
I held myself, and gave you a chance for you to be with her.
I'm not holding back any more.
Enough!
Why did you come?
Do you have something to say?
Fine. I get it.
I'm leaving.
A new girl appears in JunPyo's life.
Oh, I found him!
What do you mean, "What?"? You're engaged to me!
Hey, ugh. Aren't you gonna let GO of me?
Listen carefully, I'm only saying this once. My name's Ha JaeKyung. Starting today, I'm engaged to you.
You got it ?
From now on, I'm gonna tame you.
How is this love mess going to untangle itself?
Oh that's right! Lee Minho was chosen out of 200 people for his hairstyle?
When I went to the second tryouts, I went with my hair curled.
It's like the hair in comic books.
Yes, I made it similar to that and went.
The staff members said it suited me.
They said that, and I think they liked it.
That hairstyle is the same hairstyle for Goo JoonPyo right?
No, it wasn't.
That was the second time I curled it,
And the sixth time was when my hair turned perfectly into JoonPyo's hair.
Wow, you must've put a lot of effort into that! But now it's a trend.
That's right, every guy has the same hairstyle either as Goo JoonPyo or HyunJoong.
Yeah. Everywhere you walk, everyone has Goo Joonpyo's or Hyunjoong's hair style
Even this announcer next to me tried to copy HyunJoong's hairstyle!
Yeah, I was going to do your hair style, but I undid it.How did everyone else get their role?
I'm still preparing concert in JP...
You asked them what you would be doing and how did they reply?
For now, just do what you're doing.
And I asked them what they were doing without me knowing.
At that time, BBF was a hit in Japan.
So at first, I thought they were kidding.
So they told me we'd talk back in Korea, so after the concert,
when I got there, they wanted to have a meeting.
So at the meeting, they told me there was a drama casting, and they asked me what I thought of it.
But I told them I had to quickly release an album in Japan! But my manager said
to do it because it was a good opportunity, so I did.
So there was a story behind this!And apparently your manager is very scary!
My manager is a very nice person.
In my position, my character was cast very late.
But I think that there was no way around it, 'cause they were casting East of Eden at that time.
I think because I met the right opportunities, I'm living happily and having fun.
Kim Jun, how was your casting as WooBin?
It's my first time in a drama, so I watched the auditions.
Yes, yes. Auditions aren't something that you look at and memorize,
it's something you continuously have to look over.
Before that, we had no idea who was cast,
Lee MinHo and I met at auditions, but I didn't know his role or anything.
So I wondered, why is his hair so curled?
I saw him during the audition, so . . .
He's tall. On top of that, he was walking around with glaring eyes.
He looked cool, and I later found out that we were cast together.
I had recently seen the movie "Public Enemy Returns."
So when I saw him, I thought, "Oh, the guy who got stabbed with a knife!"
I kept remembering that part in the movie!
The dead guy shouldn't be here.
So I felt a little weird when I first saw him.
I remember Kim Bum in a drama, where he was really good at crying scenes.
So for those reasons, I found it really interesting.
So the person who dies, the person who cries, Kim Joon...
Wasn't that a first impression?
At first, I saw GaEul in a movie
"The Show Must Go on." She came out as a bad girl.
She was in that movie?Yes, as the bad daughter.
My wife is in that too.Right. That's right.
Oh yes, my wife appears in that same movie in the middle somewhere.
Why did I mention this?
So Kim Joon, aren't you the oldest in this group? How is it after being friendly with the other three of the F4?
There are some similar parts and different parts. Like MinHo, he looks very tall and sophisticated.
But when you get familiar with him, he has this cute behavior.
He's really kind and sweet unlike the character he plays.
WIth HyunJoong, it's pretty much the same. He's funny.
HyunJoong is basically your atmosphere maker.
Yes, that seems right.
He has this unexpected personality to him.
When I first saw KimBum, he looked young.
But actually, he's very experienced and I ask for help from him sometimes.
What is Kim Joon like?He's the problem solver of the group.
When we're hanging out, he handles situations like this...
He takes control of situations. He says he's not good at something and shows slight potential for scamming.
He's almost like a con artist.He says he can't do something, but he really can, and wins.
He must be really competitive.He must have really held that against me. He mentioned it before, too.
But, he really has a good heart. Really.
But, he's really modest to the extreme.
He can do everything.He says he can't, but there is nothing he can't do.
Everyone must have lost a bet to him once.
It's not as popular as the national drama "Boys over Flowers," but you must know the national pop song right?
I guess you don't know "Noona's Dream."[Hyung Young's Song "Noona's Dream"]
It's really not the national pop song, is it?
Noona's fantasies. I asked the ladies around me who are 30 and over this question.
"What present do you wish to receive from F4?"
Let's see what girls want as a present from the F4!
The first present they want to receive is . . .
To have a scarf tied by So YiJung.
That scene outside the club . . .
Although it was just an act, it was the first scene where feelings are shown for GaEul.
Well, we must see this since there are possibly some people who don't know what we're talking about.
Must be nice....and here, let me pull out your hair
Oh, and this side, too.So that was the first one.
And so what was the second one?
Here's the second one.
And the second one is...
To have shoes put on by Yoon JiHoo.
You did wash your feet this morning, right?Oh, of course...I went to the bathhouse.
Oh, these are those expensive shoes in Macau
Is this the right size for you?You must be lucky!
Oh my, what to do?
I wanted to buy you something with the first money I ever earned.
Thank you, JiHoo. I'll wear it well.
Oh, this is so awesome.
It's alright, right, Jihoo?Yes, I think it's fine.
We have one more left, to receive a back hug from Goo JoonPyo.
Everyone, please don't hate Hyun-young.
I happen to be the only woman here, so . . .
We got it all ready.Oh, shall we do the necklace? You pick one out of the two.
Actually, when the necklace is given, it's given in the state of the back hug.
So you must do both.Ladies, use your imagination and put your face in this picture right now.
I'm substituting for everyone.
I won't be placing the necklace around your neck.
What should I do?Stay still![I am so happy!]
Please give a round of applause.are you trembling from him just touching you?
Oh, I can have it?
Yes, please have it.Oh thank you
Isn't there only one of this kind in the world?No, there's a lot.
But the only two people who received this necklace from the F4 ar Geum JanDi and me.
If I could come back in another life, I would want to be in F4.Since all I've done is receive, I prepared something for you, too.
Do-shi-rak (lunch box).
The eye is like a monster.I actually like eyes are closer together.
The nose is in the middle of the face
I think it got carsick - Im sorry
Please take the lunch box
The carsick lunch box.
Because of this, girls were going crazy trying to bake cookies
I've made them too, Goo JoonPyo cookies!
Yoon JiHoo eats one, too.
Charismatic JoonPyo, smooth JiHoo,
Casanova YiJung, and tough WooBin
It is hard, so we have something prepared for you all: King before Flowers.
Out of these four gentlemen, who is the king?
You have a rose in your hand right?
We will see at the end who has the most flowers
Let's see who gets the most roses.
Let's start asking the questions now.
First question. Of the members, who is the best looking?
Please start thinking now
This is hard right? When i look at it its a hard decision too.Hmmm, maybe each thinks he is the best-looking...
In that case, you can keep the flower yourself.Oh yeah?
If you think it's yourself, you don't need to give it to anyone.Oh, it looks like Kim Bum has something planned...
1, 2, 3 . . .Oh, this is weird. Thank you.
Of the members, who has the most individual roles?
Kim Joon has 2Be sure to accept the flower that's coming to you...
You can't leave that out
In the drama it's very embarrassing to dance though
1, 2, dan dan [dance steps], 1 , 2 dan dan.Go backwards then forwards.
Yes, these are the dance steps. Ready, start.Just do that and that's the dance, right?Let's match it to the music.
Oh wait, this isn't quite right.
I heard that you're really good at guitar as well
I think in episode 17 or 18, I play the guitar for JanDi.
Which is why we've prepared a guitar for you!
Oh this is a bit...What about that piece you played...
Remember when you took the apple away?Was there guitar playing in the apple scene?Oh, what was that?
it's because my fingers are cold.
I can't play the guitar.I don't really have any musical talent.
Oh, it's totally fine.I can play the piano.
Oh, piano?This house doesn't seem to have a piano.Oh, then later, in the other room, we can use the piano.
We'll play it in the next room.Do you, by chance, know how to play the guitar as well?
I also play piano...Oh so you all play piano. We'll hear your piano playing in the next room, then.
Better than the drama, the NG's!
NG before flowers!
How should I do so?Sunbae, snap out if it, please!And if I can't... oops! sorry
Sunbae, snap out of it, please!the one who isn't snapping out of is... Aiyah! I'm going crazy. Sorry
It's a good morning.
In the name of F4, I have an announcement to make..Laughing...What's wrong with you?I'm sorry.
Go now.
I'm sorryWhere's the headrest?
Do you want to die?
Before it cools, you have to eat it when it's still warm.
Oh this is so well-cooked...Honey, what about the braised fish?
CAPTION: Do I really have to eat this?This has been cooking since the crack of dawn...
Noona!
Is this funny?
Butler Lee, ttak ok ok gah.... (Trying to say ttak kuh, meaning clean it up.)
Ah, the night air feels nice. Hey, do you remember?
The thing we did when we were young
Move; let me do it.
Call JoonPyo. JanDi's in danger.
Sorry, man, I'm really sorry.
Glad to meet you (She's Chinese)- Oh, Glad to meet you. You can speak korean!
I love you.I love you? By whom were you taught?
[They're still acting](She's speaking in Chinese)
What did you just say?
Huh?I have nothing to talk about, anymore.
I really have nothing more to say.
Mini series "Boys over Flowers..."
Flower boys' NG will be continued till the end of the drama, with you viewers.
After watched it, you guys said no, but in my opinion,
The NG King is already picked.
The NG(mistakes during shooting) King - Lee MinHo.
You admit your mistakes quickly, though, don't you?Yes, I should admit them quickly.
You have reactions each, after you make NG, don't you?
I think MinHo says he's sorry asap, if he makes one.Right, I admit my mistakes early.
Since we are visiting the house, shall we begin our tour now?Yes, we should take a look around.
Many women must be waiting for this moment.
We're now moving.
Can you lead us?- Where would you like to go first?Let's go to your room
We're here in JunPyo's room.- Right, I'm in JUNPYO's room.
Everyone has much anticipated this... Junpyo would you tell us more about the room?
Everything has been prepared in advance.The closet is actually elsewhere, but you can see the clothes that are used during filming.
This fur is Goo Joonpyo's trademark
Did you see "Gag Concert (a Korean show)" when they wore this?
Yes, I saw it.- About hat Goo JunPyo, how did you feel?
His fur didn't look that expensive.
His furs were just hairs.
So this is the bed, eh?
This bed is where JanDi laid, when she got hurt, isn't it?
No it's not.- Huh?This house has many beds.That's in a different room.
So this is just Goo Joonpyo's room
Oh, the guest room?Uh... not the guest ro-- Er, yeah. The guest room..Correct.
Then, shall we go to that room?This window, this is the window that you sneaked out of to save Jandi?
Oh, but you can't open it.- Oh, I can't open it.
Outside is just a set.
ohhh, it does open.
Why don't you try going outside?
Let's go with F4 and HyunYoung.
ohh this is yoon ji hoo's housee. -yeahh this is yoon ji hoo's/ my house.
Goo Joonpyo's house is kind of luxurious and has an antique feel to it, but Yoon Jihoo's house seems more modern.
Because it's the house of the former president's grandson, it has a more "Hano" feel to it.
The design is very modern
Just a short while ago, we find out about your grandfather, right?
Isn't it a bit too big for you to live in by yourself? Why don't you live together?
My grandfather hasn't been back in 15 years. BR Ah, it's been 15 years since he left this house...
Soon, depending on what the screenwriter decides...
We'll find out whether he will come back, or if he will forever stay away.
So it depends on the writer...Also, my house...
has a very special "tahb" (tower) in the back.
You can't see it from here, but...
Oh, there really is a tower back here. What is the name of the tower?
It's called "Dabo Tahb"Ah... "Dabo Tahb"?
Didn't this belong in Kyongju? You brought it over here?Yes, because I'm the former president's grandson, everything is permissable
Is "Dabo Tahb" the only tower name that you know, HyunJoon?
No, no..Then what other tower's do you know of?Well there's the "Big Bang Tahb..."
Joon and Bum, what do you find the most appealing about this house?
Something that you feel is really your style?I like the "hano" feel of the ceilings.
But, Joon and Bum, have you even had the chance to come to this set?
Bum: I've been here before but, Joon hasn't.Joon: Yeah, this is my first time looking around.
Take a look around. Is there anything that you like?
The interior is really nice, but what really caught my attention from when we first came in is this elephant.
Oh the elephant?Yes, is this something that i can ride?If you don't ride it properly, it could break.
In Joonpyo's room there was a horse, and here, there's an elephant. When they were young...
they got to ride these.Lucky little kids.
Shall we go over this way now?
Back over here is a piano. Just a while ago, we talked about playing.
All of you play piano well, right?We need to hear you.
Not "play well," just "play"
First, let's start with Kim Bum
Wow... then Joon...
the instruments... oh, let me move over to that side. No no, stay there.
What piece will you play for us?
I'll play something that you've probably heard, it's called "Romance"
We know the lyrics to that...BR Kim Joon appears to be an extremely well-versed pianist.
Then, since Kim Joon and I are singers, we'll hum.
Okay, but your voice is too high.
Wow, but apart from this do you know anything more modern?
Uh...Do you know ??? (some Korean pop song)by any chance?
I don't have any experience playing those kind of songs.Oh, I can't play very well.
The thing with these guys is they all say that can't play well but then...No, I really can't play well.
I'll play Moon River.
Come on, Joon, sing.Wait, that isn't right.No, it sounds right.
I'll stop here...it's been so long since I've played.Wow, all of your are so talented with instruments.
HyunJoon, you can play too, right?Well, I can play the pop tune, "Want to see you..."
"Want to see you?" Oh! In that case, since it's about time to sign off anyway,
We'll go ahead and say our farewells, then as a finale, HyunJoon can play "Want to see you" since we all want to see "Boys Over Flowers"
Thanks to your love and support, we've come to this point--Episode 16...
to 17 and 18, and about 8 more epidodes to go.
We will do our best so that we can end well.And we ask for you full support until the end. Thank you.
Because of some accidents, these car accidents...
regretful though it may seem,we really need to consider the actors' and actresses' heath first.
If you'll be patient just a bit more, then we'll present a great, upgraded...
final few epidsodes. And keep Koo Hyesun in your thoughts...and please continue to love "Boys over Flowers"
Tomorrow evening, episode 17 will air. Please keep loving "Boys over Flowers."
I'm also eagerly looking forward to watching,but I'll be patient until tomorrow. Everyone, watch with us tomorrow night.