I got your permit right here.
Catchy tune.
Fuck this game.
FUCK YOU!
We need backup,we need Kung Fury!
Yeah, that's my bicep.
One second babe.
Hello?
We got an arcade machinedown here going crazy,
it is killing everybody,it's destruction, chaos, terror-
What are you gonna do?
My job.
Game over.
I'm a cop anddamn good at my job.
It all began years ago.
In the line of duty,
me and my partner werechasing down
a mysterious Kung Fu-master.
You're under arrest, punk.
Show us your hands.
Good work, Dragon.
You could've killed both of uswith that crazy stunt
but goddammit, you're thebest partner I've ever had.
Thanks,I learned from the best.
You're like a father to me.
With one fatal blow,he hit my partner.
I could tellhe was dead straight off.
Before I could pull the trigger...
I was hit by lightningand bitten by a cobra.
I blacked out.
And saw images of ancientShaolin temples and monks,
mastering the art of Kung Fu.
There was an ancient prophecy,
about a new formof Kung Fu so powerful,
only one man could master it.
The chosen one.
When I woke up,
I saw the Kung Fu masterrunning towards me.
I could feel my body mutate
into some sort ofKung Fu freak of nature.
You!
You are the chosen one!
- Knock, knock.- Who's there?
Knuckles.
As a memento,
I put on a strip of clothfrom the dead Kung Fu master.
I decided I would usemy new super Kung Fu powers
to fight crime.
So, I becamethe best cop in the world.
I became, Kung Fury.
I don't wanna hear it Kung Fury.
I just got back from city hall,$50 million worth of damages,
and I got the mayor upmy ass like a fag on Viagra.
How am I going to explainthis to the press, hmm?
You just destroyed an entirecity block for Christ's sake.
Didn't you tell meto block it out?
I told you do it by the book.
Cut the bullshit.
Nobody else could have stopped
that arcade machineand you know it.
Oh man, listen to me Kung Fury.
You need to start followingthe rules like the rest of us,
so I'm assigning youa new partner.
What?Hell no, I work alone.
Not anymore you don't.
Say hi to your new partner,Triceracop.
Very nice meeting you Kung Fury,
looking forward toworking with you.
You're like a father to me.
I work alone.
Either you team upwith Triceracop,
or you're off the case.
I'm not off the case,
I quit.
Yeah Yeah, I did the blood test.
It was positive, yeah?
What the hellare you talking about?
Yeah no problem.
Give me the phone.
What the hell is this?
- Chief McNickles speaking.- Is this the police?
- Yeah, this is the police.- Fuck you!
MALFUNCTIONING?
I need someoneto trace that call!
But that's impossible!
Not for me it isn't.
Hackerman, he's the mostpowerful hacker of all time.
Follow me.
I was able to triangulatethe cell phone signal
and trace the caller.
His name is Adolf Hitler.
Hitler, he's the worstcriminal of all time.
Do you know him, sir?
I guess you could say that.
In the 1940's,Hitler was a Kung Fu champion.
He was so good at Kung Fu,
that he decided to changehis name to Kung Fuhrer.
But he didn't stop there.
He knew ofthe Kung Fury prophecy,
and wanted to claim the throne.
So he and his posse ofNazi soldiers
conducted experimentsfor years.
But they weren't ableto figure out
how to master the artof Kung Fury.
And one day,
he disappearedfrom the face of the earth.
And no-one has seen himever since.
Until now.
I guess he figured if he couldfind the chosen one and kill him,
he would becomeKung Fury himself.
He must have traveled in timein order to get here,
that's probably why hedisappeared in the first place.
So, what're you gonna do?
My job.
I'm gonna go back in timeto Nazi Germany,
and kill Hitler,once and for all.
So, how are you gonna do that?
I'm not sure.
I need some sort oftime machine.
Wait a minute,
using an RX modulator,I might be able to conduct
a mainframe cell direct andhack the uplink to the download.
What does that mean?
It means that with the right computeralgorithms, I can hack you back in time.
Just like a time machine.
Well then, it's hacking time.
Oh, no!
Fuck!
That's a Laser-Raptor.
I thought they went extinctthousands of years ago.
Who are you?
My name,
is Barbarianna.
What year is this?
It's the Viking age.
That explains the Laser-Raptor.Fuck!
I went too far back in time.
You need to get outof this valley.
This place is swarmingwith Laser-Raptors.
I'll meet you at the God's drop.Katana can help you get there.
Who's Katana?
I'm Katana.
I can give you a ride to Asgard.
A ride on what?
So, who are you?
I'm a cop from the future.
I was sent back in timeto kill Hitler,
but I accidentally wenttoo far back in time
and ended up in this place.
I know someonewho might be able to help you.
Thor!
Behold! It is me, Thor!
Son of Odinand protector of mankind.
Check out my pecs.
Your pecs are epic.
Thanks bro!
So, anyway.
Thor, this is Kung Fury,he's a cop from the future.
Yeah, I need to get toNazi Germany and kill Hitler...
- so if you could help me with--- Stop!
Hammer time.
Walk through this portal andyou shall end up in Nazi Germany.
Good luck to you, Kung Fury!
Thanks Thor!
Well,looks like this is my ride.
Hey, future cop,where are you going?
You know what.Here, take my number.
And use this phone to call me.
It's a personal, transportable,cellular telephone.
It features 645 channelcapacity,
10 number speed dial,and an electronic security lock.
This revolution in communicationcould make it possible
for more and more peopleto have a phone in their car!
Tank you.
I am the greatest Kung Fu masterof all time,
right guys?
Thank you!
I'm disarming you.
My arm! My arm!
Kill him!
You don't need that spine,
it's holding your back!
A-ha!
Fuck you Kung Fury.
Now nothing can stop meand my army of death.
Thank you guys!
What the fuck?
Kill them!
Alright Hitler, the gig is up,show me your hands.
Hackerman,have you seen Kung Fury?
Oh, no! We were too late.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Cobra.
I've been expecting you,Kung Fury.
I'm your spirit animal.
What the hell is this place?
This is heaven,I'm afraid you're dead.
What?
But it looks so real.
Yeah, no, it's totally real.
Mr. Cobra, I'm a police officer
and I need you to send meback to earth, pronto.
I'm sorry,I can't help you with that.
You see, you're dead.
- You're under arrest!- What?
For obstruction of justice,you're breaking the law!
What the hell happened?
I hacked away all ofyour bullet wounds Kung Fury.
Thanks!
I want to welcome youand your friends to Germany.
We are not so different,you and I.
I mean we both gotgood style, you know?
With Red, you know?
So, that's cool!
We both like doing moves, yah!Check it out, yah!
Yah!
Good, killing people, I love it,you clearly do, too!
And that's cool!
Join me,
we could be brothers,we are so alike.
It's almost likewe finish each other's...
- Balls.- What?
Oh, my,not much left of him is there?
The important thing is thathe is gone.
Sorry I doubted you Triceracop.
You're the best damn partnerI've ever had.
I came back in timefor you Kung Fury,
because, damn it,I love you.
Team work is very important.
So, what happens now, Kung Fury?
Well, I need tohead back to the office.
Looks like it's gonna behell of a lot of paperwork.
Open the doors, Hoff.
I'm sorry Fury,I can't let you do that.
Open the doors, Hoff!
I'm sorry, I can't let youopen the doors Kung Fury.
Goddammit, open the doors!
- I'm sorry I can't--- Open the doors!
Did anyone ever tell younot to hassle the Hoff 9000?
Oh, Hoff 9000,you son of a bitch.
Piece of shit.
Oh, my,not much left of him is there?
The important thing is thathe is gone.
Game over.
Wait a minute,
I've seen that symbol before...
somewhere.
Hitler!