There was once in venicea moor othello who for
his merits in the affairs of warwas held in great esteem.
It happened that he fell in lovewith a young and noble lady
called desdemona,
who drawn by his virtue,became equally enamoured of him.
So it was that since her fatherwas much opposed to the union
of desdemona with a moor,she fled her house at night.
In secret hastethey were married.
Now there was in othello'scompany, an ensign named lago,
a very amiable outward appearance
but his character wasextremely treacherous.
I have told often andi retell it again and again.
I hate the moore.
I'll poison his delight.
How? How, lago?
Proclaim him in the streets,incense her kinsmen,
and though he in fertile climatedwell, plague him with flies.
No, they come.
What will i do?
Why, go to bed and sleep.
- I'll incontinently drown myself.Oh, bitterness.
What should i do?
Put money in thy purse.
Ere i would say i would drownmyself for love of a guinea
hen, i would change myhumanity with a baboon!
Come, be a man.
Drown thyself?
Drown cats and blind puppies.
It cannot be that desdemonashould long continue her love
to the moor or he his to her.
It was a violent commencement.
And thou shalt see an answerablesequestration,
put buy money in thy purse.
When she is sated with his body
she'll fine the errorof her choice.
She must change, she must,for youth.
Your daughter!
- Look, your house!- Your house!
- Your daughter!- Your daughter!
Senior, is all your familywithin?
Why, wherefore ask you this?
Lf't be your pleasure for yourdull watch o' th' night,
transported, with no worse norbetter guard but with a knave
of common hire, a gondolier,to the gross clasps of a
lascivious moor.
This thou shalt answer!
Straight satisfy yourself, if shebe in your chamber or your house,
lago, can i depend on the issue?
Thou are sure of me.Go, make money.
It is too true an evil.Gone she is.
Is there not charms by whichthe property of youth
and maidhood may be abused?
Call up all my people!
Raise my kindred!
Where is the moor?
Keep up your bright swordsfor the dew'll rust them.
Oh, thou foul thief!
Where hast thou stowedmy daughter?
Hold your hands! Good signor,
where will you that i go toanswer this your charge?
To prison till fit time of law
and course of direct sessioncall thee to answer.
Now at the same hour, therecame messengers in haste
to the senate for there wasnews that the turkish armies
were moving against thevenetian garrison in cyprus.
The senators, already raised
the net, elected the moor to thecommander of their troops.
And officers were searching
the town to apprise othelloof this honor
when lo, desdemona's oldfather himself brings the moor
at sword's point to the councilchamber upon a charge of
working from desdemona withunlawful enchant.
She was abused,
stolen from me and, ay,corrupted by magic spells.
I'm very sorry for't.
If she in chains of magic were notbound, whether a maid so tender,
fair and happy would ever haveto incur her general mock,
run from her father
to the sooty bosom of such afierce bat!
Damned as thou art,thou hast enchanted her!
Othello, what in your own partcan you say to this?
Nothing but this is so!
Did you by indirect and forced
courses subdue and poisonthis young maid of affection?
Most potent grave andreverend signors,
my very noble and approvedgood masters,
that i've taken away this oldman's daughter it's most true.
True i have married her.
The very head and front of myoffending has this extent,
no more.
Rude in my speech,
and little blessed with the softphrase of peace,
since these arms of mine hadseven years' pith till now some
nine moon wasted theyhave used their dearest action
in the tented field and littlelittle of this great world can i
speak more than pertainsto feats of broil and battle.
And therefore little shall i gracemy cause in speaking of myself.
Yet by your gracious patience
i will round unvarnished taledeliver of my whole course of love,
what drugs, what charms,
what conjuration and what
mighty magic, for suchproceedings am i charged withal
that i won his daughter.
Her father loved me, oft
invited me, still questioned methe story of my life.
I ran it through even from my
boyish days wherein i speak ofthe most disastrous chances
of moving accidents by floodand fields of hair-breadth
scapes for the imminentdeadly breach.
Of being taken by insolent foe,and sold to slavery,
of my redemption thence andpotency my travels history
wherein a venturous vast anddesert idle, rough quarries,
rocks and tills whose headstouch heaven.
It was my head to speak.
Rest to hear, but desdemonaseriously inclined.
But still the house affairs woulddraw her thence, which ever as
she could with haste dispatch,
come again and with a greedyear devour up my discourse.
I found good means to draw
from her a prayer of earnestheart that i would all my
pilgrimage dilate, and oftendid beguile her of her tears
when i did speak of somedistressed stroke of my use of it.
She gave me for my pains,a world of sighs.
She swore, in faith: 'twasstrange, 'twas passing strange.
Twas pitiful, 'twas wondrouspitiful.
She wished she had not heard
it, yet she wished thatheaven made her such a man.
She thanked me, and bade meif i had a friend that loved her
i should but teach him how totell my story
and that would woo her.
Upon this hint i spake,
she loved my for the dangersi had passed,
and i loved her that shedid pity them.
This only is the witchcrafti have used.
I think this tale would winmy daughter, too.
Come hither, desdemona.
Do you perceive in all thisnoble company
where most owe you obedience?
My noble father, i do perceivehere a divided duty.
To you i am bound for lifeand education.
My life and education both dolearn me how to respect you.
You are the lord of duty.
I am hitherto your daughter.But here's my husband.
And so much duty as mymother showed to you
preferring you before her father
so much i challenge that imay profess,
due to the moor, my lord.God be with you. I have done.
When remedies are pastthe griefs are ended.
Please it your grace on tothe state affairs.
The turk with a most mightypreparation makes for cyprus.
Othello, the fortitude of theplace is vast known to you.
You must away this morning.
With all my heart.
When we consider the importanceof cyprus to the turk, we must
not think the turk is sounskillful to leave that latest
which concerns them first,
neglecting an attempt of ease andgain to wake and wage a danger.
Look to her, moorif thou hast eyes to see.
She has deceived her fatherand may thee.
My life upon her faith!
Mark me with what violenceshe first loved the moor
but for bragging and dealinga fantastical lie.
Will she love him still for prating?
Ah, let not thy discreet heartthink it.
- Lieutenant cassio.- Largo
what a cannon.
I know my price.
I'm worth no worse a place.
But he, sir, had the election.
And what's he? This michaelcassio, this florentine,
that never set a squadron in thefield nor the division of a battle
knows more than a spinster.Yet cassio must his lieutenant
be, by god bless the mark ofthe fellow's ancient!
Well, i would not follow him that.
Oh, sir, content you.
I follow him to serve my turnupon him.
Lago? Lago!
Honest lago!
I wake up on your lordship.
My desdemona must i leavewith thee.
I pray bring her after good timeto cyprus.
Well, me good lord, i'll do it.
The moor's of a free andopen nature, that thinks men
honest that seem to be so,and will as tenderly be led by
th' nose as asses are.
We cannot all be masters.
Nor all masters cannot bytruly followed.
You shall mark many a duteousand knee-crooking knave who
doting on his own obsequiousbondage wears out his time,
much like his master's ass, fornaught but provender; and when,
he's old, cashiered.
Whip me such honest knaves!
Others there are who, trimmed
in forms and visages of duty,keep yet their hearts attending
on themselves,and throwing but shows of
services on their lords,do well thrive by them, and when
they have lined their coatsdo themselves homage.
These fellows have some soul,
and such a one do i professmyself for, sir, it is as sure
as you're roderigo, werei the moor, i would not be lago.
In following him i followbut myself.
When my outward action dothdemonstrate the native act and
figure of my heart in compliment
extern, 'tis not long after buti will wear my heart upon my
sleeve, for daws to peck at.I am not what i am.
I have but an hour of loveto spend with thee.
We must obey the time.
Oh, lago, what tidings canyou tell of my lord?
He's not yet arrived, but the
turkish fleets be not enshelterdthey are drowned.
It is there! I knowothello's trumpet!
News, lads! News! The desperatetempest hath so banged the turks
that their designment halts.
Our wars are done!
He takes her by the palm.Well said. An excellent courtship.
With as little a web as this will iensnare as great a fly as cassio.
It gives me wonder great as mycontent to see you here before me.
Oh, my soul's joy!
If after every tempest come such
calms, may the winds blowtill they have wakened death.
- My dear othello!- Oh, my fair warrior!
I prattle out of fashion, andi dote in my own comforts.
- Worthy montano, your pardon- sir
good michael, look youto the guard tonight.
Come, my dear love.
Once more well met at cyprus.
It is othello's pleasure thatupon certain tidings now arrived
importing the destruction ofthe turkish fleet, every man
put himself into triumph.
Each man what sport and revelshis addiction lead him.
For, besides these beneficial news,
it is the celebration ofour general's nuptial.
Heaven bless the isle of cyprusand our noble general othello!
First, i must tell thee this.
Desdemona is directlyin love with him.
With cassio?Why, 'tis not possible.
Her eyes must be fed.
And what delight shall shehave to look on the devil?
Very nature will compel herto the second choice.
Now sir, this granted,
who stands so eminent in the degreeof this fortune as cassio does?
Why, none! Why, none!
A slipper and subtle knave,a devilish knave!
- He is handsome.- Cassio?
He has all the requisites in him
that folly and green mindslook after.
Oh, a pestilent complete knave
and the woman hath foundhim already.
I cannot believe that indesdemona.
Did you not see her paddlewith the palm of his hand?
Did not mark that?
Yes, that i did, but that wasbut a courtesy.
Courtesy? Lechery. An index
and obscure prologue to thehistory of lust and foul thoughts.
They met so near with their lipsthat their breaths embraced together.
Villainous thoughts, roderigo.
But, sir, be you ruled by me.
Listen, listen to cassio tonight.Watch him on the court of god.
Cassio knows you not.I'll not be far from you.
Do you find some occasionto anger him from what
other course you please.
Well
sir, he's rash and very sudden
in choler, and haply maystrike at you.
Provoke him that he may,
for even out of that will icause these of cyprus to mutiny
and the displanting of cassio.Lieutenant cassio!
Lago, i'll say, you like mewell, lago?
In the sincerity oflove and friendship.
Come, lieutenant, a stoup ofwine!
Here a brace of gallants that
fain have a measure to thehealth of black othello.
Not tonight, good lago.
I have very poor and unhappybrains for drinking.
Oh, just one cup.
I must to the watch.
Not this hour, lieutenant,'tis not yet ten o' th' clock.
Our general cast us thus earlyfor the love of his desdemona.
He hath not yet made wantonthe night with her
and she is sport for jove.
She's a most exquisite lady.
And full of game, i'll warrant.
What an eye she hasto provocation.
I object, i think right modest.
Well, happiness to their sheets.Another cup, i'll drink for you.
I have drunk two cups andi don't dare not to task
my weakness with any more.
My man, 'tis a night of revels.
I'll do't, but it dislikes me.
If it were now to die, 'twerenow to be most happy,
for i fear my soul hath her content
so absolute that not anothercomfort like to this
succeeds in unknown fate.Ah, brothers on call tonight!
God, an excellent song!
I learned it in england, where
indeed they are most potentin potting.
Your dane, your german,
and your swag-bellied hollander- drink, ho! -
are nothing to your english.
Is your englishman so exquisitein his drinking?
He drinks you with facilityyou dane dead drunk,
he sweats not to overthrowyour almain,
he gives your hollander a vomitere the next pottle can be filled.
To the health of our general!
I am for it, lieutenant, andi'll do you justice.
Good faith, a little one,not past a pint, as i'm a soldier.
Well, god above alland there be souls must be saved,
and there be souls must notbe saved.
It's true, good lieutenant.
For mine own part, no offense
to the general, nor any manof quality, i hope to be saved.
Ay, but, by your leave,not before me.
Do not think, gentlemen,i am drunk.
This is my ancient, my righthand, this is my left.
I am not drunk now. I canstand well enough, and
i speak well enough.
Excellent well!
Very well. You must not thinkthen that i am drunk.
Zounds, you rogue, you rascal!
What noise is this?
A knave teach me my duty?
What's the matter, lieutenant?
I'll beat the knave intoa twiggen bottle.
Away, i say.
Go out and cry a mutiny!
Mutiny! Mutiny! Mutiny!Mutiny! Mutiny! Mutiny!
Stop, lieutenant!
Hold this shame forever!
Have you forgot all place ofsense and duty?
Hold the rage!
Hold, gentlemen!
You're ordered above.Yeah, move, come on!
Why, sir, the generals!
Silence that dreadful bell!
Who began this? Lago.
I do not know.
Friends all, but now, even now,in quarter and terms like
bride and groom devestingthem for bed,
but now swords out and tiltingone at other's breasts.
Worthy montano, what's the matter
that you unlace yourreputation thus and spend your
rich opinion for the nameof a night-brawler?
Your officer, lago, caninform you.
Fortunate. Town of war to manageprivate and domestic quarrel?
In night, and on the courtand guard of safety?
Lago, who began't?
Thou dost deliver more or lessthan truth, thou art no soldier.
I had rather have this tonguecut from my mouth than it should
do offense to michael cassio.
Sir, men in rage strike thosethat wish them best,
yet surely cassio i believereceived from him that fled
some strange dignity, whichpatience could not pass.
I know, lago, the honestyand love doth mince this matter,
making it light to cassio.
Cassio, i love thee,but never more be officer of mine.
Look if my gentle love be notraised up.
I'll make thee an example.
What, are you hurt, lieutenant?Ay, past all surgery.
Marry, heaven forbid!
Reputation, reputation,reputation!
O, i have lost my reputation!
I have lost the immortal partof myself,
and what remains is bestial.
My reputation, lago,my reputation.
Reputation oft got withoutmerit and lost without deserving.
I tell you what you shall do.
Our general's wife isnow the general.
Confess yourself freely to her.
Desdemona is of so free, sokind, so blessed a disposition
she holds it a vice in hergoodness not to do more than
she is requested.
Farewell, lieutenant.
Roderigo.
My money is almost spent,
i have been tonight exceedinglywell cudgeled.
And i think the issue will be,
i shall have so much experiencefor my pains, and so, with
no money at all, and a littlemore wit, return again to venice.
How poor are they thathave not patience!
Does not go well?
Cassio has beaten thee, andthou by that small hurt hath
cashiered cassio.
Content thyself awhile.
For whiles this honest foolplies desdemona to repair
his fortune, and she for himpleads strongly to the moor.
Io, by how much she strives
to do him good, she shallundo her credit with the moor.
So will i turn her virtue into pitch,and out of her own
goodness make the netthat shall enmesh them all.
Do not doubt, cassio.
I'll have my lord and you againas friendly as you were.
Madam, whatever shall becomeof michael cassio, he's never
anything but your true servant.
Ha! I like not that.
What dost thou say?
Nothing, my lord, or if,i know not what.
How now, my lord?
I have been talking witha suitor here.
A man that languishes inyour displeasure.
Who is't you mean?
Why, your lieutenant cassio.
Went he hence now?
I' sooth so humbled that he hathleft part of his grief with me
to suffer with him.
Good love, call him back.
Some other time.
- Shall't be shortly?- The sooner, sweet, for you.
- Shall't be tonight at supper?- No, not tonight.
Tomorrow dinner then?
I shall not dine at home.
I meet the captainsat the citadel.
Why then, tomorrow night.I prithee name the time.
No more. Let him comewhen he will.
I will deny thee nothing.
Whereon i do beseech thee
grant me this to leave mebut a little to myself.
Shall i deny you? No.Farewell, my lord.
- My noble lord.- What dost thou say, lago?
Did michael cassio, when youwooed my lady,
know of your love?
He did, from first to last.Why dost thou ask?
But for a satisfaction of mythought, no further harm.
Why of thy thought, lago?
I did not think he had beenacquainted with her.
O, yes, and went between usvery oft.
- Indeed?- Indeed? Ay, indeed.
Discern'st thou aught in that?Is he not honest?
- Honest, my lord?- Honest? Ay, honest!
My lord, for aught i know.
What dost thou think?
Think, my lord?
Think. Thou dost mean something.
I heard thee say even now,thou lik'st not that,
when cassio left my wife.
If thou dost love meshow me thou thought.
My lord, you know i love you.
I think thou dost.
For michael cassio, i dare
be sworn, i think he is honest.I think so, too.
Men should be what they seem.
Certain, men should bewhat they seem.
Why then, i think cassio'san honest man.
Nay, yet there's more in this?
I prithee speak to me asto thy thinkings.
Good name in man and woman,
dear my lord, is the immediatejewel of their souls.
Who steals my purse stealstrash; 'this something, nothing.
Twas mine, 'tis his, and hasbeen slave to thousands.
But he that flinches from memy good name robs me of
that which not enriches himand makes me poor indeed.
By heaven, i'll knowthy thoughts.
Beware, my lord, of jealousy!It is the green-eyed monster,
which doth mock the meatit feeds on.
That cuckold lives in blisswho, certain of his fate,
loves not his wronger.
But o, what damned minutestells he over who dotes,
yet doubts, suspects,yet fondly loves!
Why? Why is this?
Think'st thou i'd make a life of
jealousy to follow still thechanges of the moon with
fresh suspicions?No, lago, i'll see before i doubt.
When i doubt, prove.I speak not yet of proof.
Look to your wife.Observe her well with cassio.
I know our country dispositionwell.
In venice they do let heaven
see the pranks they dare notshow their husbands.
Their best conscience is not toleave't undone but kept unknown.
Dost thou say so?
She did deceive her father,marrying you.
And when she seemed to shakeand fear your looks,
she loved them most.
And so she did.
Why, go to then! She that soyoung could give out such a
seeming to seel her father'seyes up close as oak.
He thought 'twas witchcraft.But i am much to blame.
I humbly do beseech you of mypardon for too much loving you.
I'm bound to thee forever.
I see this hath a littledashed your spirit.
Not a jot, not a jot.
Trust me, i fear it has.
I hope you will consider whatis spoke comes from my love.
Cassio's my worthy friend.
My lord, i see you're moved!
No, not much moved.
I do not think butdesdemona's honest.
Long live she so.And long live you to think so.
And yet, how nature erringfrom itself
ay, there's the point, as to
be bold with you, not toaffect many proposed matches
of her own clime, complexion,and degree.
One may smell in such a willmost rank, foul disproportions,
thought unnatural.
My lord, i would i might entreatyour honor to scan this thing
no further. Leave it to time.
Farewell.
Leave me, lago.
How now, my dear othello?
My lord, i take my leave.
Are you not well?
I have a pain upon myforehead here.
Why, that's with watching.
It will away again.
Let me but bind it hard, withinhours it will be well.
Your napkin is too little.Let it alone!
I have a thing for you.
You have a thing for me?
It is a common thing tohave a foolish wife.
O, is that all? What will you
give me now for thatsame handkerchief?
What handkerchief?
That which so often youdid bid me to steal.
Give it me.
If it be not for some purposeof import, give't me again.
Poor lady, she'll run mad.
I have use for it. Leave me.
How now, general?
I swear 'tis better to be much
abused than but toknow't a little.
- My lord!- Is my lord angry?
He went hence but now, andcertainly in strange unquietness.
- I will go seek him.- I prithee do so.
There's matter in't indeedif he be angry.
Villain, be sure thou provemy love a whore, be sure of it!
Give me the ocular proof,
or, by the worth of mine eternalsoul, thou hadst been better
have been born a dog thananswer my waked wrath!
Is't come to this?
Make me to see't, or at theleast so prove it that
the probation bear no hingenor loop to hang a doubt on
or woe upon thy life!
Never pray more,abandon all remorse.
For nothing canst thou todamnation add greater than that.
O monstrous world!
Take note, take note, o world!
To be direct and honestis not safe.
By the world i think my wifebe honest, and think she is not.
I think that thou art just, andthink thou art not.
I'll have some proof. Her name,
that was as fresh as dian'svisage, is now begrimed and
black as mine own face.
Would i were satisfied!
How satisfied, my lord?
Would you, the supervisor,grossly gape on?
Behold her topped?
It is impossible you shouldsee this.
Were they as prime as goats,as hot as monkey?
Give me a living reasonshe's disloyal!
I lay with cassio lately, andbeing trouble with a raging
tooth, i could not sleep.
There are a kind of men so looseor should that in their sleeps
will mutter their affairs.
One of this kind is cassio.
In sleep i heard him say,
sweet desdemona, let usbe wary, let us hid our loves.
And then, sir, would he gripeand wring my hand, cry
o sweet creature! Then kiss
me hard as if he plucked upkisses by the roots that grew
upon my lips, laid his leg o'ermy thigh, and sigh, and kiss
and then cry, cursed fatethat gave thee to the moor!
I'll tear her all to pieces!
Tell me but this. Have you notsometimes seen a handkerchief
spotted with strawberries inyour wife's hand?
I gave her such a one.
Such a handkerchief, i'm sureit was your wife's, did i today
see cassio wipe his face.
If it be that
if it be that, or any that was
hers, it speaks against herwith the other proofs.
Now do i see 'tis true.
O, that the slave hadforty thousand lives!
One is too poor, too weekfor my revenge!
- Yet be content!- Blood, blood, blood!
Patience, i say.Your mind may change.
Never, lago. Like to the pontiac
sea, whose icy current andcompulsive course nev'r keeps
retiring ebb, but keeps due onto the propontic and the
hellespont.
Even so my bloody thoughts,
with violent pace, shall nev'rlook back, nev'r ebb to humble
love, till that a capable andwide revenge swallow them up.
Witness that here lago dothgive up the execution of
his wit, hands, heart towronged othello's service.
Within these three days let me
here thee say thatcassio's not alive.
My friend is dead. 'tis doneat your request.
But let her live.
Damn her, lewd minx!
O, damn her!
Now art thou my lieutenant.
I am your own forever.
Cassio! Cassio!
Give me your hand.
This hand is moist, my lady.
It hath felt no age norknown no sorrow.
This argues fruitfulness andliberal heart. Hot, hot and most.
'Tis a good hand, a frank one.
You may, indeed, say sofor 'twas that hand that
gave away my heart.
A liberal hand.
Come now, your promise.
- What promise, chuck?- Let cassio be received again.
Lend me thy handkerchief.
I have it not about me.
- Not?- No, indeed, my lord.
That's a fault. That handkerchief
did an egyptian to my mothergive.
The worms were hallowed thatdid breed the silk.
Then would to god thati had never seen't.
Is't lost? Is't gone?Speak, is it out of the way?
It is not lost.But what an if it were?
How?
I say it is not lost.
Fetch't, let me see it!
Why, so i can, but i willnot now.
This is a trick to put mefrom my suit.
Pray you let cassiobe received again.
- The handkerchief!- I pray talking of cassio
the handkerchief!
A man that all his time hath foundedhis good fortunes on your love,
- shares dangers with you- the handkerchief!
Come, come, you'll nevermeet a more sufficient man.
Away. Away!Away!
Cassio, this handkerchief.Whose is it?
I found it here.I like the work well.
'Tis very good!Shall i see you soon at night?
I will see you soon, bianca.
- Come, lieutenant.- Cassio, handkerchief.
Take it. Have it copiedthee made for it.
Tell you yet once more,
importune desdemona toput you in your place again.
Sure there's some wonderin this handkerchief.
'Tis a year or two showsus a man.
They're all but stomachs,and we all but food. Cassio!
They eat us hungerly, andwhen they're full, they belch us.
How now, good cassio?What's the news with you?
What trumpet is that same?Something from venice.
My noble lord, whilest youwere here, overwhelmed with
your grief, cassio came hither.I shifted him aways, bade him
anon return, andhere speak with me.
Mark the fleers, the gibes,
and notable scorns that dwellin every region of his face.
For i will make him tellthe tale anew,
where, how, how oft, howlong ago, and when he hath
and is again to cope your wife.
I say, but mark his gesture.
Marry patience, or i shall sayyou're all in all in spleen,
and nothing of a man.Dost thou hear, lago?
I will be found most cunningin my patience.
But - dost thou hear? -most bloody.
- How do you know, lieutenant?- Lago.
Now, if this suit lay in bianca'spower,
how quickly should you speed!
Alas, poor caitiff!
I never knew woman loveman so.
She gives it out thatyou shall marry her.
Ay!
I was talking on the sea bank,and the bauble falls me thus
about my neck
so hangs, and lolls, andweeps upon me,
so shakes and pulls me!
- Cassio!- I must leave her company.
What did you mean by that samehandkerchief you gave me even now?
A likely piece of work thatyou should find it in your
chamber and know not wholeft i t there!
This is some minx's token.
I'll take out no work on't.
Now now, my sweet bianca?How now?
After her! After her!
Did you see how he laughedat his vice?
O lago.
Did you see the handkerchief?
Was that mine?
Desdemona gave it him, andhe hath giv'n it his whore.
I had been happy if the generalcamp, pioners and all, had
tasted her sweet body.
So i had nothing known.
What sense had i of herstolen hours of lust?
I saw it not, it harmed me not.
I slept the next night well,was free and merry!
I found not cassio's kisseson her lips.
A fine woman, a fair woman,a sweet woman.
Nay, you must forget that.
Ay, let her rot and perish,and be damned.
No, my heart is turned to stone.I strike it and it hurts my hand.
O, the world hath not asweeter creature!
She might lie by an emperor'sside and command him tasks.
Nay, that's not your way.
Hang her! I do but saywhat she is.
So delicate with her needle.
An admirable musician.
O, she will sing the savagenessout of a bear.
Of so high and plenteouswit and invention
she's the worse for all this.
O, a thousand, a thousandtimes.
Of so gentle a condition?
Ay, too gentle.
Nay, that's certain.Yet the pity of it, lago.
O lago, the pity of it, lago.
I will chop her into messes!
Cuckold me!
- Will you think so?- Think so, lago?
- What, to kiss in private?- An unauthorized kiss?
Or to be naked with herfriend in bed an hour or more
not meaning any harm.
Naked in bed?
But if i give my wifea handkerchief
what then?
Why, then 'tis hers, my lord,and being hers shy may,
i think, bestow't on any man.
By heaven, i would mostgladly have forgot it!
He had my handkerchief!
- Ay, what of that?- That's not so good now.
What if i had said i had seenhim do you wrong?
- Or heard him say- hath he said anything?
He hath, my lord, butno more than
what hath he said?
That he did i know not what he didwhat? What?
Lie.
Lie with her?
With her, on her, what you will.
Damnation!
My lord, i say, othello!
Dost thou mock me?
I mock you not, by heaven.
O now for ever farewellthe tranquil mind.
Farewell content.
Farewell the plumed troops,and the big wars that make
ambition virtue. O farewell!
Farewell the neighing steed andthe shrill trump,
the spirit-stirring drum,th'ear-piercing fife, the royal
banner, and all quality,pride, pomp, and circumstance,
of glorious war.
And o you mortal engineswhose rude throats the immortal
jove's dread clamorscounterfeit.
Farewell! Othello's occupation'sgone!
- God save you, worthy general.- Pray you.
The duke and the senatorsof venice greet you.
I kiss the instrument oftheir pleasures.
Is there division 'twixt my lordand cassio?
A most unhappy one, i woulddo much t' atome them,
for the love i bear to cassio.
My lord?
May be th' letter moved him,for, i think, they do command
him home, deputing cassioin his government.
- Trust me, i am glad on it.- Indeed?
- Why, sweet othello- devil! Out of my way!
I will not stay to offend you.
Truly an obedient lady.
I do beseech your lordshipcall her back.
- Mistress!- My lord!
What would you do with her, sir?
Who? I, my lord?
You did wish that i would makeher turn.
Sir, she can turn, and turn,and yet go on and turn again,
and she can weep, sir, weep.
And she's obedient, as you say,obedient. Very obedient.
Proceed you in your tears.
Concerning this, sir
o well-painted passion!I am commanded home.
Get you away, i'll sendfor you anon.
Sir, i obey the mandate andwill return to venice.
Cassio shall have my place.
You are welcome, sir,to cyprus.
Goats and monkeys!
Is he not light of brain?
He's that he is.
Let me see your eyes.
Look in my face.
Why, what art thou?
Your wife, my lord.Your true and loyal wife.
Had it pleased heaven to try mewith affliction, had they rained
all kinds of sores and shameson my bare head, steeped me
in poverty to the very lips,given to captivity me and
my utmost hopes.
I should have found in someplace of my soul a drop of patinece
but, alas, to make me the fixedfigure for the time of scorn
to point his slow and movingfinger at.
Yet could i bear that too, well,very well.
But there where i have garneredup my heart, where either
i must live or bear no life,the fountain from the which my
current runs or else dries up,to be discarded thence, or
keep it as a cistern for foultoads to knot and gender in.
I hope my noble lordesteems me honest.
O, ay, as summer flies arein the shambles, that quicken
even with blowing.
O, thou weed, who art solovely fair, and smell'st so
sweet, that the sense achesat thee, would thou hadst
never been born!
Alas, what ignorant sinhave i committed?
Committed? A thou publiccommoner, i should make very
forges of my cheeks that wouldto cinders burn up modestly.
Did i but speak thy deeds.What committed?
Heaven stops the nose at it,and the moon winks,
the bawdy wind that kisses allit meets is hushed within the
hollow mine of earth andwill not hear't. What committed?
- Are not you a strumpet?- By heaven you do me wrong!
- Are not you a strumpet?- No, as i am a christian!
- Is't possible?- O heaven forgive us!
I cry you mercy then.
I took you for that cunningwhore of venice that married with othello
how do you, madam?
How do you, my good lady?
Faith, half asleep.
Good madam, what's thematter with my lord?
With who?
Why, with my lord, madam.
Who is thy lord?
He that is yours, sweet lady.
I have none. Do not talkto me, emilia.
I cannot weep, nor answers havei none, but what should go by water
prithee tonight lay on mywedding sheets, remember.
Get me some poison, lago,this night.
I'll not expostulate with her,lest her body and beauty
unprovide my mind again.
Do it not with poison.
Strangle her in her bed, eventhe bed she hath contaminated.
Good, good! The justice ofit pleases.
And for cassio, let me behis undertaker.
Excellent good!
You shall hear more by midnight.
A halter pardon him!
And hell gnaw his ones!
Who should he call her whore?
Who keeps her company?
What time? What place?
What form? What likelihood?
The moor's abused by somemost villainous knave,
some base notorious knave,some scurvy fellow!
Speak within doors.
Some such squire he wasthat turned your wit the steamy
side without and made you tosuspect me with the moor.
Desdemona.
Get you to bed.
Dismiss your attendant there.
Look't be done.
I do not find that thou deal'stjustly with me.
What in the contrary?
Every day thou daff'st mewith some device, lago.
I have wasted myself out ofmy means.
The jewels you have had fromme to deliver desdemona would
half have corrupted a votarist.
You have tole me she hathreceived them, and returned
me expectations and comfortsof sudden respect and
acquaintance, but i find none.
Very well. Go to.
I cannot go to, man,nor 'tis not very well.
I will make myself knownto desdemona.
She will return me my jewels.
If not, i will seek satisfactionof you.
Now i see there's a mettlein thee, and even from this
instant do build on thee abetter opinion than ever before.
Give me thy hand, roderigo.
I protest i have dealtmostly directly in thy affair.
It hath not appeared.
I grant thee it hath not appeared,and your suspicion is not
without wit and judgment.
If thou hast that in thee indeedwhich i have greater reason
to believe now than ever,
i mean purpose, courage, andvalor, this night prove it.
If thou the next night followingenjoy not desdemona,
take me from this worldwith treachery.
There is especial commissioncome from venice to depute
cassio in othello's place.
Why, then othello and desdemonareturn again to venice.
Unless his abode be lingeredhere by some accident, wherein
none can be so determinateas the removing of cassio.
How do you mean, removing him?
Why, by making him uncapableof othello's place.
Knocking him out his brains.
And that you would haveme to do?
I will be near to second your attempt,and he shall fall between us.
I have no great devotionto the deed.
It makes us, or it mars us.
Think on that.
Lago.
Hark! Who is it that knocks?
It is the wind.
I called my love false love.
But what said he then?
O, these men, these men
dost thou in conscience think,tell me emilia, that there be
women do abuse their husbandsin such gross kind?
There be some such,no question.
Wouldst thou do such a deedfor all the world?
Why, would not you?
No, by this heavenly light!
Nor i neither by thisheavenly light.
I might do it as well asin the dark.
Wouldst thou do such a deedfor all the world?
The world's a huge place.
It is a great price for a small vice.
In troth, i think thouwouldst not.
In troth, i think i should.
Marry, i would not do such athing for a joint-ring, nor for
measures of lawn, nor forgowns, petticoats, nor caps,
nor any petty exhibition, butfor all the whole world?
I do not think there isany such woman.
Yes, a dozen, but i do thinkit is their husbands' faults
if wives do fall.
Say that they slack their dutiesand pour our treasures into
foreign laps, or else break outin peevish jealousies, throwing
restraint upon us,or say they strike us.
We have galls, and thoughwe have some grace.
Yet have we some revenge.
Let husbands know their wiveshave sense like them.
They see, and smell.
And have their palates both forsweet and sour, as husbands have.
What is it that they do whenthey change us for others?
Is it sport? I think it is.
And doth affection breed it?I think it doth.
Is't frailty that thus errs?It is so too.
And have we not affections?Desires for sport? And frailty?
As men have?
Then let them use us well,else let them know, the ills
we do, their ills instructs us so.
Good night. Good night.
It is the cause, it is the cause,my soul.
Let me not name it for you,you chaste stars.
It is the cause. Yet i'll notshed her blood.
Nor scar that whiter skin ofhers than snow, and smooth
as monumental alabaster.
Yet she must die, else she'llbetray more men.
Put out the light, and thenput out the light.
If i quench thee, thou flamingminister, i can again they
former light restore, shouldi repent me.
But once put out thy light,those cunning'st pattern of
excelling nature, i know notwhere is that promethean heat
than can thy light relume.
- Othello.- Ay, desdemona.
Will you come to bed, my lord?
Have you prayed tonight,desdemona?
Ay, my lord.
If you bethink yourself of anycrime unreconciled as yet to
heaven and grace,solicit for it straight.
Alas, my lord, what may youmean by that?
Well, do it, and be brief.
I would not kill thyunprepared spirit.
No, heaven forfend!
I would not kill thy soul.
Talk you of killing?
Ay, i do.
Then heaven have mercy on me.
Amen, with all my heart.
If you say so, i hopeyou will not kill me.
Peace! And be still.
I will so, and yet i fear you.
Why i should fear i know not,since guiltiness i know not.
But yet i feel i fear.
That handkerchief!
That handkerchief which i soloved and gave thee,
thou gave it to cassio.
No, by my life and soul!
Send for the man and ask him.
Sweet soul, take heed.
Take heed of perjury,thou art on thy deathbed.
- Lord have mercy on me.- I say amen.
And have your mercy too.I never loved cassion in my life.
I saw the handkerchief.He found it then,
i never gave it to him.
Send for him, let himconfess the truth.
He hath confessed.
What, my lord?
That he hath used thee.
How? Unlawfully?
Ay.
He will not say so.
No, his mouth is stopped.
Honest lago hath takenorder for it.
What, is he dead?
Had all his hairs been lives,my great revenge had
stomach for them all.
Out, strumpet! Weep'st thoufor him to my face?
O, banish me, my lord,but kill me not!
Down, strumpet!
Kill me tomorrow, let melive tonight!
It is too late.
Now how dost thou look now?
Cold, cold, my girl,even like thy chastity!
O cursed, cursed slave!
Whip me, ye devils, from thepossession of this heavenly sight!
Blow me about in winds!
Roast me in sulphur!
Wash me in steep-down gulfsof liquid fire!
O desdemon! Dead desdemon!Dead, o! O!
My lord! My lord!
What, ho, my lord! My lord!
I do beseech you thati may speak with you, my lord.
What, ho, my lord!
I had forgot thee.
O my good lord, yonder...,alas, what cry is that?
Yonder's murders done.
It is the very error of the moon.
She comes more nearer earththan she was wont
and that makes men mad.
Alas! That was my lady's voice.
O! Sweet desdemona!Who hath done this deed?
Nobody, i myself.
Commend me to my kind lord.
You heard her say herself.
It was not i.
She said so. I must needsreport the truth.
She's like a liar goneto burning hell!
It was i that killed her.
She turned to folly, andshe was a whore!
Liar!
Cassio did top her.
Ask thy husband else!
That she was false to wedlock?
Ay, with cassio.
Had she been true, if heavenwould make me such another
world of one entire and perfectchrysolite,
i'd not have sold her for it.
My husband say she was false?
Ay, it was he that told meon her first.
An honest man he is, and hatesthe slime that sticks
on filthy deeds.
She was too fond of hermost filthy bargain.
Peace.
- Do thy worst.- Peace.
This deed of thine is no moreworthy heaven than
thou wast worthy her.
Peace, you were best.
O gull! O dolt! As ignorantas dirt!
I'll make thee known thoughi lost twenty lives.
Help! Help, ho, help!
Murder! Help, ho!
Disprove this villain, if thoube'st a man.
He says thou told'st him thathis wife was false.
I know thou didst not.
Speak, for my heart is full.
I told him what i thought, andtold no more than what he
found himself was apt and true.
But did you ever tell himshe was false?
I did.
You told a lie, upon mysoul, a lie! A wicked lie!
Did you say with cassio?
With cassio, mistress.
Go to, charm your tongue.
I will not charm my tongue.
I am bound to speak.
My mistress here liesmurdered in her bed.
Heaven forfend!
Nay, stare not, masters.
It is true indeed.
Villainy, villainy, villainy!
I think upon it, i think i smell it.
O villainy! I thought so then.
I'll kill myself for grief.
What, are you mad?
Good gentlemen!
I'll charge you get your home.
Let me have leave to speak.
It is proper i obey him,but not now.
Perchance, lago, i willnever go home.
Nay, lay thee down and roar,for thou hast killed the sweetest
innocent that everdid lift up eye.
O, she was foul!
Lago knows that she withcassio hath the act of shame
a thousand times committed.
O heaven!
Cassio confessed it, and shedid gratify his amorous works
with that handkerchief!
Handkerchief!
- 'Twill out, 'twill out!- Hold your peace.
I peace? No! I will speak asliberal as the north!
Be wise.
Heaven! A man, devil didthem all, all, all!
I shame against me,yet i'll speak.
Oh, thou dull moor, thathandkerchief thou speaks of
i found by fortune, and didgive my husband
she was chaste, she loved thee.
She loved thee.
Othello, did you and heconsent in cassio's death?
Ay.
Dear general, i never gaveyou cause.
Othello, your power andyour command is taken off,
and cassio rules in cyprus.
Be not afraid though you dosee me weaponed.
Here is my journey's end.
Here is my butt, the veryseamark of my utmost sail.
Will you, i pray, demand thatdemi-devil why he hath thus
ensnared my soul and body?
Demand me nothing.
What you know, you know.
Are there no stones in heavenbut what serves for the thunder?
I pray you, when you shallthese unlucky deeds relate,
speak of me as i am.
Nothing extenuate, nor setdown aught in malice.
Then must you speak of one thatloved not wisely, but too well.
Of one not easily jealous,but being wrought,
perplexed in the extreme,of one whose hand like the
base indian, threw a pearlaway richer than all his tribe.
Set you down this.