Major Bradbury to communication bridge!
Nuclear com-force to main engine room!
What is it like,
the planet we're approaching?
Nothing but ice and snow.
A barren desert of whiteness.
Scan it with our computer waves.
The enemy's weapons may be
hidden beneath its surface.
Aha!
Looks like the cops.
As Thor, chief of the imperial police,
I order you to surrender at once
Stella, you cheap smuggler
I am police robot M.
You have the right to remain silent.
Go for hyper space.
Let's hope this star-buggy stays together.
What's our chances?
40% total disintegration..
30% molecular ignition..
..20% gamma contamination.
You are very reassuring
I assume that means -
we have a 10% chance
of making it.
Not really!
3% structural collapse
3%...
Alright Alright!
Just keep on course
and get ready
to reenter normal space.
Ready when you are.
We've done it!
Not quite. Look!
The Nutrant star!
If it gets a hold on us,
it'll crush us.
Prepare to release
Ath-Power stage.
Eject!
Ha Ha!
We made it.
Plot us a new course,
so that cop cant find us.
Even as you speak.
It's been taken care of.
There's the border
of the haunted stars.
If we'd traveled
one second further,
we would have wound up
right beside them.
What in the universe is that?
It's a spaceship.
No, its a launch.
Their power is totally down.
Maybe they're wounded,
to weak to send a signal.
I'm gonna have a look.
What's the radiation level?
Normal.
The hull isn't damaged.
I'm going inside.
Is everything alright?
Yes!
Wait a minute..
There's someone here.
He looks like he's hurt pretty bad,
but he's alive
I'll try to get him back to the ship.
I'll help you bring him aboard.
He's dehydrated.
Suffering from exhaustion.
But the launch was full of supplies.
Everything he could have needed.
He's also in chock.
He keeps talking about monsters..
..Red monsters
He wants us to alert someone..
Urgently.
Who?
The Emperor
of the first circle of the universe.
It's the emblem of the chief
officers of the imperial navy.
I'd say red hot potatoes for
small time smugglers on the run like us.
We'll, what do we do?
You go to prison, Stella star.
Your leap through
hyperspace didn’t fool us.
Your friction trail was easy to follow.
Hehehe..
You are completely
surrounded by fighter ships.
This time you've won.
We surrender.
There won't be a next time, Stella Star!
Don't worry.
We'll get out of this.
My Lord!
Yes. What is it Ellrik?
They found one damned survivor.
Right now, the imperial shuttle ship
has taken him to their medical centre.
But his brain seems to
be thoroughly damaged
He will be of no help to them,
to find the ship.
Mhmm..
Come to me, Golem!
I have a simple task for you.
You must not fail me.
Therefore, the great machines
of the central operating system..
..of imperial justice hereby sentence you,
Akton, of ninth Vega..
..to 220 years hard labor
in the prison planet of Ze-com the 3rd.
As for you, Stella Star,
having considered all the arguments..
Studied all the Video-tapes,
the accusations..
..we condemn you to forced labor for life..
..in the penal colony..
..of Nocturne the 2nd
This session is hereby adjourned.
Throw the radium into the furnace.
Careful now.
I said let's go, move!
Faster!
Move, Let's go!
Will you step it up!
Here! You can move faster than that!
Careful with that Radium.
Will you move!
Move down those stairs!
Throw it the furnace!
Do what I tell you!
Where do you think you are.
We haven't got all day!
Alright, 5 minutes of rest
Move quickly now!
Prisoners get back to their posts!
Let's go!
Come on quickly now!
I've been at this for 12 straight hours..
..the radiation will burn my skin off.
Were not slaves.
You'd better work.
If you don’t want the taste of the burning
of their energy whips too.
But there must be a way to escape.
There will be a way, you know.
Blow ups happen.
If I could only succeed
in overfeeding the furnace.
But overfeed it with what?
Energy!
Then a gun ray could be enough.
Planing an escape!
This is what you're gonna get, lady!
You can drop the riffle-ray.
Now turn around.
You!
I bet you never expected to see me here.
And you too.
Poor Stella.
Your escape efforts have been wasted.
OK.
I've lost again.
We were sent to free you,
your sentence has been cancelled.
Have you both gone mad?
I only have logic animotion circuits.
No room for craziness.
Well, I've been assigned
to a top secret imperial mission,
we must now leave and set Akton free.
There, he's yours
My gift to you.
Would I lie to you?
Look, it is the imperial flagship.
Akton, you are gonna meet
some real royalty.
He's here!
There is his holographic image.
His Highness; The emperor
of the first circle of the universe.
I come to you because my faithful robot,
Elle, has told me..
..that you are the only one
who could save us.
You know, you must
be the best pilot in the whole galaxy..
..and you Akton, the best navigator.
Stella, our galaxy is split..
..into 2 waring factions.
Our own and
the one ruled by the evil count..
..Zarth Arn!
From the league of the dark worlds.
Recently we've begun to receive troublesome
reports from our spies among the league.
They have informed us
that the count has created a weapon..
..a new, limitless weapon.
A Weapon so vast, so huge..
..that it would take
a whole planet to conceal it.
That is why we sent the mission ship.
Did they find the planet?
The ship came so close..
..so close..
..to discovering the counts secret..
.. when it was suddenly attacked
by a horde of unknown monsters.
We had assumed it was destroyed,
we lost all hope.
Until you found the launch from that ship.
And now, with the utmost secrecy..
..you must sail to the haunted stars.
You must find that ship.
Find the counts secret
planet and destroy it.
There's something else.
When you complete the mission..
.. search for the commander..
..of that missing ship.
He was my only son.
The first possibility is the Origa system.
Also know as the worlds asleep.
But this system is still within our galaxy
and we should've found it by now.
The same also applies
to the white sun of Ohzon
so only the third possibility remains:
The heart of the haunted stars.
An unknown planet named..
Euraphas!
Well, shall we begin our search?
Lets go!
The distance we must travel is enormous.
By using hyperspace,
what would normally take 2 months to reach
We should do in 2 hours.
Everything ready?
Ready! Right!
Every time I go into hyperspace
I get nervous.
Prepare for re-entry to normal space.
We've arrived!
Its not very far from here.
You can reach by using the space shuttle.
Thor and I will wait for you there.
Hidden in that canyon.
So that were ready in case of another
surprise attack of the count.
That sounds fine with me.
Is there air out there?
Yeah. Yeah you can breathe.
Alright. lets go!
Follow me!
I'm sure you can operate the shuttle ship.
The controls are easy!
Now watch your step right here.
Take care.
You alright?
You bet. Lets go.
Don't you think were a little low?
I haven't been programmed to walk on water.
Ohh me. water makes me so nervous
Everything makes you nervous.
It's the launch.
Lets land.
OK! Take it in easy.
Shuttle to star-ship!
We are landing now.
Roger. Out.
My seat-belt’s stuck.
Oh Elle, come on!
Take it easy, I'm coming.
Look at that!
Amazing!
It's almost buried.
The impact was tremendous.
I doubt if anyone could have survived.
The nuclear exhaust ports
have been gutted by fire.
We'd better look around.
What's that?
I don't know.
Seems to be a planetary artifact.
Well, it certainly is an antique.
Looks like some sort of Laser spear.
This planet is inhabited.
We must be very careful.
We are in the evil counts domain.
These stars are extremely far
and remote, even for him.
Probably they've set up
a fully independent kind of civilization.
We're wasting time. We'd better
start looking for the missing crew.
Come on. Lets go this way.
Look!
Amazons on horseback.
I hope they are friendly.
We'll soon find out.
Take my revenge.
Kill 'em.
Die robot.
You'll pay for this -
All of you!
Don't make us kill you.
Come on!
Stop!
There is no escape.
Take your hands off of me.
Let me go.
Get your hands off of me.
Queen Querrelia. This
is the spy we captured.
She came through the forbidden sea.
You're a spy.
As the men from the launch were too.
But nothing
is going to stop the count anymore.
Even if you had passed by this world..
..you'd never
be able to discover the counts planet.
Two packs of murdering guardians are there
to watch and protect it from intruders.
..and now:
Put her into the mind probe.
No! No!
Hold it right there!
Elle!
Release her or I'll blast your queen.
I mean it.
Come on now.
Don’t you people move or you are dead.
Give me the trouble and I'm
gonna clean out your sinuses real good lady
Now you stand there.
Ok, Close the door.
Don’t you follow us now.
Stop them!
Behind you!
Come on, lets go!
Elle you're terrific.
I didn't know you had it in you.
Where's the release mechanism?
It's jammed!
Take cover!
Here goes the last shot.
Full power!
Come on, lets go!
Hurry! Hurry!!
Guardian..
..take my revenge.
Kill them.
Look!
Whoa!
Run for your life!
There! That narrow
passage in the rocks.
Come on Stella, run!
Hurry!
Oh! Elle!
We better move!
The amazon air-fighters will be here soon.
Quick, to the ship!
They're attacking.
I'll man the laser-canon.
Specter 7..Fire!
Ok, get ready.
Here they come.
Power is up to full battle speed.
You!
Why don't you come back now?
Here they come. Specter 3.
Alright.
We've got them!
Fire! Fire!
Yeah!
One more.
There's one more!
We've got 'em.
Watch out on the right.
We're down from 6 to 5.
Get ready.
More to the left.
Steady.
Then fire 5.
Then 6.
Fire the laser-canon, robot.
Fire!
Yeah! Hahaa!
We got it!
We're holding.
Now!
8 ships approaching from the right. Fire!
Alright, we've won.
We did it.
I found the positions
to both the 3rd launch and the mother-ship.
The mother-ship is closest
so we'll check it out first.
It's here.
On the 3rd planet
of the next solar system.
I've never been there.
What's it like?
Red fogs, high winds, low gravity.
The air is breathable.
And the atmospheric conditions are stable.
However..
The entire planet
is covered with ice and snow.
And you must
be extremely careful when the sun sets.
The temperature drops
thousands of degrees.
And in an instant, everything freezes over.
What a terrible crash.
No-one could have survived.
Do you see any signs of the emperors son?
If he's in the middle of all this
I don't even know
if his own mother would recognize him.
Then it's all over.
There's no hope of ever
finding the counts secret fortress.
There's still the third launch.
It's probably
lost out in the stars, who knows?
Anyway, it's useless
to raise false hopes.
It's been too long.
And this galaxy is wild and hostile.
Come on Elle, lets go back to the ship.
We'd better hurry.
We're running out of time
and our power-packs are nearly finished.
Let's get rid of them.
It's gonna be a long walk back.
My feet are already cold.
It's times like these
i'm glad to be a robot.
What's the matter with you, Akton?
Well, I'm just refining my powers.
And what's your problem,
ships-computer, huh!
Is everything alright with Stella and Elle?
I'm not worried about them.
I'm just waiting.
Your waiting is over.
At last Thor.
You have some good news for me?
Yes Excellency.
I have killed the alien pathfinder..
..and taken over this ship.
What of Stella Star?
And that tin policeman.
This planet
will take care of them, Excellency.
Good!
And I await your immediate arrival.
Elle, how much further?
We should be close.
Just a few more radiants.
Ships-computer!
Why aren't the main engines firing?
There is a malfunction.
A malfunction?
Where?
I am not programmed for this malfunction.
Akton!
We're here!
Akton! Thor!
Let us in. The sun is setting.
That's exactly why I'm not letting you in.
Soon you'll be dead and
I'll be gone from this planet.
Have you gone crazy? Open this hatch!
No!
Where's Akton?
Akton is dead.
And I'm leaving to join Count Zarth-Arn..
..as the prince of the League of Darkness.
Thor, a traitor?
I cannot believe it.
I cannot trust
my own logic circuits anymore.
He fooled me too.
It's no use. We're gonna freeze.
Maybe not.
Maybe I can save you.
Let's stop here.
Now you lie down in the snow, face up.
Okay.
Now give me your hand
so I can monitor your temperature.
I can use my energy
to keep your heart working.
You'll be in a state
of suspended animation.
Elle!
As an opponent, I always knew
you were programmed to never give up.
Which was infuriating.
But now that quality..
..must be..
..best.
You are the most faithful companion
a woman ever had.
And I too, respect you, Stella.
You are the nicest human being I've known.
Now, maybe, is a good time
to use your ancient system of prayer.
And hope it works for robots, as well.
Goodbye my friend.
Goodbye for now, Stella.
You were expected here hours ago!
I've been delayed by a malfunction.
I don't tolerate malfunctions..
..or inefficiency here in my realm
How long will the delay be?
I think a very long time.
You shouldn't try taking off
without asking me first.
This time I'll make sure you are dead.
I'll fix you.
Alright Akton.
This is it.
Say goodbye.
What?
Stop!
Put down the gun.
No-one can survive these deadly rays.
Those deadly rays will be your death.
Elle?
Elle, do you read me?
This is Akton.
I've taken over the ship.
Do you read me?
Her pulse rate is 16.
She may survive if you can use your powers
and bring her back slowly.
Careful now.
Close the hatch.
Look! It's working!
She's going to make it.
Come on Stella!
Whats wrong?
The main engines will not fire.
Thor must have tried everything.
What are we gonna do now?
So..We get out of one mess..
..just to find ourselves in another.
Not necessarily.
What do you mean?
We are stuck!
Even the transmitter is out of order.
We can take off immediately.
Take off?
How?
The ship is not operating,
simply because I borrowed this reactor.
Then you knew about Thor.
Yes I did.
So you see into the future.
All these years you never told me.
Think of all the trouble
I might have avoided
You have tried to change the future.
Which is against the law.
So therefore, I can tell you nothing.
Let's find the 3rd launch.
Akton, you are something else!
Yes.
Time is running out.
Lets go!
We're arriving.
That's the planet Demundia.
There in barren land
and wast emptiness
we'll find the 3rd launch.
Somethings wrong.
Everything has stopped.
What's happening?
Power failure!
My circuits!
My circuits are failing.
We've been hit.
By an energy beam.
I am out of control.
Look!
What is it?
It must be the Counts weapon!
Oh my head, oh!
Fire, you stupid robot!
Fire!
What's happening?
Here, let me help you.
The attack is over.
You'll be alright.
I thought I was gonna go insane.
We've just survived an attack
of the most powerful weapon
in the entire galaxy.
If Akton's calculations
are correct
we should find the launch this way.
In a crater just over..
There!
Oh me!
Don't say it. Don't say
I know..
Steam makes you nervous.
No, no! Not really.
Why should I be nervous?
There is nothing
to be afraid of round here.
Looks totally wrecked
but it's definitely the third launch.
I'd better go down.
No, I insist.
Time for a little robot-chauvinism.
You stay here.
Be careful Elle.
You do not have to worry about me!
Release her!
Let me down!
Help!
Don't.. Don't..
Relax.
Take it easy.
I'll cut you down.
There.
You're free.
That was a little too close for comfort.
Come on.
Come on!
We rest here.
This is safe.
Who are you?
This is an energy-shield mask.
And the amount of energy is limited.
My name is Simon.
I'm the only survivor
from the wreck of an imperial mission.
Are you really?
We've been searching for you
all through these damned haunted stars.
Why?
The emperor's orders
were to find the Count's phantom planet
and to destroy it.
So you know about the monsters?
Yes I do.
But it's useless.
We did not succeed
in find the planet either.
And now there's no time left.
The cavemen will waiting for us.
Alright, stay very close and very quiet.
Oh, this way looks safe.
This way.
Simon!
No!
Akton!
You alright?
Akton, thank god you got here in time.
You must've known all along.
By the way, this is Simon.
The only survivor
from the imperial mission.
We owe you our lives.
Now maybe..
..with your help, we can still
find the Count's phantom planet
Lets go aboard your ship
and continue on at once.
There's no need to continue.
Have you gone crazy?
That's our primary mission: To
find the planet and destroy it.
I know,
but we've already found it.
Think about it.
Then you'll understand that
this is the Count's planet.
Remember what the Amazon queen said:
A planet occupied
by two packs of evil defenders.
The first we met while in space.
The red monsters.
And the second..
Right here. The Troglodytes.
And there’s no question about it.
This is the planet!
This?
That's incredible.
I was here and I didn't even realise it.
There's no way you could have.
Anyway, we proceed at once
and destroy all that machinery.
Right?
Right.
There is the door
that'll take us to the machinery.
This is the Counts secret domain.
The very heart of the phantom planer.
From here he plan to control
the entire universe.
This is incredible.
Where is everybody?
Everything is set in our destiny.
Soon you'll know all the answers.
This will take
us to operation headquarters.
After you, my dear.
Here's the nerve center
of the entire operation.
This is unbelievable.
Fantastic.
Pre-programmed computers.
They could run forever.
All these power modules,
what are they for?
This is the force
that projected the red monsters into space.
Then this is the way
they produced real monsters?
No. Not real.
The monsters never existed.
These machines discharged mental
projections of monsters in our brains
There's the control-panel.
Well, destiny must take it's course.
No, we can't allow this to happen.
We must destroy it, at once.
You've been very lucky.
And clever.
You survived every trap
that I'd lay for you.
Then I realized that your success
would become my triumph.
How much time is left, Captain?
Half a quadrant to go, My-lord.
You hear?
In less than an hours time
All that'll be left of this planet
Will be ashes and cosmic dust.
Forever.
Then you will be among the dead.
The emperor will make you pay for this.
The Emperor?
I forgot to inform you..
..that the Emperor will be
blown to pieces along with the rest of you.
Yes!
I told the emperor
that we had found you on this planet.
He's on his way here now, at top speed.
He'll get here just in time..
..to join the fireworks.
I'm sorry, your highness.
You've lost.
Highness?
Forgive me Stella.
But in the beginning
I didn't know whose side you were on.
And after-wards
I didn't know how to tell you
Yes, he is Simon, son of the Emperor
and heir to the throne.
You two are to prevent them
from leaving this room at all cost.
You will stay with them until the end.
Kill them..
..if you have to.
Now it will be just a matter of waiting.
An hour goes by quickly.
We've got to get past those golems.
Yes, but how?
Have faith.
And never give up hope.
Look out!
We are now approaching Demundia.
All crewmen to landing stations.
Don't worry.
You and the prince will live.
Akton, you've got to get up.
We must get away from here.
I shall remain here.
Please get up, please.
I'm no longer useful at this time.
You're talking nonsense.
You can heal yourself in no time at all.
No.
I must obey destiny.
Akton!
We'll carry you.
Go.
It's your duty.
You must live.
I can't.
I can't leave you.
You're the only human-like
friend I ever had.
I don't understand. You never die.
Stella, Stella.
I've accomplished the mission.
Yes, but I..
Others are coming.
Even as I speak they'll rescue you.
Don't worry.
I'll live forever.
Now go.
Go.
Father!
We must leave at once.
48 seconds left to the explosion.
We've got to get out of here.
It's true father.
The Count has mined the planet
with nuclear charges.
We're all about to die.
You know something, my boy?
I wouldn't be emperor
if I didn't have some powers at my command.
Imperial battle-ship!
Holt..
..the flow of time.
In the space of 3 minutes
Every molecule on this planet
will be immobilized.
But after the third minute
The green ray loses it's power.
Time will flow once again.
And everything will explode.
Three minutes are enough, father.
Now, the Count believe that we are dead.
That our armies have dispersed.
And that we have no leader.
He is supremely confident that he can
overcome us with the greatest of ease.
Well then.
Now is the time to surprise him.
We will attack his headquarters
before his fleets can join him.
If we succeed in this
we could save billions of lives.
Gather together all our legions.
Sir!
And order the attack.
By sunset,
I'll be the new Emperor.
And I will be the master
of the whole universe.
Kill them!
Enemy arriving with torpedoes.
Prepare for attack.
Kill! Kill!
Over there.
We've got them, father.
It's working
Kill!
Kill them!
Let's squad. Come on
Over there, quickly.
Now let's give the Emperor
a great reception.
Put in use the mightiest weapon.
The doom-machine.
Send it off to towards
the Emperor's capital world
and destroy the emperor's imperial planet.
Zarth-Arn!!
Yeah!
It's over.
We're finished.
We've lost.
No.
No, there's still a way.
There's one solution left.
I'm afraid we're forced to use it.
What?
Starcrash!
Four dimensional attack.
Yes!
If we can re-enter space
at the precise moment
the impact of surprise upon the Count
will be so overwhelming
that he cannot halt us.
But father,
there is not a weapon powerful enough.
Oh yes, there is.
The floating city.
Yes, yes I know.
Although we destroy it's
hope, it's future..
..I'm afraid we must sacrifice it.
By setting it towards the Count's fortress.
It's our only way.
Now you must help me.
Both of you.
Go!
And direct it's course.
Zoltan!
Yes, my-lord.
Now set the doom-machine
against the imperial space station itself.
How long will it take?
15 minutes.
The set it in motion.
I want to wipe out the Emperor
from the whole of the universe.
Yes, my-lord.
When do we reach the floating city?
In less than 2 minutes.
Right. I'll check the docking facility.
Right!
Everything checks out OK.
Look!
The floating city.
Already evacuated.
The technicians have already set the
charges and freed the atomic engines.
If everything goes smoothly
I'll try to eject myself
as soon as I re-enter space.
But surely I'll come with you!
No, no, no!
It's more important that you stay here
to rescue me once this is all over.
Alright.
I'll stay.
But I cannot let you go alone.
In fact our best scientists
have spent the last
few hours reconstructing
an old friend of yours.
Elle!
You can't keep a good robot down.
This is incredible, they rebuild you.
But how?
You look marvelous.
Very carefully.
And they used the latest components.
I feel like a new machine.
Go now. Quickly!
The survival of our galaxy
is in your hands.
This will take us directly
to the control-room.
We have a lot to do in a very short time.
Get ready to ease out of orbit.
This doesn't make you nervous, does it?
I've never flown a city before.
Well, leave it to me.
Build up maximum energy.
We must leap
through the very heart of the stars.
Prepare to transit. 8 degrees.
Ok. I'm ready.
My-lord!
Yes Ellrik?
A floating ship is about to crash into us.
What?
Zoltan!
Yes my-lord.
Destroy the floating ship approaching us.
It can't be done.
It's too close.
There it is. Dead-ahead.
Alright!
The Count's fighters.
We've got to evade them.
All systems prepare for full power.
Let's lock in these controls.
Move it out. Quick.
Right!
Let's go!
Come back, you fools.
You cowards.
Come back and fight.
My-lord?
Yes!
Come, or you'll be destroyed.
You stay here.
Go!
Let's get out of here or there won't be
enough left of me to put back together.
You can bet on that!
Circuits, don't fail me now.
Zarth-Arn!! Zarth-Arn!!
It's Simon. Simon!
We're over here.
Stella. Stella!
And welcome home.
Stella!
Simon!
Ah Stella.
Simon.
Is that so.
Well..
It's done
It's happened.
The stars are clear.
The planets shine.
We've won.
Oh, some dark force no doubt
Will show it's face once more.
The wheel will always turn.
But for now it's calm.
And for a little time..
..at least..
..we can rest.