Sub by Sayok88
It is a Translation by software so
quit whinning
In a Nearby galaxy
It is part of virgo
Are there a life?
If no signs of life there,
what their standards?
Prepare equipment
nearby galaxy, we found something moving very fast
Please
What the hell is that?
I had never seen a vehicle like that
It looks just as ancient transportation
Well, it's next target is a galaxy
First, we landed on the planet's normal
and see the condition of the surrounding
We went with the speed of light
Departure ..!!
Do you guys ever heard of the express train?
Where to dismissal
very confidential, cool right?
And the dismissal is
in places very amazing
To get tickets is very difficult to
Many people who want to buy
I got 3 tickets
Who wants to come with me?
I wanted
Well if so
But what Nobita, he also wanted to be sure
Shizuka, I will not ask
Oh, he come .. he might hear us
Nobita ..
You want to ask me so I can go, right?
But sorry tickets are already full
I do not care
Do you see Doraemon?
It's been 3 days he did not come home
He never went for it, without asking first
to me
Maybe he had an accident
Or maybe there is someone targeting pockets of magic
You do not say no-no ..!
I'm so worried about him
If something happened to him ..
I do not know what else to do...
Do not worry ..
I'm sure Doraemon'll be fine
That's right
My cat has also been missing for
1 week, but in the end returned to the house
The saying is true Suneo
You must install doraemon photo posters all over the place
Do not forget to place shelter animals
He's not an animal ..
DORAEMON....
Translate By: Ghie Lhanx
http://www.ghie-lhanx.com
17 Doraemon Movie Nobita and the Galaxy Superexpress
Welcome Watching
I'm home ..
Where have you been?
Doraemon looking than earlier
Huh, Doraemon?
Nobita, be careful ..!
Good
Doraemon
Why so late, exhausted from where have you been?
I should be asking you ..!
I was very troubling to you
Sorry .. sorry ..
I'm no purpose, so
I have to go to Century 22
Purposes what?
I went to buy tickets
What ..! You go for it
just to buy a ticket?
This is a mystery train tickets,
a lot of people in the age 22 who want membili tickets
mystery train  22 century ..?
So I queued for
3 days to get tickets
This is it "Mystery Train Ticket"
You know why he went so long
That's because he was buying a train ticket
mystery
Trains  this mystery is a
spaceship shaped rail
The pemberangkatannya from the central station galaxy, and the dismissal so in secret
The amazing thing is, all the passengers
no one knows where the place dismissal
I would like to invite you, too,
but it seems you already have an appointment
Go into space, it seems very interesting ..
Ah, I've regretted that
had made the wrong decision
What? would you say if I invited
where it is not attractive?
Anyway, the place is very dangerous space
There are very dark place, then vacuum
And there are many evil aliens
Dan will have an accident,
then sucked into a black hole
Then you will stay there for
forever and not be able to return to Earth
Is that true?
Doraeemon
I think it is highly unlikely if the train mystery
experienced anything like it
mystery train is actually a spaceship
type ships that are not used anymore because of the changing times
and
maketh a vehicle for sightseeing
In the past, it was used as a means of transportation
very
important to have inter-galaxy
But now it is no longer a vehicle that uses
Since the advent of tools called Door Where Only
And now the vehicle is only used as a vehicle for sightseeing
only
Oh, thank goodness ..
So so so story
Absolutely
Approximately how  days for this trip?
I still do not know
Since galaxy is a vast place
But we do not have to worry
Because we can go home at any time using the
Doors Where Only
true is not it?
Wow, really great
Thanks a lot Doraemon
Sounds very interesting ..
I can not wait...
We've reached the edge of the galaxy that
First, we find an uninhabited planet
planet  But it seems there is only
rocks only, no other option
Okay, now we landed
and build a base
toothbrushes, bath soap, comic books ..
I think you do not need all that
Let's quickly go
Do not forget to turn off the lights
Okay
Also do not forget the window
would be a problem if the mother finds out.
The station was where?
Train fire will wait for us at the top of the hill school
Here? but when the train will arrive?
Exactly at 12
And do not be late even though only 1 minute
My heart was pounding
I'm as
Ah, I slept first yes
Do not stay long yes
It ..!
Ah...
Well, it's huge
Let's quickly run
What is totally outer space wagon
Yeah right, how cool is it?
Carriage in which we exist?
Our carriage at no 7
here, Excuse me ..
Excuse me ..
Let's see...
Well,, huge
What is true is on the train?
In each car there are 5 rooms
Equipped with meeting
and the bathroom too
Awesome ..
But why so quiet here?
Hello conductor ..
Two passengers of the earth has gone up ..
Odd
Ah, train set
No conductor or masinisnya ..
It's a very mysterious train ..
Ah, the earth looks smaller ..
Are you sure you'll be fine?
Do not worry
Besides the ticket price is also very expensive...
It would be fine ..
Unfortunately Shizuka could not join
And here are 5 rooms
What...
But he was already involved with Suneo
Okay ..
Better now we see room
You want the room where?
I'm in room no. 1
If so I'm in the room no. 2
Okay
Wow, this is too big for the room occupied alone
Ah, definitely padded mattress
Squishy once ..
"Thank you for join this trip '
' Every passenger should be taking this"
"That way you will be able to survive in space"
"you will feel comfortable, without worrying
more oxygen and high temperatures "
This way I do not have anymore space suits
Ah, what's this button?
Well, I could look out the screen
red planet that seems so close
Surely it is the planet Mars
And it's definitely a collection of asteroids
Nobita Hey, let's take a look at the other cars
Good
As if this train has how many cars?
Hm .. if not one was 58 carriages...
Hah, 58 carriage?
When viewed from the outside still only 8 carriages
But actually there are 120 cars you know ..!
What, 120 wagon?
There are so many cars here,
I'm not strong anymore ..
Wait ..
Not so fast way ..
Doraemon ..!
What is Nobita?
A.. There is a ninja
appears from the outside that window
Ninja?
There's nothing here
You must be exhausted, so the illusion
a no-no ..
With this you will not be tired anymore
Why did not before ..
Not
suspect in the train station using bamboo propellers hehe ..
So once plush
How nice, right?
Wah...
Let's get down
Good
beautiful scenery
I want to show it to shizuka ..
You can tell this to her klo gone home ..
True
What is it?
Jupiter
Planet Jupiter? huge ..!
Jupiter is the largest planet that is
in our solar system
Is that so?
Passenger Earth
Welcome
Can I see tickets
Do you masinisnya?
Where were you?
Since the head office has called me
So I just got back
right  Sorry I
Here there are about 600 people on board
Since this is a long journey
They are all resting in his room each each
There is also a home using only kemene Doors
Do you want to drink juice?
If you INGN food
I can send it to your rooms
Thanks
Soon
This train will jump into the space and time
So we could not see anything
This will take a while
Let's go back to the room
At start here
You will see a virtual image
Ah, very boring, I've decided
Let's go back to the room
You sleepy huh?
I went first, yes, good evening
Congratulations to rest
You look
Apparently there are also other passengers, yes!
Goodnight
See you tomorrow
Before sleep, pee first ah...
Private bathrooms
Really fancy one
There's something in the mirror
nothing
Huh?
There was an emerging
Maybe you sleepy
So hallucinating again ..
But I really see it!!
Get back to your room  ..
I'm afraid
Please let me sleep with you ..
Here there is no place anymore ..
I'm afraid to sleep alone
We sleep together, yes ..!
You is how Nobita?, Klo
which way I'm going to bed?
Nobita, wake up ..!
Let's go home
But I'm still sleepy ..
You can be too late to go to school
Huh, school?
We come back here after you get home from school
let
n
We home
Nobita, let's get some breakfast!
Yes
It's not just as a train that normally
So comfortable, the service is very satisfying
Can see into space ¥ X ¥ h
Jupiter, Saturn looks very beautiful
Not  departure tonight?
So, enjoy your trip ..
See you later ..
Why are you silent?
If you want to talk just say it ..!
I know, you also will want to go with
Nobita, right?
True, right?
Then go ..!
I will not forbid
After all it is your right
I thought you were my best friend
I hate you all ..!
Wait Suneo
We did not mean it like that
Why is he so angry?
Let's go to the house Nobita and
so we can ask him to come with him
But...
Good evening ..
My good friend, we should take it with you?
I already know you'll be here
Come please log
true?
Ah, Giant Suneo what?
Anyway do not mind him
Permissions
Mom, we'll learn together
So do not bother us, yes ..!
Excuse me ..
Please login ..
You want to study with you?
Learning diligent ya ..!
Okay ..
But we have not been informed Suneo
- Hey ..
- Hah, you ..!
I come faster, hehe ..
Basic liar
You are also the same, right?
- You
- It's not a fight ..!
This is the Super Galaxy Express
It is on the train?
As in any hotel
Superb all
conductor trains, I carry passengers again ..
Let's go to my room
I'd like a room no. 5
my room at no. 4
And I'm in the room no. 3 ..!
Well, after you save a picture of your things © ñ
n «á
We headed to the sights
Good
I'll wait for you in the meeting room
I can not wait... ª º
Giant, open the door ..
What? There cowboy? ..
Give him to me...
Hey, is not no one...
He was here
And bring a gun
You come on...
Basic cowards...
But I actually shot at him earlier ..
Really weird ..
Ninja, the creature in the mirror, then cowboy ..
Then there would be anything else right?...
Nobita ..
Ah ..
Ready
Off we go ..!
Right
Where are the others?...
Do not know
You go ahead only
Fabulous, Here are 3 dimensional game
It is very satisfactory service ..
We came here not for something like that ..! ¥ h
Oh well we go alone
Yeah, I think they also need peace
What place is still far away?
There, the landscape is very nice ..
How? the landscape is very beautiful is not it?...
A beautiful view? where?
But first there too!
Nobita, why be like this?
I do not know.
Nobita, are you okay? ..
Nobita
What is it? Let me see .. ¬ Ý ¬ Ý
Do not worry, this is only a mild head injury
Let him rest a little
He would realize more
thankfully ..
But why the sudden glow?
"Beginning of the creation of a galaxy"
In other words ..
This place will menampilakan visual images
Yang recounts the beginning of the creation of a galaxy
Because the trains are on time and space
So this show was at the start
Ah, Nobita it turns out you're awake? ..
Thankfully ..
Where is this?
Look ..!
A visual performances
"Cosmic Era"
"occurred over the past 10 years"
"Virgo is our galaxy .."
I do not understand ..
Let's go back to the room and play video games
I'm here alone
Okay, so if I want to find doraemon
Now more crowded than last night
You where doraemon?
Nobita...
What is Suneo?
A.. No
What is it?
® ü ... Pirates
pirate?
True, I saw a terrible pirate
He's in my room
You can also view it
Ah, .. Giant
® £... ® £ Di .. Dinaosaurus
Dinosaurs?
He came and broke the glass...
What? ..
Will you look into...
No nothing...
Glass which are solved by it?
There ..
Why?
I sure see it ..!
If I did not believe you at
Yes, I believe...
Previously I've said if
I saw a cowboy, right?
I saw a pirate
We have to ask this to doraemon
Shizuka ..
Do you see doraemon?
He's not here...
He goes everywhere huh ..?
Doraemon  ..
Ah, you guys...
You out of nowhere?
We seek you out earlier ..
You follow me
I'll explain everything in the meeting room
What happened?
What is it exactly?
What is it?
- What's going on?
- Is something wrong?
Here ..
Train company is providing emergency alerts
What? mission thieves? ..
The mission of the Black Shadow in mysterious
They've landed in this galaxy
And make a base in an uninhabited planet
A base?
They come with using the spacecraft
I've never heard of them
We do not believe this is happening
She said this trip is guaranteed safe
Now what should we do?
Better for you to go to your room and lock the door
And pray lah ..
Why did you take us into dangerous
trip like this ..
What?
You are asking yourself right?
What did you say?
I want to go home ..
Oh, yes ..!
We can kembai the door anywhere, right?
Ah. very true
Why not occurred to me ya ..
If black shadow appeared ..
Then all the passengers and no masinisnya
They can not do anything about it
So their plan was going to fail ..
Let's go home
Good
Please
Ah, the doors closed
Perhaps the black shadow had mengkuncinya
Their actions really clever
Now it is no longer a way out
The train is already out of space and time
Now being in the universe
Train is entering a collection of small planets plenet-high speed
It will probably take quite a while
So be careful ..
Mom ..
Why would eventually be like this?
Hey, guys ..!
Do not you realize something?
As it is today ..
Before, we always had a dangerous adventure
..
No matter what, we
always together and fight to the end ..
Let's do the same thing
There is no other option, we have
fight against them until the end ..
Nobita suddenly talking like that
It's remarkable...
Good word once
If they were to attack
Let us versus them together
Good
We were villains ..
"Circle Invisible Wall"
Nobita you go into the hole and saw the situation beyond
Be careful ..!
Why?
As if being in space
bamboo blades will not be able to use the
So yes
Wah ..
Nobita, watch out
I remember something ..
"Shoes And Gloves Anti Slippery"
With this there is nothing to worry about anymore
It's like the frog only
Let's go ahead
There is a man ..
Ah, chief machinist
guys, here is very dangerous ..!
But you're doing here?
Does not matter with
carriage without anyone driving?
Train is on the run automatically
You are here too I suppose?
You are...
I Bam ..
A reporter
Nobita  Do you?
I robot doraemon
May I ask?
Why would a journalist participating in this trip?
I just was on vacation ..
But just as it happened
Ah.
There are a shining
There
Anything else ..!
One by one, the light emerging from behind a rock ..
It was definitely the black shadow
And give signals to others
Then waiting to attack us
Is that a gun?
This is not just a shot emergency signaling
But it's better than nothing at all
They come ..!
Here, let me do it.
This is not a toy ..
Do not worry, after all ..
Nobita very proficient at shooting
Success
They are coming more and more
Fast  ask for help
What should I do? ..
I do not know ..
Success again ..
You really terrific
Do not be happy first
Doraemon
Ah, we shall fall
We are heading to a planet that had smoke ..
What is this?
Nobita ..
Where is this?
Is this heaven?
It's not possible...
But, wagon looks fine
What really happened?
Hello Nobita
ah, Giant ..
Here ..
Which group of his black shadow?
They have disappeared ..
Unfortunately
If they came back again
I'll beat him to a pulp ..
I will beat...
Do not take for granted ..
They might still be here in hiding ..
And immediately came lucky strike again ..
Nonsense
How This doraemon ..?
I do not know
Where did the head machinist?
We should stay together berama
What is it? whether the black shadow?
No, it's just fireworks ..
What ..?
Look, there is the sound of music ..
Yeah, right
His eyes began pins
Everything
Welcome to the visitors
Welcome to the park's biggest dream universe
"The Best Of Dream Park"
dream park ? ..
I understand, this is a dismissal
Garden dreams
Here's the place
"Attack of the black shadow is
is one of our performances"
"Do you enjoy it? .. "
What? ..
So that was one of the show? ..
I can not believe ..
I almost died today...
"Dream park is the center of the planet
adventure, but it also .."
"There is a planet ninja"
"Planet Dinosaur planet too cowboy"
"And there are many other planets play"
Come
Airing directly from the train
Planet dinosaur ..
Come on guys
Wait ..
Many people here
I heard there were about 600 passengers
Wait a minute ..
You see ..
Children who wear clothes
old-fashioned clothes ..!
Looks like they come from the past ..
Hi ..
I come from the 20th century ..
Ah? The 20th century?
No wonder you guys are so old-fashioned clothing
Ah ..
Ancient people
Ever seen a television?
Not in the 20th century it ..
Lived inside a cave, right?
And the dining table is made of stone, right?
Do ..
You also never been to school huh?
Less guys kick ass ..! watch ya ..!
Giant, do not ..!
Visitors
Now lets go to the Dream Park...
First you enter the train
first, because the train will depart ..
Planet what it is?
In the area of ​​small planets
There is a group who entered the big planet
Group what it is?
What is their purpose?
Send a spy to see the situation there
Be careful lah ..!
Good
The train landed automatically,
and became a cabin
It's so cool
Let us hurry
We went to the planet cowboys
"This is the owner's manual"
"A vampire planet"
This one looks interesting
So ..
We went to the planet cowboys, right?
Who's
Nobita, let's go
Come on, let's go to the planet as a cowboy
What do you say? the planet Ninja ..!
No, we are the first cowboy planet ..!
Suneo also want to ninja planet, right?
I.. yes, Planet Ninja!
You see, two against one?
Already on disconnect, go to the planet ninja ..!
But we see Shizuka opinion first ..
Shizuka
Where is he?
Ah, why no doors anywhere here?
He said there is a need for a while, so I loaned
..
So ya ..
Why do not you go
a separate course to the planet ..
What you want.
To borrow a rocket ship
So you want to be free to go anywhere
true?
Well, I go ..
We all ninja planet ..
A.. I
Klo so we also went ..
Wait
We had to leave a message to shizuka
Giant and go to the planet Suneo ninja
I and Nobita to planet cowboy
Shizuka also be involved ..
We are waiting for you there
Departure ..!
Where to borrowing  rocket?
Straight, about 2km from here
What? 2 Kilometers? ..
We should belari 2km so far? ..
A long way ..!
Hey ancient human ..
What are you doing?...
You really stupid
What you do not know the road wheels
Ah, right!
Road wheels
What is the road wheels? ..
You look down
The road is made of balls very small
If you want to go ahead
So little balls will receive a response from your mind
I mngerti
Rocket  here all use the power of gravity
model varies
How about this?
Is not it hard to control?
True, in fact it can be controlled automatically
So easy to control...
But I ask that you not go to a planet forbidden
Okay, I understand
Anyway we do not want to go there
Hope your trip enjoyable
Towards planet cowboy, go ..! !
What is it? forbidden planet?
Previously the place was used for mining
But now it is not anything else
there is only a hole dug only
Very dangerous, never approached the place
Welcome to the Gun Smoke City
clinton  I was mayor, mayor of this place
Now, today we will have a selection
To become a sheriff
Soon the contest will start
And my assistant will yangf selecting
= = We will start with a shooting contest
for anyone who made it to the end will receive the title as Sheriff
Everything now we are to the hotel to change costumes
- Then we gathered again here
- For sure I will win
Surely I win
I will be Sheriff
What? ancient people also joined this event ..!
You should carry a bow and arrows
, instead of a gun ..
You do not laugh at me
'll see ..!
How?
If the costume is appropriate?
As a real cowboy
Ah, what's this real gun?
Not
here writing ..
If the robot enemy hit by this bullet
Then the body will be disabled.
But if the human body
Then the body will swell
And fly into the air
So the bullet would not be harmful
View only
I can definitely be a winner
This is the place
For all participants please gather here
As the targets here are six empty bottles and cans
Participants may shoot after a whistle from my
You have 6 bullets, if the remaining two or more then you are forever barred
So who would like to first start? ..
Seems he is very strong
Looks like someone at the time of cowboys
Is it ready? ..
Whenever I'm ready!!
Ah, just one shot, you fail ..
It looks like the gun is broken
It is not possible
Strange ..
Next ..
Pity
The shot misses
Only shot 2 ..
Failed
Next ..
Now I...
Good luck ..
Do not fail ya ..!
Failed, missed all, then ..
Look at me ..
You shoot me ..?
FAIL...!
Next ..
Do not fail ya ..!
Give me
I support
Shot five
Only the remaining 1
You qualify
How?
You really terrific
You would be Sherif
Failed
Escaped
Shot  3
Next
Ah, the ancient human's turn
Come, let us hiding
We do not know where the bullet will shoot
You laugh ..
Although it is very difficult
But I have to focus on the target so I can certainly
Only shot 1
Failed
Haha .. ancient people have failed
Please look fine ..!
6 holes?
Bullet in cans
There are 6 rounds in the tin
Escaped ..
You terrific
Nobita
Now that you are a sheriff
Please keep law and order
And eradicate all criminals
Keep  Gun Smoke City to become the city of peace forever ..
Then ..
Badge award ..
Sheriff
Nobita, congratulations ..
Ah, Doraemon
's cool
Thanks Sherif  A
good ..
I also want to like you ..
's Been a while
I waited
end could be well Sherif
What will we do next
We're just waiting for the criminals
which appears in this town ..
Please, there was a robbery at a Bank
Nobita, this time
What?
Wait ..
Nobita
Let us follow from behind and shot
Good
Doraemon, bamboo propellers
right
Breach, banned disposable bamboo propellers
On this planet are not allowed to use
babling bamboo blades
If people are going to protest
right
Do not block the road, quickly get out ..!
Basic ancient man
Do not waste time
Hurry
If you use a horse, it is possible
Okay ..
Though this kind...
However, this is only left for us
Sorry
But when we would arrive
It was getting dark
According to the guidebook
They are headquartered in DEATH VALLEY
There criminals hiding
"Death Valey"
Ah, that ..
I shot
There are 4 people there I
one shot
Are you okay?
Yes, in 1 hour also will shrink ..
It seems everyone has been shot
Man  fashioned ..
Penjahatya so great, you have to be careful
Nobita, it looks like we are close ..
Let's go
There
We approached slowly
But, do not let them know our arrival
"Liquid Powder"
With this we can take a dip in the ground
True
Nobita, be careful ..
Good
Quietly take a look through the window ¬ Ý ¬ Ý
Some come
No one dared to come here
They are all really cowards
Huh? why is there a cap?
Ah, Nobita will be caught
What is it?
A fox? he wears a badge sheriff
Faster  check around
Who knew he brought a friend
Let me check
No, let me just
Wait, I was Nobita, her friend
Success
Nobita has mnyelamatkan this city of the criminals ..
Boring
let's go to another planet
Wait
Do you want to go to a planet where?
It really is great ..
I want to show it to Shizuka
What is Giant and Suneo do, huh?
Is also fun ninja on the planet? ..
This is because of you
Why did you choose this ninja planet? ..
It's not noisy, if we continue to talk
will fall ..!
Giant ~ ..
Do not waste my time ..!
You do not practice with sincerely
Ninja is strong, and not afraid to die
Do not be afraid that his name had ..
Exactly what are you trying to teach us?
What do you say?
We want the name  can walk on water ..
Using the techniques of magic that can penetrate walls
But we learned this
Not the same as what we know
on TV and comics
You people very impatient ..
Suneo, we go to another planet only
Okay
Hold
So you want to be like that?
I'm going to teach you the secret ninja...
Secret ninja?
A ninja will always show his best
Using this scroll, you can disappear.
With this you can also penetrate walls?
Can disappear and through walls?...
How how to use it?
In it was programmed by computer
Then you keep it in your mouth
Then think something like
Through the wall, the power to fly
And turned into a rat
Just like that?
This is only a secret ninja moves usual ..!
Suneo, you try to practice
right
Success, Giant ..!
Really great
Now you will carry out a mission
If you succeed
Then I will give you the real secret tricks
Go into the house and stole a confidential document
Do tricks secrets
could actually do a lot more than what this moment
Sure
Because actual rolls have a lot of great moves
interesting
Suneo, let's go
We must have a real roll
Stop
There's a guard
this way ..
With moves through the wall, we
can enter very easily
It's pretty quiet , where ya at?
Intruder ..!
There intruder
Do not run ..
Turns into mouse
Kick useful
True
We need to find documents secret place
confidential document storage space, there must have been here
The rooms were very large
Giant
There something, it's definitely the secret documents
What?
Ah, this ..
Secret document box
Found ..
It's very easy to ..
Ah, You're really stupid
Do not be that easy
Come in 10 years
Mother...
Are you kidding?
No
Fairy  planet is only suitable for women
I'm also the girl
Welcome to the planet fairy
Wow, take a look ..
Very beautiful rainbow
Apparently you happy
What is a fly?
Is that a flock of birds?
Pegasus, was a group of pegasus ..
Yes .. ya .. yea...
's Cool
Come path
Hello ..
Office over here
In the fairy tale planet
You will be protoganist the planet fairy tale
There are many characters here
and allow you to express
Like Cinderella, Thumbelina
no...
I want to be a princess snow
Sorry ..
Puteri very popular snow
So there is no longer a role for the full
What?
If you want you can be a wolf Evil
The show is about to begin
I do not want
If so must wait 3 rounds before
You both were there
Do you want to be a prince?
No
Sorry ..
It makes you wait
You better eat fast poisonous apple ..
Hmm ..
While you wait
If you are bored
You can watch the show ..
This is the story of the princess snow
What?
There are 7 princess snow ..
Because a lot of people who are interested in
Then the snow princess also 7 people
At the same time
Ah, there he is prince
Prince, help the princess snow
Prince
What? there are 7 princess snow?
Prince, you ..
Wow, so beautiful ..
The daughter ..
Prince ..
I've been waiting for you
Please come along with me to the palace ..
I want ..!
Hey, I've been waiting for from earlier ..
Me too ..!
Why only selected him?
I waited this role up to 5 times
What is this?
Do you still want to follow?
I told you from the beginning
Planet fairy was very boring
Now my decision ..
We went to a planet of dinosaurs
Then fight dinosaurs
There looks no sign of life ..
Reporting to headquarters
One person would I catch
So then you want to be a princess what?.
Asda, what's wrong with you?
You what? Asda ..
Why the sudden you shut up?
Asda, what are you doing?
Finally this body so Miliku
- I've wanted to have a body like this
- Asda ..
- What are you doing?
- Why did you leave us here?
Emergency calls
General, I no.008
I have managed to get into the human body
At a small planet where there are many people who live ..
I await orders from you ..
This General Heahdquartes
No.008 you really terrific
Send immediately forces there
Our mission is to enter their bodies all
Once we get him, then
will be easy to carry out secret missions ¥ O
Everything is ready to strike ..!!
Then we would soon control the entire universe
Then the guards caught us
and enter us into the dungeon
But with the power of the ninja stance
We got away
On the planet very nice fairy
The cowboy  planet too, we enjoy...
If so, tomorrow we will go to a planet where?
Planet Dinosaur course ..!!
Right
Is not nothing?
We'll get attacked by dinosaurs...
The problem is it's not a real dinosaur, so it will be very safe
Well, should we go to bed now, see you tomorrow ..
sampa
Location is at the galaxy's
There are many small planets
Though small planet
But there are abundant mineral
Dan called mineral planet
Since many people are digging
now only a small planet full of holes
Then they lose their job
And everything is back to his hometown
If this let alone
Then mineral planet will be damaged
Our dream is to build a park
lmpian It has been discussed several times
I know ..
Therefore, in the wake of a Dream Park
True
The people on the planet minerals
Everything moved here
Bam, this is what I'm looking for
I want you to write this story
then released at the media, so that everyone knows
Okay, I will do it ..
Then I published in the media
First, we have to think about security
In Dreams Park
How many robots that were damaged?
And that could endanger visitors
It is quite impossible ¯ Ã ª º
You see the building there?
It is the central controller
Working 24 hours without stopping
Attention all planets around
Starting from such a large robot to robot dinosaurs
smallest
But, what if
an accident there ..?
Behind control center that
There is installed a communications tower that will emit a signal
If there is an error, then
aid will directly come within 1 day
Well, tomorrow...
I'm going to visit all the places that are here
If you have time, stop here ..
- Okay ..
- Please follow me ..
- Thanks
Do not be shy...
Ah, it's too late ..
That is, what light is that? ..
It was just a meteor...
Disni are common things like that
Thank you.
Equally, during the night...
Good night...
We've seen it all
Now  saaatnya to take action
Each of you must choose one man
Then go into the body, and you will be a man
Our goal in the control center
and communications center
We should make all the robots being fucked
That's it ..
The man was an employee at the head office communications
001, do it ..!
Ah, you're what?
Are you okay?
It's okay .. I'm fine
Alright, time turns case ..
Are you sure you okay??
Do not worry, I'm fine really ..!
Well, selamt night ..
Confirm identity
Confirmation fingerprint
Confirmation finished
Door open ..
Tomorrow, I will destroy all the equipment here
Communications  would be cut off, so there will be no relief
can come here
's easy ..
What, no one calling ..
Detected an alien who is not well known around there
Would you please check back around there.
Well, I'll check it out ..!
Basic, stupid people
Soon you will soon come to an end ..
Doraemon, are you awake? ..
Doraemon
Yes, good morning.
Good morning ..
Shizuka, What are you doing?
It's still early ..
Before that I wanted to ask more
Ah, Doors Everywhere?
Do you want to go? home?
- To the bathroom
- Ah?
Since last night I have not gone to the bathroom
In the end it was the bathroom door
Why did you just say?
Ha ..  ha .. Shizuka .. Shizuka .. You were weird ..
I'm still sleepy, sleep ah ..
Good morning ..!
Let's go to the planet of dinosaurs
But...
What?
While in the bathroom?
Bath under the stars ..
Feels very fun
Ah, it's not polite!!
What is this? robot from the Garden of Dreams?
This UFO toy, huh?
Is it true that it is a UFO?
It looks just a toy unusual
Feels very soft
Already let alone
Let's quickly go
right
Departure
Ah, Mr. Bam ..
Good morning
Do you want to come with us to the planet
dinosaurs?
No thanks
You guys go ahead, I was there first needs ..
Hurry you'll be late
Well if so
We berngkat first yes ..!
Today we will do a suspenseful adventure
..
On this planet is the Mesozoic era
Here there are 3 kinds of time, ie the time Triassik,
Jurassic era, and the era of dinosaurs era
Taken together, they live in the same place
Enjoy adventures ..
On the first day you should find that you like dinosaurs
Then you make as a friend
Once you get a dinosaur, then ..
In the next days you will follow a contest
Ah, what a race contest?
True, Start start from the volcano and its
Finish seaside
As a prize for the winner, you may bring back dinosaurs
that you like
I want diosaurus greatest
Giant , where you want to save?
Ah, oh yes yes ..!
What is here also there tyranosaurus?
Of course there is.
Is he going to attack us?
Yes of course.
Would we be eating?
True, after you eat...
Then what will happen?
You will go into the stomach, and then after the
exit you will be fossilized
Then the game is finished.
It is not possible ..!
But do not worry
Our officer will return you to the original state again
thankfully ..
If so we have to be very careful
Here we shall use bamboo propellers
I wanted to capture the dinosaur and friends with
I want the greatest diosaurus
According to your device. .
Here are dinosaurs, that were located not far from here
Let's go down
should be around here ..
That is, there ..!
True?
- Where?
Where is it?
Shizuka, Come here does nothing ko ..!
Dragon Sword is a type of herbivore
It's okay, just touch.
He will not eat you ..
Is that true?
True, you just try it ..
Why is he silent?
Is he sleeping?
I'll make it move...
Ah, do not do it ..!
Dragon Sword is not a suitable race
True enough
I would look for a smaller course lah,
because I think it's good labih
If so, let us look for more ..
What do you think?
I also agree
So what are you waiting?
According to the guide tool, around here
there are other types of dinosaurs
Let's go
Alright, let Suneo ..
If you find something not forget
call the other, yes ..!
It's very broad, huh?
It is Velociraptor dinosaurs, carnivorous type
He was not a great
But he has a smart brain
For example, he uses a dinosaur
for fishing target, after that ..
Friends are in hiding and waiting to attack from behind
Ah, so close ..
Look, a Triceratops
He dinosaurs running slow ..
My stomach is hungry ..
Let's take a break first, after that we proceed further
Good
Biscuits mini
It was very tasty ..
Although only eat one, but immediately can make a full stomach
seems tyranosaurus has good speed...
What is it? dinosaur chicks
Hey, it's just food for the people not for the dinosaurs
No, not eating ..!!
Oh no, I really hate small dinosaur ..
I'm just like a big dinosaur
Giant, you liha footprints?
Wow, this is definitely the biggest dinosaur footprints here
this means....
Giant, there .. it ..!
Ah, it's huge ..
It must Brachiosaurus ..
Finally I found a huge dinosaur was also ..
He fits untuku ..
Although the fast is not necessarily running, right?
Are you saying?
If ants and dog races run.
Who will win?
If so how to get it?
Sorry, I had to find other dinosaur ..
There must be a way to get it
I will not give up
Ah, I know.
Suneo, wait ..!
What is it?
I need your help ..
What? ~
You see, why he
very long neck?
That's because ..
But that's not my problem ..
You do not know ya ..!
That's because she likes to eat young leaves at the top
tree
So what to do?
Fast
you'll get untuku young leaves in the tree
Why should I? ..
Why is not he alone who took it ..
Get it a lot ..!
Well, now you approach the mouth ..
And for him to follow you .. ¥ L
Good ..
Now faster  more ..
Ah, but I also have to find dinosaurs for riding
Continues is so...
Make him to continue to follow you ..
You really outrageous...
I do not know if I can find a dinosaur
I like...
Ah, funny as hell ..
Do you want this? ..
How, do you like?
You can not ride
Although there is no choice, but I have to keep looking ..
I'm sorry ..
Ah, you follow me ..
However, eating too much is not good
Ah, dinosaur mother ..
Is it a ferocious dinosaur?
This is the kind Gallomimus Variety ..
Can run very fast and eating all the food
This is the type that is suitable for riding
You want to be friends with me, right?
Come on, eat ..
Do they have found dinosaur? ..
Do not know too if they had found him or not
..
Doraemon, what if Ptesaurus?
Yeah, right
If you can fly in the air, it must be very fast flight
..
Let's try it ..!
Departing
See, there are lots of them in the sea ..
Looks like they're looking for food
But how to ride it??
Alright, I'll give it a try ..
Success ..
Doraemon ..
This is very enjoyable ..
Okay I'll try
Can ..
Nobita, if we use
Ptesaurus maybe we'll be the first ..
You come on ..!
Let's faster ..
I'm tired, let me down...
We might be the winner...
It would not be possible ..
Ah, why?
Suneo, quickly stop him ..!
Suneo
Giant
Why would he be like that? ..
Ah, It's Tyrannosaurus
He's heading here
What should we do?
Ah, you're too heavy so it can not fly
Do not leave me ..
Ah, bamboo propellers ..
Giant
Mama .. Mama ..
Hey, why him?
Stop
Nobita, have you been able to control it?
True, if you pull your left leg, then he will turn to the left ..
Look doraemon ..
Nobita ..
Why is this?
Everything is falling down ..
Actually, what has happened?
Do the engines were damaged ..
Who's calling?
I Doraemon
- I'm catching Tyranosaurus, but suddenly like
- Actually, what has happened?
But because of this incident we are so over
Hmm .. but, really well yes......
How Shizuka?
I'll call him
Dinosaurs Gallomimus suddenly fell Variety
What is it exactly?
Is there also the same?
What makes Dream Park is really suck ..
We must immediately ask her ..
Let us go to the head office
Sorry ..
The robots are controlled from the central office control
If so please contact them to immediately fix
Actually we just got in contact to the control center
but no response ..
This is from the center of the planet
Control Center, you hear? ..
Please answer ..
Looks like something is happening beyond
Ah, how can this be?
All robots become chaotic....
Why would they be?
Something may have occurred in the central office control
Let's check
Control Center... control center ..
Please answer...
Ah, look at that ..
Ptesaurus group wants to attack us
Go ASAP
Hurry...
We ran out of space
They will not follow us into space
Okay, faster
Looks like they will attack us from the air
Do not worry, high speed ..
Apparently they had not attended a us again
It is the center of the planet
The situation there seems is night
See there ..!
Is there a fire?
Looks like something did happen on this planet
Quickly we investigate ..!
We should split up to check it out ..
I and Suneo will check where it came from smoke
If something happens quickly call us...
I understand, Suneo fast ..
You
Be careful ..
This is definitely communication towers, right?
Hello .. is there anybody in there? ..
This place is really falling apart
The fire is huge
Giant  very dangerous here, let's go ..
- Are there people inside?
- No, Giant do not go ..!
A place like this where there may be someone inside ..
I'll wait here ..
Who's there?
Here there is no one there ..
Suneo, what is it? Suneo ..
Where are you? Suneo ..
Why did you run away like that,
base coward ..
Suneo ..
We've checked the entire building
But no one
Even a cockroach was not there ..
How can this be?
Where did all the people?
Giant, you find something?
Suneo disappear
What, Suneo missing?
Giant, you wait over there ..
Boy, always cause problems ..
Ah, do not stop suddenly so ..!
Ssstt, There's something wrong ..
Hidden ..
There's something behind the wall of the garden ..
What is it?? ..
It is a toy from Dream Park ..
He is moving on its own ..
Ah, look up there!
There are many ghosts that fly over
It's just a robot from the planet and the planet Fairy Tale
Actually, what happened here? ..
I do not know, let's have to look for Giant ..
Nobita, here ..
Giant
Are you finding Suneo?
No, I can not go anywhere
Maybe he was captured by the monster
Yeah, right ..
Suneo
Giant, where are you?
You suddenly disappeared, we were
worrying you ..
I'm sorry ..
Now you no where?
I've found a safe place to hide
You come on here ..
Well, we'll soon get there ..
Is it true that there is no monster ..
But, if we continue here long
get caught, too ..
Stop ..!
Ah, apparently there ..
Suneo, are you okay?
Ah, finally met also ..
Good, all here ..
Well, fast do ..!
What are you doing? ..
Do not worry that I'm just making you fall asleep...
No.0009, nice work.
Bring them into the cabin with the others.
While there are 600 people, but it's still not enough
In our base, there are 8 million parasites are waiting ..
Now we have to immediately find another galaxy
to add shortcomings ..
Heh, the water is up
I know, we've mnghabiskan everything ..
The food also was not there
Do not people come here and save us
..
How could anyone want to come to a place like this?
It's all because asda
Since her father's rich, he's just so delicious
se us
I'm so membecinya ..!
True,
If I'll see you, I'll teach him a lesson ..
Ah, you see? is not it a spaceship?
Yeah right ..!
We're here.
Please save us ..
Suneo, come quickly open the door ..!
Let us out
It's not much to say, just shut up ..!
Suneo, we are friends
Why are you doing this to us?
What was Suneo? I am the parasite no.0009
Hah, he said parachute? ..
Parachute?
No, but PARASITES ..!
We are a highly intelligent species
If you surrender your body to us
So, you'll be one of us ..
He told me to be one of us ..
It is a parasite?
Parasites?
He lives in the human body
By taking over his brain
So he can mngendalikan whole body
Like the stuffed toy?
I can not believe it happened
If it continues like this, the world would be taken over by their
all
Doraemon, use
Everywhere door to ask for help as soon as possible ..
Yes. You're right
Doraemon, are you okay?
He had locked his magic bag
So the magic bag can not be used?
Yes
Ah, you...
Sorry to make you faint
When I realized this, but it was too late ..
Everywhere many monsters roam
Lucky I met with the head machinist ..
If not, maybe I've become one of them
The situation became more serious ..
Doraemon , is not there another way out?
I have a great way ..
But it is very risky
We should try
Patrol report...
I see a fairly thick smoke
Yesterday I had burned several buildings
Perhaps the smoke was coming from the building which I have burned
Do not mind, anyway here are no longer human
= = I understand
It worked
We create a thick smoke
Then the train left the planet with
hiding in thick smoke this
Because of suspected smoke just plain
So the monster was not aware of
= = Thank God...
What, run away?
Since you say have arrested 600 people, therefore
I immediately came here
But why did you let them escape? ..
No. . 0008
If the security team to know, then
master plan for the universe will fail miserably
You have to do something ..!
You did not have to worry
It will not happen, because I had to take half of
fuel
What do you mean?
So, they would not have been able to go far
If the fuel runs out, they will land on the planet
a short distance away from here
If so, find them quickly
600 people and bring it to me
Doraemon
Looks like this room upside down ..!
How can this be right? ..
Earlier I was sleeping and suddenly this way
Sorry, this is all my fault ..
I do not realize if it turns out the material is low burn
Due to running out of fuel, so
carriage fell into the planet
But this is not your fault
mean this train now landed on a planet?
Seems so
Hey man, why you locked me like this ..!
I'm sorry, because you are not Suneo, so I was locked in there
Be patient ..
Ah, you guys here ..
Bamboo blades are very useful
I use it to patrol
other passengers stay safe
They all still sound asleep
Let's take a look at conditions beyond
Well, the carriage overturned all
Looks very chaotic ....
Luckily we are all still alive ..
This is due to touch down between the gray cart
Is this volcanic ash?
True, the ash was produced by artisanal mining in plenet mineral
Planet That place is off limits?
Yes
The front of the train was damaged
What could be improved?
Very difficult
Overall, we give up
We can no longer fight ..
We're doomed to die in this place ..
Calm down, we're not that bad Events
Please follow me ..
Near this mountain there is a town called
dg mineral town
But now it is no longer occupied
Although now uninhabited, but here
there are still a lot of food and drink
Let's quickly take a look ..
Is it true, Fun ..
Now that he's home
Ah, true
food is aplenty
As supermarkert
Hamburger spicy specials ..
Spaghetti pasta
My favorite food ..
Unfortunately here is no dorayaki
Bon appetite
Eat as much as you like
Wow, it feels so good
True
Hey, chief machinist
Iya
I found this thing out of the building
There is a mineralized corridor approximately
1000 meters below ground
Yes, of course
Well, this is what will bring us out of the mines
towards the underground station, right?
Absolutely
And there is a train station that still express the
can be used as a means of transportation, right?
I want to eat anymore ..
Although there is train
But all the tracks are closed all
Pity
I think this way we
get out of this place ..
It would not be possible
Anyway dijalur was a lot of that collapse
So, the train could not be used again
Okay ..
So do not even try to go in there
okay .. okay ..
We should discuss a plan anymore ..
There is a train again here
Although the train exits are closed
But here there are many holes
One of the holes is definitely heading
to where the train was.
I'll look for it by using
map, so I will not get lost
Browsing at the start ..!
I am the Giant, the adventurer strong ..
Ah, we've forgotten Suneo ..
Not parasites never feel hungry?
Because the human body, so...
We should give him a little food too
But she's very nasty ..
You're all prepared
We need to find where it landed train
Okay, full speed ..
Melangkahnya  carefully ..
Doraemon, it's okay?
This...
That's the time it entered the UFO when I was in the shower
Basic toys less kick ass ..!
What it's really just a toy?
Who knows what to do with the parasite creature
I will show it on the host Bam ..
Suneo, we bring you some food for you
Open the door carefully
Suneo, you what? Suneo ..
What is it?
Man is really easy to enter ..
The line was supposed to take me to the floor 3 F
Then in front of it ..
Ah, no, the line was closed again ..
So .. to get to the 7th floor, I have to turn around and then
..
Ah, is there a point yng covered again ..
I do not care, here there are many others
path, I will try it ..
I am the Giant ..
It fell off when I shoot
with the spray in the bathroom
spray?
Yes, a spray that is in the bathroom.
Hey, there's something in it
What is this?
Previously I have never seen this type
Do you shoot with it?
Yeah, that's true
It is a spray soap
With this the body will be protected for a time
So the parasite could not enter
Mr Bam
Please come here for a while .. .
Nobita, what is it?
Nobita
Nobita, get up ..
What? .. I just attacked you?
That's because you invaded by parasites ..
But we've found a weakness
Oh, Suneo is back
thankfully ..
Doraemon  and you all listen
I really did not realize you guys had attacked
Do not worry, it's his actions parasites ..
Now that everything is together again
Ah, Giant where?
Ah right, Giant go where ya?
I've given up ..!
I do not believe has been lost here
how this ..!
Ah, there was the sound of someone ..
Do you come to save me? ..
Are you going to save me? ..
- Thankfully ..
Ah, why this, we both lost
What a pity ..
I think you know the way out ..
I came here to look for
train left here
trains? I see there is a train station in the rear
true?
Train fire really there ..
We can use this train to get out of this planet
We will survive ..
But how do we get
out of the basement?
Ah right,
may be our fate to die here
Maybe I should eat something first
Ah, what was it?
Giant, where are you?
I do not find everywhere Giant
I will check on the train
Actually, he goes where?
Hey, You're all I found footprints here
I'm going to look
-
do not go - or you'll get lost
But I can not let him ..
- Giant
- Takeshi
Danger, this place would collapse
Giant
-
Giant - Giant
It is no longer a choice
Giant, I'm sorry ..
Though he is rude, but his heart is very good
I will greatly miss him ..
Strength ninja, moves through walls ..
Giant
You terrific
You survived
We did it
Put ​​all food and drink into the train
But I think we need some weapons
Here, no, because this place always peaceful
But as long as this planet will be maintained
So do not worry
detected a strong gravitational wave energy
Radar discover the presence of a train
Finally the train came too
- Raise the screen
- Received, Rev screen
This time I will definitely catch
You have to get it
Railway has been found
Finally, they found also
They did not imagine it would be so soon
They have found us
At this rate they will easily catch
us
We do not have weapons
Is this train can be accelerated again?
We are entering a collection area asteroids
If we want to avoid a collision, we need
special skills in driving
I leave it to you
I'm going to try to steer this train as much as possible
Fight. .
We can not pass through this area a
Reduce speed .. if not, we are going to collide with the asteroid
Do not reduce the speed
We do not need to reduce the speed
, we shoot them with guns
Shoot them ..
Do not shoot the cars
We need the human body
Train out of control We'll be landing on the planet
Surrender  is your man and come on
exit...
Then submit your body to us
We will not hurt
Why are they silent?
Come on, we try to pick out ..
Stop, do not run ..
Damn, we are caught up ..!
Shoot ..!
Asda
Asda, you okay?
What is it? Where am I?
What happened?? ..
Asda
Shoot continues, there are still many enemies ..
Yeah right
Backward ..
Its leaders want to escape ..
Do not let get away ..
I will not be defeated by man
He entered
and hide in the ship
You'll view the actual strength ..
Parasites that enter the body robot
Parasites not only get into the bodies of living alone
But he can also control the computer
Come on fire ..! ?
Ah, did not work.
The liquid can not be absorbed into the body
We need to find a point of weakness
Basic Human stupid
You think you can escape
Ah, no man is standing here
looks like her body is very weak. .
It's not important, what is important now
I need to log into his body ..
Nobita
It is not possible ..
Nobita, you are terrific ..
Nobita looks cool ..
When he was shot parasite
Ah, it's nothing ..
See, the troops flee parasites
I'm sorry you melbatkan into this
We are very grateful to you all
In this way, not
parasitic forces will probably come back to this place
Soon we will immediately fix all the damage that occurs in
Dream Park this
We'll fill fuel
Please fill in the full, yes ..!
We will always try to help ..
Thank you very much
Head machinist,
please deliver them to the destination.
Good
Be careful on the street, bye ..
Bye...
Although dangerous, but very pleasing ..
Other passengers also survived all
asda father has promised to fix everything
Thankfully
I also must take responsibility
But it's not your responsibility
parasites who should be responsible
True, it is their fault
Giant, you're acting like parasites alone ..
Ah, really ..
Apparently ancient man also likes to joke
I do not think...
I'm really sorry you guys are mocking ridicule
They're coming from the 20th century ..
So they are ancestors You
Ah, so they are the grandparents .. grandfather ..
Grandfather .. grandfather...
We are not very old ..
Soon landed ..
The 20th century, the third planet in the solar system ..
Thanks
sometime come back here, yes ..!
Certainly
The passengers earth, beriap prepared ..
Get ready...
Please do not forget your luggage ..
Keep yourself well ..
Thanks
Has Witnessed
Subtitle By: Ghie Lhanx
http://www.ghie-lhanx.com