Oh my boy! nanika ga (na na na na na na)
(Oh my boy! It’s like)
Hisohiso someone’s talking (ah ah ah ah ah ah)
(Whispering, someone’s talking)
Nee zutto
(Hey, I’m always)
Looking at you look-looking at you I
Anata miteru wa
(I’m looking at you)
Nee sore wa Kira hoshi na supernova
(Hey, that’s a sparkling star-like supernova)
Unmei no supernova
(Destiny’s supernova)
Majikaru na supernova
(A magical supernova)
Gingakei sukeerukan de number one!
(In the galaxy threaded scale, we feel we’re number one)
Uneru beesu rain raiku na shooting stars
(With rolling baselines like shooting stars)
Ga coming! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(Oh coming)
Cutest! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
Uwasa no teki da wa
(We’re the typical rumors)
Yeah-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh
Taito na hippu rain wa maru de (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(With our tight hips we’re like the)
Cutest! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!
Oh boy
Do you believe the situation
Yeah, you better keep this a secret
Makasete mimashou yobu koe no hou he
(Let’s try to rely on our voices that shout out)
Jittai wa nazo na no houseki no you na me de
(In mysterious ways with eyes like jewels, I am)
Looking at you look-looking at you oh
Ima mo miteru wa
(Even now, I’m looking at you)
Nee sore wa Utagai nai supernova
(Hey, that’s an unquestionable supernova)
Chou genjitsu supernova
(Hyper-reality supernova)
Anata no supernova!
(Your supernova)
Daikiken ourai desou in and out
(In and out of the atmosphere, yeah in and out)
Sekai kaesou na shock sugata Kae
(Changing out form, arriving like a shock that can change)
Te tourai! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(The world)
Perfect! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
Chijou de kirameite
(We shine atop the ground)
Yeah-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh
Ukabiagatta shiruetto (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(With our silhouettes that rose to the surface we are the)
Perfect! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!
Tsukamaete
(We grasp on to)
Sururi to nigerarete
(you who just now)
Kieru no
(Escaped and disappeared)
We’re dancing and looking at you, yeah...
Gingakei sukeerukan de number one!
(In the galaxy threaded scale, we feel we’re number one)
Uneru beesu rain raiku na shooting stars
(Our rolling baselines like shooting stars)
Ga coming! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(Oh coming)
Cutest! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
Uwasa no teki da wa
(We’re the typical rumors)
Yeah-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh
Taito na hippu rain wa maru de (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
(With our tight hips we’re like the)
Cutest! (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
Girls in (tu-tu-tu-tu-tu-tu)
In the galaxy! galaxy! Oh!