Lyrics Created and Edited by
Ryan Hawk Najoan
Join on facebook
-- The Coders Subs Team --
Oh! my boy nanika ga (na na na na na)
Isso isso someone's talking (ah ah ah ah)
Nee zutto
Looking at you lo-looking at you i'm looking at you lo-looking i...
Anata Miteru wa
Nee sore wa killer boyish na Supernova
Majikaru na Supernova
Gingakei sukeitan de Number 1
[Sooyoung]
Majikaru na Supernova
Gingakei sukeitan de Number 1
Uneru like like a shooting star, a comet
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Cutest!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In the Galaxy! Galaxy! Oh!
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Uawasa no matoda wa
Yeah eh eh eh eh eh eh
Tauto na hippu rain marude
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Cutest!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In the Galaxy! Galaxy! Oh
Oh boy, do you believe this situation?
Yeah!
You better keep this a secret
Makasete mi mashou yobu koe no hou e
Zetai naze na ni houseki no you na me de
Looking at you lo-looking at you
I looking at you lo-looking i
Ima mo miteru wa
Ne sore wa utagaenai Supernova
Chougenjitsu Supernova
Anata no Supernova
In The Galaxy!
Taikiken ourai de sou in and out!
sekai kaesou na shock sugata kaete tourai
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Perfect!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In the Galaxy! Galaxy! oh!
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Chijou de kirameite
Yeah eh eh eh eh eh eh
Ukabiagatta shiruetto
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Perfect!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In The Galaxy! Galaxy! Oh!
Tsukamae te
Suitto nigarare te
Keiru no
We're dancing and looking at you yeah!
Gingakei sukeitan de Number 1
Uneru base line like a shooting star, a comet
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Cutest!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In the Galaxy! Galaxy! Oh!
OH OH OH OH OH!
Uwasa no mato da wa
Yeah eh eh eh eh eh
Tauto na hippu rain wa marude
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
Cutest!
Girls in...
(Tu-tu-tu-ru-tu-tu)
In the Galaxy! Galaxy! oh!
-- GIRL's GENERATION --
-- GALAXY SUPERNOVA --
Brought to you by
-- RYAN HAWK NAJOAN --
Join us on facebook
-- The Coders Subs Team --
Special Thanks to
-- KpopLyrics.net --
Presented to you by Ryan Hawk Najoan
..:: Girls Generation - Galaxy Supernova ::..
..:: Ryan Hawk Najoan ::..