It's an important and popular fact
that things are not always
what they seem.
For instance, on the planet Earth,
man had always assumed
that he was the most intelligent
species occupying the planet,
instead of the third most intelligent.
The second most intelligent creatures were,
of course, dolphins, who, curiously enough,
had long known of the impending
destruction of the planet Earth.
They'd made many attempts
to alert mankind to the danger,
but most of their communications
were misinterpreted
as amusing attempts to punch footballs
or whistle for tidbits.
So, they eventually decided they would
leave Earth by their own means.
The last ever dolphin message
was misinterpreted
as a surprisingly sophisticated attempt
to do a double backward somersault
through a hoop, while whistling
the 'Star-Spangled Banner'.
But in fact, the message was this...
"So long and thanks for all the fish."
[So Long & Thanks for All the Fish
by Hilary Summers]
♪ So long and thanks for all the fish ♪
♪ So sad that it should come to this ♪
♪ We tried to warn you all but, oh, dear! ♪
♪ You may not share our intellect ♪
♪ Which might explain your disrespect ♪
♪ For all the natural wonders
that grow around you ♪
♪ So long, so long and thanks for all the fish ♪
♪ The world's about to be destroyed ♪
♪ There's no point getting all annoyed ♪
♪ Lie back and let the planet
dissolve around you ♪
♪ Despite those nets of tuna fleets ♪
♪ We thought that most of you were sweet ♪
♪ Especially tiny tots and
your pregnant women ♪
♪ So long, so long, so long, so long, so long ♪
♪ So long, so long and thanks for all the fish ♪
♪ If I had just one last wish ♪
♪ I would like a tasty fish ♪
♪ If we could just change one thing ♪
♪ We would all have learned to sing ♪
♪ Come one and all ♪
♪ Man and mammal ♪
♪ Side by side ♪
♪ In life's great gene pool ♪
♪ So long, so long, so long, so long, so long ♪
♪ So long, so long and thanks for all the fish ♪♪
The extraordinary story of
'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy'
begins very simply.
It begins with a man.
An Earthman, to be precise.
Who no more knows his destiny,
than a tea leaf knows the history
of the East India Company.
His name is Arthur Dent.
He is a 5'8''-tall ape descendant
and someone is trying to drive
a bypass through his house.
What do I want you to do about it?
Well, I want you to find him
and tell him that I'm currently
lying flat on my back in front of...
Fine, I'll hold.
Come off it, Mr. Dent. You can't lie
in front of the bulldozers for ever.
Well, I'm game. We'll see who rusts first.
This bypass has got to be built
and it is going to be built.
- Why has it got to be built?
- It's a bypass!
You've got to build bypasses.
Besides, you should've made
your protest months ago.
These plans have been on display
at the planning office now for a year.
On display? I had to go down to a cellar!
Mr. Dent, have you any idea how much
damage this bulldozer would suffer,
if I just let it roll straight over you?
- How much?
- None at all.
By a strange coincidence, none at all
is exactly how much suspicion
the ape-descendant Arthur Dent had
that one of his closest friends
was not descended from an ape,
but was, in fact, from a small planet
somewhere in the vicinity of Betelgeuse.
Arthur! Arthur!
- Ford!
- Yes?
Here.
Ah, there you are!
Come, eat, drink with me. We gotta talk.
Now's not the best time.
They're going to demolish my home.
Whoa! You already...
You already know? How?
What do you m...?
Oh, they, they? When you say "they",
you mean they? Got it.
Listen, I got something important
I gotta tell you. I gotta tell you right now.
Well, what about my house?
Workers of the Earth, I bring
good tidings of peanuts and beer!
- Good. Next thing. Come on,
let's go to the pub. - Huh?
They said they won't demolish your home
until they've finished the beers.
- Can we trust them?
- I trust them to the end of the Earth.
- How far's that?
- About 12 minutes away.
Huh?
Barman, six pints of bitter and quickly.
The world's about to end.
Six pints coming up.
Keep the change.
You got about ten minutes to spend it.
Three pints each? At lunchtime?
Sorry.
Time is an illusion.
Lunchtime, doubly so.
And eat those peanuts,
because you'll need the salt.
- Look, what is going on, Ford?
- Arthur...
What if I told you
I really wasn't from Guildford?
I was from a small planet somewhere
in the vicinity of Betelgeuse?
Is that something you're likely to say?
Remember when we met?
Get out the way!
Hi.
Do you think it was a bit strange
I was trying to shake hands with a car?
I assumed you were drunk.
I thought cars were the dominant life form.
I was trying to introducing myself.
You saved my life that day, and now
I'm saving yours. Please drink.
It must be Thursday. I could never
get the hang of Thursdays.
- Arthur, if this is about your house--
- No, it's not about the house.
- Who's he?
- She. She!
Tricia McMillan.
We met at a fancy-dress party.
See, I hate those kind of parties.
I'd much rather have stayed at home
and, I don't know, ironed my hankies.
- But anyway, there I was.
- Who are you?
- Oh!
- And there she was.
- Dent. Arthur Dent.
- Oh, no. I mean, who are you?
Oh, the costume? Right.
"Livingstone, I presume!"
Yeah, it's not as clever as Darwin, I know,
but it's the best I could do at short notice.
You're the first preson who's done that right.
- Really?
- Yes.
Everyone keeps calling me Santa.
Right.
And I thought the beagle made it
a dead giveaway.
Yes! Well, so did I.
I guess most of the people who come
to these sort of parties are drunken idiots.
What?
I said, all these people are idiots! God!
That's awkward.
Tell me.
She was amazing though, Ford.
Beautiful, witty, mad as a balloon.
I've got to say, without the beard,
you look at least 80 years younger.
Maybe I'm de-evolving.
Well, I feel should tell you
that I do not date single-celled organisms,
okay?
Let's go somewhere.
Yeah, definitely.
Where do you have in mind?
- Madagascar.
- Is that that new club on Dean Street?
No, it's a country off the coast of Africa.
That Madagascar?!
Why are we waiting here?
Wait a sec.
Go!
God, you're serious.
I can't go to Madagascar.
- Why not?
- Well, because, I just, you know...
- You're really serious?
- Yeah.
I want to go somewhere I've never been
and I'd like to go with you, so...
What do you say, Dr Livingstone?
I say that's an extraordinary proposition.
I can't go. I mean, I've got a job.
Quit. Get a new one when you come back.
I don't even know your real name.
- Tricia McMillan.
- Well, Tricia McMillan.
I have a proposition for you.
Why don't we go somewhere
a little closer first, say Cornwall,
and we'll see how it goes.
Right, of course, Cornwall.
Hey, excuse me.
Is this guy boring you?
Why don't you talk to me instead?
I'm from a different planet.
It's true. You want to see my spaceship?
"Do you want to see my spaceship?"
I mean, really, what kind of chat-up line is that?
Mmm, that does happen.
Speaking of...
We've got two minutes.
Drink up, drink up, drink up.
That's my house!
People of Earth, a round of drinks,
for everyone on me.
Do you really think the world's going to end?
Yes.
Shouldn't we lie down, or put a paper
bag over our heads, or something?
- If you like.
- Will it help?
Not at all. See you.
Last order today!
- What is that?!
- Run!
Look out!
A-ha! Towel!
Arthur!
What the hell are those things?
They're ships from a Vogon constructor fleet.
I picked up their signal this morning.
Here, you'll need this.
- What are you doing?
- Hang on, we're hitching a ride.
People of Earth,
this is Prostetnic Vogon Jeltz of the
Galactic Hyperspace Planning Council.
As you are probably aware,
plans for the development of
the outlying regions of the galaxy
involve the building of a hyperspace
express route through your star system.
And your planet is one of those
scheduled for demolition.
There's no point acting
all surprised about it.
The plans and demolition orders
have been on display
at your local planning office
in Alpha Centauri for 50 of your Earth years.
If you can't be bothered to take any interest
in your local affairs, that's your own lookout.
Apathetic bloody planet.
I've no sympathy at all.
'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy'
is a wholly remarkable book.
Perhaps the most remarkable,
certainly the most successful book,
ever to come out of the great publishing
corporations of Ursa Minor.
More popular than
'The Celestial Homecare Omnibus',
better selling than
'53 More Things to Do in Zero Gravity',
and more controversial than
Oolon Colluphid's trilogy
of philosophical blockbusters,
'Where God Went Wrong',
'Some More of God's Greatest Mistakes',
and 'Who Is This God Person Anyway?'
It's already supplanted
the 'Encyclopedia Galactica'
as the standard repository
of all knowledge and wisdom
for two important reasons.
First, it's slightly cheaper,
and second, it has the words "Don't Panic"
printed in large, friendly letters on its cover.
So you're not from Guildford.
Which would explain the accent,
which I've always wondered about.
You're not an out-of-work actor,
but rather a writer for this... this book thing.
It's good, huh?
I don't feel well. I need a cup of tea.
If I asked where we were, would I regret it?
- We're safe for now.
- Good.
We're in the washroom on one of the
ships of the Vogon constructor fleet.
- Oh, get me home, Ford!
- Arthur, your home is...
Oh, God, my home!
My home was demolished.
You don't remember.
Okay, Arthur, I've got something to tell you.
It's unfortunate, but it's true.
Your home planet has been blown up.
Blown up!
Couldn't you have done something?
I saved your life.
Okay, that makes us even.
It's a tough galaxy. If you want
to survive out here, you've...
gotta know where your towel is.
Okay, give me a hand over here.
Careful. It's hot.
We've gotta get off this ship.
Before the Vogons find us.
Vogons, they hate hitchhikers. Pull.
- Now we'll get a signal.
- What is a Vogon?
Ask the Guide. Say "Vogons".
Vogons.
Vogons are one of the most
unpleasant races in the galaxy.
Not evil, but bad-tempered,
bureaucratic, officious and callous.
They wouldn't even lift a finger
to save their own grandmothers
from the Ravenous Bugblatter
Beast of Traal without orders
signed in triplicate, sent in, sent back,
queried, lost, found,
subjected to public inquiry,
lost again and finally buried
in soft peat for three months
and recycled as firelighters.
On no account should you allow
a Vogon to read poetry to you.
They can't think, they can't imagine. Most of
them can't even spell. They just run things.
Hmm?
And if we don't get a ride soon,
we won't need the Guide to tell us
just how unpleasant the Vogons can be.
They've already destroyed a planet today.
That always makes them a little eee!
What is that?
Put this in your ear.
Huh? Ford!
We have unwittingly picked up
a couple of hitchhikers.
The fish is translating for you.
The Babel fish is small, yellow, leech-like,
and probably the oddest thing
in the universe.
It feeds on brainwave energy,
absorbing unconscious frequencies,
and excreting a matrix
of conscious frequencies
to the speech centers of the brain.
The practical upshot of which is that,
if you stick one in your ear,
you instantly understand
anything said to you in any language.
Resistance is useless.
- All right.
- Someone's coming.
Here we go. Look lively.
Sir?
- What?
- Hitchhikers.
"O freddled gruntbuggly..."
Oh, no, no, really.
Really you don't have to read.
We've put you through
enough trouble already.
"... as plerdled gabbleblotchits
on a lurgid bee."
Vogon poetry is widely accepted
as the third worst in the universe.
The second worst
is that of the Azgoths of Kria.
During a recitation by their Poet Master,
Grunthos the Flatulent,
of his poem
'Ode to a Small Lump of Green Putty
'I Found in my Armpit
One Midsummer Morning',
four of his audience
died of internal hemorrhaging,
and the President of the
Mid-Galactic Arts Nobbling Council
survived by gnawing
one of his own legs off.
"Or I will rend thee in the gobberwarts"
"with my blurgle..."
The absolute worst poetry was written
by Paula Nancy Millstone Jennings of Sussex.
Luckily, it was destroyed
when the Earth was.
"See if I don't." Yeah.
So, Earthlings, I present you with a choice.
Either die in the vacuum of space,
or tell me what you thought of my poem.
Actually, I rather liked it.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
That's good. That's good, Arthur. Run with it.
Some of the words I didn't understand,
but I found the imagery quite effective.
Continue.
Well, yes, interesting rhythmic devices,
which seemed to counterpoint
the underlying metaphor of the humanity of...
- Vogonity!
- Vogonity, sorry, vogonity.
...of the poet's soul.
So, what you're saying is,
I write poetry, because
underneath this mean,
callous, heartless exterior,
I just want to be loved?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yeah, please.
Throw them off the ship!
All right! All right!
Resistance is useless!
Shut up! Get a job! Wash your filthy hands!
Don't panic. Don't panic.
So this is it. We're gonna die.
Yeah, we're gonna die.
No, no, what's this?
- What's that?
- What's this?
What's this? This is nothing.
Yeah, we're gonna die.
You're sweating.
- Would you like a hug?
- No.
"Space", says the introduction
to 'The Hitchhiker's Guide',
"is big. Really big.
"You just won't believe how vastly,
hugely, mind-bogglingly big it is."
And so on.
It also says that if you hold a lungful of air,
you can survive in the total vacuum
of space for about 30 seconds.
But with space being really big and all,
the chances of being picked up
within that time
are two to the power of two billion,
79 million, 460 thousand,
347 to one against.
Which, by a staggering coincidence,
is also the telephone number
of the Islington flat,
where Arthur went to a fancy dress party
and met a very nice young woman
whom he totally blew it with.
Though the planet Earth,
the Islington flat and telephone
have all now been demolished,
Ford and Arthur were, in fact, rescued.
- Ford?
- Yes.
- I think I'm a sofa.
- I know how you feel.
So much for the laws of physics.
And once again our top story.
The sensational theft of the most
coveted ship in the universe,
the starship Heart of Gold.
Stolen at the launch ceremony
by none other
than Galactic President
Zaphod Beeblebrox.
In the name of people, freedom,
and democracy, stuff like that,
I hereby kidnap myself
and I'm taking the ship with me.
Come on!
Beeblebrox, universally considered
to be the dimmest star
in several solar systems,
is most famous for his controversial
defeat of Humma Kavula,
who claimed many thought they were voting
for the worst-dressed sentient being
in the universe contest.
Great.
Humma Kavula is, of course,
best remembered for his slanderous
"Don't Vote for Stupid!" campaign.
Can we put your ego aside for a minute?
Something important has happened.
If there's anything more important
than my ego on this ship,
I want it caught and shot right now.
Hey, come on, I love it.
Zaphod's just this guy, you know.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. What d'you...?
I was just watching myself.
The computer says we have a couple
of hitchhikers in our receiving bay.
Hitchhikers? Why'd you pick up hitchhikers?
I didn't. The ship did.
What? Say what?
When we engaged the Improbability Drive...
- This? The big button?
- Yeah, I know.
They were picked up here
in sector ZZ9 Plural Z Alpha.
Wait a minite. That's where you picked me up.
- What?
- On Earth.
- That's impossible.
- No.
- Just very improbable.
- Listen, Slam.
I don't have time for this, you know?
We've got the police of half the galaxy after us.
We've stopped to pick up hitchhikers. Okay!
So ten out of ten for style, but...
minus several million for good thinking.
You're too gorgeous, baby.
Stop it. You drive me crazy.
Don't. I'll send Marvin.
Marvin!
I think you ought to know
I'm feeling very depressed.
Well, we have something that
should take your mind off things.
It won't work.
I have an exceptionally large mind.
Yeah, we know. But we need you to go
down to the number two entry bay
and pick up our stowaways
and bring them up here.
Just that? I won't enjoy it.
Yeah, well, that's life.
Life? Don't talk to me about life.
- Commander Kwaltz.
- Yes?
We have located the spaceship
Heart of Gold and President Beeblebrox.
- Where?
- Sector ZZ9 Plural Z Alpha.
Requesting hyperspace clearance.
Hold your position, captain,
until clearance is granted.
- Yes, sir.
- Get me Vice-President Questular.
Hyperspace permission granted, captain.
Here we go.
I think that door just sighed.
Ghastly, isn't it?
All the doors in this spaceship
have been programmed
to have a cheerful and sunny disposition.
Anyway, come on. I've been ordered
to take you up to the bridge.
Please yourselves.
Here I am, brain the size of a planet,
and they ask me to take you up to the bridge.
Call that job satisfaction? 'Cause I don't.
You can thank the Sirius Cybernetics
Corp. for building robots with G.P.P.
- What's G.P.P.?
- Genuine People Personalities.
I'm a personality prototype.
You can tell, can't you?
Arthur?
Hey, Slim, are you wearing my underwear?
'Cause I'm wearing yours.
And they ain't doing the trick.
Come on. All right!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
I've brought the aliens.
Don't thank me or anything.
Freeze!
Freeze? I'm a robot. Not a refrigerator.
- I wasn't talking to you, Giggles.
- Oh, why do I bother?
- Zaphod?
- Ford?!
Is that you? Ford! Praxibetel Ix!
What the hell are you doing here?
I don't know. I just stuck out
my thumb and here I am.
- That is so you!
- Look at you!
President of the Galaxy!
I can't believe you beat Humma Kavula.
- You zarkin' frood.
- Hey, come here, come here.
I want you to meet a friend.
Arthur, this is Zaphod Beeblebrox.
Oh!
President of the Galaxy. This is my
cousin. He's a semi-half brother...
- He shares three of the same mothers as me.
- We've met.
- Have we?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. I've got a terrible
memory for species.
This is him, Ford. The would-you-
like-to-see-my-spaceship bloke.
- Hello, Arthur.
- Tricia!
- How you doin'?
- Hey, Trillian!
This is my semi-half-brother Ix,
I'm sorry, Ford.
- Hi.
Would you excuse us for a second, please?
You went down on that little planet
and didn't even call me?
Sorry, pal, I didn't know.
You know, I had a galaxy to run.
Hi, Tricia McMillan, right?
I think I heard him call you Trillian.
Which of us got the right one?
Oh, I shortened it.
Something a little more spacey.
Right. Yes, well... Actually
I was thinking of changing mine to,
I don't know, Arthoolia.
That's a good one!
Well, this is weird.
- How'd you get here?
- I just stuck out my thumb, here I am.
- Right. In your pajamas?
- I was in a hurry.
Okay. Did you know I was here?
Don't flatter yourself.
I've got a spaceman too.
Yeah, that's kinda like the Dingo Shuffle, yeah.
Okay, look...
I left you at the party. I feel bad about it,
but I was gonna call you when I got back.
Well, there is no going back now, is there?
You do know what happened, don't you?
Hey, enough small talk. Tria, we're
on the run, remember? I stole a ship.
Excuse me, mate, we're in the middle
of a chat here. Do you mind?
Well, I think the girl's getting... Boo!
You blew it with her, Earthman, so
shut your face or I'll kick you in the zatch.
- You wanna fight? You wanna fight?
- Yeah, okay.
- No, no.
- Earthman wants to fight.
- No.
- I'm just kidding.
I'm a kidder. Come on. Let's be friends.
Let's connect. You and I.
Didn't see that one coming, did you?
Popped right out of the box.
You foxy, yeah!
You should teach your pal a lesson, Ford.
He's a guest on my ship.
He's a guest on my ship!
I thought you said you stole it.
Stole what? What are we talking about?
Uh-oh! That doesn't sound good.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, just fabulous, thanks, Trill.
Hey, baby, a little help over here.
I think I'm in over my head.
I'll take care of this. Good Zarquon,
do I have to do everything?
Yes, I do!
Hey, hey, Slim, this is really pretty.
- Don't!
- They're on our tail.
Fire a gun! Launch a missile!
Do some damage!
Ow! Stop that! Ow!
Just kiddin'. I love it rough.
Hit me! Hit me, baby!
- Computer?
- Hi, there.
I'm Eddie, your ship-board computer.
I'm just pleased as punch to report that
it's a fleet of a hundred Vogon battle destroyers.
They're sending you a message.
This is Vice-President Questular Rontok.
I am speaking to the kidnapper
of the President?
She digs me. Check it out.
Surrender the stolen vessel at once,
or we will take action
as defined and permitted by...
section 1-8 of the Galactic
Interstellar Space Bylaws...
Zaphod, please come back now.
This is ridiculous.
Leap to hyperspace! Come on!
Oh, sure thing, fella!
No!
Did they have proper
hyperspace authorization?
- No, commander!
- Oh.
Bring me the request
to pursue fugitive forms.
I'm coming, sir.
I'm boiling! Here's the form, sir.
So, are you along for the ride,
or am I just dropping you somewhere?
That depends. Where are you going?
Where am I going?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Don't suppose there's any tea
in this spaceship, is it?
Yes, there is. Come on.
I'll show you the kitchen.
When you see what I'm about to show you,
you'll beg me to take you with us.
The best drink in existence
is the Pan-Galactic Gargle Blaster,
the effect of which is like having your brains
smashed out by a slice of lemon
wrapped round a large gold brick.
- Belgium.
Hold it one second.
Hey, Ape-man, Earth dude...
I'm sorry, what's your name again?
- Arthur.
- Right. Gorgeous.
No hard feelings, okay?
Sorry to hear about your planet...
- What's it called?
- Earth.
Yeah, yeah. I liked Earth.
Got these boots there.
But listen, don't mention it to the girl, okay?
Because if you do, I'll pull your
spleen out through your throat.
- All right. Thanks, buddy.
- Okay, okay.
Good stuff. Like those jammies.
Hey, hey, Zaphod,
what's with the two-head thing?
Oh, yeah. Apparently, you can't be
president with a whole brain.
It's crazy.
- Oh, so you carved it up?
- Yes.
Some parts of my personality weren't
exactly what you'd call... presidential.
- You know what I mean?
- No, no, no!
No, you know what I'm talking about.
Your tea is ready.
I suppose I should've said it resembles tea.
So, two heads is what does it for a girl?
I mean, if I'd had two heads,
or, I don't know, three...
Or your own spaceship.
Anything else he's got two of?
Come on, Arthur, don't be like that.
What am I supposed to be like?
You know. Green? Bleeping?
I can fold my eyelids inside out if you like.
Okay, look. Do you see this?
This detects what you're craving
and makes it for you.
Enjoy your doughnut.
Do you see this?
This toasts bread while you're slicing it.
We're on a spaceship, Arthur! In space!
- I told you I wanted to get away.
- To Madagascar.
That was... some sort of test.
And I failed.
- How badly does it hurt?
- It doesn't feel great.
No, I mean your chin.
- I might have an aspirin.
- Right.
Hey!
Tricia... Trillian, sorry.
There's something I have to tell you.
- Please, don't.
- Showtime, Trill!
I'm going to set up.
Buttons aren't toys.
Anyway, when I saw
what I'm about to show you,
that's when I realized why I had to do
what I did to my brain.
I think, it's all a little...
shaky.
I've seen it. It's rubbish.
Many millions of years ago,
a race of hyper intelligent,
pan-dimensional beings
got so fed up with the constant
bickering about the meaning of life,
that they commissioned
two of their brightest and best
to design and build
a stupendous super-computer
to calculate the answer to life,
the universe and everything.
O' Deep Thought,
we want you to tell us the answer.
The answer to what?
The answer to life,
the universe, everything.
We'd really like an answer.
Something simple.
I'd have to think about that.
Return to this place in exactly
7.5 million years.
- Is it finished?
- No, no, no, there's more. There's more.
They go back.
- What, 7.5 million years later?
- That's right, they do.
- Deep Thought, do you have--
- An answer for you?
Yes, but you're not gonna like it.
- It doesn't matter. We must know it.
- All right.
The answer to the ultimate question...
of life, the universe and everything...
is...
42.
Yeah? What?
42!
Yes, yes, I thought it over
quite thoroughly. It is. It's 42.
It would've been simpler, of course,
to have known what the actual question was.
But it was the question.
The ultimate question. Of everything!
That's not a question.
Only when you know the question
will you know what the answer means.
- Give us the ultimate question then.
- I can't. But there is one who can.
A computer that will calculate
the ultimate question.
A computer of such infinite complexity,
that life itself will form part
of its operational matrix.
And you yourselves shall take on new,
more primitive forms,
and go down into the computer to
navigate its 10-million-year program.
I shall design this computer for you,
and it shall be called...
- That's it?
- That's it.
You're looking for the ultimate question.
- Yep.
- You?
- Me.
- Why?
No, I tried that. Why? 42. Doesn't work.
- Let's get it ready, baby.
- Why...
do you wanna know the ultimate question?
Oh, well, partly the curiosity,
partly a sense of adventure,
but mostly I think
it's for the fame and the money.
You're President of the Galaxy, aren't you?
- That's right, Arman.
- Arthur.
Whatever. Presidential fame is temporary.
I find the question, that's permanent. It sticks.
Plus, everyone thinks you're deep. Win-win.
We just hit that button and... Bam!
...we're at Magrathea, I think.
I mean, I don't know, we've hit it twice
and we're still not there, but anyway...
- You in?
- Always.
- All right!
- I want to get off.
- Sorry, what exactly are we doing?
- This!
The Infinite Improbability Drive
is a wonderful new method
of crossing interstellar distances
in a few seconds,
without all that tedious
mucking about in hyperspace.
As the Improbability Drive
reaches infinite improbability,
it passes through every conceivable
point in every conceivable universe
almost simultaneously.
In other words, you're never sure
where you'll end up,
or even what species you'll be
when you get there.
It's therefore important
to dress accordingly.
The Infinite Improbability Drive was invented
following research into finite improbability,
which was often used
to break the ice at parties
by making all the molecules
in the hostess' undergarments
leap simultaneously one foot to the left
in accordance with
the theory of indeterminacy.
Many respectable physicists said they
weren't going stand for that sort of thing,
partly because it was
a debased of science,
but mostly because they didn't get
invited to those sort of parties.
Wow! Is this gonna happen
every time we hit that button?
Very probably, yes.
I think the Earthman's about to be sick.
Whoa, whoa! Do it in the trashcan,
ape-man. This ship's brand new.
Aw, Come on!
We have normality.
Did it work? Are we there?
Yeah. We're here. Magrathea!
- I don't think so. Eddie...
- Magrathea!
What planet are we looking at?
I'm checking for you.
Did you just pluck one of my hairs?
Off my head?
Thank you so much for waiting.
I'm sorry to disappoint you gang,
but this is not Magrathea.
We are currently in orbit around
the planet Viltvodle Six.
Humma Kavula!
Magrathea's gonna have to wait.
I got a score to settle on this planet.
Humma Kavula!
In the beginning,
the universe was created.
This made a lot of people very angry,
and has been widely regarded as a bad move.
Many races believed that
it was created by some sort of god.
Though the Jatravartid people
of Viltvodle Six firmly believed
that the entire universe was, in fact,
sneezed out of the nose of a being
called the Great Green Arkleseizure.
Humma Kavula!
The Jatravartids,
who lived in perpetual fear
of the time they called the
'Coming of the Great White Handkerchief',
were small blue creatures
with more than 50 arms each.
They were unique in being
the only race in history
to have invented the aerosol deodorant
before the wheel.
Mr. President!
Hey, all right. How you doin'? All right.
Hey, what have we here? I love it!
Hey, I love you. Fantastic!
You guys related? Don't go changing. Keep up!
Arthur, I want a drink.
I think I've been here before.
Have I been here before?
Ixxie!
- I've been here before.
- Humma Kavula!
Come on.
Tricia! Tricia!
♪ Thy Handkerchief to bring us back to Thee ♪
Hello, Humma.
Please, join us. Sit down.
Hey, good to see you. Thanks. All right.
The handkerchief is coming beloveds.
Let us pray the Almighty will exhale
a breath of compassion on us all.
So that's Humma Kavula.
I thought he was just swearing.
We lift our noses, clogged and unblown,
in reverence to you.
Send the handkerchief, O' Blessed One,
so that it may wipe us clean.
We ask this and all things
in Thy precious and alliterative name.
Bless you.
Where're we going? We're in here?
All right, I like it. It's big,
it's gold, it's fancy. Fancy pants.
Zaphod Beeblebrox,
our infamous President.
What brings you to our humble planet?
Oh, I think you know why I'm here.
No, I don't think I do.
Oh, I think you think you don't.
But we both know you do.
Eloquent as always, Zaphod.
Your ability to articulate
never ceases to amaze.
That's funny. During the campaign, Humma,
when you were my opponent
running against me,
you said I was stupid.
The election is ancient history, Zaphod, but...
if memory serves, you won,
proving that good looks and charm win
over brilliance and the ability to govern.
And, incidentally, you are stupid.
Excuse me, excuse me, Mr. Humma, sir.
I just want to say, there's been
some sort of terrible mix up, hasn't it?
'Cause, actually, he's not with us.
We came to worship you.
He followed us and...
He grew, didn't he. He's not that tall.
You didn't come half-way across the galaxy
to settle a campaign grudge, Zaphod.
Why are you here?
Of course not. That's... that's ridiculous.
I've been stranded on a strange planet
for a number of years.
I haven't been avoiding you.
You look great. You're doing well.
You've grown, obviously.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
We don't know why we're here.
We were trying to get to Magrathea,
and our ship brought us here.
How very, very improbable.
I kept a few souvenirs from my former life.
The heady days of space piracy.
But even an Infinite Improbability
Drive requires coordinates.
Which I happen to have.
No, no, no.
You don't get something for nothing, Zaphod.
You must bring me something in return.
- What?
- A gun.
- A gun?
- A very special gun.
Designed by the greatest
computer ever invented.
But the only way to find it
is to go to Magrathea.
Fine. I'll get your gun.
Just give me the coordinates.
And what will you give me
to ensure your return?
My word as President.
No. I need a hostage.
Only... what does Zaphod
Beeblebrox treasure?
Come on.
Oh, no!
Hey, hey, hey! Take it easy now.
Think about this before you do.
No, stop it! Oh, that kind of tickles.
Two heads are better than one.
Double your pleasure.
It's not fair! You need me!
Come back! Come back!
Don't leave me alone.
Come back!
Well, now, that was fun, wasn't it?
And there I was thinking I was the only one
who considered your boyfriend
a narcissistic moron,
when apparently the whole galaxy does!
What about you?
"Oh, excuse me, Mr. Humma, sir.
"We're not actually with him.
We just came here to worship you."
- Very brave!
- Where the hell is Ford?
By the left, march.
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
Mr. President, we're here for your protection.
Fire upon the kidnapper.
Hey, come on!
Commander, the President is the kidnapper!
You're going to kill him!
Bang, bang, bang, bang!
It's locked!
Thank you, darling. I'll be in touch.
Come on, Zaphod.
- Hey, hey, what did I miss?
- What the hell have you been doing?!
I was out doing field research.
So, they found where we are.
Belgium bummer!
Bummer? They're shooting at us!
What are we gonna do?
I have an idea.
Does it involve pushing him out there
and running the other way?
What? He's the one they want.
Tricia, you can't go out there.
What are you doing?
- Back off!
- What's going on?
I have the President
and I will kill him, I swear I will.
- Could that actually kill him?
- I don't think so.
- It's an aerosol can.
- Oh.
Okay, frightened now, frightened.
- Hi, little guy.
- Get her!
- Zaphod, no, come on!
- Arthur!
- Tricia!
- Tricia! Wait!
Arthur!
Resistance is useless!
Bring her to Vogsphere
for processing, captain.
Circus? Circus?
They got her and it's my fault.
We have to go. Let's go!
Let's go!
Computer, take us to Magrathea!
What? No, no, no, no, no.
We've got to go after Tricia.
- Who?
- Trillian, Trillian!
They've got Trillian,
you stupid half-brained git!
Right, you're coming out!
Computer, we don't want to go to
Magrathea yet. We want to follow the ships.
Oh, I'd love to, fella, but, wouldn't you know it,
my guidance system has been deactivated.
Oh, come on!
I'm sorry about that, but it wasn't my fault.
What are you doing on this spaceship?
- Ford?
- Marvin.
I've been talking to the ship's computer.
And?
It hates me.
No, uh-uh. Eddie, computer...
There must be another way.
Is there another way to follow the ships?
Activating Emergency Escape Pod.
It's super-neat and fun to fly!
Unbelievable!
I'm in. I'm in.
- Okay, Ford!
- Yeah, I'm here.
Do you have any idea?
- Okay, we'll press this button here.
- Okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Press this button again.
- No. Nothing's...
- Okay! Here we go!
- That's good.
- Good man, good man, good man.
- Good move.
- Okay. No, no! Not now!
Okay, we're wobbling.
- Hey, you forgot your towel.
- No!
Get him off me! I'll kill him! I'll kill...
- Okay, Ford, there's a...
- Is that better?
No, that's worse, that's worse.
- Do what... I don't need that.
- No, no, no.
- I don't need that.
- Okay.
Can you stop the rocking?
Okay, Marvin, any ideas?
I have a million ideas.
They all point to certain death.
Thanks very much, Marv!
Magrathea!
- No. We're on the Vogon planet.
- Yes!
- Yes, it is! It's Magrathea!
- This is Vogsphere.
Yeah, Magrathea!
- No, it's not.
- Yes it is! I know it is!
- There is no Magrathea.
- Yes, it is! Yes, it is!
- What are you doing?
- They took my head.
- They have these on Arcturan mega freighters.
Captains use them when
they really need to concentrate.
- What is it?
- It's a thinking cap.
There you go.
It should give him some zest
for about ten minutes or so.
Now I'm feeling much better
about our predicament.
By the way, I checked the Guide for the best
way to rescue a prisoner from Vogsphere.
It said don't.
I'm assuming you have a better plan.
Well, I kind of had this idea that we could...
- Did anyone see that?
- See what?
- What was it?
- Huh!
Nothing, it's... nothing.
It's just my imagination.
Okay, right now, stop! Everyone just
stop a minute, please, and look at me.
There's... definitely
something going on here.
Just... just watch.
Just watch.
Okay, I think we...
Ah-ha! You too!
Yeah, what was that?
I thi...
Zaphod, what do you think?
I think...
Zarquon! What was that? Jeez!
I'd make a suggestion,
but you wouldn't listen.
- No one ever does.
- I have an idea.
Ford! Kill it! Get rid of it!
Okay, don't think.
Nobody think. No ideas.
No theories. No nothing.
This is crazy!
Trillian is in there somewhere.
And we need an idea to help save her.
I have an ide...
Run!
You're supposed to stop.
Okay, so I'm not thinking.
Not thinking. No ideas coming.
All right, this isn't an idea
that has any merit at all,
but, Marvin, can you give me a hand?
Okay, where is she?!
Who, the director of robot arm repair?
Tricia Yggarstuk McMillanus of... Blaard?
No, Tricia Marie McMillan of Earth.
Oh, right.
Sorry, no record of Earth.
Galactic sector ZZ9 Plural Z Alpha?
- Oh, yes.
- She's lying.
She's skinny, and she's pretty,
and she's lying.
Oh, yes, here we are. Earth.
Oh! "Destroyed".
Do you have a second home planet?
- Destroyed? That's impossible.
- That's what it says here.
Says it was destroyed to make way
for a hyperspace expressway.
Who in their right mind gives
an order to destroy a planet?
- He said the gray building, right?
- All the buildings are gray.
"Give me a hand." Ha-ha, very funny.
How am I supposed to drive this pod
with one arm? Stupid human.
So, you need to go back and fill that in.
And then, make sure,
- when you fill in the facilitating form...
- Okay.
Leave this to me. I'm British.
I know how to queue.
If you'd fill that form in for me,
and return it as soon as possible.
You'll find writing implements to your left...
You're President. Can you do anything?
Presidents don't have power.
Their job is to draw attention away from it.
- No offense. You're a great guy.
- Hey!
Hey, how're you doin'?
Hey, it's me, your President!
What's goin' on? Nice to see you.
Thanks for coming.
All right. I know that sponge. All right!
- Next!
- President coming through.
How you doin', Pinhead?
Thank you. No, really, it's me.
I love kabuki. Look at that little thing.
Out the way. Out the way.
Give us a kiss! Give us a kiss, darling!
Hi, I've come about release of a prisoner.
Prisoner release form.
Oh, wha...?
I don't believe you.
These are the orders.
"Love and kisses"?!
Now, according to the Galactic Penal Code,
- the punishment for a presidential kidnapping...
- Come on, love!
...is to be fed to the Ravenous
Bugblatter Beast of Traal.
Good day.
Get off of me!
What the hell is that?
No! wait, wait!
There's been some kind of mistake.
- Tick all the boxes at the right-hand side
of the page. - Okay. Right. Yeah, I've got it.
- Uh-huh.
- Not that one!
What to do if you find yourself
stuck with no hope of rescue.
Consider how lucky you are that
life has been good to you so far.
Alternatively, if life hasn't
been good to you so far,
which, given your current
circumstances seems more likely,
consider how lucky you are that
it won't be troubling you much longer.
Right, there we go.
Oh, kidnapping the President!
And, no, she's not eligible
for release at this time.
Okay. Right. Look...
This... this is the President.
- Oh!
- Okay. See, there?
He says the whole kidnapping business
was just a horrible misunderstanding.
Oh, yeah.
She didn't mean anything by it.
He's ordering you to let her go.
But this isn't a presidential
release of prisoner form.
Those are blue.
- I'll stay here.
- Okay. All right. Hold that. Okay.
Oh, he's hungry today.
That's blue. Right.
- I'm not a journalist.
- We're just hanging out.
Okay. Okay, this is...
it's for Tricia McMillan.
Tricia McMillan. Okay.
Sir, it's a release form.
Thank you.
She's free to go.
Release her.
Zaphod's here. Well then, that's fine then.
Let's just go and him.
Who are we waiting for again?
No, I'm serious.
Tricia!
- Tricia!
- Trill.
- Hey, come on.
- You idiot!
You signed the order to destroy Earth.
- He did?!
- I did?
Yes. "Love and kisses, Zaphod"?
You didn't even read it, did you?
Honey, I'm President of the Galaxy.
I don't get a lot of time for reading.
An entire planet, my home,
destroyed all because you thought
somebody wanted your autograph!
- Honey, they framed me!
- Are you an idiot?! Serously?!
- Trillian!
- You knew. Why didn't you tell me?
- He threatened me.
- Get a backbone, Arthur.
Oh, a backbone? What about coming
here to rescue you? Thank you. My idea.
Stupid!
- Got your arm.
- How considerate.
Right, then, all those of you lucky enough
to have two arms, hold tight.
The President tests my patience.
This time I shall pursue him myself.
Ready my ship.
Fantastic. At last.
Oh! That's one hour for lunch, everybody.
I think I'll have soup today.
The Encyclopedia Galactica,
in its chapter on love,
states that it is
far too complicated to define.
'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy'
has this to say on the subject of love.
"Avoid, if at all possible."
Unfortunately, Arthur Dent has never read
'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy'.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- No, come in.
I didn't...
Look...
Trillian, I just wanted to say,
you were right, of course.
I should've told you, and I understand
totally if you're angry with me.
For what it's worth,
I know how you must be feeling.
- Can you hand me a towel?
- Yeah, sure, this...
Thank you.
Actually, what I was gonna say was...
if I'd said yes to you
and gone to Madagascar,
then neither of us would be here now.
I just thought that might count for something.
It doesn't matter.
All right, computer, take us to...
Where we headed again?
Okay, I'm gonna get you another lemon.
All right.
Engaging Improbability Drive.
No, no, no. Zaphod, no.
Buttons are not toys. What did you do?
Magrathean coordinates accepted.
Guys, it just blows my circuits to tell you
that we're currently in an orbit
at an altitude of 300 miles,
around the legendary planet of Magrathea.
Magrathea! Magrathea!
Magrathea!
Unbelievable.
Incredible.
It's even worse than I thought it would be.
Greetings. This is a recorded announcement
as we are all out at the moment.
The Commercial Council of Magrathea
thanks you for your esteemed visit,
but regrets that the entire planet
is temporarily closed.
If you would like to leave your name
and a planet where you can be contacted,
kindly do so at the tone.
- How can a planet be closed?
- Zarkin' A, cousin.
Okay, computer, keep going. Take us down.
I'd be happy to.
It is most gratifying that your enthusiasm
for our planet continues unabated.
As a token of our appreciation,
we hope you will enjoy
the two thermo-nuclear missiles
we've just sent
to converge with your craft.
To ensure on-going quality of service,
your death may be monitored
for training purposes. Thank you.
Guys, I'm delighted to tell you
that there are two thermo-nuclear
missiles heading right for us.
If you don't mind, I'm gonna go ahead
and take evasive action.
There seems to be something
jamming my guidance system.
Impact minus 45 seconds.
Computer, do something!
Sure thing, fella. Handing over
manual control. Good luck!
I need some help!
I can't do this without my third arm.
Arthur, grab my hand!
- Did we lose 'em?
- No, they're coming right at us.
- Why don't I just press this thing?!
- No, we're not fully back to normal yet!
- So, what will happen then?!
- I don't know!
No! Don't do it! We're here.
No telling where it'll send us. Don't do it.
- Sod it all.
- No!
Wow! Where are we?
Exactly where we were.
And the missiles?
Apparently, they've turned
into a bowl of petunias.
And a very surprised-looking whale.
And an improbability factor
of 8,767,128 to 1 against.
We have normality.
Normality, right.
We can talk about normality
till the cows come home.
- What is normal?
- What's home?
What are cows?
A proper cup of tea
would restore my normality.
It is important to note that,
suddenly and against all probability,
a sperm whale had been
called into existence
several miles above
the surface of an alien planet.
And since this is not a naturally
tenable position for a whale,
this innocent creature had very little
time to come to terms with its identity.
This is what it thought as it fell...
Whoa! What's happening? Who am I?
Why am I here? What's my purpose in life?
What do I mean by who am I?
Okay, okay. Calm down, calm down.
Get a grip now.
Ooh, this is an interesting sensation.
What is it? It is a sort of tingling in my...
Well, I suppose I better start finding names
for things. Let's call it a... tail. Yeah, tail!
And, hey, what's this roaring sound whooshing
past what I'm suddenly gonna call my head?
Wind. Is that a good name? That'll do.
Yay, this is really exciting.
I'm dizzy with anticipation.
Or is it the wind?
There's a lot of that now, isn't it?
And what's this thing coming towards me
very fast? So big and flat and round.
It needs a big wide-sounding name
like ow, ound, round, ground!
That's it, ground! I wonder if it'll be
friends with me. Hello, ground.
Curiously, the only thing that went
through the mind of the bowl of petunias
as it fell was, "Oh, no, not again!"
Many have speculated that if we knew exactly
why the bowl of petunias had thought that,
we should know a lot more about the
nature of the universe than we do now.
What are those things?
They're portals to another dimension.
Right. I don't suppose this portal
has central heating, does it?
Ah, this is the one.
This will all end in tears, I just know it.
Right here.
Hey! Whoa!
Okay, in we go!
We can't just step into that... that!
We don't know where it leads.
If we pick the wrong one,
we just... we come back,
we pick another one. It's no biggie.
What?! Yeah, it's a big biggie, Ford.
A big biggie!
I mean, what if it rips us all into
tiny little atomic particle thingies?!
This is the right one. I have a hunch.
- Ford!
- His hunches are good.
Arthur, I say we go.
Go with the hunch of a man
whose brain is fuelled by lemons?!
This is suicide!
- I think I resent that.
- I don't care what you think you think.
I'm getting a lot of hostility from you,
Alex or...
- Arthur!
- Have you ever tried yoga?
- Trillian!
- I think that's supposed to happen.
She's gone! Ford, she's gone!
Arthur, don't panic!
- Ford!
- Hey, wait for me!
Idiot! Come on, come on, come on!
No, no, no, don't leave.
Come on, come on, just start!
I told you this would end in tears.
Did you?! Did you?!
Geronimo!
Far out! Far out!
This is it! This is it!
Deep Thought. I'm a-coming.
So, this is how it's all going to end, is it, ey?
Me, alone on a dead planet,
with a manically depressed robot.
You think you've got problems.
What are you supposed to do,
if you are a manically depressed robot?
Excuse me.
- Who are you?
- What? No, my name is not important.
You must come with me.
- Get away.
- Terrible events are afoot.
You must come or you'll be late.
- Late? What for?
- What?
No, no. What's your name, Earthman?
- Dent. Arthur Dent.
- Well...
late as in "the late Dentarthurdent".
It's a sort of threat, do you see? No.
- No.
- Your friends are safe.
- You can trust me.
- Trust a man who won't tell me his name?
Okay, my name is...
My name is... Slartibartfast.
I said it wasn't important.
Well... so my friends are safe?
Let me show you.
I could calculate your chances
of survival, but you won't like it.
Did you know we built planets?
Oh, yes! Fascinating trade.
Doing the coastlines
was always my favorite.
And we used to have endless fun doing
the little fiddly bits around the fjords.
But then the galactic economy collapsed,
and seeing that custom-built planets
are a bit of a luxury commodity...
Anyway, you must come with me, because
there's been a terrible mix-up with your planet.
Best laid plans of mice, you know.
- And men.
- What?
Best laid plans of mice and men.
Yes, well, I don't think men have
got much to do with it. Here.
I must warn you,
we're going to pass through,
well, a sort of gateway thing.
- Huh?
- It may disturb you.
It scares the willies out of me.
Welcome to our factory floor.
All right. All right.
Yeah, this is it.
This is it.
O' great Deep Thought!
We have traveled long...
and far.
Have you calculated
the ultimate question of life,
the universe and everything?
No.
- What?
- I've been watching TV.
Oh.
I designed another computer to do that.
Oh, right, I forgot. Is it here?
No, it's not here. It's another world.
It's on another world.
It is another world, stupid.
Or at least it was until the Vogons destroyed it
to make way for a hyperspace expressway.
Well... Okay.
You sure you don't have the question,
or a way to, you know, access it or something?
'Cause I think I've done like a lot to get here.
Oh, shh, shush! The show's back on.
Well, I don't wanna bother you,
so I'm gonna... Good stuff.
Great. I'm gonna go and find something
else for my entire life to be about.
- Zaphod, Zaphod, there's the gun.
- Yeah?
- Gun?
- That Humma sent you for.
- You gave him your head.
- Why'd I do that?
- Okay.
- That's stupid.
O' Deep Thought,
we were told that there is a gun.
- There you are.
- Hmm?
Look familiar?
So, it wasn't destroyed?
Actually, it was. This is a back-up.
Earth Mark II.
So, you made the Earth?
Not me alone, but I did my part.
Ever heard of a place,
I think it's called Norway?
That was one of mine.
I got an award for it.
All right, Frank? That's... that's Frank.
Ah-ha. They've nearly finished the oceans.
Zaphod.
Here, it's...
It's just like Humma said.
Now you can go get your head back.
- Hey, Ford.
- Hey.
It's been nice knowing you,
you zarking frood.
No, no, no, no, no!
- Whoa!
- Lucky this is a bust too.
Hey, man. You know,
you must really be frustrated.
You go through all you're going through,
you come all this way, you don't get an answer,
which means no money and no fame,
which you deserve, man
The Point-of-View Gun, conveniently,
does precisely what its name suggests.
Fantastic. Fantastic.
That is, if you point it at someone
and pull the trigger,
they instantly see things
from your point of view.
Give me that thing.
It was designed by Deep Thought,
but commissioned by a consortium
of intergalactic angry housewives,
who, after countless arguments
with their husbands,
was sick to the teeth of ending
those arguments with the phrase,
"You just don't get it, do you?"
And you're right, I shouldn't be so upset,
because life goes on, you know,
and I should just go on with it.
Shoot him again.
Whoa!
Hitchhiking's good. Towels are good too.
- Say what?
- That is brilliant.
What's goin'...?
I can see why Humma Kavula
would want one of these.
- We better get back. Arthur's waiting.
- Yeah, who cares?
Well, I do. Especially since we're both somewhat
of an endangered species now, thanks to you.
Why so edgy, baby doll? Relax.
Why so edgy?
You wanna know why I'm edgy?
Of course you're edgy.
Your planet's been blown up
and you've been tooling around the galaxy
with the guy who signed the order.
Huh?
You actually wanted to know the question,
because you always wondered to know
if there was more to life,
and now you're crushed,
because you find out there really isn't.
Hey, fantastic! Psychedelic!
You've got no home, no family,
and you're stuck with me,
another in a long line of men
who doesn't really get you.
Huh? That's not true.
And you're worried you might have blown it
with the one guy who really does.
Hey, whoops.
Oh, baby doll!
Give me that thing!
It won't affect me. I'm already a woman.
Hey, it's okay.
It's only a couple of little mice!
Voilà! Himalayas! Good, ey?
Earthman, you must realize
that the planet you lived on was
commissioned, paid for and run by mice.
When you're saying mice, do you mean
the little furry white creatures
with whiskers, ears, cheese?
Yeah, but then they're protrusions into our dimension
of hyper intelligent pandimensional beings.
I mean, I don't know this...
cheese of which you speak,
but they were there on Earth
as mice experimenting on you.
I see where you've become confused now.
You see, we were experimenting on them.
Ah, no, well, yeah, no. I gather
that's what they wanted you to think,
but you were actually elements
in their computer program.
Actually, this explains a lot, you know.
All my life, I've had this strange feeling
that there's something big and
sinister going on in the world.
No, that's perfectly normal paranoia.
Everyone in the universe gets that.
Perhaps I'm old and tired,
but I think that the chances of finding out
what's actually going on
are so absurdly remote
that the only thing to do is say hang
the sense of it and keep yourself busy.
I'd much rather be happy than right any day.
- And are you?
- No.
Well, that's where it all falls down, of course.
Here you are then.
Is this...?
It's all there.
You know, it all works.
Welcome home.
- Hey!
- Hey, man!
- There you are!
- Surprise!
What are you doing?
What happened to you?
Is that tea?
- First, our hosts attacked us.
- Right.
But then they made up for it by making us...
this amazing meal.
It's so... Everything's right.
Everything's delicious.
Oh, come on, that's lovely.
We're glad you like it, Earth creature.
The... talking... talking mice. Cool.
- Sit, Earthman.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you for that.
- Please, drink.
- Excuse me.
- Is there anything else?
- No, we're quite happy, thank you.
Good, I'll be outside, so...
You were right.
- Please, drink.
- Yes.
He was right.
Now, to business.
- To business!
- Eat!
- Shh.
- Sorry.
As you know, we've spent a lot of time on
your planet looking for this ultimate question.
Only to have it blow up in our faces, literally.
Which is why you're here.
We've been offered a lucrative contract
- to do several 5-D TV chat shows.
- Right.
But here's the point.
We must have product.
We need the ultimate question,
or at least one that sounds ultimate.
- Of course.
- Yes, we've rebuilt the planet,
and now all we need is
the missing piece of the puzzle.
- Which happens to be your brain.
- Right.
More tea?
Sorry, did you just say you need my brain?
Yes, to complete the program.
Okay. You can't have my brain. I'm using it.
- Hardly.
- Hardly? Cheeky... Cheeky mouse.
Zaphod! Trillian!
Ford.
What was in that food?
What was in my tea?
Don't worry. You won't feel a thing.
Just wait a sodding minute!
You want a question
that goes with the answer 42?
What about, what's 6x7?
Or... how many Vogons does
it take to change a light bulb?
Here's one, how many roads
must a man walk down?
Hey, that's not bad!
Fine.
Fine, take it, 'cause my head
is filled with questions,
and, I can ssure you,
no answer to any one of them
has ever brought me one iota of happiness.
Except for one.
The one. The only question
I've ever wanted an answer to.
Is she the one?
The answer bloody well isn't 42, it's yes.
Undoubtedly, unequivocally,
unabashedly, yes.
And for one week,
one week in my sad little
blip of an existence...
it made me happy.
That's a good answer.
Rubbish, we don't want to be happy.
We want to be famous.
Yeah! What's all this "Is she the one" tripe?
Take his brain!
No, don't take the brain!
Don't take the brain, mice!
It wasn't me!
I'm famous.
Shoot him, quickly, shoot him!
Oh, bollocks!
I'm gonna be sick.
Belgium.
Follow me.
Left, right, left, right.
Attention!
Thanks a lot for leaving me behind.
Though I can't say I blame you.
Mr. President, we're here for your protection.
Oh, hey, thanks, man. I appreciate it.
Fire!
No! No!
I don't see what all the fuss is about.
Vogons are the worst marksmen
in the galaxy.
- For God's sake, stop!
- Cease fire.
Now I've got a headache...
Marvin!
Oh, no!
He's got a towel. Run away!
I'm gonna get us outta here.
How do you drive this thing?
Hey, what's going on?
We need that gun.
Come on, let's get this ship started.
Come on, start!
Come on. Oh, fire, fire!
Fire, fire!
Oh, he's locked the gate
from the other side.
We'll have to go the other way.
Come on, let's go!
Stop!
Oh, no!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop shooting at us! Stop it!
Oh, I feel so depressed.
- I can't face another day.
- I feel so depressed.
What's the point?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Sorry about your spaceship, Arthur.
Marvin, you saved our lives.
I know. Wretched, isn't it?
You got to ask yourself, what's the point?
Take it away.
You could do all of that, but it's not gonna...
Well, I'll ask... I'll just ask.
I've just been informed by some of the lads...
- ...that since we're so near completion...
- Yeah?
...we're gonna go ahead and finish Earth.
- Oh!
- So...
We, well, we can put it back exactly
as it was when you left, you know.
Unless there's...
there's, you know, anything
you want to change.
Something you think
your planet could do without.
Yeah. Me.
Oh! Hello?
No, as is. Yep, leave it. Yep.
Let's go somewhere.
Definitely. Where did you have in mind?
I know this great restaurant
at the end of the universe.
I am a little peckish.
I need to go to Humma's.
He's got something of mine.
I think.
- I'm so confused.
- Don't worry, baby. We'll sort it out.
All right, let's trip the light fantastic, baby.
Just you and me.
Come on.
- You got your towel?
- Yeah. Why? Am I gonna need it?
- Only always.
- Right. Yeah.
'Cause I wouldn't wanna go anywhere
without my wonderful towel.
Okay. Hold tight.
Stand by for commencement
of life cycle. In three, two, one...
All right!
Not that anyone cares what I say,
but the restaurant is
at the other end of the universe.
It is, of course, well known
that careless talk costs lives.
But the full scale of the problem
is not always appreciated.
For instance, at the very moment
that Arthur Dent said...
"I wouldn't want to go anywhere
without my wonderful towel",
a freak wormhole opened up in the
fabric of the space-time continuum
and carried his words far, far back in time,
across almost infinite reaches
of space, to a distant galaxy,
where strange and warlike beings
were poised on the brink
of frightful interstellar battle.
The two opposing leaders, resplendent
in their black-jeweled battle shorts
were meeting for the last time,
when a dreadful silence fell.
And at that very moment,
the words "I wouldn't want to go
anywhere without my wonderful towel"
drifted across the conference table.
Unfortunately, in their native tongue,
this was the most appalling
insult imaginable.
So, the two opposing battle fleets
decided to settle their few
remaining differences,
in order to launch
a joint attack on our galaxy,
now positively identified
as the source of the offending remark.
For thousands of years,
the mighty starships tore across
the empty wastes of space and finally
dived screaming onto the planet Earth,
where, due to a terrible
miscalculation of scale,
the entire battle fleet was accidentally
swallowed by a small dog.
Those who study the complex
interplay of cause and effect
in the history of the universe,
say that this sort of thing
is going on all the time.