From a distant star they came.
A brotherhood of heroes.
Their names are legend ...
Ultraman!
Ultra Seven!
May
Ultraman Jack!
Ace!
Taro!
The Ultra Brothers!
Born in the nebula known as M78,
they fight for peace and justice
throughout the galaxy.
Warriors great
compassion and courage.
Over time ...
part of humanity to the stars.
Pioneers Astronomical Zeta,
development experts planetary
begin to explore the universe
looking for resources.
But soon they find
Fierce battles
with terrible monsters,
the scourge of the galaxy.
Ray, a half-human warrior
and half-alien Raybrad.
He is one who has the power Rayonix
to control certain monsters.
With them, he fights for peace
while battling his
bloodthirsty nature.
With the fate of
universe in the balance,
a great new challenge awaits
humanity and Ultramans.
The legend begins now ...
MEGA MONSTERS BATTLE
ULTRA GALAXY LEGENDS
PLANET ULTRA NEBULA M78
THE LAND OF LIGHT
SPACE PORT ULTRA
COLISEU ULTRA
TOWER OF RAYS OF PLASMA
POLICE HEADQUARTERS SPACE
I'm back.
Well, Mebius.
The energy is negative ...
waving monsters.
I have a bad feeling.
Many planets have been affected.
Ice, Ace and 80 were
sent to investigate.
We have to find
what is causing this.
A horde of monsters agitated
would be hard ... even for us.
Maybe we should send ... he?
No, not yet.
It? You mean ...
There is an increased flow
Nucleus of Energy.
People, keep alert.
This can be ...
PRISON SPACE
Who goes there?
Do not move!
Good and powerful.
Ultra Black Warrior
locked for eternity!
He will serve me well!
Belial!
Ultraman Belial!
A shadow living in the Land of Light!
Reine this universe to me!
Here, cunningly stolen
Valley of Flames,
Giga-Battlenizer!
Stolen?
I got it!
This universe is ours!
This is true.
Damn.
Belial! Stay where you are!
You go back to prison!
I'll have a good heating.
Come on!
Ultra signal Taro!
It was what I feared.
There was an escape from
Prison Space!
He's behind the Tower Rais Plasma!
We have to protect
the tower at all cost!
Come on!
Yes!
This is the best they can do?
You bore me to death.
Try me!
Belial! Do not forgive!
This one has more spirit!
Strium Kousen!
Taro!
I'm back!
This is terrible!
Take this!
You too!
Idiots!
Hikari!
Mebius!
I will level the city!
Belial, enough!
You'll have to go through us!
He should never have come back.
You talk a lot.
Are you okay?
Personal! Fusion-ray!
Finally ...
Stop it already gone too far.
Get your hands off me!
Belial!
The Spirit of Ultra Warrior in you
is truly lost.
I want the supreme power in the universe.
With the supreme power, the New Order
to be my creation!
Take this!
Stop!
- Taro!
And so it falls into the old guard ...
Taro!
Taro! Get up, Taro!
You're fine.
Finally it will be mine!
And so begins my reign!
No. .. I will not kill him.
Keep looking forever
their fallen people.
Belial ...
Hilarious!
If the light fade
the planet will die!
It is up to me to keep him alive.
Planet Ultra reborn.
Until then, I will protect this light!
Taro!
Our son ... is
protecting the last light.
Yes.
There is still hope.
Can not be ...
Mebius!
Are you okay?
Not much time left.
How do we beat?
The power of Ultra alone
will not be enough.
But through it ...
It?
Rayonix a human ... he
share the blood of Belial!
Rayonix? "
He's kind Raybrad. He has
power to control monsters.
Maybe it will help us
to defeat Belial.
Where do I find?
Come on, Space Pendragon.
Musashi! Long time!
Lord Hyuga, you look good.
I see you are on the route
for the planet Dent.
It is very similar to Earth and can
become a foothold for humanity.
I hear it's beautiful.
But there is no sign of any monster.
So boring!
What do you want?
We deliver cargo,
not hunt monsters.
I know!
I do not think you know ...
A planet like the Earth ...
Planet Dent: All clear. Landing.
PLANET DENT
Really nice.
Ray
It is much like Earth.
Oxygen is so yummy!
Meteorite?
Guys, beware!
That's Zaragosa!
What are you doing here?
Fire!
Are you okay?
I'll take care of the rest!
Ray!
Battlenizer Monsload!
Go, Gomora!
We will provide coverage!
Yes, sir!
Ray needs help!
Attacking it only makes you stronger!
So what do we do?
When in power-up,
it freezes for a moment!
We will have to strike when the moment
when this happens.
Ok! Pendragon, take off!
Ok!
Ray, come in!
Boss!
Oki has a plan.
Distracted for Zaragosa
you destroy it!
Understood!
Missile Wyvern!
- Shoot!
Now!
Super Wave Swing!
Cool!
He has improved!
As a hero!
Gomora, very well!
Come back!
Ultraman!
Mebius!
Ultraman Mebius!
He looks hurt!
Ray!
What ...
What happened?
Where am I?
Ultraman?
No, it's not!
I can feel ...
Rayonix!
No way!
His name is Belial.
Who is it?
He is a demon that will leave
worlds in ruins.
We must stop him.
I'm Mirai Hibino.
Hibino ...
Mirai?
Rayonix human ... Ray
We need your help.
A long time ago ...
Raybrad was an alien ...
a creature with great power.
A black minister who
terrorized the universe
with his flock of monsters.
You have the DNA of the people Raybrad.
He has been a long time.
The battle ended Rayonix.
I got rid of my destiny.
There is a mission that
only you can do.
Let me show you
truth of my planet.
This is ...
Nebula M78, my house
to 270,000 years ago ...
Planet Ultra.
Our ancestors looked like
much with humans.
But ...
The sun!
The planet quiet
faced his end.
But they never surrendered.
After many years of research,
our greatest minds together
created the Tower of Lightning Plasma.
An artificial sun.
Our new history began.
The energies in the transformed
and gave us great powers.
The beginning of Ultramans!
We use these powers
to fight for universal peace
But there was one ...
A large Ultra ...
young, strong ...
and ambitious.
In their search for higher
powers, he tried
catch the energy of the plasma radius.
But it was too much for him.
He was exiled from the Land of Light
So that's the best deal with them?
Who is it?
I'm Raybrad
I reign the universe.
I'll give you the power you seek.
No, stop!
That's it.
The birth of
Ultra Black Warrior, Belial.
Giga-Battlenizer can
control 100 monsters.
A deadly weapon.
Now, the all powerful Belial had
revenge against the Land of Light!
Go! Attack!
Belial! Destroy everything!
Eliminate Ultramans and
Destroy the Land of Light!
Personal flee! Now!
Belial!
Zoffy!
Mary, seeing as I become
King of the Galaxy!
We will not allow!
Really?
Stop!
Ken!
You!
This is your home!
Home?
All this means nothing to me!
I came back for revenge!
You're finished!
Belial! He who dishonors
the Land of Light!
Ultraman King!
Stop! Let me go!
You pay for your
sins in the dark!
Forever!
The King held Belial
Prison Space.
And sealed the Giga-Battlenizer
Valley of Flames.
The Land of Light ..
lady had a history.
Now and again Belial
Land of Light is dying.
The entire universe
it will be soon!
We have to stop him!
You, a Rayonix, and we
Warriors Ultra ...
together we can defeat
the strongest of enemies.
Please fight me!
Okay ... will be honored.
To protect my team, no ...
to protect this universe!
Take me with you!
To the Land of Light!
Come on!
PORTAL TOMB
The Munsters BURIED
I let them make messes again!
Come back to life! Monsters!
My Monster Battalion returned!
What is this place?
The Land of Light
But she is ..
Mirai, what should we do?
That's ...
Dorako! And Bemstar!
Saramandra too!
Mirai!
Alien Shaplay!
So .. some of you survived.
Belial sent?
Correct.
I'll catch them!
Ray-san!
Damn!
Stand!
Ray-san!
Windom! Act! Micle! Go!
You are ...
I'll kill you first!
Yes!
Hunt them down!
Incredible!
Micle! Windom! Act! Come back!
You two have survived!
Yes.
You're back, Mebius.
Ray
How long.
Glad you came.
You are ...
Ultraman?
E. ..
Ultra Seven?
We do not have enough energy to
Ultra maintain our ways.
We are caught in this way.
No way.
Mebius, which was feared came out in force.
Monsters of the Cemetery
Revived monsters!
He used the power of the Tower
Lightning Plasma.
He used our power to do so?
Let's go to the Tower!
Inside the Tower,
Ultraman Taro remains
protecting the light they can.
The light may be the last chance for our
Heroes return to form of Ultraman.
Your mind wanders, brother.
It can be very helpful.
Hey, it's a great idea.
We should get him!
No, we can not even
achieve it as well.
It?
A young fighter with
unlimited potential!
K76 PLANET
Damn! I can not do
anything in this armor!
Part of your training!
Be patient!
Damn!
Stay away.
I can still beat him ...
even in this rattletrap!
I left him with Leo.
We can not see it until
that your training ends.
Why not?
Once, he was also behind
the energy of the plasma radius.
He was young, immature.
Tempted by power.
He almost lost his soul to evil.
Just as Belial.
Stop!
Why?
Stay away from it!
You're not ready!
Do not underestimate me!
I'm ready!
Do not move!
You are violating the law Ultra.
Come with us!
Let me go!
Be quiet!
You are no longer qualified
Warrior as Ultra.
That was the hardest thing
I've had to do.
He was too young to realize
the danger of power without justice.
The danger of power without justice.
You only believe in physical force.
This is not the true strength!
Shut up!
Stop rambling!
Brother Taro, hold on!
Beware!
Still not finished!
Go, Blackking!
Damn! I can not transform!
Let me!
Battlenizer Monsload!
Attack! Gomora!
Go ahead!
Ray-san, thank you!
Taro ...
Finished!
We'll take care of it.
Now, Mirai!
Yes!
Gomora, Super Wave Swing!
Ultra Willpower!
Immense energy.
Use my power ... save us!
This is our last chance.
The Planet Ultra will perish if not
recover the Center of Energy.
We have to defeat Belial.
Come to the Graveyard of Monsters!
Mebius!
I will use them and
the universe will be king!
What?
Belial!
We are here to stop this.
Still alive, huh?
Who are you?
I am Ray
A Rayonix Earth!
Interesting! We are brothers!
We're different!
How so?
I fight for my team, for peace!
Useless folly!
You're a disgrace Raybrad.
I will like to watch
you all die!
Go! 100 Monsload!
Attack!
The Center for Energy!
Mebius, you know what to do.
Yes!
Gomora! Cover the Mebius!
Come on, Gomora!
Ray was with that
Ultraman ... for M78?
Yes, sir!
The planet's Ultraman!
We also must go!
He is 3 million light years.
Would take decades to get there.
Really.
Something is approaching!
Enemy?
Fugitive!
Stay away from my Pendragon!
A ship? From where?
Return fire!
Missile Wyvern! Shoot!
Shoot!
Pick!
No, stay alert!
It is ...
It's not a ship!
Dragon Space Nurse!
A monster!
Is winding us!
Will crush our ship!
Damn!
Freeze!
Human surrender immediately!
Alien Z-Ton!
Why are you here?
To delete you.
May be able to join your partner
Monster in the Graveyard.
A Graveyard of Monsters?
Damn, who are you?
Alien Z-ton, his
quarrel is with me now.
What did you think of my
Waddle ultra thin?
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Are you?
I am Shin Asuka.
Asuka?
I was known on Earth
as Ultraman Dyna.
Ultraman Dyna!?
Great. Maybe you can help us.
We need to get to
Graveyard of Monsters!
To save our partner!
This is serious.
Ok! I will lead them to
Graveyard of Monsters!
Damn! Looks like someone
first go to the graveyard!
Dyna!
Are safe now.
Ok Let's go to the Cemetery
Dyna Ultraman monsters.
And save the Ray!
Ok!
Show you how
a real monster fight.
He will be a problem.
Mebius!
Gomora, Litra, go!
Stay down!
Rayonix Earth! Listen.
Your place is with me ... brother.
Together we can govern
the universe will.
Never. We will defeat you.
You can fight me.
But can not fight
against what you are.
What?
Show me your true power!
You'll pay for this! Belial!
The perverse nature of Raybrad!
Finally. Your true self!
Use this power and end
Ultra with the Warriors!
Personnel ... back.
Ray-san!
Attack!
Destroy! Kill!
That's right! Mate Ultra Seven!
Stop!
Who is that?
That's ...
My god. It is a gathering of monsters.
I caught the leader.
Ray!
Ray was lost!
We have to stop him!
Haruna, we landed!
Land! Here?
Ok!
Ray, come on!
Come to light!
Ray!
Get out!
Ray! Come back to us! Please!
Ray!
You're one of us, Ray!
We're your family, Ray!
Not him ... us!
Hear my voice, Ray Hear me!
Head ...
Humans! How dare they intefere?
No!
Brother!
Seven!
Seven was ...
Kill him.
Our last hope.
Imbecile!
That was close.
Find a safe place.
I glad you're okay.
Now, where were we?
Wait!
Wait? Is surrendering?
You just saved a little life.
So what?
Shut up and let's finish this!
Zero ...
do you remember?
The day you were exiled?
Only then forget it!
Seven, at that time did
you just do.
What?
You were immature.
Seven If they had not detained,
you would have been lost.
You would have ended as Belial.
Eye Slugger!
Why the Eye Slugger
Seven of here?
The Graveyard of Monsters ...
Belial is creating disorder there.
Ultra Seven is asking for help.
He's calling his son.
Son?
Seven is ... my father?
We could not tell you before.
Seven entrusted to us ...
to train him. To help you find
their spirit of Warrior Ultra.
Looks like you're time has come.
Go!
Ultraman Zero!
This is my fault!
Ultra Seven!
Ray, not now! Suffer later!
I'm bored.
Going to finish this now!
Stay away from them!
He's back!
My son ... you grew up ...
Who are you?
Zero!
Ultraman Zero! Son of Seven!
The son of Seven?
You can join the
his father in hell!
Attack!
My turn.
You pay for what you did!
Ok! I'll kill you!
Now ended.
Incredible!
Awesome!
It must be the strongest Ultraman!
That is all that is concerned?
Personnel ...
Etam all right?
Are you alright brother?
Yes.
Zero, the Center for Energy should be
brought back home immediately.
Understood.
What's happening?
You believed me
defeat so easily?
It ... it ...
The monsters have merged!
A monster made of monsters.
Let's smash it.
Ok!
Attack!
Gomora!
This fight is also ours!
Ok!
Zero!
Yes!
No use!
Shoot!
Ok! Shoot!
Go!
Leo!
Their lives will end
in a rain of fire!
Giga-Battlenizer!
My Battlenizer also
should work on it!
Listen, 100 monsters!
Listen to me!
No, stop!
Look!
The monsters are revolting!
It's Ray! He did it!
Now the chance!
Zero, you can!
Ok!
The sacred light chose the Zero!
Deem coverage to Zero!
Understood!
Me too!
We provide coverage to our ultimate weapon!
Ok!
Pedanium launcher!
Shoot!
Go!
Super Wave Swing!
Not finished yet!
I swear I'll be back!
And I'll be waiting for you.
You'll pay for this!
Haruna, takes us out of here!
Ok!
Cool!
Hooray!
We did it!
Incredible! Unbelievable!
Hey, look at that!
Calm down.
But we are the only human
to see the Land of Light!
Beware!
You have to stay behind
force field.
Oh, sorry!
The light from the planet is
too strong for you.
Thanks ... for everything.
No, we who must
thank you.
Ray ..
we are in debt.
See you on Earth.
Yes.
Someday.
Well ..
we still have to deliver cargo.
Ok
We're kind of too off course.
Are we leaving?
Well, you can stay!
Without this!
I will send you.
I'm still on a journey.
Thank you!
Beauty!
Come on.
Goodbye.
Hurry! Hurry!
Come on!
I am very proud
you ... my son.
Father ..
Ultra Warriors!
Once again we are together
in the light of justice.
But our work
not finished yet.
Out in the universe,
evil still remains.
We shall find.
We will fight him.
We will defeat our enemies
and protect the innocent.
This is the code for the Ultra people.
Let's start date.
Here, in this Land of Light
For peace! For justice!
For the future of the galaxy!