A hybrid can withstand these things
My heart can beat with bricks and strings
My ARTPOP could mean anything
We could
Belong together
ARTPOP
We could
Belong together
ARTPOP
We could
Belong together
ARTPOP
Come to me
With all your subtext and fantasy
Just do that thing that you do
In a perverse hue
Rocket number 9 take off to the planet
To the planet
Venus
Aphrodite lady seashell bikini
Garden panty
Venus
Let’s blast off to a new dimension
In your bedroom
Venus
Aphrodite lady seashell bikini
Get with me
Venus
I can’t help the way I’m feeling
Goddess of love, please take me to your leader
I can’t help, I keep on dancing
Goddess of Love
Take me to your planet
Take me to your Venus
Your Venus
When you touch me, I die
Just a little inside
I wonder if this could be love
This could be love
Cuz you’re out of this world
Galaxy, space, and time
I wonder if this could be love
Venus
Greetings, Himeros
God of sexual desire
Son of Aphrodite
Lay back
And feast as this audio guides you
Through new and exciting positions
I wanna be the girl
Under you
I wanna be your G.U.Y
I wanna be the grave
And unearth you
Our sexes tell us no lies
I'm gonna wear the tie
The power to leave you
I'm aiming for full control of this love
Of this Love
Touch me
Don't be sweet
Love me
Please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (GUY)
I'm gonna say the word
And own you
You'll be my (G.I.R.L)
Guy I’m Romancing Loves
To hold you
Know, you wear my make-up well
I'm gonna wear the tie
The power to leave you
I'm aiming for full control of this love
Of this Love
Touch me
Don't be sweet
Love me
Please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (GUY)
I don’t need to be on top
To know I’m worth it
Cause I'm strong enough to know the truth
I just want it to be hot
Because I’m best when I’m in love
And I’m in love with you
Touch me
Mount your goddess
A summer moon comes into full phase
Get on top of me
And Mars' warring spirit rams into the atmosphere
Touch me
Don’t be shy
I’m in charge like a G.U.Y
I’ll lay down face up this time
Under you like a G.U.Y
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (GUY)
I'll wrap you right up guy (G.U.Y.)
I'll lie down face up guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (GUY)
Vierzehn
Drei
Eins
Nein Zedd