Presented by Hellboy20
A hybrid can withstand these things
My heart can beat with bricks and strings
My artpop could mean anything
We could, we could, belong together (artpop) x3
ARTPOP, ARTPOP
Come to me, without your sub-techs and fantasy
Just do the thing that you do
For my love is you
Rocket #9 take off to the planet (to the planet)
Venus
Aphrodite lady seashell bikini (garden panty)
Let's blast off to a new dimension (in your bedroom)
Venus
Aphrodite lady seashell bikini (get with me)
I can't help the way I'm feeling
Goddess of love, please take me to your leader
I can't help, I keep on dancing
Goddess of love, goddess of love
Take me to your planet x2
Take me to your Venus, Venus, Venus
When you touch me, I die
Just a little inside
I wonder if this could be love
This could be love
Read more: Lady GaGa - Venus Lyrics | MetroLyrics
'Cause you're out of this world
Galaxy, space, and time
I wonder if this could be love (Venus)
Greetings from Eros
God of sexual desire
Son of Aphrodite
Lay back and feast as this audio guides you through new and exciting positions
Read more: Lady GaGa - GUY Lyrics | MetroLyrics
I wanna be the girl under you
I wanna be your G.U.Y.
Yeah I wanna be the grave, unearth you
Our sex doesn't tell us no lies
I'm gonna wear the tie, want the power to leave you
I'm aimin' for full control of this love
(Of this love)
Touch me touch me, don't be sweet
Love me love me, please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
Read more: Lady GaGa - GUY Lyrics | MetroLyrics
I wanna be that G.U.Y. x3
The girl under you, G.U.Y.
I'm gonna say the word and own you
You'll be my G.I.R.L
Got our romance and loves to hold you
Know you'll wear my makeup well
I'm gonna wear the tie, want the power to leave you
I'm aimin' for full control of this love (Of this love)
Touch me touch me, don't be sweet
Love me love me, please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
I wanna be that G.U.Y. x3
The girl under you, G.U.Y.
I don't need to be on top to know I'm worth it
Cuz I'm strong enough to know the truth
I just want it to be hot
Because I'm best when I'm in love, and I'm in love with you
Touch me touch me
(Mount your goddess)
(A summer moon comes into full phase)
Get on top of me
(And Mars' warm spirit rams into the atmosphere)
Touch me touch me, don't be shy
I'm in charge like a G.U.Y.
Read more: Lady GaGa - GUY Lyrics | MetroLyrics
I'll lay down, face up this time
Under you, like a G.U.Y.
I wanna be that G.U.Y.x3
The girl under you, G.U.Y.
I wanna be that G.U.Y.
I'll wrap you right up, G.U.Y.
I'll lie down face up, G.U.Y.
The girl under you, G.U.Y.
Achtzehn, sechzen
Fourteen, vierzehn
Drei eins
Nein Zedd! x4