Greetings Himeros
God of sexual desire, son of Aphrodite
Lay back, and feast as this audio guides you through new and exciting positions
I wanna be the girl under you (oh yeah)
I wanna be your G.U.Y. (yeah)
I wanna be the grave and earth you (oh yeah)
Our sex doesn't tell us no lies
I'm gonna wear the tie, want the power to leave you
I'm aiming for full control of this love (of this love)
Touch me, touch me, don't be sweet
Love me, love me, please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (G.U.Y.)
I'm gonna say the word
And own you
You'll be my (G.I.R.L.)
Guy, I'm romancin' loves to hold you
Know, you'll wear my make-up well
I'm gonna wear the tie, want the power to leave you
I'm aiming for full control of this love (of this love)
Touch me, touch me, don't be sweet
Love me, love me, please retweet
Let me be the girl under you that makes you cry
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you (G.U.Y.)
I don't need to be on top to know I'm worth it
'Cause I'm strong enough to know the truth
I just want it to be hot because I'm best when I'm in love
And I'm in love with you
(G.U.Y.)
Touch me, touch me
(G.U.Y.)Mount your goddess, Touch me, touch me
(G.U.Y.)As summer and moon comes into full phase,Get on top of me
(G.U.Y.)And Mars' warring spirit rams into the atmosphere
Touch me, touch me, don't be shy, I'm in charge like a G.U.Y.
I'll lay down face up this time under you like a G.U.Y.
I wanna be that guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you G.U.Y.
I'll wrap you right up guy (G.U.Y.)
I'll lie down face up guy (G.U.Y.)
The girl under you G.U.Y.