A little longer.
QUEMAR LAS NAVES
-Did you find Sebastian?
-No! There's no way through!
Touch him and l'll have
your legs broken!
You're new, right?
Hey! Hey!
What's going on?
Nothing, Father.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Mom? Your pill.
lt's time.
Do you like it, Mom?
lt looks better on you
than it did on me.
Cherries.
lf you don't find cherries
buy raspberries...
...if not, strawberries,
but the ones in a basket.
Then, those flavored
vitamins for Sebastian...
...and cod oil.
Buy beef liver
and lots of onions.
Sebastian doesn't like liver.
Neither onions
but he's very weak.
And for your mom?
The usual.
And some chalk for the ants.
That's Efrain.
l'll get it.
She doesn't want that.
l know, but with a nurse at hand
l'll be at ease.
At least one shift,
don't be stubborn.
You don't get to decide.
She already said no.
Helena, your mother
is very weak.
-Chayo can't do everything.
-Chayo?
What's Chayo got to do
with anything?
Who takes care of my mom?
l do.
Because you... one thing
is to come and give orders...
...1 5 minutes every day,
Monday through Friday...
...and another is to stay.
Don't even think
that's an invitation.
You have your life.
-Smoking is...
-You are not my father.
You're the doctor.
Do you have everything?
Those vials for the pain
are almost out.
Morphine. l'll send them over.
Anything else?
Nothing.
Well, the usual.
Money.
l'll write you a check.
You look very pretty
with that dress.
Let's see.
Helena is becoming
as stubborn as you.
How long has it been
since you showered?
Aren't you going
to go see mom?
Don't go in.
She's with you-know-who.
Take a bath, pig.
-What?
-''And yet, it moves''.
Oh, allow me.
Oh, Javier,
you didn't understand.
l'll explain later.
Javier...
You're so strong!
Who said you could sit here?
Make me move.
Where are you going?
This guy is moving!
Okay, hormones!
Sit down!
Sit down.
Helena.
The shot, Sebastian.
The shot.
Leave it.
You don't know how.
Where are you going?
Learn.
I had no voice.
My throat had cIosed up...
...and there I was,
standing on a dark stage...
...scared to death.
And suddenly,
all the lights came on...
...and l saw thousands
and thousands...
...and thousands of people
applauding...
...applauding me.
And then...
And then what?
She fell asleep.
One day, I'II Ieave...
...and I won't come back
ever again.
I know I have to carry on...
...my Iife somewhere eIse.
One day, I'II Ieave...
...sureIy you'II miss me...
...Iike a city bird...
...that is searching
for the sea.
Because in the end...
...even though
I'm happy here...
...I have to go...
...to a worId far from you.
Don't get me wrong...
...it's not both our business.
It Iooks Iike the end
but it's my beginning.
One day, I'II Ieave...
...and I won't come back
ever again.
I'd rather have IoneIiness...
...to Iive without freedom.
Don't try to hoId me back,
because...
...I'm Iike a bird,
searching for the sea.
I'm Iike a bird
that wants to find...
...new skies where to fIy.
Because in the end...
...even though
I'm happy here...
...I have to go...
...to a worId far from you.
It Iooks Iike the end
but it's my beginning.
Don't get me wrong...
...it's not both our business.
It Iooks Iike the end
but it's my beginning.
One day, I'II Ieave...
...and I won't come back
ever again.
I'd rather have IoneIiness...
...to Iive...
...without freedom.
Without freedom!
Your mother is asleep.
Let's have dinner.
LO YALTY
Juan!
STUDENTS ARE FORBlDDEN
FROM ENTERlNG HERE
Turn left!
Now!
March!
Juan!
Who goes there?
Come out before
l kick you out.
What are you doing?
Look at them!
Just go out already!
Don't hug her like
when l'm hugging your sister.
Jump.
Look!
Jump!
Yes, but don't yell at me.
You're yelling.
All right.
l'll bring him over.
What did Helena say?
Oh, boy, boy.
Seven.
There.
They'll come off now.
He shoved me!
Did you see?
l take care of him
and he hits me!
lt's only his leg.
He'll be all right.
He can die for all l care.
''lt's not that, dumb girl''.
Don't talk to me
like l'm a girl.
lt's friendly talk, dumb girl.
Where were you
when he fell?
ln the courtyard.
He was up a wall.
Sebastian has vertigo.
Yeah, but he wasn't
up there alone.
-He was with a guy.
-What guy?
Some idiot.
He shoved him.
He didn't shove me.
l jumped.
You jumped?
You?
Yes.
l jumped.
My mom's up.
Chayo!
There's nothing to clean up!
What do you want to clean?
Everything's clean!
Chayo!
Everything's in order.
Do your homework or you'll
never finish grade school.
-Junior high.
-That's what l meant.
l'm finished.
Then why don't you take
the day off?
Why don't you go skiing?
What a bad attitude!
See why l don't study?
Every graduate becomes
a bitter hag!
Look what l found.
''Canada, eight days.
Niagara, Toronto...
...Ottawa, Quebec
and Montreal...
...for only US$800.''
This is great.
l hate that you're always
in my room.
All l care about your room
is the computer, not you.
Then take it
as well as your wall.
Put all your trips
in your room.
They're not my trips!
They're our trips.
We're going together, cripple.
Goodbye, Russia.
Now explain me why.
Chelita loved you!
She's a great woman!
lntelligent, educated,
sensible, funny...
Her children live in Houston.
You didn't even have
that problem!
l'm not saying you should
remarry or anything.
l know Blondie,
God rest her soul...
...was one-of-a-kind.
Do you remember
your aunt Blondie, honey?
Wasn't she some woman?
There are no women
like that anymore.
l'm telling you, honey,
so you can start thinking...
...about the woman
you'll bring over.
By the way,
do you have a girlfriend yet?
When do you find the time?
You see, Efrain?
He's just like you!
Shacked up in that
singer's house day and night!
How awful.
-Pour some for me.
-Ma'am!
lt's ready!
That one always yells.
Let's go have lunch.
Bring the flowers, honey.
You're lsmael's uncle
and godfather...
...don't screw him up.
The singer's children are
growing up like savages.
Arm up.
Now the other one.
l can do it.
What else?
They say his mom
was a prostitute.
But a real prostitute.
ln fact, she worked
in Mazatlan.
She died later
due to alcohol...
...or she caught syphilis
or something...
...and they came to live here.
His father has a run-down bar
at the market.
Well, no one really knows
if he's his father.
But he was born there...
...at the ocean.
At the ocean?
He was born in
a damn public hospital.
Why are you so interested?
This one?
Pink is for secretaries...
...and president's wives.
lt doesn't go with us.
This one?
You're strong like me.
That's why you have
to take care of your brother.
''ldleness is the mother
of all vice.'' Alvarado Diaz.
Cut your hair! l've told you,
you look like a girl!
Go to the office.
See if you can help.
You can use
your hands, right?
To be on grant
isn't only a privilege.
is a responsibility.
Next time you take off
during class...
...you won't even have
to come talk to me.
Be warned.
What happened to you?
Oh, right.
Get better soon.
Damn unfair high-school.
Why do you go here?
Because l promised my mom.
What did you do?
Nothing. Father Chacon
sent me here to help.
Do you always do
what you're told?
-You're always scared, right?
-No.
Of course you are. Because
of you, we almost got caught.
l told you to jump
and you froze.
-But l jumped.
-After l pushed you.
Hey, do you want
to take off?
Right now?
You see?
You're scared.
Juan!
Bring me a damp cloth
and clean sheets.
She wet herself.
She's filthy.
You can cry later.
Fifty pesos.
l'm talking to you.
Yes, you do have them.
Who invited...?
Please go. Go.
What now?
Why are you here?
Didn't you go to school?
-l did.
-Two rum and cokes.
Go cry at home.
You have such pretty eyes.
Such bushy eyebrows.
Where's your lD, kid?
l'm with him.
Sit down, dude.
He wasn't in last period.
l thought he came here.
All you have to do
is take and bring him.
How did you lose him?
When did my uncle leave?
-Hours ago.
-What did he say?
What do you think,
dumb girl?
Don't call me ''girl'' again.
l'm the only idiot
locked up here.
l want to go to the movies.
So, let's go.
Don't you get it?
l can't go out.
-Chayo can stay.
-Chayo doesn't know.
She's taken care
of your mom for years!
lf you don't go out
it's your decision.
Exactly!
l don't want to.
Go.
lf you put honey,
more will come.
lt's poisoned honey.
l'll take these.
What table?
-One.
-Are you hungry?
-Yeah.
-There's roasted chicken.
ls that your dad?
What's it to you?
You really broke
a sweat now, huh?
Want a beer?
Cheers.
lt looks beautiful, huh?
The city.
From a distance.
l'm getting the hell out
of here as soon as l can.
-Where to?
-The ocean.
To Mazatlan.
That's where l'm from.
-l've never been there.
-To Mazatlan?
To the ocean.
Really?
See those damn hills?
-Yeah.
-Close your eyes.
Close them up.
Now imagine they're
made of water...
...instead of soil.
They fall over you.
Open them.
No Russians.
Oh, Mom.
Again?
''l wish l could stop you.
l go on bitterly...
...until both of us have died.
l don't care
what you go through.
Your feelings are
indifferent to me...''
Leave him alone.
Go on.
''Why don't they suffer?
l do suffer.''
''Without a doubt, you
are possessed by the devil...
...said he with ferocity,
if you talk to me like this...
...when you are dying.
Don't you understand
that your words...
...will be burned
into my memory...
...like hot iron and
that l'll remember them...
...even when
you cease to exist?
lsn't it enough for
your diabolic selfishness...
...to think that when
you rest in peace...
...l will writhe from
the tortures of Hell?
l will not rest in peace,
said Catalina pitifully.''
''Next to whom he stood,
quietly, becoming...''
The white one.
The white linen.
Don't let anyone touch me...
...only you.
You wash my face...
...and dress me
in my white dress.
l don't want anyone
from here to come.
We aren't from here.
That's the one.
Where's your brother?
Answer me!
Who were you with?
-What do you care?
-l do care!
l'm the one who's
locked up here...
...taking care of everything!
You, mom, the house...
...and who knows
what you're up to!
What are you up to?
l'm asking you a question
Why don't you answer?
Don't you have anything
else to do but nag at me?
l'm not!
l'm taking care of you!
lf it wasn't for me,
the house would fall on you!
Let it fall!
Let it all go to hell!
-l don't care!
-Yeah, l know!
All you care about
is your stupid drawings!
Efrain came today.
Mom is very sick.
Did you hear me?
-Did you hear me?
-Helena, don't yell.
You'll wake your mom.
Shut up! l'll yell if l want to!
lt's my house!
lf you don't like it, pack your
shit and go back to your ranch!
Don't look at me like that.
l'm tired.
l couldn't find him,
but we should go.
-He must've gone with Scarface.
-Did you see him?
No. But they're
very friendly now.
Shut up.
l'll see you.
Aren't you going?
''lf my girl doesn't go,
l won't go.''
-What did you say, idiot?
-Nothing. Nothing.
What's up? Hey!
-How did you get that?
-What's it to you?
There.
Did you bring it?
Okay. Walk.
Wait!
Come on, cripple!
l can't run so fast!
Helena.
Call Efrain!
Mom.
Helena?
Chayo?
-Answer me.
-Whatever you say.
No, not whatever l say.
Why do l always have
to decide on my own?
Do we throw it all away?
l don't know.
Whatever you want.
Do we throw it all away?
Chayo?
Chayo, come here.
l'm giving away all
my mother's things.
l need you to help me.
Want me to tell you
how l got my scar?
My mom was carrying me.
She was happily dancing
with me...
...and l let go of her.
When l fell,
l hit the edge of the stair.
They're my mom's things.
l don't want them to take it.
Didn't you hear me?!
Give everything back!
And Chayo said nothing?
She just Ieft?
Have you thought
about what we discussed?
lf you sell the house
you could save a lot.
You wouldn't spend
living with me.
l'd take care of everything.
We're going to rent rooms.
l put out an ad.
l'm studying English...
...while Sebastian finishes
the school year.
We don't want to leave.
Helena, your mother is gone.
We can manage alone.
lt's our house.
Sebastian?
Sebastian wants
to stay as well.
You'd be more comfortable
at my place.
No.
We'll be fine.
On August 16th 1 51 9...
...Hernan Cortes begins
his journey to Mexico...
...joined by his allies,
the Totonacas...
...who hate the emperor,
Montezuma.
But, as he has to protect
the port of Veracruz...
...in case Diego Velázquez
attacks from Cuba...
...he decides to leave
a battalion there.
The Spaniards are scared
and want to return home...
...so Cortes has all
the boats burned down.
Ships.
Why does he have
all the ships burned?
So no one can go back
until they conquer Mexico.
Exactly.
Okay, you've given me
the historical context...
...of the novel,
but we're talking about...
...the metaphorical figures.
What does one mean when you say:
''Burn the ships''?
lt means that in order
to leave...
...you have to let go
of what's left behind...
...so you can't go back...
...even if you're scared.
What are you thinking?
About mom.
lt's weird that she never
left this place...
...not even on holiday.
We never went to the ocean.
Of course we did.
You were very little,
that's why you don't remember.
Really?
l got a terrible
skin infection.
There are some pictures
around here.
-Where?
-l'm not finished yet!
Ready.
So what?
No.
Stop acting like a child
and get dressed!
l said no.
-We need the money!
-Then sell the house!
We talked about it
and decided...!
''We'' decided?
You decided!
Okay.
But tell me, truthfully.
Do you want us to leave?
Too late.
lt's her.
As of now you can't go
around the house naked.
You'll scare her.
-Where are you living?
-ln a board room.
lt's cool, but it's awful.
l want to move.
Okay, we get groceries
once a week.
We can divide
the expense later.
Do you know how to cook?
Yeah, l love it!
Great because l don't cook.
Hello.
-Do you live here alone?
-Yeah.
l don't know.
My parents...
Shall l show you your room?
Can l put
my ping-pong table here?
-Your what?
-l love ping-pong.
l have the table
and everything.
lt was my sweet sixteen
birthday present.
l couldn't open it
at the board room...
...but there's room here.
l'll tell them to send it over.
lt's cool, isn't it?
All right.
You should stop smoking.
Tobacco dries the skin.
Thank you for your concern.
l'll bear it in mind.
Hey, if you run into
my brother again...
...don't even try
to talk to him.
He's an enemy of society.
He's sick.
l'll show you your room.
lt's cool, isn't it?
-Can you play?
-No.
l'm a champ.
l can teach you.
Okay.
Won't it hurt you?
Why?
Because of your health.
Oh!
Let me give you some advice.
Don't believe anything
Helena tells you.
She's got problems.
Okay, but l play lefty
to give you the upper hand.
l'm sorry. The champ
comes out with the left.
One, zero to me.
Two, zero. Bend down a little
to see it.
Three, zero.
That one was hard.
Do your best.
-So he didn't sleep here?
-l said he didn't.
-l'll call my uncle.
-No!
l told you to come and help me
not so you'd gossip to Efrain.
lf you say a word...
...you can never set foot
here again for treason.
Let's go look for him
in your car.
Something must've
happened to him.
-Hey...
-Don't say anything, Aurora!
l saw him leave.
-Hello. l'm Aurora.
-Yeah. When did you see him?
Last night. A friend of his
came to pick him up.
-They left together.
-A friend? Who was he?
l don't know.
lt was really dark.
l didn't see him.
l couldn't sleep.
Since l was a girl,
l've had trouble breathing.
Shut up, Aurora!
Come on.
lt was a pleasure.
What are you doing
in my room?
Take them.
lf you're man enough,
come take them.
You're a fag, aren't you?
Take them!
His fag friend's drawings.
Don't you dare, bitch.
Fag!
Get away!
Let go!
Let me go, idiot!
Get away!
Helena, can l come in?
l've got some ice
for your face.
Tell Sebastian
to bring them in.
Dude.
-Your mother was a prostitute.
-What, pig?
Your mother was
a prostitute!
Your mother was...!
BIood! BIood!
Blood! Blood!
Come on!
Got anymore jokes?!
Let go of me!
Can't you see this guy
is insane?!
You see?!
Dario, go get Father Miguel!
Move!
Wait, Juan!
-What will we do?
-Nothing!
You and l aren't
doing anything.
l'm getting the first bus
out of this damn town.
Me, too.
Tell them to let him go.
Tell them!
This guy is sick!
Where are you going?
He's leaving.
So am l.
Where?
Why do you want to know?
To have us beaten up?
l'll go with you.
You can't.
You see?
You'll never do it.
-Didn't l tell you to go away?!
-l can't, sir! Get in the car!
l can do whatever l want
and go wherever l want!
-Get the hell away!
-l'm calling your mother!
Sebastian?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
l need money.
Give me money.
-What for?
-l have to go.
-How much do you have?
-Three thousand. What for?
-Give them to me!
-Who are you leaving with?
First you have to explain!
-l don't have time.
-You won't get anything.
Sebastian, wait!
Wait!
Aurora, open the door.
Open the door, Aurora!
Sebastian!
-Did you give him money?
-l swear l didn't. He took it.
He'll come back.
BUS STATlON
What's up?
l can't.
Go to hell!
What is this?
Nothing.
Your room is very cold
and winter's almost here.
We're better off here.
lf she finds out l've been
talking to you she'll kill me.
But she's really
starting to scare me.
First, she put all
of Sebastian's things...
...in her room.
Then, even the bed.
l had to help her
and l even told her...
...that l had a hernia.
They've been locked in
for three days.
When l say locked in,
l mean it.
Helena?
Helena, open up.
We want to see Sebastian!
We're not to blame
for anything.
l am.
lsmael!
lsmael, would you like
to play a little ping-pong?
You're pIaying reaIIy weII.
Stop it with your stupid ball!
Why don't they leave?
One day, I'II Ieave...
...and I won't come back
ever again.
I know I have to carry on...
...with my Iife somewhere eIse.
Can you stop
that damn song?
Can you make something
for lunch, Aurora?
Let's go see a movie.
l haven't heard from him,
l told you before.
He won't call.
He stole from me
in order to leave.
He'd be stupid to call me.
When his mother died...
...his aunts wanted
to take him to Mazatlan.
He chose to stay.
l don't know why.
Maybe he got very
attached to me.
He never said anything.
The opposite of his mother
who'd never stop talking.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
l'm really confused.
But l'm not wrong.
They are screwed up.
What? Do you think
this is normal?
lt's not normal.
Why do you let them
treat you like that?
l'm sorry.
l'm not mad at you.
You're really nice
to everyone.
ln fact, you're too nice.
lt's Helena!
She heard us!
She was spying on us!
She'll kill me!
She'll slap me!
Wait here.
Aren't you going back
to school?
Was it Helena?
lt was, wasn't it?
Did she tell you
awful things about me?
l'm hungry.
Go buy something.
Do you have money?
You can also sell this.
Things mom didn't like.
How do l look?
l'm going to see
if there's any coffee.
Let's go!
Yes, doctor. l have a mark again.
One moment, please.
What's that?
Take that hideous thing
to the corner.
One moment, please.
My ping-pong table!
Honey, we can't take
so much crap.
Let's go. l don't want
to be seen here.
Thank you.
Here you go.
l want to tell you something.
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
That man is hard working.
He works in the land.
He grows corn and beans.
He works doing anything.
-Excuse me.
-lt's okay.
That's enough for you.
Go home.
Go on.
Straight home, okay?
Hey!
What's up?
Hop in.
-When did Sebastian leave?
-Five days ago.
Want me to look for him?
He comes and goes.
He leaves three days,
comes back...
...he leaves again.
l guess he'll come back.
What are you going to do?
l don't know.
Promise me you'll come.
ls she pregnant?
Will you be okay?
Hey, if you need money...
What's wrong?
What is it?
-Good afternoon, sir.
-Hello.
Miss?
A young man just arrived.
Efrain sent them
to clean the house.
l'm going to sell it.
Why?
lt's falling apart.
Half the money is yours.
You can go
wherever you want.
What about you?
l don't know yet.
You can go now,
Sebastian.
Take a bath.
People are coming
to look at the house.
You stink.
l left you something
in your room.
SUBTITLES BY
DISTRIMAX INC.