please click the link below to watch the official release and support our Seohyun!
subs by Taeyeontaeoff
I'm not perfect at korean, but I'm better than nothing, right?
Ruby Ruby Love
The secret of the Ruby Ring
God has hidden a great present in a secluded place on earth
a gift of mystery (?)
that gift is
Gemstones
I'm a freelance jewelry designer who loves all of the gems of the world
Lee Ruby
That's me
I have a name that sounds like a brilliant and beautiful jewel but-
Delivery
Oh no
What do I do?
Delivery!
Just leave the package and go~
what are you doing?
Just leave it by the door and-
my biggest flaw is
Severe Agoraphobia
So I always just stay home
and I'm a pathetic Homebody
Turquoise Prince
How awesome is he going to look today?
Turquoise Prince: Turquoise is the December birthstone that represents success a victory. the stone of success.
My turquoise prince
He's the handsome guy who always leaves the building at this time
and he always has a cup of coffee
He seems so smart and cool
ah, I wanna see him up close
are you a pervert?
This guy is Wondol
no- Gemstone
this is my one and only friend, butler, delivery guy, etc
Sometimes he's more like a devil than a friend
but he's actually an all around cool guy
He's my best friend
hey, Ruby!
Here, take this
and...
hey, what are you doing?
I have to take a picture for the awards
what are you talking about?
The winner of the Grand Jewelry Design Award:
Lee Ruby!
Ruby...
Ru... Ruby Ruby Ru!
I won the award?
really?! - Of course!
Seriously?!
really? oh my gosh!
Yes, I did it!
oh, by the way
I'm supposed to take you to the office
Me? Why?
there're some things you need to take care of
They told me you had to come
Come on, let's go
no, I don't want to
I'm not going out, you know that
Come on, don't you know how much these people have helped you?
You have to say hi to the artists as well
But, the thing is-
hey, you know people shouldn't act like this
you need to keep it together
didn't i teach you that?
I don't want to! I'm not going. never!
Come on- no! I don't want to!
Hurry up, let's go!
It's so dangerous out here
hey, why aren't you coming?
Let's go
This is the center Director Dan Hobak
She's my mom's junior, and my sponsor
It's not a pumpkin(hobak) you can eat
She's like a pretty jewel
Ruby! Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
You got the award! you did it!
I can't believe it
Omo, this is incredible
Your mom would have loved to see you win this
Hobak
I mean, Miss Director
Thank you
It's all thanks to you and this center
hey, what are you saying?
If you're this thankful
If you really are thankful
Then go to the awards ceremony, you have to
what?!
no, I can't go
WHAT?!
are you serious?
Lee Ruby!
Get it together!
You don't have time for this! you have a chance to launch your own brand!
How long are you going to live like a hermit?
You seriously need to fix this now
I can launch my own brand?
Yes, we're going to carry your brand
my own brand?
Yes~
*not sure what she's saying*
But in order to do this, you really need to go to the awards. You know that right?
If she doesn't go, you're not going to give her the award?
Well, about that...We're going to give it to you, we will
But launching your own brand needs to be your first priority
are you going to give it to to Yu Biju?
Biju?
Thanks Ruby, I'll look after it for you!
Lee Ruby
If you really want to save your moms legacy
There's no better chance than this
You know you have to go, right?
I want to go too
But, I really can't go
Ruby, you can do it
I'll take you there. You can go
ah, seriously
Mom
I got the Design award!
Surprising, right?
I was surprised too
They told me I could even launch my own brand
It looks like I'll be able to continue what you started
no, I can't
What should I do?
Hobak told me I have to go but...
5 years ago
I really can't deal with Ruby
Don't you know how scary she is?
wait, what happened?
what? what is it?
It's nothing
She got first place this time, right?
So, I went to congratulate her
but she acted like she had no idea what I was talking about
What in the world?
How rude is she?
she's so rude
It's nothing
Why would someone who wins all the time care what I have to say?
ah, what a bitch
Did you hear the rumor?
That Lee Ruby is a bully?
really? wow...
Maybe she gets first place all the time through bribes
Didn't someone say that she killed her mom?
wow...
I heard that she changed everything on her face, she's a plastic surgery monster
I'm sorry, mom
It's not that I don't want to do it
I just can't
The next day at the awards ceremony
Did she answer?
No she didn't
ah, I guess she can't do it
I told her I could go get her-
No, we told her we would wait
There's nothing you could have done
If we want to do this right, she needs to do this herself
Director!
Ruby didn't come, right?
How long has it been since she left the house?
You don't have any right to talk! This is all because of you...
Next up is today's highlight
It's the Grand Design award
hey, you go up there, okay?
The Grand jewelry design award goes to
The winner is
Lee Ruby!