[ Bell Ringing ]
[ Woman ]
Hold Your Horses Now.
[ Laughs ]
Wait!
[ Kids Chattering, Laughing ]
Be Careful. Bye.
Did You See
Cathy's Glove?
Yeah, It Was Neat.
I Bet If I Had Her Glove,
I Could Catch Real Good.
Yeah, Right.
[ Man ] All Right,
Keep Your Eye On That Ball.
Keep Your Eye On It.
Here We Go, Here We Go.
Come On, Now. Come On.
Pitch It! Come On Now.
All Right, Here We Go.
Here We Go.
All Right. You Ready?
You Ready?
Y'all Back Up Out There.
Back Up!
Come On Now.
Come On! All Right.
That's The Way.
All Right.
♪ Na, Na, Na-Na, Na ♪
Ruby!
Ruby Nelle!
Shh!
Mrs. Bridges,
Your Ruby Scored
Very, Very Well
On The School Board Exam.
So Well, In Fact,
That She Outdid
Most Of The First Graders
Throughout The Entire District.
[ Laughs ]
My Ruby?
Yes!
[ People Chattering ]
Throw The Ball!
Go On, Ruby!
Go On, Girl!
Come On! Run!
Tag The Base!
- Out! Out!
- [ Shouting, Cheering ]
- [ Girl ] Out!
- Safe!
- You Know You Were Out.
- [ Indistinct Arguing ]
- You Know You Were Out!
- Safe, Safe, Safe.
You Were Out.
Mrs. Johnson.
Mrs. Johnson!
- [ Laughing ]
- [ People Cheering ]
- Safe.
- Safe, Boy! I Told You!
Safe.
This Time.
Champion!
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy!
[ Kids Chattering ]
♪ I Got The Blues
I'm Just As Blue As I Can Be ♪
Hi, Mr. Taylor.
Hey, Ruby, Sweetie.
Hi, Abon.
Mr. Taylor.
♪ I Got The Blues ♪
Hey, Y'all.
Hey, Abon.
[ Chattering ]
Come On, Daddy.
Go On.
[ Ruby Giggles ]
- Hi, Mrs. Stein.
- Ruby Nelle, Looks Like
You've Grown There A Bit.
Huh, Sweetie Pie?
[ Giggles ]
Seems Last Week You Couldn't
See Over The Counter.
[ Chuckles ]
Thanks For The Good News,
Doctor.
I'm Sure Ruby
Will Do Us Proud.
I Have No Doubt.
And Thank You, Mrs. Bridges.
See You Again Soon.
Oh, This Here's
My Husband, Abon.
Dr. A.C. Broyard
Of The Naacp.
Glad To Meet You,
Mr. Bridges.
And This Here
Is My Ruby.
Is This The Little Girl
I Hear Is So Smart?
Congratulations,
Honey.
You've Got
A Special One Here, Sir.
Special, Indeed.
She's Been Picked
With Five Other Girls,
And They're
About To Do Something
That No Other Negro Children
Have Done In New Orleans.
You've Got A Lot
To Be Proud Of.
Good Day.
Bye Now.
[ Kids Chattering ]
[ Boy ]
♪ I Got The Blues ♪
♪ Just A Blue As I Can Be
I Got The Blues ♪
Hey, Hey, Hey.
[ Man On Television ] We Go Now
To Our Network Correspondent.
[ Together ]
Now I Lay Me Down To Sleep.
I Pray The Lord My Soul To Keep.
[ Kids Continue Praying ]
In Baton Rouge Today,
Governor James Houston Davis
Called For A Special
Legislative Session
To Determine How To Stop
The Racial Mixing In
New Orleans Public Schools,
Which Is Set To Begin
On Monday.
The Attorney General
Warned The Governor
Not To Interfere With
The Federal Court's Order
To Desegregate
The Schools.
But Davis Vowed Vehemently
To Preserve Segregation
Despite The Warning.
The Lawmakers--
[ Television Off ]
[ Sighs ]
We Gotta Talk Some More.
I Heard What He Said, Abon,
And I'm Not Lettin' It
Scare Me.
Now, Gov. Davis Can Fuss
All He Want To,
But The Federal Government
Is Above The State.
So He Just
Ain't Got No Choice.
But Why We Gotta Put Ruby
Where She Ain't Even Wanted?
I Mean, If She Did So Good
On That Test,
That Must Mean She Doin'
Just Fine Where She At.
But You Know Colored Schools
Ain't As Good
As The White Ones.
Now Dr. Broyard Said That Ruby
Has What It Takes To Go Far.
Honey, No One Ever Took
That Type Of Interest
In You And Me As Kids.
Now Did They?
She Won This Right...
With Her Own Mind.
So Don't You Think
She Deserves To Take It?
If She Does This, This
Could Make Things Better
For Our Other Children Too.
For All Colored Children.
[ Choir And Congregation ]
♪ Let It Be ♪
♪ Dear Lord, Let It Be ♪
♪ Just A Closer Walk With Thee
Just A Closer Walk With Thee ♪
♪ A Daily Walk With Along
Through Thee ♪
♪ Oh, Yeah
Let It Be ♪
♪ Oh, Dear Lord
♪ Just A Closer Walk
With Thee ♪
Amen!
[ Man ]
Hallelujah, Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
Let The Church
Say Amen!
Amen!
Let The Church
Say Amen!
Amen!
Thank The Lord
For His Anointing!
Amen!
You Know, There's
A Message In There.
Yes.
If We Walk With The Lord,
If We Stay With The Lord,
Yes, Lord! Hallelujah!
We Are Never Alone,
Even When It May Seem So.
Today We Are
A People Under Fire.
There's No Denying That.
There's No Denying The Fact
That America Does Not
And Have Not Embraced Us.
[ Agreeing ]
You Been Keeping Up
With The Newspapers.
I Don't Have To Tell You,
Brothers And Sisters,
That Every Day
There's A New Plan...
To Keep Us Down,
To Keep Us Out,
To Keep Us Oppressed.
Yes, Lord.
But, Hallelujah,
I Got Some News
For You Here Today.
- In Order For Us To Rise Up,
- [ Cheering ]
In Order For Us
To Rise Out,
Yes.
We Gonna Have To
Stay Before The Lord!
Yes! Hallelujah.
We're Goin' On Through.
In Spite Of The Opposition,
We're Persevering.
We Gotta Know That God
Will Deliver Us, That
He'll Bring Us Through.
[ Congregation Applauding,
Agreeing ]
[ Pastor ]
Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Hallelujah.
So You Ain't Gonna
Be Walkin' With Us
Tomorrow, Huh?
I'm Goin' To A New School.
We're Gonna Get To Ride
In A Car, Mama Says.
Oh.
Daddy Say I Got To Go
To A Catholic School
Starting Soon,
And We Ain't
Even Catholic!
Why You Gotta
Do That?
Mm-Mmm.
Well, I'm-A Still See You
After School.
And I'm Gonna Still Whup
Your Butt In The Game, Girl.
You Ain't Whup Me!
You Know You Was Out.
See You Later.
We'll See You Later.
You Nervous,
Baby Girl?
I Wish I Could
Go With You.
But You Can Tell Daddy
All About It Later,
Okay?
Hmm?
You're Daddy's
Brave Little Girl.
[ Engine Running ]
[ Man ]
Are You A Resident, Sir?
Can I See
Your I.D.?
Thank You Much.
Mornin'.
Are You A Resident
Of Logan Street?
Yes, Sir.
Do You Have I.D.?
No, No, It's Fine
For Now, But...
You're Gonna Need It
On Your Way Back In Case
You Run Into The Next Shift.
So, Uh, Just Be Prepared
Till All The Guards
Know Everyone.
Hold It.
[ Indistinct ]
[ Humming ]
My, My.
Isn't She Pretty?
She Sure Is.
[ Cielle ] Well, Thank The Lord
For You, Mrs. Taylor.
I Don't Think I Could Have
Done This Without You.
- Honey, You Know
I Love Them Kids.
- [ Humming Continues ]
Now, Ruby You Remember
To Answer The Teacher,
"Yes, Ma'am," When She
Speaks To You.
Okay, Baby?
Yes, Mama.
Good Mornin', Mrs. Bridges.
I'm Deputy U.S. Marshal
Al Butler.
But I Thought The Man
From The Naacp Was Gonna--
You're Being Escorted
By U.S. Marshals Today,
Ma'am.
- [ Baby Crying ]
- Come On, Ruby.
Y'all Mind Mrs. Taylor,
You Hear?
[ Kids ] Yes, Mama.
Come On, Ruby.
Let's Roll, Guys.
Mama? Who Are
Those Big Men?
Just Some Men Gonna Drive Us
To School, Baby. That's All.
Alison.
Get Down, Baby.
Get Down.
Hold It Up Right There!
[ Butler ]
Wait Till I Open The Door
Before You Get Out.
We'll Get Behind You.
The Two Men In The Front Car
Will Walk In Front Of You.
We'll All Go
In The Building Together.
Stay Between The Four Of Us
And Do Not Look Back.
No Matter What Happens,
Don't Look Back At The Crowd.
- Just Keep 'Em Back.
- There Ain't Nothin'
Goin' Through.
I'm Late For
A Medical Conference.
What--
[ Horn Honks ]
Hey!
What's Goin' On Here?
[ People Shouting,
Horns Honking ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
[ Woman ]
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
[ Crowd ]
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
- Move! Get Outta The Way!
- Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
Keep Them In The Middle.
Hold It.
[ Crowd Continues ]
Stop Right There!
[ Indistinct ]
The Governor Of The
Great State Of Louisiana
Says You Cannot Enter.
- [ Man ] No!
- [ Butler ]
Thank You, Sir.
The President Of
The United States
Says That I Can.
[ Man ] We Don't
Want Her Here! We Don't Need
No Coloreds In This School!
Listen To What We're Saying!
This Is Our School!
[ Woman ]
Take Her Back To The Colored
School Where She Belongs!
[ Shouting Continues ]
Let's Go, Baby.
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
Back Off! Back Off!
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
This Way, Mrs. Bridges.
[ Woman ]
What Is Goin' On?
I Can't Believe
They're Sending
That Little Negro Here.
- Miss Woodmere? This Is
Ruby Bridges And Her Mother.
- You Girls Get Back.
[ Woman ]
...Sittin' Next To My Kid!
What Are We Gonna Do!
Take My Child
Outta Here.
[ Rotary Dial Clicking ]
That's Real Good, Honey.
Come On, Boy.
Come On!
Mrs. Ridley,
What Are You Doin'?
Go-- Go Back
To Your Coloring.
[ Woman ]
It Ain't Gonna Happen.
My Child Ain't Gonna Sit
With Their Kind.
It Ain't Gonna Happen!
[ Miss Woodmere ] This Is The
Administrative Vice Principal
At William Franz.
Superintendant Redmond, Please.
My Kid Ain't Going
To School With No Jigaboo.
Mama?
Where's The Other Girls
Who Were Supposed To
Come With Me?
[ Miss Woodmere ]
I Didn't Know For Sure
It Was Going To Be Here.
What About The Other Children?
They Told Me
There Was Two More
Supposed To Be Comin'
To School With Ruby Nelle.
Well, I Suppose Their Parents
Had The Good Sense
Not To Put Their Children
Through This.
[ Door Closes ]
Would You-- Hello?
Tell Him To Call Miss Woodmere.
Miss Woodmere,
This Here Woman Says
She's The New Teacher
Supposed To Be Here.
She Don't Look Like
No Teacher, Though.
Yes, Can I Help You?
Yes. Good Morning.
I'm Barbara Henry.
Uh, Superintendent Redmond
Told Me To Report The Principal
For Work Today.
Oh, Not Today.
Not Today.
Well, She's In A Board Meetin'
Downtown And It's, It's Just
Not Sorted Out Just Yet.
Come Back Tomorrow.
Mm-Hmm.
Okay.
[ Water Running ]
[ Woman Whispering ]
She's Gonna Use Our Washroom.
[ Door Closes ]
That Ain't Right.
You Sure You Don't Want
Somethin' To Drink, Honey?
No, Mama.
[ Bell Ringing ]
She Is Dismissed.
Come On, Baby.
Let's Go.
This School Is Easy,
Mama.
[ Man On Tape Recorder ] With
Children In Crisis Situations,
Hey!
Stress Seems To Present
Itself In A Variety Of Ways.
Hi, Sweetie. What Happened?
Did It End Early?
I Never Got There.
The Streets Were Blocked.
You're Never Gonna Believe
Why. It Was Crazy.
I'm, Uh, Sitting
In The Car, Right?
There's Police
Everywhere. I Can't Move.
And There's
This Crowd Of Women
Standing In Front
Of A School.
Then This Little, Tiny,
Adorable Negro Girl
Gets Out Of A Car
Surrounded By Huge Marshals.
And Then These Women--
I'm Pretty Sure
They're Mothers--
They, They Start Chanting
These, These Hateful Things
At This Little, Bitty Girl.
I've Never Seen
Anything Like It.
People Can Be
So Mean, Bob.
Yeah.
I Grew Up Watching How
They Treated Effie, My Nanny.
They'd Act Like Her Color
Made Her Guilty Of Something.
Maybe I Could Work With Her.
You Know, Offer My Help
To Her And Her Family.
And Study The Situation
And Try To Help Her Cope.
I Think It Would Certainly
Be As Important
As The Work I Did With
The Kids In The Polio Ward.
- I Think It's A Great Idea.
- Yeah?
[ Crowd Shouting ]
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Get These People Back.
[ Butler ]
Wait A Minute, Mrs. Bridges.
[ Crowd Pounding On Car ]
Clear The Way. Okay.
Okay, Mrs. Bridges.
Come On, Ruby.
[ Cop ]
All Right Now, Keep It Clear!
Get Back! Get Back!
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Don't Mind Them, Ruby.
Keep Walking.
[ Man ]
Get Back, You Scum.
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
We Don't Wa--
This Is Your Teacher,
Mrs. Henry.
[ Phone Ringing ]
Well, Hello, Ruby Nelle.
It's So Nice To Meet You.
Very Nice To Meet You Too,
Mrs. Bridges.
Likewise.
So, Ruby, I Hear That
You're Quite A Good Student.
Is That True?
Yes, Ma'am.
Well, That's Perfect 'Cause
I'm Pretty Good Myself.
[ Woman Clicks Tongue ]
I Don't Know.
[ Crowd Chanting ]
This Here Is The
Captain Doctor Robert Coles.
Pleased To Meet You,
Captain.
Pleasure.
Sorry, But I Have To Check
Everyone That Comes In Here.
I Understand.
Would You Turn Around,
Please?
Sure.
[ Crowd Shouting ]
There Was A Phonics Book
In Here Just A Minute Ago.
[ Woman ]
Get Out Now!
You'll Have To Forgive Me. I--
I Haven't Quite Gotten
My Bearings Yet.
How Long Have You Been Here?
Since 8:30.
[ Woman ]
Go Home, You Pickaninny!
You Don't Belong Here!
[ Shouting Continues ]
[ Shouting Continues,
Muted ]
The Humidity Here
Is Something.
Where You From?
Boston, Originally.
But I've Been Teaching Children
Overseas On A Military Base.
I Just Recently Was Married,
And My Husband's Work
Is Here In New Orleans,
So I've Come
To Join Him.
Well, Welcome To The South.
Yeah.
Well, I'm Here Today
Because I'd Like To Talk
To The Negro Child Who's
Attending Here And, Uh--
Now What Would You Wanna Talk
To That Little Nigra For?
I'd Like To See
How She's Doing.
The Focus Of My Work
Is To Study How
Children Handle Stress.
How They Cope With Crisis
Intrigues Me.
I Can Tell You Right Now
There's Nothin' Intriguing
About That Colored Child.
I Certainly Respect
Your Opinion, Ma'am.
Um--
But, Uh,
If You Would Allow Me
To Speak To Her Mother,
I'd Appreciate It.
I Can't Get More Involved
Than I'm Required To.
Maybe You Could
Give Me The Child's Name.
We Have Strict Orders.
I'd Be Breakin' The Law.
Well, If You're So Interested
In The Colored,
You Ought To Go
Talk To Their Organization.
I'm Sorry.
What Organization?
That Colored People's
Organization.
Good Day.
[ Barbara ]
Okay, I'm Gonna Write
A Word On Your Paper.
Christmas!
Very Good.
Now, Listen.
Using The Letters
In Christmas,
I Want You To Write Down
As Many Words As You Can,
Using Only The Letters
In The Word.
Okay?
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
C-H-
R-I-
S-T!
Christ!
Her Dexterity
Is Advanced For This Age.
She Writes Fast And Well.
[ Cielle ]
She Picks Up Everything,
Just Like A Sponge.
C-A-R. Car.
H-I-T. Hit.
S-I-T. Sit.
H-I-M. Him.
S-T-A-R. Star.
Excuse Me.
Can You Tell Me
Where The Lounge Is?
Please?
This Way.
You Know, I Don't Envy You,
Mrs. Henry.
You Must Have
Really Needed A Job.
[ Laughing ]
Did You See That Dress
She Was Wearin'?
There's No Need For
Consolation, Miss Spencer.
I've Taught Children From
Many Different Backgrounds,
And I Enjoy Them All.
This Is A Disgrace.
This Place Is Ruined.
And You're Part Of It.
Well, It's Unfortunate
That She Feels That Way.
Frankly, I Think
It's Pretty Silly
For A Whole School To Empty Out
Because Of One Little Girl.
When Superintendent Redmond
Offered Me This Position,
I Had No Idea
I'd Have One Student.
I-I Told Miss Woodmere
I Couldn't Teach
That Little Negress.
We Have Friends That
Gave Their Resignation
Rather Than Teach Her.
[ Sighs ]
For What We Are About To Receive
May We Truly Be Thankful. Amen.
'Round Here,
We Don't Teach Them,
And Our Kids Don't
Learn With 'Em.
[ Crowd Shouting ]
Black Trash, Don't Come Back!
♪ [ Indistinct Singing ]
This Is Dangerous,
Lucielle.
It's Only Day Two.
It Ain't Too Late
To Back Out Of This.
Why Are You Always
Scared Of Everything, Huh?
Never Wanna Make No Waves.
The Only Way We Gonna
Have Something
Is If We Take It.
I Fought In A War
And I Won A Medal.
You Think I Got That Medal
Bein' Scared?
Hon, You Best Mind
Who You Talkin' To.
I'm Sorry.
Baby,
I've Been To The School,
And I've Seen It. It's Better.
It's Cleaner.
It's Nicer. It's Newer.
And Her Teacher.
Her Teacher's From Up North,
And She's Smart,
And She's Kind.
She's Supposed To
Go Alone Tomorrow.
Now,
She's Just A Little Girl.
How Can We Put Her
Through That?
I'm Sick Of People
Telling Us
Where We Can't Go,
What We Can't Do,
What We Ain't
Supposed To Have.
My Children
Are Gonna Have More.
They Deserve More.
And The Only Way Things Are
Gonna Get Better For Them
Is If We Make 'Em Better.
Honey,
We Can't Be Afraid.
Give Mama Some Sugar.
Give Mama A Kiss.
[ Murmuring ]
Good Night, Baby.
[ Girl ]
Good Night, Mom.
You Know Mama's Gotta
Go Back To Work Tomorrow.
And Daddy's Working.
So You Think You Could
Be A Brave Girl
And Go To School By Yourself
With The Big Men?
Hmm?
Okay.
[ Sighs ]
You Know Jesus
Faced A Mob Too, Baby.
Just Like You.
And You Know What He Did?
He Prayed For Them.
Because The Bible Says,
"Bless Them That
Persecute You.
Bless And Curse Not."
[ Crowd Shouting ]
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
Ruby, Remember What I Told You.
Keep Lookin' Straight Ahead.
[ Shouting Continues ]
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Woman Spits ]
[ Reporter ]
Sir!
I Hate You! Hear Me?
I'm Gonna Hang You
Till You Choke To Death!
[ Abon's Voice ]
You're Daddy's
Brave Little Girl.
[ Abon's Voice ]
You're Daddy's
Brave Little Girl.
[ Cielle's Voice ]
Remember, God Loves You,
Ruby Nelle.
God Loves You, Baby.
[ Abon's Voice ]
You're Daddy's
Brave Little Girl.
Two, Four, Six, Eight!
We Don't Wanna Integrate!
Two, Four, Six--
[ Woman ]
I'm Gonna Hang You!
I'm Gonna Hang You
Till You Choke To Death!
Go Home!
[ Shouting Continues ]
We Don't Want You Here!
Go Home!
[ Door Slams ]
[ Woman ]
Look. She's Come Back Again.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Barbara ]
Ruby Nelle.
Don't You Look
So Very Special Today.
Your... Dress Is Lovely,
And Your Bow Matches
So Perfectly.
So, You Catholic Yet?
Uh-Uh.
Them Nuns Are Mean.
They Be Hittin' Me
On My Knuckles And Stuff.
Yeah?
My Teacher's Nice.
Daddy Says Sore Knuckles Is
The Price You Have To Pay
For Private School,
And Private School
Means You Better.
You Got Lots Of Kids
In Your Class?
Tsk.
That Ain't Private Then.
My School Is Private.
I'm The Only One There.
My Daddy
Said It's Your Fault
We Got All Them Horses
Up The Street.
And Ain't Nobody
Like 'Em, Neither.
Hey, Daddy!
Look At All Those Doughnuts.
♪ I've Got The Blues ♪
[ Baby Cooing ]
Daddy, You Ain't Hungry?
Somethin' Wrong
With My Cookin' Tonight?
Why You Got So Many Doughnuts
Today, Daddy?
Honey?
Folks Down At The Bakery
Heard What A...
Brave Thing
You Was Doin' And--
And They Wanted To Give You
And Your Sister And Brothers
An Extra Special Treat.
Ain't That Nice
Of Them?
Boss Told Me Today,
"I Can't--
"I Can't Have No Negro
Workin' For Me
What's Got A Child
In A White School."
Been Workin' There
Goin' On Eight Years Now.
Ain't Never Had
One Unhappy Customer.
Not One.
Ain't-- Ain't Nobody Better
At Fixin' Cars Than Me.
I Know, Baby.
I Know, But It'll All
Work Itself Out.
You'll Get Another Job.
[ Chuckles ] My Buddy
Owns The Bake Shop Was
Watchin' Out The Window,
I Guess, When--
When My Boss Tol--
Told Me To Go.
Gave Me All The Doughnuts
He Had.
I Told Him
I Appreciate It, But...
I Didn't Wanna...
Take All He Got.
He--
He Said,
"Abon, Man, Don't
Even Worry About It.
"I Can--
I Can Always
Make More."
[ Sniffling ]
What Can I Make More Of,
Cielle?
Abon, Don't.
Ah!
I Was In The Army.
I Know About Integration.
I Know All About It.
It Don't Work.
It Don't Work!
You Know, They Ain't--
They Ain't Treat Me
Like A Soldier.
I Was A Colored Soldier.
A Nobody!
It Was-- It Was Just Fine
With White Folk
When I Was Willin' To Die
For This Country,
But You Try To Give My Kid,
My, My Beautiful Little
Daughter, What That Kid's Got,
And They're All Up On My Back
Remindin' Me
How It's Their Country!
Abon, Come On. I Know
Everything Seems Wrong.
And You're Probably
Blamin' Me For It,
But, Honey, We're Gonna
Get Through This.
I Believe In You
So Much.
And I Know God's Gonna
Make A Way For Us.
[ Baby Crying ]
I Just Know It.
[ Sighs ]
[ Crying Continues ]
Oh, God.
My Daddy's
Coming With Me Today.
I'm Sorry, Sir,
That'll Be Too Dangerous.
Why? I'm Her Father.
Ain't Nobody--
I Understand, Sir.
And You're A Man.
But As A Man And Her Father,
I'm Not Sure That You'd
Be Able To Restrain Yourself.
Listen, I--
She'll Be Fine.
Them Crackers'll Make You
Want To Beat 'Em Down.
I'm Sorry.
[ Whispers ]
Daddy Loves You.
Give Me A Kiss.
Go On.
Let's Go, Ruby.
[ Barbara ]
Miss Woodmere.
Miss Woodmere!
As You Know,
She Has No Phys Ed,
And She Should Have
Some Type Of Music Lesson.
I Just Wanted To Know
What You Thought.
Well, Due To Your Student,
I Really Don't Have Time
To Think.
As You Know, We're Forced
To Vacate School Property
Expeditiously.
That Is Not Due To My Student,
Miss Woodmere.
We Must Be Escorted
From The Premises
Because Of People's Attitudes
Toward My Student.
That Is Exactly The Point.
They've Given Us No Time
To Prepare,
And I'm
Caught In The Middle.
Now What Do You
Expect Me To Do?
"Hang."
Good.
Very Good.
"And The Hat.
I Have A New Hat."
And 30 And 40
And 50...
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
And 60 And 70--
[ Woman ]
I'm Gonna Poison You!
It's Okay, Ruby.
It's Gonna Be Okay.
[ Shouting Continues ]
When Are All The Other Kids
Coming Back
So It Can Be
Like A Normal School?
They'll Come Back
Eventually.
Their Parents Are
Just Angry Right Now.
But Soon They'll Get Over It
And Bring Them Back.
For Now, You Should
Just Think Of This
As Your Very Own School.
What Do You
Think Of That?
[ Mumbles ]
I Don't Know.
We Can Have Fun,
Just The Two Of Us, Can't We?
[ Giggles ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
Okay. Now I Will Be Back
In 30 Minutes.
And I Want You
To Eat Your Lunch Now Too.
[ Whispers ]
Okay.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
♪ [ Blues ]
Here We Go.
[ Broyard ]
Good Afternoon, Mr. Bridges.
Good To See You Again.
[ Abon ]
Cielle.
Good Afternoon,
Mrs. Bridges.
I'd Like You To Meet
Dr. And Mrs. Coles.
Jane.
Pleased To Meetcha.
Nice To Meet You Both.
[ Dr. Coles ]
Pleasure's Ours, Ma'am.
He's A Psychiatrist.
A What?
Psychiatrist.
Sorry For Dropping By
Unannounced,
But The Coles Have Wanted
To Meet You For Some Time,
And They Came
All The Way From Biloxi.
Oh.
He And I Have
Spoken At Length,
And I'm Confident
Ruby Would Benefit
From Talking With Him.
[ Dr. Coles ]
I'm, Uh, Aware Of What's Going
On Out At The Franz School.
I've, I've Seen And
I'd Love To Be Of Help,
If I May.
Uh, Well, Uh--
We Can't Afford
No Psychiatrist.
No.
Oh, No, No, No, No. I Won't
Be Charging You Anything.
Well, Thank You Very Much,
But, Uh,
We're Just Regular Folk.
Ain't Nobody Crazy Here.
I Understand.
You Should Know, Though,
That I Have
Extensive Experience
Working With Children,
Especially Children
Facing Great Adversity.
And, Uh, In Most Cases,
It Can Be Quite Helpful
If They Have An Opportunity
To Speak With Someone
Outside Of The Family.
You All Have A Nice Day.
Good Afternoon.
Um, I'll Tell You What.
If You Happen To Change
Your Mind For Any Reason,
Please Don't Hesitate To Call.
Thank You Very Much.
Thank You.
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
Okay?
Dr. Broyard, You Know
My Husband's Been Laid Off
For Quite Some Time.
And We Were Wondering If
Someone In The Organization
Might Be Able To Find
Him Some Work.
I Mean, He's Really Good
At A Lot Of Things.
We Don't Think That Now's
A Good Time For Him
To Be Looking.
Better To Lay Low For A While,
Let Things Simmer Down.
So I'm Supposed To Just Sit
Around Here Doin' Nothin'
'Cept Worry About
How I'm Gonna Pay The Rent
And Take Care Of My Family.
These Donations
Ain't Gonna Last Forever.
I Understand How You Feel.
I'm A Man With
A Family Myself.
But... It's Just Temporary.
In The Meantime,
We'll Make Sure
Your Family's Needs Are Met.
And Try To Remember
What A Privilege It Is
For Ruby To Be Doing This.
Really?
Any Of Them Little
Colored Girls
At That Other White School
Happen To Be Children
Of Naacp Folk?
Huh? I Mean,
How Many Of Y'all
Put Your Six-Year-Olds
Up To This Here Privilege?
Any Of You Had The Privilege
Of Losin' Your Jobs?
[ Boy ]
Uh-Oh. Daddy's Mad.
I Don't Wanna Talk Right Now.
Go On Back Inside.
Baby, I--
I'm Serious, Lucielle.
- Daddy, Daddy.
- Hey.
You Promised To Play Ball
With Me Today.
[ Blows Whistle ]
Come On.
Go On.
Ow!
[ Giggling ]
I Don't Wanna Play.
Stop It, Carl.
You Can't Play!
[ Kids Chattering ]
Mama!
Ruby Called Carl A Nigger,
And She Said She Was
Gonna Kill Him.
[ Humming ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Continues Humming ]
[ Dr. Coles ]
Why Don't We
Start With You, Uh,
Drawing A Picture
Of Your School.
Can You Tell Me Something
About Your School?
It's Fun.
My Teacher Likes Me.
Oh. Know What?
I Got A Tea Set In The Mail.
Wanna Play?
Um, No. Why Don't We Just
Keep Drawing For Now, Okay?
Okay.
[ Humming ]
I Wanna Draw
My Teacher Now.
Why Don't You Wanna
Finish This One?
It Is Finished.
Are These The People
Out In Front Of The School?
Is That How They Look To You?
I Don't Know How They Look
'Cause I Don't Look At 'Em.
Why Don't You Look At Them?
'Cause My Mama And The Man
Told Me Not To,
So I Don't.
Me And Mrs. Henry Count High
When We Do Jumping Jacks.
All The Way
To A Hundred.
[ Humming ]
They Were Just Lovely.
Next Time You Should Really
Sit Down And Chat With Them.
You Know, Jane, I'm Not
There To Socialize. Okay?
[ Sighs ]
So How Did It Go
In There?
Oh. According To Ruby,
Everything's Just Fine
At School.
She's Having A Good Time.
Well, Maybe--
I Mean, How Can That Be?
It Doesn't Make Any Sense.
She Doesn't Show Any Signs Of
Being Scared Or Traumatized.
Honey, You'll Figure It Out.
- It's The First Meeting.
- Mm-Hmm.
[ Crowd Shouting ]
[ Woman ] Go Home!
We Don't Want You Here!
- I'm Gonna Poison You!
- Black, Black,
Don't Come Back!
- [ Chanting Continues ]
- Don't Look, Ruby.
We're Gonna Poison You!
We're Gonna Poison You
Till You Choke To Death!
[ Sobbing ]
What's The Matter, Baby?
[ Sniffs ]
I'm Scared.
Did You Have
A Bad Dream?
No, But I Was
Thinking Bad Things.
Mmm.
Did You Say
Your Prayers?
Well, What Do You Expect,
Honey? Come On.
Come On.
I Want You To Go In There,
Get Back On Your Knees,
And You Ask Him
To Take Care Of It.
I'm Scared.
Go On.
Thank You, Mrs. Stein.
[ Indistinct ]
Hey.
It's That Colored Girl.
[ Doorbell Jangling ]
Hi, Mrs. Stein.
Hi.
I'm So Sorry, Abon,
But Will You Please...
Not Come Here Anymore?
Why?
Please.
Please, Just Go.
Okay, Fine.
Won't Come In Here No More,
If That's How You Want It.
You Remember Who Was First
To Come In Here
When You First Moved Here
And Them Crackers
Wouldn't Buy From No Jews.
Ain't Never Been Nothin'
But Nice To You, Ma'am,
But If That's How You Want It,
That's How It's Gonna Be.
Come On.
[ Doorbell Jangling ]
[ Mocking Humming ]
[ Abon ]
Come On, Y'all.
Let's Go.
Get Ready For Bed.
Come On. Ruby Nelle,
You Better Eat That Food.
[ Cielle ] Child, You
Better Finish That Plate
And Stop
That Foolishness.
I'm Just Not Hungry.
You Heard Your Daddy.
Baby, Please.
Please Eat Something.
Maybe I'll Have Some Chips
Out Of The Bag.
Only A New Bag, Though.
And A "Co-Cola."
[ Sighs ]
Here, Swallow This.
My Cookin' That Bad,
All You Want To Eat
Is Packaged Foods?
You Didn't Eat Nothin'
Yesterday. You Didn't
Eat Nothin' This Mornin'.
All You Wanna Eat
Is Chips.
Does Mrs. Stein
Stand Outside My School
And Say Those Mean Things?
[ Sighs ]
No. Baby, She's Jewish.
They Not Much Nicer
To Her, Either.
But She Said We Can't
Come In Her Store No More.
She Did?
Well, That's
Not Very Nice, But--
It's Because Of Me, Right?
How Come No One
Likes Me, Mama?
No. Baby, No.
No.
See, You And The Other
Colored Girls
Are Doin' Something
That White Folks Don't Like.
It's Not You. They Don't
Want Colored Children
Goin' To Their Schools.
But You Know What?
You're Special,
And You're Smart,
And You Deserve An Education
Just As Good As Theirs.
They Say Those Mean Things
'Cause They Want You To Think
That You Don't Deserve It.
But No Matter What They Say,
You Know God Loves You.
And They Don't Know
What They're Talking About.
[ Crowd Shouting ]
- Go Home!
- [ Shouting Continues ]
I'm Gonna Poison You.
I'm Gonna Poison You
Till You Choke To Death,
You Little Nigger!
- Don't Look, Ruby.
- Go Home! Go Home!
Step Back!
Get Her Inside!
Yes, Sir! I Got You!
- I-I'm Just Tryin' To Take
My Daughter To School.
- Traitor!
[ Shouting ]
Okay, Reverend.
Come On. Hurry Up.
[ Girl Whimpering ]
Let's Get Outta Here.
Traitor! Traitor! Traitor!
[ Sobbing ]
They're Crazy.
Traitor!
Why Don't You Go Home?
We Don't Want You Here!
- Go Home!
- Traitor!
Honey,
Some People Were Raised
With Funny Ideas
About People That Are
Different Than Them.
You See, They--
[ Sighs ]
They Think Skin Color
Is Everything.
And If You Don't Have
The Same Skin As Theirs,
They Don't Like You.
Oh.
Not All People
Are Like That.
We're Not Like That.
We Know That All People
Are Special.
And That We Should
Respect Everyone.
Is It Only My Skin?
[ Sighs ]
Ruby, Do You Know What,
What Slavery Is?
No? Well, There Was
A Time In The South
When White People
Used To Own Negroes.
Like You Would Own
A Pet Or, Or A Toy.
And They Used To Make
The Negroes Work Very Hard
Without Any Pay.
But In The North,
Where I'm From,
We Knew That Was Wrong.
And The North And South
Had A Big Fight,
And The North Won.
And They Told The South
They They Had To
Free All The Slaves.
Praise The Lord.
[ Chuckles ]
But You See, Some People
Still Haven't Gotten Over
The Difference
Between Negro And White,
And They Don't Want Them
To Be Together.
And Those People Outside
Are Angry
Because The Laws
Are Forcing The Whites
To Be With The Negroes,
And They Don't Like That.
But Why Do They Say
Those Mean Things To Me?
I Didn't Do Anything.
No, You Didn't
Do Anything, Honey.
You See, They Just--
They Just Feel Threatened
And-- [ Sighs ]
They're So Angry That
They Don't Like Anybody,
Not Even Themselves.
You Know, Some People
Sometimes When They
Feel Kicked Down That--
Hey Don't Know
How To Do Anything Else
But Kick Other People Down.
And You And I Both Know
That That's Not Right.
Right? Yeah.
Okay.
[ Baby Crying ]
Why Don't We Take A Look
At Our Drawings Now?
Shall We? Let's See
What You've Done.
Hmm.
Let Me See That.
- Is This You Here, Ruby?
- Uh-Uh.
It's My Friend Alison
And Her Daddy.
She's Sad Because He Don't
Like Her To Play With No One
Whose Daddy Doesn't
Make As Much Money
As Her Daddy Makes.
Oh. So Alison's
A White Girl.
No.
No?
She's Like Me.
Oh? I Couldn't Tell
Because You Draw Her
And Her Father
With Pink Crayons
Instead Of Brown.
In Fact, You Draw Yourself
With Pink Crayons A Lot Too.
So You've Got Blue Hair
Instead Of Black.
And, Um, You've Drawn Yourself
And Alison And Her Father
With Missing Parts.
See, You Don't Have
A Mouth There,
Alison Doesn't Have Ears,
And Her Father Has No Eyes.
But You Teacher And I--
You've Drawn Us
With All Of Our Parts
Carefully Intact.
Why Do You Think
That Is?
You Call This Good?
There's Kindergartners
Who Draw Better Than That.
[ Laughing ]
What's Wrong
With My Drawing?
[ Laughing ]
Yeah, That Is
Pretty Bad, Huh?
[ Laughing ]
That's Good.
Oh.
Oh, Bob.
You've Gotta Try This.
Lucielle Taught Me
How To Make Red Beans And Rice.
[ Laughs ]
Uh, No, Thank You.
[ Kids ] Good Night, Daddy.
He Never Gets Anything
This Good At Home.
Everyone In Bed?
Yeah.
[ Clears Throat ]
Why Don't You Have
A Seat, Doc?
Oh, Uh, No.
No, Thank You.
It's Kind Of You,
But We Really Need
To Hit The Road.
Oh. Well, At Least
Let Me Give You Some Pie.
I Mean, Biloxi Is A Long Way.
Uh, No. I'm Not Hungry.
Really.
Uh, I Should Tell You,
Though, Before We Go
That I'm A Bit
Concerned About Ruby
And What's Going On
Out At The School.
Have Either Of You Noticed
Any Peculiar Behavior
With Ruby, Uh,
Aside From The Doll And How
She Spoke To Her Siblings?
[ Abon Sighs ]
Uh, No, No. She, Uh,
Seems All Right To Me.
She Won't Eat
Like She Used To.
Doctor, Let Me Tell You
Something.
She Don't Want Nothin'
'Cept Packaged Food.
Like Cookies And Chips,
And... She Won't Drink
Nothin' But Coca-Cola.
Um, I Think I Know
What's Happening.
I've Observed The Hecklers
Out In Front Of The School,
And There's
One Particular Woman Who--
Well, She...
Threatens To Poison Ruby.
I'm Sorry Very Much
To Have To Tell You Both,
But She Threatens
To Kill Her.
[ Gasps ]
Oh.
What?
Excuse Me.
I'm Sorry, Mr. Bridges.
I Am.
Ain't Your Fault.
[ Lucielle Crying ]
You Gotta Show
Yourselves Out. I Gotta--
Of Course. Yeah.
Good Night.
[ Crying Continues ]
How Can They Be So Cruel
To My Baby?
I Thought I Was Doing
The Right Thing.
I Really Did.
Shh. Come On. Come On.
It Ain't All Your Fault.
I Should
Have Put My Foot Down.
I Shouldn't Have Let You
Talk Me Into It.
I Ain't Never Been For This
In The First Place.
So You Think
We Should Stop?
Ruby Ain't Stayin'
In That School, Cielle.
I Just Need To Pray
About This.
I Know My God Wouldn't Give Me
More Than We Could Handle.
He--
What Do You Think
You're Doin'?
I'm Doin' What's Best
For Our Daughter.
I Watched Her Tonight,
And I Listened
And I See She--
She Got It In Her Head
That White Folks
Is Better Than Colored.
She Draws Colored Folk
Deformed
And White Folk Perfect.
But What's That Got To Do
With Jesus?
[ Whispering ]
Ain't Nobody Really Know
What He Looks Like.
But When She
Sees This Every Day,
Tells Her That God
Looks More Like
Them White Folks
Outside Her School
Than Her.
[ Sighs ]
Can You Make Some Dinner
Now, Please?
Oh, So You're Hungry,
Huh?
Yes.
Oh, Well, I'm Not.
I Had
A Home-Cooked Meal.
Good Night.
[ Groans ]
Daddy! Daddy!
I Have To Show
You Something!
All Right.
Hold On.
[ Sighs ]
Ah, Report Card.
Arithmetic, "A".
Readin', "A".
Spellin', "A".
Music, "A".
Art, "A".
All A's, Daddy!
Yeah.
I See.
That's Great, Baby.
That's--
That's A--
You Like Your New School,
Don't Ya?
Yeah, I'm--
I'm Glad You Do.
Go-- Go Get Changed,
And, Uh, Go Play.
Mary And Carl Waitin'
For Ya Up The Street.
Hi, Jimmy,
We Goin' In!
Hi, Scott!
Traitor!
Tra-- Jimmy!
Hey, Scott,
Wait Up!
Jimmy! Come Back Here, Boy!
No, I Wanna Go
To School, Ma!
Jimmy! Jimmy!
Scott, I'm Comin' Too!
Now, Ruby, You Was With Me
At The Supermarket
When I Bought That Rice
And Those Beans.
You Saw They Was
Wrapped Tight.
No One's Put
Nothin' In There.
Ruby, Baby,
You've Got To Eat!
You Hear Me?
Good Girl.
Mama,
You Said Those People
Outside My School Would Stop.
They Will, Honey.
They Will!
When?
You Know, Ruby,
When You Feel Like This,
You Gotta Remember,
Just Turn Unto The Lord.
Remember What
I Told You
Jesus Did?
They Can't
Hurt You, Honey.
Those Men Are There
To Protect You.
And Remember,
God Loves You!
[ Kissing Sound ]
Mmm.
[ Abon ] Cielle.
Hey!
Hi!
Hello! Got Some Goodies
For You.
Hey, Alma!
Good To See You.
Oh, Thank You!
What Can I Get You Two?
Oh, Nothing. Thank You.
Jus' Some Coffee, Darlin'.
But Let Me Help.
Ooh,
It's Pretty!
I Want It!
No.
It's Mine!
Ruby Nelle, Not Everything
Comes In This House
Is For You.
[ Alma Chuckling ]
Now, You Gonna
Have To Share!
Oh, My. Would Y'all
Like To Adopt
A Couple Of Kids?
Actually, We'd Love
To Have Ruby Spend A Day
With Our Girl Sometime,
If That's All Right.
[ Ruby ] Ooh!
Oh, I'm Sure
She Would Love That!
Honey, We've Got A Piano,
And My Wife Would Like
To Teach You To Play.
Would You Like That?
Oh, My. You Have
Your Very Own Piano?
You Know,
She's Been Learnin'
A Bit With Miss Henry.
Well, We Just Want
To Spend Some Time
With Her.
- Let Her Know
We're Here For Her.
- [ Scoffs ]
[ Paper Shuffling ]
I Gotta Get Me
Some Air.
[ Door Slams ]
I'm Sorry.
He's Havin' A Hard Time.
I Understand.
What He's Goin' Through Has
Got To Be Hard On Any Man.
Abon! Abon!
[ Sighs ]
Honey, I Know
You Don't Believe Me,
But I Really Think They
Do Mean Well.
[ Scoffs ]
Please, Those People
Ain't Interested In Ruby.
Yes, They Are Too!
And I Think
It Will Be A Good Idea
For Her
To See How They Live.
Show Her What Our Folks
Can Have When They Have
A Good Education.
They Were Just
Being Polite.
But Not Polite Enough
To Invite Us, Huh?
You Know, Tell Me.
Did Alma Broyard Invite You
To Tea? Oh, No.
No! Why?
Well, Their--
Their Little Visits
Every Once In A While,
Having Ruby To Their House
And-- And Showin' Her
How They Live--
That Ain't Gonna Help
This Family!
Huh?
Where Are The Broyards
When My Daughter Ain't
Eatin' And When She's
Havin' Nightmares?
They Don't Wanna Know
About All That!
They Don't Want
To Support Us Like
Real Friends!
And You--
You Just-- You Just Smile
And Just Suckin' It Up!
That's Enough, Abon!
There's Nothing Wrong
With Me Wantin' Ruby To See
Another Side Of Life!
I Want Her To Learn
To Play The Piano,
If She Wants To.
I Want Her To Experience
Being In A Nice House...
Without Havin' To Clean It.
I Don't Wanna See
My Daughter Being Used,
No More... By Nobody.
[ Sobs ]
[ Man ]
Hey, Charlie!
Hey, Abon!
How's It Goin'?
Mr. Taylor.
I Know Those Folks
Told You
Not To Go Out Lookin' For Work,
But I Have A Few
Painting Gigs,
And I Could Sure
Use Your Help.
I Can't Pay You
Mechanic's Salary,
But It'd
Be Something.
Appreciate It.
See You In The Morning.
Gotta Go
To A Gig Now.
House Painter.
[ Noises Behind Door ]
Hey, Sweetie.
How Was Your Lunch?
Fine.
Is Everything Okay, Ruby?
More Kids Came Back,
Mrs. Henry.
It's Not My School
Anymore.
How-- How Do You Know
More Kids Came Back, Ruby?
I Saw 'Em.
How Come They're All
In The Class Together
And I'm Not?
Um--
Uh--
Why Don't You Make
Some More Valentines,
Sweetheart?
And, Uh-- And I'll Be Back
In Just A Few Moments, Okay?
Okay.
There Is No Good Reason
Why She Should Be
By Herself All Day,
Especially Since The Other
Children Are First Graders
And Right Next Door.
Miss Spencer Does Not
Want To Teach That Child,
And Nobody's
Gonna Force Her.
Fine.
Then Let Her Children
Come Into Ruby's Class
For Part Of The Day,
And I'll Teach Them!
As An Outsider,
What Makes You
So Concerned?
Miss Woodmere,
It Is Cruel
To Isolate A Child.
Those Children
Are Not Goin'
To Accept Her.
So You Just Let It Be!
This School Was Ordered
To Integrate!
If You Continue
To Separate Ruby,
You Are Breaking
The Federal Law!
Shall We Call
Superintendent Redmond
And Discuss It
With Him?
Mrs. Spencer?
Uh-Huh!
Children!
This Is Mrs. Henry.
Hello.
C'mon Now!
Let's All Line Up
Behind Marie.
We're Gonna Go
Into Mrs. Henry's Class
For A While.
[ Child ]
Oh, No, Her Class?
Oh, No!
[ Barbara ]
This Is Ruby, Everyone.
Go Ahead.
Come On. In You Go.
This Is Ruby.
Here We Go.
Duck.
Ruby's In The Game Too.
No Skipping!
Duck. Duck.
Duck.
Goose!
[ Footsteps ]
[ Kids Chattering ]
My Mommy Told Me Not
To Play With You
Because You're A "Niggah."
He Not Gonna Go!
[ Whispering ]
I Don't Want To Play With Her.
Scott, You're It!
[ Whispering ] I Don't Wanna
Play With Her, Either.
Don't You Want
To Play, Scott?
No.
C'mon.
It's Fun To Be "It."
I Don't Wanna Be!
Come On.
You Can Do It.
Stand Up. Let's Go!
I Don't Wanna Be "It."
No, Jim Didn't
Hurt My Feelings,
'Cause If My Mama
Or My Daddy
Told Me Not
To Play With Someone,
I Wouldn't, Either.
Alison Daddy Told Her
Not To Play With Me Too,
[ Whispering ]
But She Still Does
Sometimes.
[ Whispering ]
I Won't Tell.
[ Laughs ]
Will Your Mom Let
You Have Some Of My Tea?
It's Special Blend.
Imported From Up North.
Hmm.
Yeah, I Think That
Would Be A Good Thing.
It'll Be Just A Moment
While It Brews.
Ruby,
Would, Uh-- Would You Be
Disappointed If, Uh,
My Mommy Said
I Couldn't Have Tea
With You?
I Would Be Sad,
'Cause Maybe You
Wouldn't Visit Me Anymore.
Is It, Uh--
Is It Lonely For You
At School?
When I'm By Myself
At Lunchtime.
Mrs. Henry's Nice.
But The Other Kids
Don't Play With Me.
You Know, It-- It's Good
To Know How You Feel, A-And
To Tell Someone, Ruby.
It'll Make You
Feel Better.
I'm Certainly Glad
You Told Me.
Is There Anything
Else That, Uh--
You Could Do
To Make Yourself
Feel Better,
Like Cry
Or Laugh Or, Uh--
Draw With The Crayons?
Our Tea Is Ready!
Ah!
Oh! For Me?
Mm!
But We Have To Pray
Before We Eat It.
Mm.
God Is Great. God Is Good.
Now We Thank Him
For This Food.
In Jesus' Name. Amen.
Amen.
Your Daddy Gonna Let
You Be In The Ball Game
Next Time We Play?
Don't Think So.
Says Colored Folk
Ain't Got Time
To Be Playin' Games.
Says You Gotta Work Hard
If You Wanna Have Something
In This World.
- [ Man ] Alison!
- Uh-Oh.
Where Are You?
I'm Comin', Daddy!
What Did I Tell You?
You Just March Yourself
On Back Over To That House!
Lewis,
Ain't No Need
To Holler.
I Reckon,
We Hear You,
All Right.
You Know, Bridges,
'Fo' Your Kid
Went To That School,
This Neighborhood
Was Doin' Fine.
But Now We Got Barricades,
Ain't Welcome In Stein's,
White Folks Up The Street
Lookin' At Us Sideways.
Now, Colored Folks
Is Talkin' About
Boycottin' Mardi Gras.
Which Means
My Tavern Ain't Gonna
Do No Business!
So, If I Wanna Holler--
Well, You Sure Are Gonna
Hear Me, All Right!
[ Sighs ]
Uh!
[ Laughs ]
[ Angry Chanting ]
Go Home! Go Home! Go Home!
Go Home!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Ruby, Don't Look.
Hold It, Guys!
No, Ruby!
Come Back, Sweetie.
[ Angry Chanting
Continues ]
But, Honey, I Saw You
Talking To Them.
Did You Finally
Get Angry With Them?
Did Ya... Tell 'Em Just
To Leave You Alone?
No. I Didn't Tell
Them Anything.
I Didn't Talk To Them.
But, Ruby.
I Was There.
I Saw Your Lips Moving.
I Wasn't Talking To Them.
I Was Praying For Them.
Praying For Them?
Yes. I Pray For Them
Every Day In The Car.
But I Forgot That Day.
Oh.
What Prayer Did You Say?
Please, God,
Forgive These People.
Because Even If They Say
Those Mean Things,
They Don't Know
What They're Doing.
So You Can Forgive Them.
Just Like You Did Those Folks
A Long Time Ago
When They Said
Terrible Things About You.
We Used To Have
One Painting Of Jesus
On The Wall.
Somebody Stole It.
Know What?
I'm Going To Put
My Paintings
Up On The Wall Now.
Okay.
Hey, Little Boy!
[ Laughs ]
Whee!
[ Cielle ]
Carl, Don't Jump
On Miss Jane Like That!
Get Off There!
He's Okay. He's Okay.
Just Wanted To--
[ Laughing ]
Okay. Where Do You
Want To Put Them?
Right There.
All Right.
So, Doc, How's
My Little Girl Doin'?
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
You Know,
You Comin' Here,
Payin' Attention
To Her Like That,
Listenin' To Her--
That Makes Her Feel
Real Special.
Dr. Coles, Would You
Like Something To Drink?
Ah, That Sounds Great.
Thanks.
Here We Go.
C'mon, Baby.
C'mon, Carl.
And, Uh,
It's Bob, Please.
Bob.
I, Uh, Appreciate
Your Kind Words Very Much.
But, Uh, I Think
What Makes Ruby Feel
So Special Is...
You And Your Family
And...
Something Greater Than,
Than All Of Us.
[ Sighs ]
All This Time I Wondered
What Makes Her So Strong.
Don't Be Too Hard
On Yourself, Doc.
I Think There're Things
We're Not Supposed
To Figure Out
Till The Time Is Right.
Know What I Mean?
Uh-Huh.
Yeah. Huh.
I Mean,
Look At These Pictures.
Remember All The Ones
She Did
With The Pink Crayons?
Pink And Deformed.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah.
She's Certainly Wearing Out
The Brown Ones Now, Huh?
[ Sighs ]
Now, That's Progress.
Here We Are!
Wow.
What's That?
That's Gumbo.
Looks Great!
Mmm, Try It!
Mmm!
[ Laughs ]
[ Dr. Coles On Tape Recorder ]
And So, I Learned
That A Family And A Child
Under Great Stress And Fear
Could Show Exquisite
Dignity And Courage
Because Of Their Moral
And Religious Values,
And Because They Had
A Definite Purpose
In What They Were
Trying To Accomplish.
This Purpose
Made Them Resilient.
I Couldn't Figure Out The
Source Of This Resilience
Because I Had Only Worked
With Well-To-Do Children
Who Really Had Nothing
To Work Hard For--
No Reason Driving Them
To Accomplish Anything.
So Now I See That
The Issue Is Not Stress
But Stress
For What Purpose.
Having Something
To Believe In
Protected Ruby
From Psychiatric Symptoms
And Gave Her A Dignity
And A Strength
That Is Utterly Remarkable.
"So All We Could Do
Was To Sit, Sit, Sit."
She Is A Good Teacher.
My Kids Can't Read
That Well Yet.
Miss Woodmere?
From The Janitor.
Oh, Thank You.
Uh-Huh.
[ Bell Ringing ]
Lunchtime. Walk!
C'mon. Let's Walk.
Walk!
[ Clears Throat ]
There Have Been Mice
And Cockroaches In Here,
And The Janitor Needs
To See Why.
[ Cabinet Door Slams ]
What's All This?
Oh!
[ Miss Woodmere ]
Ugh!
Disgusting!
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Sighs ]
Tsk.
I'm Not Angry
With You, Honey.
I'm Just Very Concerned
That You're Not Eating
Your Lunches.
I Mean, You're So Tiny
At It Is.
I Been Eatin' More
Than I Used To, Mrs. Henry.
Really.
But I Don't Like
What My Mama Makes Me
All The Time.
[ Giggling ]
[ Laughing ]
Want Some More?
That's For You.
Okay, Ruby, Here's A Test
To See How Well
You've Learned This Year.
Now, Honey,
You Take Your Time,
And You Do Your Best.
What's In The Box?
It's A Surprise.
That's What's In The Box.
What's In The Box?
He-He-Here We Go. Ho!
Look! I Draw Good Too!
Mine, Look At Mine!
You Two Get In The House!
Wow! Here. I'll Look
At Those Later. Okay?
I'm Sorry
About That, Bob.
Aw, That's Okay.
Hey.
You Wanna Play A Game?
What You Paint, Baby?
Okay?
This Is Your Classroom.
And Let's Say
That These Are, Uh,
You And The Other Students.
And I Was Wondering
If Maybe
You Could Tell Me
Something About Them.
And, Who They Are
And-- And What They're Like.
This One's Marie.
She's Nice.
Her Daddy's
A Minister.
Oh, Yeah?
This One's Scott.
He's Okay.
But He Doesn't
Really Like Girls.
Uh-Huh.
[ Dog Barking ]
This Is Jimmy.
He Used To Be Bad.
Now He Plays
Okay Sometimes.
But, Then, He Remembers
I'm Colored...
And Gets Bad Again.
How Exactly
Does He Act
When He Gets Bad?
He Pushes Me.
He Calls Me
Mean Things.
What Do You Do, Ruby,
When He Calls You
Mean Things?
Do You Get Angry And
Do Mean Things Back?
No. I Used To Be Bad
When Someone Did
Mean Things To Me.
At Church, I Heard
When Someone Is Bad,
God Makes A Bad Thing
Come Back On That Person.
So, I Don't
Do It Anymore.
I Want A "Co-Cola."
Okay.
You Want One?
Yeah.
Hey, Daddy!
Hey, Doc!
Cielle's Teachin'
Your Wife To Make Gumbo.
Uh-Oh.
Man, It's
Gonna Be A While.
[ Chuckles ]
Feel Like Takin' A Walk
When You Get Done?
- Sure. Great.
- All Right.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knocking ]
Mrs. Stein.
This Is For
Your Family.
[ Abon ] Things Finally
Calmin' Down Around Here.
[ Dr. Coles ]
Yeah.
Well, Thank You.
♪ I Said Tell Me, Darlin'
Why You Got To Be So Mean ♪
Hey, Abon!
♪ But Where I Come From ♪
♪ You're Still
The Prettiest Thing
I've Ever Seen ♪
Now, Go On,
Blow Your Horn, Boy!
♪ [ Continues ]
Who Got The Medals?
Holden.
I Ever Tell You
I Got Me A Purple Heart?
Ah, No, But Janie Told Me.
How'd You Get It?
Got Wounded In Korea
Savin' A White Soldier.
Mmm.
So You Shed Blood
For A Country That Doesn't
Really Allow You
To Enjoy The Freedom
You Fought To Maintain.
That Can't Feel Good.
Nope.
That's Why
I Ain't Never Put Much Faith
In Integration, You Know.
I Mean, Even In The War,
Fightin' Side By Side,
We Were Still Colored,
They Were Still White.
Risked My Life For 'Em,
And... We Still Didn't Mix.
[ Laughs ]
We Sure Ain't Never...
Hung Out Together
Or Nothin'.
Before I Met Ruby,
I Never Thought
About Segregation.
You Didn't Have To.
- It's Gotta Make You
Angry, Huh?
- [ Sighs ]
No.
Not No More.
[ Laughs ]
Don't Do Me No Good.
You Know, Doc,
Believe It Or Not,
I Learn A Lot
From Watching My Ruby.
Oh,
I Definitely Believe It.
[ Laughs ]
She's A Great Teacher.
[ Woman ]
I'm So Happy This Year
Is Comin' To A Close.
You Have No Idea.
Miss Woodmere, May I Have
Ruby's Test Scores, Please?
Oh!
Oh, This Is Wonderful!
I Knew She Would Do Well.
Her Test Scores
Are Incredible!
Hmm, That's Exactly
What I Thought.
That's Why I'm Lowering Them
To More Accurately Reflect
A True Assessment
Of Her Ability.
What?
Well, She's Been
Privately Tutored
The Whole Year Through,
Which Makes Her Scores
Inaccurate.
She's Had Special Attention
The Other Children
Just Did Not Have.
[ Woman ]
That's True.
That's What This Is.
You're Upset
Because She Did Better
Than The Other Children.
Her Scores Are Too High,
And I'll Change Them
As I See Fit.
Then I Would Like
To Discuss It
With The Principal.
I Already Have.
She Did The Work By Herself,
So The Scores Are Accurate.
The Only Reason
She Was Privately Taught
Is Because You Would Not
Put Her With Other Children.
You Tried To Mix
Those Children,
And You Failed, Didn't You?
They Didn't Accept Her.
That's Not True.
- Oh?
- They're Children.
They Don't Care
What Color She Is.
It Is Only Their Parents
And Ignorant People
Who Teach Them To Hate.
If You Are Unhappy Here,
Please Don't Come Back.
- Miss Woodmere!
- Shut Up!
What About The Children,
Miss Woodmere?
Do They Mean
Anything To You?
You May Dismiss
The Hard Work
Of One Little Girl,
But There Will Be
Other Little Girls
And Boys.
The Country Is Changing,
Miss Woodmere,
Whether You Like It
Or Not.
[ Footsteps Receding ]
That Woman Worked
Her Behind Off This Year,
Miss Woodmere.
She Spent Nearly Every
Minute Of Every Day
Bein' Dedicated
To Her Job!
And Your Job,
Miss Woodmere,
Is To Support
All Your Teachers,
Not To Sabotage Them.
Huh.
All Right, Carl, Come On Now!
Keep Your Eye On It. Get Your
Grip On The Bat. Swing!
C'mon!
Hit It Carl!
That's Right, Carl!
You Gonna Knock It
Over The Fence!
[ Laughs ]
Hey, Abon.
How About That Carl, Huh?
- C'mon, Carl,
Hit It! Hit It! Hit It!
- A Real Little Slugger.
And Ruby's Been Playin'
Real Good Too.
Been Coachin' 'Em?
Nah, No-- She--
She Don't Need My Help.
She Just Got Natural Talent.
- C'mon, Carl! Hit It!
C'mon, Carl!
- Give Me The Bat. It's Mine!
Aw, Abon, Maybe She Gets
Some Of It From You.
Whatever It Is,
We All Real Proud Of Her
Around Here.
Anybody? Is That All?
Anybody Want Anymore?
We Got Popsicles.
- You Want A Popsicle?
- Popsicle?
Oh, Boy!
What Kind You Got?
Gimme The Bat.
Gimme It!
Uh! Uh-Uh!
Give Me The Bat.
[ Ruby ]
You Know What?
What?
I'm Gonna Have
A Birthday Party Soon.
No!
And You And Mrs. Coles
Can Come To It.
You Know What?
We'll Be There.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Tell Me About
Your Picture.
This Is You
And Mrs. Coles.
That's Mrs. Henry,
And That's The Broyards.
And Why'd You Put Us
In There?
'Cause I Like You Now.
Who's This Here?
That's Jimmy.
He's Says He's Gonna Be
My Friend Now,
Even Though His Mom
Told Him Not To Be.
He Doesn't Call Me
Bad Names Anymore.
That's Good.
I Think People Are Happier
When They Make Friends.
What Do You Think?
[ Sighs ]
I Think You've Been
A Great Teacher.
That's What I Think.
Can I Have A Hug,
Teacher?
[ Laughs ]
Oh, Ruby!
[ Children Shouting ]
C'mon!
Barbara, I'm Sorry
We Didn't Get
To Know Each Other
Better This Year.
Get On!
I Think What You Did
Was The Right Thing.
And I Think
You Did It Really Well.
Believe It
Or Not, That...
Means A Lot To Me.
Maybe Next Year,
If You Get Ruby
Or Someone Like Her
In Your Class...
You'll Be Able
To Do The Same.
[ Narrator ] In 1995,
Ruby Bridges Established
The Ruby Bridges
Educational Foundation,
Which Seeks To Build
An Understanding
Of Cultural Diversity
Within Public Schools
Across The Nation.
Under Her Leadership,
The Growth And Success
Of This Foundation
Continues To Prove
That The Sacrifices
Her Family Made
Were Not In Vain.