Subs by Taeyeontaeoff
I'm not perfect at Korean, but I'm better than nothing, right?
Ruby Ruby Love
Opal, the Gem of Bad Luck
am I going crazy?
Get it together, Ruby!
Are you zoning out?
omo!
you scared me!
I have something for you-
what?
oh, put out your hand
It's Opal
wow, it's so pretty!
But...
Why are you giving me this?
what do you mean?
Opal
The Gem of bad luck
By chance- are you trying to give me bad luck?
By giving me the icon of bad luck?
Aigoo- you're superstitious
It's just a superstition!
There's no proof at all
Actually, Opal has a very different meaning-
Ah, Just a sec
Hello?
Yes
What?
I'll be right there!
what is it?
What happened?
Wondol-
What am I gonna do?
This is your design!
Ma'am you can't sell this here!
Why are you yelling at me?
I bought these from someone!
I have no idea what you're even talking about
How did this happen?
Director!
Team leader!
seriously-
How could Ruby do this?
Omo
Team Leader!
Ruby didn't do this!
But-
Her showcase is in a week so-
What can we do?
A week?
Hey-
Who is that?
what are you talking about? it's Ru-
It's in a week? I'll call Ruby and tell her
but-
Mom
It looks like I messed things up
you bought that design?
Do you remember who sold it to you?
I didn't get their name
by chance-
was it this person?
So she really isn't going to do it?
Right-
You know that Ruby has agoraphobia
She really can't do the modelling?
No. It's just not possible
Ah, what a shame
How can she waste an opportunity like this?
Fine
That's just how it is
Okay, I'll call you back
Ruby! Lee Roo!
Lee Ruby!
What are you doing?
Are you really going to give up like this?
This is such a good opportunity-
Well, what do you want me to do?
The concept, design, production- that all takes about a month!
How am I supposed to do that in a week?
I will help you!
It's fine- don't
I mean, you can't
It's not possible. Now, give that back!
Ruby- Ruby: Give it back now!
It's a blackout
Wondol: Hey- Ruby: I-
You first
No, you first
I'm sorry
for giving you the opal
But Opal isn't really bad luck
This is probably all a coincidence
This all started with the Opal
But Opal has a different real meaning
Opal isn't really bad luck. It represents love, hope, innocence, luck and happiness.
So, I gave it to you as a gift
Did you research that?
I'm impressed
huh?
*not sure what she said here*
How long did you know that?
I'm sorry for before
I wasn't even mad at you
I'm just upset over what happened
oh?
How could I leave it out like that?
Opal needs to be kept in water to protect it from cracks
I really appreciate this gift. Look how beautiful it looks in the water
Look at this!
what?
I thought of a new concept!
All gemstones have a different meaning
I'll make jewelry that can grant anyone's wish
This isn't something that's normally easy to do (?)
But I talked to the higher ups, and they agreed to it (?)
so we're able to do it (?)
Okay
Thank you
I can't do it
How could I do this in two days?
I really can't do it
But Sir!
When you think of Jewelry, you think of Korea
Korea is a country that's developing at a rapid pace
What is there that can't be done in this world?
Come on, how can you do this to her?
Our center has done business with you for a long time-
Sir- Please~
please- seriously
Sir~
Please~ help us~
Please~
Help us~
Please help us~
please~ you have to~
I knew you could do it
Now, when you release this-
Hey- I'll give you a piggy back ride!
Huh? I'm really heavy
I'll be fine
Don't worry!
oh, you ARE heavy
You were right
you should lose some weight~