Click the link in the description to watch the original video and support our Seohyun!
Subs by Taeyeontaeoff
thanks for watching, and don't forget to subscribe <3
I'll take care of you, peridot
We now grant this award to Lee Ruby, congratulations
ah, Oh my gosh
how did this happen, how did this happen?
are you really our Ruby?
It's really me!
How did you do it?
one month ago
The stage that every designer wants their work to be displayed in
Jewelry week!
It's the best place to see all of the newest trends in jewelry
and I REALLY wanted to go but-
ah, what should I do?
I don't think I can go over there
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry
hey, what do you have to be sorry for?
Well, would you look at this?
ooh, It's shiny, right?
A ruby ring?
That's right. A ruby!
A gemstone that can make you fearless
This gemstone can push away fear, but It can't completely cure it
You can use this ring when you need to be brave
This ring will give you three chances
Only three!
Why?
How?
Ah, that doesn't matter
W-wait!
Since you can only use it 3 times, use it wisely
*not sure what he says here*
Only 3 times, got it?
The day of the awards ceremony
Hey, are you really Lee Ruby?
why? Is something wrong?
It's the awards ceremony, so I had to dress up of course
What did you say?
Omo, Director, she spoke to me without even mumbling!
Does this even make sense?
uh, yeah it does
Omo~
It's the Turquoise Prince!
Ah, our awesome team leader~
Thank you for coming all the way out here to watch our awards ceremony. What did you think of it?
It was really nice thanks to you
I look forward to working with you in the future - We do as well
and who is this?
Ah, yes! This is the winner of the Grand Design Award, Lee Ruby
From now on, he will be working with you to help you lanch your brand
Why don't you two get acquainted?
Hello!
Miss Ruby
I was really curious what kind of person you were
Why is that?
If you look at a piece of jewelry, it usually tells you something about the designer
Like their personality, or
Maybe even what they look like
What did you think of my design?
I thought it had a subtle, girly kind of feel to it
Were you right?
Well, the feel is a bit different from the designer but- you're great!
Calm, cool, confident!
Since we're coming up with a new concept
We'll have a lot to talk about from the set design to the marketing
Even your model campaign
I'll work really hard
Model?
Yeah, modelling
Didn't the director tell you?
Getting your face out there is important for a new brand launch
We'll work hard to make this brand launch successful
oh, don't worry too much Miss Ruby
Your designs are beautiful, so I know it'll be successful
You can trust me
I'm sorry but I have to go!
R-r-Ruby
Miss Ruby!
hey-
What happened?
wonseok...
Why did I do that?
and then my hair suddenly starting changing
and even my shoes were changing back!
and that's how it happened
all because of this ring
you don't believe me do you?
I believe you!
This is horrible
What do I do now?
This ring was supposed to turn me into a confident person
Don't cry
You still have two uses left
you can use it again later
But then what do I do when I suddenly change back?
hey-
Do you know why you suddenly changed back?
Didn't that person explain how to use the ring?
explain?
Caution: 3 chances, effects lasting for only 3 hours
Ruby, give me your hand
why?
Just let me see it
I got you this when I found out you won the award
oh, It's Peridot
That's right. I gemstone that can get rid of all worries
You knew that, didn't you?
so there's no need to worry now
ah, seriously
what would you do without me?
Ruby's Studio
Mom...
I came too late, didn't I?
I'm sorry
Instead
I'll try really hard now
Just watch
Hey, what are you doing?
Here, take this
Yes, sir!
Miss Ruby-