Jet launch has been cancelled.
Clear both catapults.
Two flights returning.
Expect to recover aircraft in ten minutes.
Stand by with fire bottle
for helicopter turn-up.
Shake a leg, Forney.
There're two flights coming in.
We're here, ain't we?
Keep your jumper on, sir.
And Mike, don't put that hat on
until you clear the deck.
- Captain Parker doesn't like it.
- Very well, sir.
Prepare to launch helicopter.
Top off all jets and check Fly One
for ordinance load.
Launch helicopter.
My hat and scarf, please.
Can't you wait until we get off the ship?
- What if the captain had seen you?
- We don't save captains, Nestor.
We save pilots.
When they're in the icy water with only
minutes to live, it makes them feel awful
good to look up and see this green hat.
I know that, but I'm telling you, Mike,
you're gonna get yourself in trouble.
And another thing. You gotta quit
sassing them officers like you just did.
When are you gonna learn, Nestor?
You can say anything you like to them
as long as you put "sir" on the end of it.
Take 215 and 207
down the deck-edge elevator.
Prepare to re-spot aircraft for recovery.
We've got two flights of jets to land
and they're low on fuel. Look alive.
Stand by to land jets.
Clear the catwalks portside aft.
Check number six wire.
The centre fiddle bridge is down.
Let's hear the checks, boy.
- Wheels down.
- Flaps down.
- Hook down.
- All down, sir.
- All down.
- Clear deck.
Come on, Commander. Keep your nose up
so your hook will catch. That's it.
Good boy.
202, number three wire.
He did real good.
Clear the catwalk aft.
211 to Bluejay. 211 to Bluejay.
Flame-out. Flame-out.
CIC is reporting an emergency, sir.
Go ahead, CIC.
211 reports a flame-out. Will have to ditch.
We'll dispatch a helicopter.
- What's his position?
- 18 miles out.
- Is there another jet with him?
- Affirmative. 210 is wingman.
- Can he ditch near the destroyers?
- Negative.
- Very well. Keep me advised.
- Aye, aye, sir.
- Have you got a fix on their position?
- Affirmative.
- How much fuel has the wingman got?
- 1,200 pounds.
Angel from Bluejay.
Your vector, 3-4-5 magnetic.
211 will have to ditch 18 miles out.
I say again. Your vector at 3-4-5 magnetic.
- Bluejay out.
- Bluejay from Angel. Roger.
210 from Bluejay.
Helicopter on way.
- What is the condition of 211? Over.
- 210 to Bluejay.
211 is losing altitude rapidly
and is all set to ditch.
210 to Bluejay.
There he goes.
211 just ditched.
Aircraft sank immediately.
Pilot got out.
Dye marker is visible.
Downed pilot afloat.
Have him in sight.
- I'm staying here.
- CIC to Flag Plot.
210 requests permission
to stay with downed pilot.
Permission granted.
Who is the pilot in the water?
- Brubaker, sir.
- Brubaker?
Just an hour ago a dispatch came in.
His wife and two kids are waiting for him
in Tokyo. He doesn't even know it yet.
- Keep me advised on Brubaker.
- Aye, aye, sir.
- Brubaker, huh?
- You know him?
I don't think I've ever seen him.
But I bet I can describe him.
He's about 30, well built,
a good-looking boy with a bit of a temper.
That's Brubaker all right.
Did you ever notice the pilots
the admiral takes special interest
in always look like that?
Now that you mention it, yeah.
That's what the admiral's son, George,
would have looked like.
CIC to Flag Bridge.
210 has sighted helicopter approaching.
- Tell 210 to return as quickly as possible.
We can't hold this course much longer.
- Aye, aye, sir.
Angel from 210. Come on, Forney,
I can't hold him in sight much longer.
210 from Angel. I see him.
Go on home. Dinner's waiting.
Roger.
If you have to jump in, I'll wait around until
the Hornet sends one of its helicopters.
He looks froze.
I'll have to go down.
Sorry you have to ride in the rumble, sir.
But I haven't got anybody here
to haul you inside. Savo Angel to Bluejay.
Two Angels coming home
with two frozen mackerel.
- Admiral.
- Go ahead.
Helicopter reports Brubaker aboard, sir.
The Hornet's helicopter
picked up Forney's crewman.
- Good.
- The helicopter will land in three minutes.
- Turn right 90 degrees.
- Aye, aye, sir.
Round Table, this is Jehovah.
Turn right, 0-3-5.
Stand by. Execute.
I wish you could see this, Lieutenant.
Awful pretty sight.
You know, sir, it looks like
they're coming to meet us.
Land the two helicopters aft
and stand by with a stretcher.
Keep clear of those rotors.
Clear a passage for that stretcher.
- How are you feeling, boy?
- Oh, he's all right.
- That water's pretty cold, isn't it?
- It's not bad enough when
you're used to it like he is.
- Oh, Doctor, he's much
too young for brandy.
- You weren't in the water.
I know, but I had the hatch open.
It's awful cold in there.
Hello, Harry.
You don't look so bad.
- Hi, CAG.
- How's it going?
I didn't know water could get
so cold without being ice.
- Feel like talking to the admiral?
- Now?
- No, no.
- He says whenever you feel up to it.
He just wants to chat with you.
The doctor thinks you'll be fine tonight.
- Okay.
- I'll send for a uniform.
- Oh, you don't have to dress.
The admiral says just come up in your robe.
- See you later, Harry.
- Right.
- I believe the admiral wants to see me.
I'm Lieutenant Brubaker.
- Yes, sir.
He's in his cabin.
I'll tell him you're here.
From the world-famous Chez Paris
in Chicago, overlooking beautiful
Lake Michigan,
the Armed Forces Radio Service
is brings you the music of
Henry Busse and his orchestra.
This way, Lieutenant.
Come in.
- You sent for me, sir?
- Yes, come in, son.
- Coffee?
- No, thank you, sir.
Sit down.
- How do you feel?
- I guess I'm thawed out by now.
I got the report on your ditching.
How long did it stay afloat?
- After the first bounce, sir,
I was a submarine.
- Didn't have time to get
your life raft out, huh?
It hooked on the seat.
I was lucky just to get myself out.
Well, those helicopter boys
are pretty good fishermen.
As far as I'm concerned,
they deserve every medal in the book.
You're out there all by yourself,
you know you can't last very long.
You're scared and you're freezing.
You curse and you pray.
Then suddenly you see that Mixmaster
whirling at you out of nowhere.
You look up and there's Forney
and his green hat.
Then you relax,
because you know you got it knocked.
Well, I'm mighty glad they pulled you out,
son. We can use you around here.
- Coming from you, Admiral,
I appreciate that.
- Oh, I mean it.
You fly well.
You go in low and you do your job.
You'd have a great future in the Navy.
Why don't you make it your career?
- You know what I think of the Navy, sir.
- Still bitter, hmm?
Go ahead, say what you think.
I always do.
Of course,
I've said it a couple of times too often.
Well, sir, the organized reserves were
drawing pay, but they weren't called up.
I was completely inactive and yet I was.
I had to give up my home,
my law practice, everything.
Yes, I'm still bitter.
Sometimes I'm so bitter I could put on
a phony act to the flight surgeon,
get a green slip and myself grounded.
Why don't you?
That's what I kept asking myself
this afternoon when I was
bobbing around in that ice water.
You do a lot of thinking at a time like that,
mostly about your friends who are
back home leading perfectly normal lives.
I wonder if you were back home
whether you wouldn't do the same.
It's not a question of indifference.
It's a question of distance.
They act that way they do
because they're there.
You don't quit, and go on doing
your job because you're here.
It's just as simple as that.
Son, whatever progress this world
has made, it's always been
because of the efforts
and the sacrifices of a few.
I was one of the few, Admiral,
at New Guinea, Leyte, Okinawa.
Why does it have to be me again?
Nobody ever knows why he gets
the dirty job, and this is a dirty job.
- Militarily, this war is a tragedy.
- I think we ought to pull out.
That's rubbish, son, you know it.
If we did, they'd take Japan,
Indo-China, the Philippines.
Where would you have us make our stand,
at the Mississippi?
All through history, men have had to
fight the wrong war in the wrong place,
but that's the one they're stuck with.
That's why, one of these days,
we'll knock out those bridges at Toko-Ri.
- Do we have to knock out
those particular bridges?
- Yes, we must.
I believe without question, some morning,
Communist generals and commissars
will be holding a meeting to
discuss the future of the war.
A messenger will run in and tell them,
"They've knocked out even
the bridges at Toko-Ri."
That little mission will convince
them that we'll never stop,
never weaken in our purpose.
And that's the day they'll quit.
But I didn't call you here
to discuss strategy, Brubaker.
I'm supposed to chew you out
because of your wife.
My wife?
- You knew she was in Japan.
- She made it.
- I hope she's got the kids with her.
- You better hope
you don't get a court martial.
- I had nothing to do with it, sir.
- How did she and the children
get here without your help?
Her father used to be a senator
from Massachusetts.
- Admiral, I don't care
if she's broken a dozen rules to make it.
- War's no place for women.
- I'll tell COMNAVFE you had nothing
to do with bringing her out here.
- Thank you, sir.
- When we get ashore,
I'd like to meet your wife.
- It'll be a pleasure.
- Why don't you see if the surgeon
can spare you a nightcap?
- I'll do that, sir.
- Give you a good night's sleep.
In three days, you'll be in Japan.
No more worries about take-offs for a while.
No, sir.
But it's gonna be a long three days.
Group One, idle.
Group Two, idle.
Group One, full throttle.
Group Three, full.
Come in.
- CAG wants to see you, Admiral.
- Hmm?
- Lee, Commander of the Air Group, is here.
Oh, send him in. Wait a minute.
What do you think of Lee?
He's a good man, popular.
The pilots all swear by him.
I got a letter from a friend in
the personnel office. They're looking for
someone for higher command training.
They want my confidential opinion of Lee.
Send him in.
Group One, full throttle.
Admiral, I received a dispatch
this morning from COMFAIRJAP.
It said the replacement aircraft
for the next tour are not available.
- Yes, I saw it.
- Well, all we'll have is
what's aboard this minute.
The captain's burning up the engines.
- Have you talked to the captain about it?
- I tried to, but he wouldn't see me.
I don't wonder.
He's a little busy berthing the ship.
Well, if he keeps doing it this way, sir,
we won't have any propeller planes left.
How would you berth a carrier
against the wind, Commander?
I'd anchor in the stream before
I'd run a lash-down engine at top speed.
That's not fair to the pilots
who have to fly them, sir.
You know as well as I do that the pinwheel
operation is necessary in this harbor.
There's no room to get a tug between
the dock and the ship. Those planes are
the only thing that can hold us off.
For the last hundred yards, yes.
But he's been running those engines
from the moment we hit the channel.
Do you consider a few engines
more valuable than a carrier?
No, sir, but they've only got so many
good hours. Burn them up on deck...
- How long have you been in the Navy, Lee?
- 20 years, sir.
20 years. You're the commander
of the Air Group.
What would you think of one of your pilots
if he went over your head and came to me?
You know the task-force
commander doesn't interfere
with the running of any ship.
Yes, sir. But under extraordinary
circumstances such as these I feel...
You're coming up for promotion, Lee.
Don't you realize Captain Parker will
have to turn in a fitness report on you?
- Yes, sir.
- Suppose I did talk to the captain?
What kind of a fitness report
do you think he'd give you then?
I guess I was only looking at it
from my point of view, sir.
I was just thinking of
what was best for my pilots.
- Next time, think twice.
- Yes, sir, I will.
There are two things I don't like to see
a young officer do. The first is going
over somebody's head.
But once he does, I hate to see
him back down so quickly from
something he believes is right.
He'll be all right for some job,
but as far as higher command goes.
And I'll have to tell them so.
The uniform of the day for liberty
is dress blue.
Liberty will expire on board at 0700.
- Looking for your wife, sir?
- Yeah. There she is.
Mrs. Brubaker.
You know, sir, I've got the same kind of
reception waiting for me outside the gates.
- You married?
- Not yet, but I may be after this leave.
Liberty party fall in. Muster
on the flight deck for inspection.
Lower away. Easy.
All right, men.
Open up, front and centre.
- Hey, Beer Barrel, what's your handicap?
- I only have two hands, junior.
That's my handicap.
- I can't lift those beer mugs fast enough.
- Hey, Beer Barrel, do you need a caddy?
You bet. After the first nine steins,
they get pretty heavy.
Permission to leave the ship, sir.
Oh, darling. Darling.
- Where are the kids?
- It was too long of a trip for them.
- How long is your leave?
- A week. Are the kids okay?
Oh, they're fine. I found a wonderful
Japanese nurse. Come on, darling.
They're dying to see you.
Have your liberty cards ready.
All right. Have your liberty cards ready.
There she is, Nestor.
Hey, Kimiko. Your man's back!
Not so fast, Big Boy.
Things are different. We got to talk.
All right, let's find some cosy
little nook where we can talk.
- Daddy, Daddy!
Kathy! Susie!
- We saw you getting out of the car.
- You did, huh? They've gotten so big.
- This is Setsuko, Daddy.
- How are you?
- Have they been good?
- Oh, yes.
- Come on, come on!
- I'm coming. I'm coming.
Thank you.
- Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy!
- Yes, Kathy?
- Come here, I want to
show you the fish pond.
Kathy, take your sweater off and put it away
in the closet and see that Susie does, too.
- Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
- Yes, honey?
- Come on, I want to show you
the funny bed I sleep in.
Okay, young lady, you show me.
Why don't you leave me alone?
When I'm standing out there
with those paddles in my hands,
I have enough to worry about you, guys.
When I get ashore,
I don't want to worry about anything.
One thing does worry me, though.
Have they got enough beer in Japan?
- Good evening, boys.
- Good evening, Admiral.
- Brubaker, how's the family?
- Oh, fine, thank you, sir.
- Admiral, this is Mrs. Brubaker, Nancy.
- How do you do?
I thought your husband was
going to take off like a jet when
he heard you were here, Mrs. Brubaker,
- and now I understand why.
- Thank you, Admiral.
- I was kind of pleased to see him, too.
- Won't you sit down, sir?
- Thanks.
- Well, they didn't keep you
in Tokyo too long.
- No, they don't any more.
Not since that first press conference.
I told them we were fighting
Russian guns, Russian radar,
Russian planes and Russian submarines.
A lot of our men are being killed by Russian
equipment manned by Russian experts.
Ever since then, they bundle me
out here as fast as possible.
- I'm Lieutenant Brubaker.
- A gentleman to see you, sir.
- Oh.
Excuse me.
- Will you have a drink?
- Doctor won't let me.
- What is it, Nestor?
- Mike's been in a terrible fight, Lieutenant.
- Just Mike?
- No, sir.
But I got away. Mike's in jail, sir, in Tokyo.
- I came out as quick as I could.
- What happened?
His girl's marrying a boatswain
from the Essex.
Oh, it was bad, sir. If you don't come,
he'll be locked up permanent.
- Nestor, Tokyo is 60 miles away.
I'll phone the MPs right...
- Calling won't help, sir.
Mike clobbered two MPs,
along with the gang from the Essex.
- What did you two do,
take on the whole town?
- Yes, sir. Practically.
- Nestor, I'd like to do something, but...
- Oh, please, Lieutenant.
You gotta help Mike.
Okay, I'll come.
You wait here.
- Excuse me, Admiral.
Honey, there's been some trouble in Tokyo
and I think I better go.
- Oh, Harry.
- What kind of trouble?
- It's Mike Forney again, sir.
- Uh-oh.
A girl, another sailor, a brawl,
the usual consequences. He's in jail.
Oh, Harry, you don't have to get
mixed up with brawling sailors.
Darling, if Forney were in China
I'd have to help him.
Harry.
If you were freezing to death in the sea
and a man brought his helicopter
right over your head and rescued you,
wouldn't you help that man
if he got in trouble?
- Did Harry crash at sea?
- Yes, four days ago.
You know your husband's at war,
but somehow you just can't believe
that he'd crash into the sea.
- Hasn't Harry told you anything
about what he's been doing?
- He never talks about the war.
With the rest of them, he's been
doing a tough job and doing it well.
But when we go back to sea,
he's got a tough one ahead of him.
He's going to have to fly against
some certain bridges.
- Ask him to tell you about them.
- I don't even want to think about it.
I suppose to you that's
a sign of weakness, isn't it?
Maybe not weakness.
But like most people at home, you've been
protected. You're ignorant and defenseless.
- Harry doesn't want me to worry.
- That's the way my son, George, felt.
Harry often reminds me of him...
Same quick temper and the same
thorough way of doing things.
As a matter of fact, in certain ways
you remind me a little of George's wife.
She didn't want to think
about it either, is that it?
When George was killed at Midway,
she never recovered.
For a while, she tried to make love
with every man in uniform.
Thought he might die one day.
Then she grew to loathe herself
and attempted suicide.
I don't know where she is now
or what she's doing.
Once she was my... my son's wife.
And you think, if things go wrong
at those bridges, I might be like that?
Perhaps, if you don't let yourself
think about certain things.
If you refuse to acknowledge
what you're up against,
terrible consequences can follow.
I shouldn't have come out here.
That's what you're trying to tell me, isn't it?
No. In spite of all the regulations,
maybe you were right to come.
Perhaps when George was killed,
if my wife had come out to join me,
things might have been different.
But she stayed at home,
like a good Navy wife.
Then when our other boy was killed
trying to torpedo a Japanese carrier,
it was just too much for her.
- You lost two sons and your wife?
- No.
Margaret is still alive.
But all that was gentle and loving
about her slowly withered away.
Now she sits quietly alone in her room,
knitting a baby's sweater.
- Oh, Admiral, I'm so ashamed.
- Don't be.
Just be grateful for what you have.
And above all, be honest with yourself.
If I can't face the reality now,
then there won't be much hope for me
afterward if anything should happen.
I have a feeling you'll be all right.
Let's get your little girls have dinner.
Come on, Nestor.
Major, I'm Lieutenant Brubaker. You've
got a chief here by the name of Forney.
He's off our ship, the Savo Island.
- I'd like to get him out.
- I wish I could help you, Lieutenant.
But your wild Irishman
just wrecked a dance hall.
- Well, he also saved the lives of four pilots.
- Look, Lieutenant,
I got a lot of monsters
back there in that birdcage.
Every one of them was a hero in Korea.
But here in Tokyo, they're all monsters.
Well, Forney's a helicopter pilot.
The other day I had to ditch my plane at sea.
These two men saved my life.
As a matter of fact,
this man here jumped into the ocean...
And I suppose his face got chopped up
that way by the waves.
- Well, I know there was a brawl...
- A brawl?
Lieutenant, a brawl is when may be
six guys get to throwing punches.
But these two monsters
took on half of Tokyo.
- Are you married, Major?
- Yes.
Well, we just got in at noon today. I haven't
seen my wife or kids for over a year.
I left them at Fuji-san and came all
the way up here to get Mike out of jail.
That's what I think of these two men.
Well, you willing to cough up 80 bucks
for the damage he did?
- I'd pay 800 if I had to.
- Okay, Sergeant, drag Forney out here.
Sign here. He's yours,
but you're not getting any bargain.
I knew you could do it, Lieutenant.
- Thanks, Major. Come on.
- Oh, Lieutenant.
Don't let him get away from you.
There are parts of Tokyo
comparatively unharmed yet.
- Look, Lieutenant...
- You two are going back to Yokosuka.
- You gotta come with me.
You gotta talk to Kimiko.
She can't marry that ape from the Essex.
- Look, Mike, I'm not...
Sure, you are.
She'll listen to you, Lieutenant.
Please just do me this one favour.
- All right, where is she?
- Follow me, sir.
- Pardon me, sir, but you're
not supposed to be in here.
- It's all right, sonny, he's with me.
Lieutenant, there she is!
- Kimiko, this is Lieutenant Brubaker.
- Oh.
I wondered whether any girl
warranted a riot. I guess you do.
- Thank you, Lieutenant.
- He wants to talk to you.
I'm very sorry, Lieutenant.
But while Mike at sea,
I lose my heart to Essex man.
Essex not at sea.
But Mike's a fine man.
You couldn't do better than Mike.
I know. Mike good man.
But I lose my heart, Lieutenant.
Not in my dress, you don't!
Lieutenant, she took me through
too much pain! Leave me alone!
- Hey, Mike.
- What is it? You...
- What's going on over there?
- All right, break it up.
- Get out of the way, fellas.
- Break it up.
Break it up. Break it up.
What's going on here?
I'll guess you'll live.
- Kimiko.
- Here, Lieutenant. Don't worry, sir.
I'll get him back for everything.
- Kimiko.
- Come on, you're going back to the ship.
- That's my girl.
Kimiko.
- I'm sorry, darling.
- It's all right.
- Did you get him out of jail?
- Yes, I got him out.
Admiral Tarrant told me about Mike Forney.
I wish he hadn't.
Don't worry. I've had it now.
No one ever crashes twice.
Harry, what are the bridges
you have to bomb when you go back?
Tell me about the bridges, darling.
You know, I think Kathy and Susie
ought to have piano lessons
when they get a bit older.
It's funny. I was thinking
the same thing just the other day.
I always wanted to learn.
Never got around to it.
Same here.
They say if you start young enough...
- They got new methods now.
It doesn't take as long.
- I know.
Mildred Porter learned in just a few months.
Even after four or five weeks...
Harry, you've got to tell me
about those bridges!
The bridges span a narrow gap
between two mountains.
It's one of the most important
targets in all of Korea.
Consequently, it's fortified accordingly.
Although we're only over the target
about 30 seconds...
...it's a lifetime.
Every kind of gun imaginable is
hidden in those mountainsides.
The men behind those guns know where
we're coming from and where we're headed.
They know we're not going to
fly above the mountains.
We're gonna fly between them.
We're coming in low and straight.
There's no room to twist or duck.
And there's no surprising them.
They're just sitting there...
waiting for us...
...hoping we'll come.
That's Toko-Ri, Nancy.
- I'm glad you told me.
- Does it help?
I think so.
You didn't want to tell me
because you didn't want me to worry.
Well, I don't want you to worry either.
About me, I mean.
I know what the admiral
was trying to tell me.
I had to face those bridges, too.
Well, I have.
And I'll be all right now.
- I'm gonna swim all the way
across the pool.
- So am I.
- Harry, I'm not so sure about this.
- Oh, don't be silly, Nancy.
Now, you ladies go in there
and I'll go in here.
Harry, you get in the pool first. We're not
coming out until I know the coast is clear.
Okay, you modest violets.
- Daddy, why does the water taste so funny?
- Because it's mineral water, Kathy.
It comes right out of the spring.
- Watch me swim, Daddy.
- Okay.
That's fine, Kathy, fine.
- Harry, are you sure that door is locked?
- Absolutely.
- Watch me swim, too, Daddy.
- Okay, Susie.
Hey, hey, this is private. This is private.
We had it reserved.
No, private, reserved.
Number one. Good morning.
No, no, you don't understand.
We had it reserved.
The whole pool is reserved.
- No, no!
- Harry, do something!
- What can I do?
- Take a deep breath.
- Ohayo.
That means "good morning" in Japanese.
- Belong you?
- Yes.
Belong me.
- Keiko. Takako.
- I'm Kathy.
I'm Susie.
Happy family.
Yes, happy family!
This is Tilly. She picks up aircraft
and gets them off the deck
if they lose a wheel or something.
- Why do they call her Tilly?
- Why do they call you Nancy?
The ship will get under way
in 45 minutes.
Visitors are requested
to be off the ship in 15 minutes.
Now hear this. The officer of the deck
is shifting his watch to the bridge.
Here comes Beer Barrel.
- Hey, Beer Barrel, give me...
- What was your score, Beer Barrel?
- Don't drop your putter.
Hey, what's par for the cruise, Beer Barrel?
- Pull your flaps up, boys.
- You get it away off.
- You sure are overloaded.
- Report my return aboard, sir.
- Get refuelled, Beer Barrel.
Can I help you with those, sir?
Thanks, sonny, but this is a man's work.
We've got a few minutes yet.
That's Mike Forney.
- Green scarf?
- Yeah.
I never knew there were
so many beautiful girls.
- There ain't. We cornered the market.
- Best thing ever happened to you, Mike,
losing Kimiko to that big ape
from the Essex.
Nestor, you're a wise man.
There she is, girls.
The Savo, the greatest flat top in the fleet.
What's called this ship?
Oh, that.
That's the Essex.
Not here, Mike!
There's too much brass and SPs.
You're right.
She ain't worth it.
What's one girl?
The flower of Japan.
The pride of the fleet, my lad.
The best man won.
- Thank you.
- Bless you, my children.
Come on, Forney's at it again.
- Hey, look, Chico's in a fight.
- Swing at me and I'll flatten you.
- Kill that little shrimp.
- That's the guy that started it.
- Hey, give me your hand.
- Who do you think you're hitting, Mike?
Hey, get back. Get back.
This ain't no place for a lady.
- Come on, we need you.
- Charlie, come here.
- Hey, what's going on here?
- All right, all right, break it up.
- Come on, back to the ship.
- Come on, get on board or we'll run you in.
- All right, come on, come on, fellas.
- Let's go.
- Come on, boys, back to the ship.
That's the man you spent
half the night getting out of jail?
Yes, and I'd do it again.
Although we're going out to get
new pictures of the target area,
this flak intelligence photo
will give you some idea
how rough this mission is gonna be.
In order to determine the tactical
approach, I'll fly the mission to get
the pre-strike photos.
- Brubaker, you'll fly cover for me.
- Roger.
- We'll come in from the west. You stay
at least 3,000 feet above me at all times.
But keep away from even altitudes.
It makes it tougher on the gunners.
We'll take off in an hour.
All right, Martin, you've got it.
Boy, what a spot to take pictures.
When I go, I want bombs, not cameras.
All cameras ready on photographic plane.
Clear port and starboard catwalks forward.
Prepare to launch photographic mission.
Launch jets.
Bluejay, this is Peter Peter 21.
My feet are dry.
Crossing first checkpoint.
There's our second checkpoint.
Town of Majon-ni.
Just passed Yang-dok.
Target 15 miles ahead.
Remember, CAG, all you got is
a camera. Get in and get out.
I'm only gonna take their pictures,
but watch how mad they get.
Commencing run.
I've seen it rough, CAG,
but that was the roughest.
- You all right?
- I think so. I felt something
that could've been a hit.
My tail-hook position light came on.
Drop down, look me, over.
- Nothing visible.
- Good. Mission completed.
Returning to carrier.
Real estate sure looks
better on the way home.
Stand by to land jet aircraft.
- Wheels down.
- Flaps down.
- Hook down.
- All down, sir.
- All down.
- Clear deck.
Clear deck. Land aircraft.
Nice going, CAG.
Roger pass!
Clear the deck!
Stand by to rig a new barricade.
I'm all right.
Bluejay to 209er. Follow deck.
Peter Peter 21 crashed. He's okay.
- What is your state?
- Fuel critical.
- Only 650 pounds remaining.
- Barrier being repaired.
- Estimate ten-minute delay.
- I'll be out of fuel by then.
- How about the Hornet?
- Hornet not spotted for recovery.
- Orbit ship.
- Roger.
Get that barrier cleared
and that plane out of there.
Man Tilly!
Barricade is not repairable.
Tilly will be used
to protect planes forward.
I've only got 450 pounds left. How about it?
I don't want to go into the sea again.
Position Tilly
in the number-three barrier spot.
- On the double!
- Impossible to repair barrier in time.
Must use Tilly to protect planes forward.
Deck is pitching badly.
Do you wish to attempt deck landing
or do you wish to ditch?
I'll come aboard.
Pri fly says if he doesn't make it
the first time, he'll have to ditch.
He hasn't got enough fuel for another pass.
I'll bring him in
if Tilly doesn't bother him.
Stand by.
All personnel, clear the deck aft
and at base of the island.
Stand by with crash equipment.
Bring me in, Beer Barrel!
No wave-off!
Come on, junior. I know the deck's dancing,
but you gotta make it this time.
All planes aboard.
Continue clearing barrier.
Strike Peter Peter 21 below
as soon as possible.
Commence refuelling. The smoking
lamp is out throughout the ship.
Maybe you'd better not fly for a few days.
I'm all right. Thanks.
This is all I needed.
- What are they doing? Moving you, Doc?
- They're not moving me.
We're sending some medical
supplies to the destroyer.
She's coming alongside
to pick up Forney and Gamidge.
- Forney and Gamidge?
- Haven't you heard?
The captain's having them transferred.
They're going to the helicopter scow
at Yodo Island.
- So long, Gamidge. Good luck.
- Thanks. Same to you, sir.
Watch out, Nestor.
Don't get your feet wet.
You're liable to catch cold!
So long, Lieutenant.
We'll send you the 80 bucks.
Good luck, Nestor.
They want us to fly our eggbeater in behind
enemy lines three times a day after meals.
I don't mind rough duty, though.
I really hate them Commies!
Take care of yourself, Mike.
The pilots need men like you.
Thank you, sir.
Well, Lieutenant, if you ever have to
ditch around Wonsan Harbor,
we'll be there to fish you out again.
What's the matter, Lieutenant?
You look kind to edgy. You know
what I used to do when I got jittery?
I used to walk to the forward end
of that flight deck,
let that spray hit me in the kisser.
- Used to fix me up every time.
- All right, Forney, let's go.
- Right.
Why don't you try it sometime, Lieutenant?
The two stone bridges offer the best targets.
But you'll also have to hit the low ones.
We'll give you coordinates and checkpoints
the final briefing tomorrow afternoon.
Now, your secondary target
will be this fuel dump at Tok-tong.
We've hit this before, of course,
but there's evidence of new activity in
the area. Are there any questions?
Yes, about Toko-Ri. Where would you say is
the heaviest concentration of flak?
Here are the shots from my wing camera.
Does that answer your question?
The flight will consist of three divisions.
We'll make our approach from the west,
and attack three times if necessary.
Martin, you'll take your four jets
in to suppress flak.
I'll follow with my division on
the western bridges.
Brubaker, your division will take
the two bridges to the east.
Roy, you'll be the last man down.
You'll give a damage report
after each attack.
Take-off will be at 1500, so when we go in,
we'll have the sun at our backs.
Any questions?
We're back here in the Broadcasting Room
on a warm, sunny day here at the Memorial
Coliseum in Los Angeles.
The temperature in the high eighties
and you oughta see this sight!
80,000 fans are sure getting
the thrill of their lives this afternoon.
This is the big one.
The rams trail the 49ers by six points.
And the winner meets Cleveland for the title.
Now, the Rams line up again.
The ends are split wide.
Van Brocklin is dropping back to pass.
He gets good protection.
It's a long one to Fears.
He's dropped on the six-yard line.
First and goal to go.
Dear Nancy,
these will probably be the last words...
...you'll ever receive from me.
Dear Nancy,
I wish I could tell you
how wonderful it was to see you.
I'll never forget the picture of you...
...standing there on the dock as we came in.
- What are you doing, Harry?
- I was just writing a letter to Nancy.
- I can't sleep with all this racket going on.
- Yeah, I've noticed that, too.
- It always seems louder just before
you're going out on a mission. You all right?
- Yeah.
Look, Harry,
this is an important mission, very important.
We've gotta do a first-rate professional job.
I can't afford to take chances.
I know.
If a guy comes clean and grounds himself,
I'm grateful.
But if he tries to bluff it out and endangers
an entire mission, it's unforgivable.
Think it over, Harry.
Pilots, man planes.
Stand by to start jet engines.
Launch jets.
Flight from CAG.
Target dead ahead. Prepare to attack.
205 to CAG.
Commencing flak-suppression run.
- 212 from Zero-Zero.
- This is 212. Damage report follows.
Three bridges down.
One railway bridge intact.
Are you sure, Roy?
It looked like direct hits on all of them.
- Negative.
- Stand by for second attack.
CAG to Flight.
Commencing second attack.
All bridges down.
All bridges down. Nice going, CAG.
CAG to Flight.
Rendezvous and proceed to secondary target.
CAG to Flight. Secondary target below.
Commencing first run.
210 from 209er.
I think I just took a hit.
210! 210 from 209er.
Just took a hit. Where are you?
Harry, this is CAG.
210 must have radio failure.
I have you in sight.
I'll be with you in a minute.
No visible damage.
A little vapour coming from your fuselage.
- Could it be hydraulic fluid or fuel.
- RPM is surging a little bit.
Everything else seems okay.
CAG to 205. Martin, take over.
I'm staying with Brubaker.
CAG from 205. Roger.
Will stay above and keep you in sight.
Thanks, CAG. I was worried there
for a minute. I thought I might have to
land here. I think I'll make it all right.
- Brubaker from CAG. What state?
- Fuel okay. 2,000 pounds.
Keep checking, Harry. You're losing fuel.
Hydraulic fluid would be gone by now.
- Can you still see vapour trail?
- Affirmative. Don't your gauges show it?
- Can't tell.
- You'll make it to the sea all right.
Wonsan Harbor's just over the ridge.
If you can make the helicopter scow,
they'll pick you up.
Yeah, sure, I'll make it.
I'm losing fuel fast now, CAG.
Down to 1,600 pounds.
You'd better call the word now, Harry.
You'd better call the scow.
Yeah.
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
This is 209er. RDF call.
35 miles north-west Wonsan.
Flak damage.
Losing fuel rapidly.
Let's go, Nestor.
Alligator 1 to 209er.
Give me a call for a bearing.
Emergency! Emergency!
Prepare helicopter for launch.
1-2-3-4-4-3.
Launch helicopter.
Bluejay, Bluejay.
This is Alligator 1.
- Alligator 1, this is Bluejay. Go ahead.
- 209er has had an emergency.
He bears 3-3-0 degrees,
35 miles from Wonsan.
Air Op, CIC. We have an emergency.
Stand by to write.
- Can't last much longer, CAG.
- You're doing fine, Harry. You'll make it.
Fuel tanks empty.
I've had it.
I still think you can make it, Harry.
I've got enough altitude to glide to
the water if I can only clear the ridge.
Can't make it.
- What are you gonna do, Harry?
- Crash.
They love to fire at parachutes.
Alligator 1, this is Zero-Zero.
209er crash-landing,
bearing 3-3-5 degrees.
- 25 miles from Yodo Island.
- Roger your transmission.
Trying to divert propellered aircraft to crash
for rescap protection of downed pilot.
- There's a clearing ahead looks pretty good.
- I see it.
- Looks like an irrigation ditch
along the side.
- That's right.
Try to land near it.
Get out fast. Make for that ditch.
- Be sure and hit every item
on your checkoff list, Harry.
- I'm doing that now.
Tighten your shoulder straps
as tight as you can stand them.
- I can hardly breathe.
- Gun?
I've got one.
Not that I've ever used it.
The other division's coming in above us.
How does the field look, Harry?
- You pick them real good, CAG.
- Jettison your canopy.
Get out fast, Harry.
No matter what happens, get out fast!
Forney!
Nestor!
Nestor.
And they was gonna
give nestor a medal too.
How much longer can them ADs stay?
Not very long.
They must be running out of ammunition.
They won't send another helicopter now,
not after dark.
If we can hold out through the night,
they'll find us in the morning.
Here, you better take this.
You know how to fire a carbine, sir? Just
release the safety and squeeze the trigger.
It fires automatic until you stop fire.
I'm a lawyer from Denver, Colorado, Mike.
I probably can't hit a thing.
Judas! How did you ever get out here
in a smelly ditch in Korea?
That's just what I've been asking myself.
Better get these things off.
Too good a target.
"The wrong war in the wrong place,
and that's the one you're stuck with."
What did you say, Lieutenant?
Did you ever hear Admiral Tarrant
go on about this war?
About the chosen few
who have to lay it on the line?
Nestor and me never done much
fraternised with the admirals.
I can see now he was right.
You fight simply because you're here.
Watch out, Lieutenant!
- Where's Lee?
- He's waiting on the bridge, sir.
- Admiral from CIC.
- Go ahead.
Just received final report, sir,
authenticated by Army Intelligence.
Jet aircraft crashed.
Helicopter shot down.
Three Americans killed
by Communist troops.
- Why was Brubaker abandoned?
- Admiral, we kept a rescap
over him as long as we could.
If one helicopter crashed,
why didn't you call in another?
I called in the downed-pilot
condition report before I was
forced to leave. My fuel was low.
The first helicopter hadn't even arrived.
There was nothing more that I could do.
- Was Brubaker hit at the bridges?
- No, sir, at our secondary target.
We got the bridges. We still had bombs left
so we went to work on the fuel dump.
- Was that good judgment?
- Admiral, this was a good mission.
We did everything just right.
I put Brubaker in charge of the third
division because I knew he would fly low
and bore in with the bombs. He did just that.
I don't care what kind of fitness report
you give me. This was a good mission!
It cost the lives of three men:
Forney, Gamidge, and Brubaker.
I know how you feel. But what
makes you think you're the only one.
He may have been your boy, Admiral,
but he was my boy, too! I lost him.
You're right, CAG.
You're right.
I was wrong about CAG, Evans.
He's a good man. A good man.
I'd like to write Brubaker's wife,
but what can you say, are you?
Explain this to the mother of two little girls.
Prepare to launch jets.
Where do we get such men?
They leave this ship
and they do their job.
Then they must find this speck
lost somewhere on the sea.
When they find it,
they have to land on its pitching deck.
- Where do we get such men?
- Launch jets.