Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
The Cincinnati Accord has brought
a cease-fire to Bosnia.
And it appears to be holding.
NATO forces have begun withdrawal...
...which should be complete
by New Year's Day...
...close to the president's
"Home by the Holidays" pledge.
Yet as the conflict winds down,
the U.S. military remains at readiness...
...eager to answer the call.
Golden Eagle, this is Hawkeye.
Unknown rider not responding.
Unclassified bandit. Launch the alert.
Let's move it. We need
this craft airborne in five minutes.
- Nose. Radome.
- Check. Secure.
- Diffuser.
- Clear.
- Right, left intake.
- Check.
- Ejection seat is safe.
- Copy.
- Comm, IFF.
- Up and up. Let's go.
- DDI, MPCD and HUD.
- Go flight.
- FCS, ECS, AWP.
- It's green across the board.
- Okay for start.
- Copy.
- Right throttle, 15 percent.
- Copy. Go for two.
Two is up. Turbine is online.
Copy, nozzle coming to 73 percent.
- Good to go.
- Copy.
That's a NATO bird.
Stand it down.
Abort, abort.
- That's bullshit!
- Come on. Are you kidding me?
Abort. Launch is canceled.
Come on. That's twice today.
Yeah, we're wound up tight today.
That's the price of peace.
I cannot wait for this shit to be done.
Oh, man.
Four more days.
You know what I read?
Bill Gates has more money than Peru.
He needs someone to fly his jets.
We ought to fly for him.
I bet Bill won't let you fly upside down.
Or fly for a rock star.
Those guys need good pilots.
Every day we lose a band to some
shitty hack they got flying for them.
A Navy pilot could have saved Ritchie
Valens from being a one-hit wonder.
That kid had talent.
You know, Lynyrd Skynyrd, Buddy Holly.
- What about John Denver?
- Well, let's not get carried away.
Let me ask you something.
How fast are we headed into the wind?
Chris, we're on alert. Reigart wanders
up to the tower, we're dead.
All right, let's do it.
That's the spirit.
- Rutherford, right here.
- Incoming!
You guys ready for
a little lesson in physics?
I'm gonna take your money this week.
Wind's blowing up a gale.
I'll bet you $20 each I catch it.
You'll lose a finger along with that 20.
This one?
All right. Always happy
to take an officer's money.
Look! It's coming back!
Man, that is awesome!
Watch out for the catwalk!
I got it!
Wilson!
On the flight deck, heads up.
NATO helo landing spot 6. Spot 6.
A lot of sorties for action
that's winding down, Leslie.
I'm trying to get my pilots
15 hours a month up there.
You know it's important your pilots
don't stray from agreed flight zones?
- This treaty is fragile.
- Routes will be flown as ordered.
The treaty depends on it.
Aernout Van Lynden.
He's with Sky News.
- What's this?
- I invited him to report on us.
Give him a tour of the ship.
Show him how everything works.
I find the press to be intrusive.
It inspires showing off.
What's so funny?
You, admiral.
You're just what the conflict needs.
- An uncomplicated man.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
But wait a second.
Did you see the one with the...?
Lookit here. Stackhouse.
I know that's not Burnett.
Captain, good to see you.
Look at you.
- You guys back?
- You know the routine.
Finished in Sarajevo.
Your admiral wanted us to pump you up.
Sounds like Reigart. Be prepared.
Better to be prepared than
caught sleeping in the field.
Don't forget what you're doing here.
What we're doing here?
Are you kidding me?
Well, I'm eating Jell-O.
He's wiping his hands.
Everybody has a role to play.
I'm a Marine. We take care
of the serious business.
You, you're a Navy pilot,
and your role is to eat Jell-O.
You don't pick your fight.
It comes to you.
I get it. But at least give me
a fight I can understand.
Vukovar? Where did we fly
over the other day? Sreb--?
Srebrenica.
Good luck explaining to someone:
"Today's Tuesday.
We're helping these people.
No, it's switched around.
Now we're helping--"
I mean, it's like a joke.
- Just be glad it's over.
- Yeah, I am.
Look at these guys.
That's what I'm talking about.
Everybody thinks they'll get a chance
to punch some Nazi in the face.
Those days are over.
They are long gone.
I used to think I'd get to do it.
Now I'm eating Jell-O.
Are you gonna eat that?
- First you complain, now you want it.
- Lieutenant Burnett.
Admiral Reigart wants
to see you immediately.
- What the hell is this?
- Be prepared.
Thank you.
He wants to give you
his daughter's number.
Did you see Tennessee on Saturday?
They looked good.
- I don't know anything, lieutenant.
- That is cynical.
Southerners usually aren't cynical.
I compliment how great
your alma mater looks...
...and you think I'm pumping you.
What does he want?
You'll have to see, sir.
Come.
- Lieutenant Burnett, sir.
- Master Chief O'Malley, thank you.
Lieutenant Burnett.
Sir, about the football--
I have your letter. You're interested
in leaving the Navy.
- I thought it might be time to move on.
- Move on to what?
Sir?
You're gonna fly commercial jets?
Troll the friendly skies in a bus?
You've had an interesting career.
I remember when you came onboard.
Smart as a whip, tons of potential.
- Thank you, sir.
- Then on September 23...
...you received a non-punitive
letter of caution...
...for disorderly behavior
at the Fleet Club in Hong Kong.
Another letter for something
involving Chinese New Year...
...at Pattaya Beach in Thailand.
One can only imagine what that was.
Just out of curiosity, lieutenant,
what happened to you?
Sir, I signed up to be
a fighter pilot, not a cop.
I certainly didn't want to be a cop
in a neighborhood no one cares about.
That and the routine wore me out.
- The routine?
- The routine.
What you don't know is
that the routine...
...the systems checks, the drills,
the maintaining of discipline...
...prepare you for war.
- We're not at war, sir.
- Yes, we are.
Unless we're parked in San Diego Bay,
you're at war on this boat. Understand?
No, sir, I do not understand.
Why don't we act like we're at war?
As far as I can tell,
we go out, fly around and come back.
All we're doing is pretending because
we're not fighting. We're watching.
Be glad you're not. With your attitude
you wouldn't last long.
I've given the Navy seven years.
I think I've served my country.
You wouldn't know the first thing
about serving your country.
You have two weeks remaining.
You'll serve them in a manner
befitting a naval officer.
I'll keep your letter.
At the end of those two weeks,
you be on your way.
- You're dismissed, mister.
- Sir.
O'Malley said you quit. Bullshit, right?
Nope. He's telling the truth.
You're gonna break up the band, huh?
Oh, that's good.
Chris, I thought you were kidding
about getting out.
You saying I gotta find
another navigator?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm done. I'm sorry.
All hands, an air contact believed to
have originated at the North Pole...
...has been spotted
and is inbound to USS Carl Vinson.
It's good to hear your voice.
They're taking care of us great.
Putting up tinsel, it's very Christmassy.
Don't wake her.
Tell her merry Christmas.
-We're disappointed we won't see you.
- You may see a lot of me soon.
We understand. You got important
things to do over there.
Dad, I gotta go.
- We're very proud of you.
-Dad, I gotta go.
- All right, I love you.
-Bye.
Son of a bitch! He put us on
the holiday mission. Goddamn it!
Well, at least we get to fly.
During the one good meal.
It's like he doesn't like us.
No. You, not me. You.
Merry Christmas.
On the flight deck, it's showtime.
Aircraft remaining for the NATO
solo photo reconnaissance mission.
Wouldn't it be great to see Britney Spears?
She wants to fly the plane!
"Just move the stick there.
You're doing great."
The Cincinnati Accord verifies Serbia's
commitment to peace in Yugoslavia.
I welcome the announcement
that NATO will leave the region.
Coordinates 3-0-1-5-0-6.5...
...1-1-5-0 confirmed.
Sectors are all concurrent.
- You sure about that?
- Reading it right here, pal.
Yeah, well....
The Serbs must've bought some U-boats
because we're over a lake.
Goddamn it.
And a warm thank-you goes out
to the U.S. intelligence community.
Another useless joyride at the cost
of millions to the U.S. taxpayer.
Hang on. Showing activity
in 4-Alpha to our left.
Must be in that forested area.
That's the demilitarized zone.
There shouldn't be any activity.
I know, but the scope doesn't lie.
There it is. Check it out.
We're not supposed
to fly that section, Chris.
We're on recon,
so let's recon something.
Stack, it's probably
some locals fooling around.
An opportunity to test
our shiny, new digital camera.
Why do I listen to you?
All right, let's do it.
ECM is clear. GPS is synced
with new coordinates.
Steady at 0-3-4 and fly the director.
- IDEM camera is at speed.
- Got it. Going into burner.
On condition. Stand by for roll. Now.
Rolling digital.
Smile, guys. You're on TV.
- Won't you miss all this excitement?
- Absolutely.
- What is it?
- Holy shit, we're being painted!
What?
- Shit, they fired! Scoop it now!
- Copy.
- Pull up! Get the nose moving!
- Roger!
I see a missile.
- I don't see it. Call my turn.
- Just slice left. Hard.
Jesus Christ.
Where is it?
Reverse right!
Try to break the lock!
Golden Eagle, Ark Angel.
We have been engaged.
- Put out decoy flares.
- Copy. Hang on!
- No joy!
- Where is it, goddamn it? Where is it?
- Can't see shit.
- Where is he?
Jesus Christ, second missile!
Three miles and closing! Pull up!
I got him, I got him!
We need a bigger heat decoy.
We're screwed!
Missile's closing.
2.8. 1.8. One mile!
Drop those fuel tanks and pull up!
Good fireball!
Clear on top! Coming back down!
I got two missiles in sight,
both tracking for the fireball.
That's it! One down! Up we go!
- Where's the second?
- No joy. I don't have it in sight.
- He's back on us. Push over.
- Copy!
Hard left!
I'm going for a pass!
Here he comes! Head-on! Right side!
He clipped part of the tail!
Controls going to shit!
-Warning, warning.
- Where is it?
He's coming back. Arcing right.
Break right!
I got no turn left. The controls are shot!
No, break right!
Shit!
Seat eject! Eject, eject!
Goddamn it!
- A hell of a party, sir.
- I really like Christmas.
Sir, we've lost a bird. An F-18, feet dry.
- Ark Angel 0-6.
- Burnett and Stackhouse.
Damn it, I put them on a holiday
mission. Beacon activity?
Not yet, admiral.
We have a flight path
from feet dry to last contact.
Here in yellow is the assigned path.
And the red is actual.
Lost contact is here.
They're off mission. What happened?
If they ejected, it'll be tough
to pick up a signal.
- The terrain is extremely rough.
- Weather's not helping.
Contact Admiral Piquet, alert NATO.
Make sure we have a flash op rep
out over all U.S. national circuits.
Get to Admiral Donnelly. No names.
No names, sir.
Stack! Stackhouse!
Stack!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
- Shit, man, you okay?
- I'm okay. You look terrible.
Hey, man, that looks pretty bad.
Let me see. Oh, man.
We gotta change this.
We need a new field dressing on this.
Shit. Squeeze right here.
So where are we, Mr. Navigator Man?
In the mountains north of Miciovic.
You think they saw us eject?
We are not gonna be around to find out.
Reigart will wonder
what happened to his plane.
I already tried.
You need to get to higher ground.
You think it'll work up there?
Yeah. Just get high enough.
All right. All right, sit tight.
- Hey, Chris.
- What?
Listen, I should have dodged
that second missile.
Yeah, you blew it
and took me down with you.
I thought you had great reflexes.
What happened?
- You're slipping. You need to watch it.
- Son of a bitch.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Oh, goddamn it.
Son of a bitch!
Reconnaissance mission, yes?
Not bombing mission, right?
You photograph?
You alone?
Correct.
No!
Alpha Whiskey,
this is Ark Angel 06, over.
Alpha Whiskey, this is Ark Angel 06,
over. Can you read me?
- What is that?
- Sorry, sir. There's interference.
The homing beacon.
- Well, shut it off.
- Aye, aye, sir.
Alpha Echo, Alpha Echo. Alpha
Whiskey directs cease buzzer on 06.
Alpha Whiskey, this is Ark Angel 06,
over. Do you read?
06, this is Alpha Whiskey.
I read you. Go ahead.
Ark Angel is down. Ark Angel is down
and I am on the run.
Slow down. What is your count?
Minus one. Stackhouse. They shot him.
No names over the net.
Confirm your last.
Minus one confirmed.
Serbs in camo shot my pilot.
A uniformed soldier killed
your flight officer?
No, I'm saying they executed him.
They were talking to him,
then they shot him in the head.
Calm down, son.
We're working on it. Wait one.
- How soon can your team be ready?
- Say the word, and we'll saddle up.
06, consult your chart.
Reposition to rally point 3.
I read 133-41. Maintain radio silence.
We're coming.
Make your way to the rally point.
-Understood?
- 06 copies. Out.
- Contact Piquet and Donnelly.
- Aye, aye, sir.
I need a green light to get my boy.
Command comes from red fighter.
You'll have three slicks loaded with
rockets and guns at your disposal.
Use advisedly.
I want gimbal attachments
for fast ropers.
Team leaders report to me
as soon as your squad is ready.
Come.
What's going on down there?
We have an F-18 down in Bosnia.
One pilot suspected dead.
- Who authorized a search and rescue?
- I did.
Call it off. Stand down.
Maybe I wasn't clear.
We have pilots down, one probably dead.
I have spoken
to Bosnian military commanders.
They say that the shoot-down
was perpetrated by renegades...
...trying disrupt the peace process.
- Of course.
- They're also claiming...
...that your aircraft was
way off mission.
If we fly in there,
the whole treaty will collapse.
Burnett says that
Serb troops murdered his pilot.
Is your pilot a Bosnian expert?
Can he tell between the uniforms
of Serbs, Croats and Muslims?
Because I can't.
And I've been posted here for 5 years.
If he's in danger,
he should go to the safe zone.
That is what he's briefed
and trained to do.
I can have your fleet commander
order you to stand down...
...or you can do it yourself.
Alpha Whiskey, this is 06. Come in.
06, go ahead.
06 is at rally point three
and standing by.
06, latest intel says
your current location...
...undoable for pickup.
Stand by to copy rendezvous point.
Say again your last.
I am at the rendezvous point.
You need to hump to a safe zone.
I set IP Cadillac, Canada 1-5...
...Virginia 2-0. Read back.
No.
Negative. Negative.
I do not understand.
Why is this spot not doable?
I am good to go.
I say again, I am good to go now.
Burnett!
06, you are a combat naval aviator.
Start acting like one.
You've been shot down.
Life is tough. I am very sorry.
But you pull yourself together.
You do whatever it takes.
Create angles between
you and your pursuers.
Use your training. Evade and survive,
and we will bring you home.
Do you understand?
06.
Someone's coming.
We lost the signal, sir.
- Triangulate his position.
- We're on it, sir.
We're tracking him in the SCIF, sir.
On me.
At ease.
Sir, we tracked the radio signal
to somewhere in this radius.
It's pretty far away. But we think
the transmission came from here.
314 Recycle, pair it with the I-F.
This is imagery from a satellite
downlinked at a center in Stuttgart.
We've hot-wired it for heat image
and it's streaming in now.
This isn't strictly legal, sir.
Here we go.
- That's Burnett?
- Yes, sir.
What's going on? He's down.
Has he been shot?
They're almost on him.
Son of a bitch.
- Why isn't he moving?
- Come on, Burnett, move.
They're right on him!
What are they doing?
What's going on?
Has he been killed?
He's moving. That's him.
Stay on it.
Resizing wide and broadband.
Stay with him.
Plug it in with NSA.
- What the hell's going on?
- The door's closing.
- Fix it, for chrissakes!
- We're down. It's cooked.
I want intel on this.
Who's chasing him and why? Understand?
Yes, sir.
Come.
Sorry, sir. Nothing in the last hour.
- I was trying to motivate him, Tom.
- Sir?
Burnett, in the radio room.
I was trying to motivate him.
Maybe I carried it too far.
Called him by his name. Stupid.
Just human, sir.
- Tom.
- Sir.
It's why I push them so hard.
For times like these.
May I speak freely?
You're gonna say whatever
you're gonna say. Don't patronize me.
Sir, what are we doing?
Our guy's stuck and we're sitting here.
- It's a complicated situation.
- Why isn't this all over the news?
Why isn't the president talking with
Pale to make sure he gets out safe?
He was off mission. Piquet has a point.
Piquet's got his own agenda, sir.
This kid's no idiot. If he says
he's getting shot at, I believe him.
What do you expect me to do?
Command says I gotta sit on my hands.
What else can I do?
Right. I forgot. It's not your call.
You're damn right it's not my call!
Apologies, sir.
Of course you can't do anything.
It's been confirmed to us
that a U.S. combat aircraft...
...has been shot down.
It was hit over Miciovic in Bosnia
at around 6:00 a.m. yesterday.
The pilot is feared dead,
but his navigator may have survived.
It's your son.
Names are withheld, pending
notification of their next of kin.
We still don't know
who shot the F-18 down.
The Serbs control
most of southern Bosnia.
They allege insurgents are to blame...
...and say they're doing everything
to locate the crew.
It's also unclear what,
if any, impact...
...this will have
on NATO's withdrawal.
Admiral.
We've known each other
for how long? Five years?
Something like that.
I've always commended your work
to your superiors.
I've sent you information you needed.
Thank you. I appreciate your support.
And this is the thanks I get?
We have one disagreement,
and you stab me in the back?
You go to the media
and make me look like an asshole.
You brought him on my boat.
His press report is accurate.
Our man is down behind enemy lines.
Now, what the fuck is the problem?
Do you know how much damage
this may cause to the peace process?
All I know is, the American people
want their pilot back.
Exactly!
Americans. All you care about
is your own damn pilots!
What happens when
the fighting starts again?
Will America recommit its forces
to stop a major war?
No. You don't have any control
over that little detail, do you?
You might have helped save your man
today. And I emphasize "might."
But you have risked the lives
of thousands tomorrow.
Shit!
Oh, shit.
Alpha Whiskey, this is Ark Angel.
They have a signal. It's Burnett.
Ark Angel 06, this is Alpha Whiskey.
Go ahead, 06.
I'm on course
with your last instructions...
...and keyed up and waiting
for you to name the fairway.
06, this is Alpha Whiskey.
How you doing, son?
I don't know. You tell me, sir.
The hard bit's over. You need
to get yourself five klicks east...
...to the sweet spot. Understood?
Roger. The spot's friendly?
Good for birds?
Affirmative. Spot is friendly.
You need to get there,
stay out of trouble...
...and big mother will pick you up.
Next contact at 1700.
Roger.
Alpha Whiskey?
Go ahead, 06.
Sir, I shouldn't have left Stackhouse.
Distract him.
06, your last transmission was garbled.
Let's talk about your gear.
How's it holding up?
My gear's good. I have a basic pack.
I left some of it at the crash site.
I guess I got rattled
when I ejected at Mach 3.
You still got your boots, cowboy?
Roger. They were tied on.
You've got it made.
You're an optimist, sir.
I had you figured for a grouch.
Okay, 06. Just make it to the RP.
Roger.
Will you be there, sir?
That's affirmative, son. Out.
He's here.
Yes, sir. I suggest we place them here.
It's open ground near the town of Haè,
well inside the safe zone.
Let's go for the extraction.
Bridge command area responsibility:
Ingress will be north, egress south.
From the position of
the radio contacts, you see...
...he's circled back
towards the crash site.
Call sign is Avalanche.
Authenticate: Romeo 2, X-ray.
Continue, Bulldog. Delay, cycle.
Abort is wash down.
Aircraft down is Cobalt.
Success is Ripper.
- Captain, take it from here.
- Thank you, sir.
Bravo will establish a security perimeter,
then return to the helo.
This is Colonel Brigand.
He will conduct the pickup.
My team is ready now.
- Get Admiral Donnelly on the line.
- I have spoken with him.
I have his full support.
You will stand down.
Chris.
Hold on, hold on!
You American?
9 mm?
- Yes.
- 9 mm.
- You have water?
- Water? No water.
Thanks.
It's good.
Ice Cube.
Yeah. I like Ice Cube.
I like all hip-hop, rap music.
West Coast, East Coast.
NWA, Public Enemy.
That's good. That's good.
You know where we're going?
- Haè.
- Haè. That's good. Good.
Jesus Christ!
Tell him to go!
Come out! Come out! Here.
Hey, bonjour.
Come on, come on. Let's go.
Hold it, hold it.
I'm an American soldier--
Shut up.
- What were you bombing?
- We were taking photographs.
Photographs of what? Of what?
Lokar is coming back again,
killing everyone.
It's true. He killed everyone.
Children, women.
- Buried them in the hills.
- Yes, I saw them. I saw the graves.
I saw them. I saw the bodies in the hills.
Tell him I am an American.
I am on your side.
Then you go outside. Tell them you're
American. They don't kill Americans.
Ice Cube, get over here.
Tell him we have pictures that can help--
Bullshit!
America say they make them sign deal.
But they already break it.
America government for shit! Now go!
Ice, hey. It's okay! It's me.
Come on. Come on.
- Time?
- Three minutes, sir.
Stop!
Let's go.
Reigart.
Leslie, I'm afraid there's bad news.
Bosnian-Serb Fourth Army Patrol
found Lieutenant Burnett near Haè.
I regret to inform you that
Lieutenant Burnett is dead. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It was a peace deal.
Haè was meant to be a safe haven.
Once again, that's proved an illusion.
In the midst of fighting
around the southern enclave...
...Bosnian-Serb forces said they found
the body of American navigator...
...Lt. Chris Burnett, whose plane
was shot down two days ago.
Serb authorities claim
he was shot by Muslim guerrillas...
...opposed to the recently signed
Cincinnati Peace Accord.
Serbs say one of their teams
found the body...
...in a search and rescue attempt
since the F-18 was shot down.
This is bound to spoil NATO's hope
of a clean exit from the Balkans...
...and frustrates U.S. leaders
who are near to a complete withdrawal.
For NATO forces on the eve
of departure from this region...
...Burnett's death comes as another
blow at the end of a disturbing...
...and ultimately unsuccessful chapter
in the alliance's history.
Savior Six, from Gold Eagle command,
the package is not in position.
Mission is scrubbed.
Return to base immediately.
Hey! Wait for me!
Hey! Come on! Fuck!
Damn it! We're right here!
You've got to be shitting me!
Son of a bitch! They killed him!
They killed him, and we did nothing!
We did nothing.
We're right here.
We're right....
What's that?
It's not safe here. We keep going.
No. You go.
They killed my pilot because
we took pictures of the graves.
I know where they are.
And I'm gonna get them.
So he didn't die for no reason.
Don't follow me. You'll be safer here.
Shit.
Goddamn. Why is this off?
Why is this off? Why is this...?
Come on.
Come on! Goddamn it!
All right. Okay, come on.
Yeah!
For the information of all hands:
this ship will be relieved on station.
It will set course for home base,
effective 2300 this evening.
Sir, your presence is requested
in the SCIF.
All right.
It's the homing beacon
on the second ejection seat.
It can only be reactivated
from the seat.
- How long has that been on?
- Seven minutes.
You've gotta be very familiar with
our systems to reactivate that beacon.
- That's Burnett.
- It could be a setup.
It's a radio transmission.
They're hearing the same music.
Sir, I agree.
We should notify NATO or contact
Donnelly for clearance before launch.
- Of course, that will take time.
- Tom, I get it. We wait, Burnett dies.
Piquet was very clear
with his objections.
- You'll lose your command.
- So be it!
I won't let that kid die out there
while we sit around on this ship!
Okay. All right.
Goddamn it!
Gentlemen, I want to make
one thing clear before we leave.
I intend to put you in harm's way.
Any man who doesn't wish
to join this mission...
...step away right now.
All right, then.
Let's go get our boy back.
Two klicks up this valley,
we're gonna make a hard right.
There he is. There he is.
Come on, come on! Damn it!
What the hell is he waiting for?
Come on!
Come on! Come on, kid!
Too hot to set down.
- Going around.
- Roger.
Goddamn it!
Come on!
- Go!
- Captain. Fast rope, go get him.
He's on the right.
- Sniper in the open.
- We'll take him.
Come on, son! Come on!
Go!
They got him! Pull up! Pull up!
- Hey, Chris.
- Hey, Glenn.
Admiral.
This is why they killed Stackhouse!
Admiral, you're holding a letter for me.
I'd like to get it back.
I think I can find it.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player