I still don't know why l'm here.
Couldn't you just make them say yes?
Yes, l could, but it's not my way.
And l would expect you, of all people,
would understand
my feelings on misuse of power.
Ah, power corrupts and all that.
Yes, l know, Charles.
- When are you going to stop lecturing me?
- When you start listening.
You're here because I need you.
We don't have to meet
every one of them in person?
No. This one's special.
What a beautiful campus.
John, don't you think?
Yeah, the brochure is great.
But what about Jean?
What about her illness?
- Illness?
- John.
You think your daughter is sick, mr grey?
Perhaps it would be best
if we were to speak to her. Alone.
Of course.
Jean, can you come down, dear?
We'll leave you, then.
It's very rude to read my thoughts,
or mr lensherr's, without our permission.
Did you think you were
the only one of your kind, young lady?
We're mutants, Jean. We're like you.
Really? L doubt that.
Oh, Charles.
I like this one.
You have more power
than you can imagine, Jean.
The question is,
will you control that power?
Or let it control you?
Warren? Son, is everything all right?
- What's going on?
- Nothing. L'll be right out.
Come on.
You've been in there for over an hour.
Open the door. Warren.
One second!
Open this door.
Warren.
Let me in there right now. Open the door.
Oh, god.
- Not you.
- Dad, l'm sorry.
The whole world's going to hell and
you're just going to sit there? Let's go.
Bobby!
Thanks, kitty.
- We're getting killed out here.
- Yeah, I know. They're not ready, storm.
- Logan.
- Oh, don't get your panties in a bunch.
That was my last cigar.
Logan.
- It's getting closer.
- Come on. Let's keep moving.
Hey, tin man. Come here.
- How's your throwing arm?
- Logan, we work as a team.
Yeah. Good luck with that.
Throw me. Now.
Dammit, Logan, don't do this.
Class dismissed.
Hey, colossus. Nice throw.
Simulation complete.
- What was that?
- Danger room session.
- You know what l mean.
- Lighten up.
You can't change the rules.
I'm trying to teach 'em something.
- I taught 'em something.
- It was a defensive exercise.
Yeah, best defense is a good offense.
Or is it the other way round?
- This isn't a game, Logan.
- Well, you sure fooled me.
Hey, I'm just a sub.
You got a problem, talk to Scott.
- Scott!
- Jean.
Scott. Scott.
Scott.
- Are you ok?
- I'm fine.
You seem like you're avoiding me.
Something's wrong.
I can't touch my boyfriend without
killing him. Other than that I'm wonderful.
Hey. I don't think that's fair.
Have l ever put any pressure on you?
You're a guy, Bobby.
Your mind's only on one thing.
They were looking for you.
You didn't show.
What do you care?
- For starters, l had to cover your ass.
- I didn't ask you to.
No, you didn't. The professor did.
- I was just passing through.
- So pass through, Logan.
Hey, look.
- I know how you feel. When Jean died...
- Don't.
Maybe it's time for us to move on.
Not everybody heals as fast as you, Logan.
- Mr secretary.
- Yes.
- The meeting's begun, sir.
- Thank you.
Mr president.
Have a seat, Hank.
Homeland security was tracking Magneto.
We got hits in Lisbon, Geneva, Montreal.
Navsat lost him crossing the border,
but we did get a consolation prize.
We picked her up breaking into the fda.
You know who she's been imitating?
Secretary trask here.
Yes, sir. She can do that.
- Not any more, she can't. We got her.
- You think your prisons can hold her?
We have some new prisons.
We'll keep them mobile. Be a step ahead.
Where is Magneto?
Raven?
- Raven, l asked you a question.
- I don't answer to my slave name.
Raven darkholme.
That's your real name, isn't it?
Or has he convinced you
you don't have a family any more?
My family tried to kill me,
you pathetic meat sack.
Ok, then. Mystique - where is he?
In here with us.
I don't want to play games with you.
I want answers.
You don't want to play games with me?
You are going to stop this.
Tell me, where is Magneto?
You wanna know where he is?
Homo sapien.
You know, her capture
will only provoke Magneto,
but having her does give us
some diplomatic leverage.
On principle, I can't negotiate
with these people.
- I thought that's why you appointed me, sir.
- Yes, it is.
- But that's not why you called me here.
- No. This is.
It's what she stole from the fda.
Dear lord.
- Is it viable?
- We believe it is.
You realize the impact
this'll have on the mutant community?
Yes. L do. That's precisely why
we need some of your diplomacy now.
When an individual acquires great power,
the use or misuse of that power
is everything.
Will it be for the greater good or will it be
used for personal or for destructive ends?
Now, this is a question
we must all ask ourselves.
Why? Because we are mutants.
For psychics,
this presents a particular problem.
When is it acceptable to use our power
and when do we cross that invisible line
that turns us into tyrants
over our fellow man?
But Einstein said that ethics
are an exclusive human concern
without any superhuman authority behind it.
Einstein wasn't a mutant
so far as we know.
This case study was sent to me
by a colleague, dr moira mctaggert. Jones.
The man you see here was born
with no higher-level brain functions.
His organs and nervous system work,
but he has no consciousness to speak of.
What if we were to transfer
the consciousness of one person,
say a father of four with terminal cancer,
into the body of this man?
How are we to decide what falls within
the range of ethical behavior and what...
Professor?
We'll continue this tomorrow.
Class dismissed.
The forecast was for sunny skies.
I'm sorry.
I don't have to be psychic
to see that something's bothering you.
I don't understand. Magneto's a fugitive,
we've a mutant in the cabinet,
a president who understands us - why hide?
We're not hiding. But we still have enemies.
I must protect my students. You know that.
Yes, but we can't be students forever.
Storm, I haven't thought of you
as my student for years.
In fact, l thought that perhaps
you might take my place some day.
- But Scott's...
- Scott's a changed man.
He took Jean's death so hard.
Yes, things are better out there,
but you, of all people,
know how fast the weather can change.
There's something you're not telling us.
Hank?
Ororo. Charles.
I love what you've done with your hair.
You too. Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
Henry, you are always welcome here.
You're a part of this place.
- I have news.
- Is it Eric?
No. Though we have been making
some progress on that front.
- Mystique was recently apprehended.
- Who's the fur ball?
Hank McCoy. Secretary of mutant affairs.
Right, right. The secretary. Nice suit.
- Henry, this is Logan. He's...
- Wolverine.
- I hear you're quite an animal.
- Look who's talking.
Magneto's gonna come get mystique.
Magneto's not the problem.
At least not our most pressing one.
A major pharmaceutical company
has developed a mutant antibody.
A way to suppress the mutant x gene.
- Suppress?
- Permanently.
They're calling it a cure.
That's ridiculous.
You can't cure being a mutant.
- Scientifically speaking...
- When did we become a disease?
Storm.
They're announcing it now.
These so-called mutants
are people just like us.
Their affliction is nothing more
than a disease,
a corruption of healthy cellular activity.
But l stand here today
to tell you that there's hope.
This site, once the world's
most famous prison,
will now be the source of freedom
for all mutants who choose it.
Ladies and gentlemen...
I proudly present the answer to mutation.
Finally, we have a cure.
Who would want this cure? L mean, what kind
of coward would take it just to fit in?
Is it cowardice to save oneself
from persecution?
Not all of us can fit in so easily.
- You don't shed on the furniture.
- The government probably cooked this up.
- The government had nothing to do with it.
- I've heard that before.
My boy, I have been fighting for mutant
rights since before you had claws.
- Did he just call me boy?
- Is it true? They can cure us?
Yes, rogue. It appears to be true.
No. Professor.
They can't cure us.
You wanna know why? Because there's
nothing to cure. Nothing's wrong with you.
Or any of us, for that matter.
How should we, as mutants, respond?
Here's what l think.
This is about getting organized. Bringing
our complaints to the right people.
We need to put together a committee
and talk to the government.
They don't understand. They don't know
what it means to be a mutant.
We need to show them, educate them,
let them know that we're here to stay.
People, you must listen.
They won't take us seriously...
- They wanna exterminate us.
- This cure is voluntary.
Nobody is talking about extermination.
No one ever talks about it.
They just do it.
And you'll go on with your lives
ignoring the signs all around you.
And then one day, when the air is still and
the night has fallen, they come for you.
Then you realize, while you're talking
about organizing and committees,
the extermination has already begun.
Make no mistake, my brothers.
They will draw first blood.
They will force their cure upon us.
The only question is,
will you join my brotherhood and fight?
Or wait for the inevitable genocide?
Who will you stand with? The humans?
Or us?
You talk pretty tough for a guy in a cape.
Back off.
If you're so proud of being a mutant,
where's your mark?
I have been marked once, my dear.
Let me assure you.
No needle shall ever touch my skin again.
You know who you're talking to?
Do you?
And what can you do?
So you have talents?
That and more. I know you control metal.
And l know there's 87 mutants in here,
none above a class three.
Other than you two.
You can sense other mutants
and their powers?
Could you locate one for me?
Let me out of here.
I demand that you release me.
Do you know who l am?
I'm the President of the United States.
Oh, mr president.
Shut up.
Why are you doing this to me? Let me down.
I'll be a good girl. Please let me go.
Please.
Keep it up. L'll spray
you in the face, bitch.
When I get out of here,
I'm going to kill you myself.
Yeah, right.
Secretary McCoy,
welcome to worthington labs.
Thank you, dr rao.
Not an easy place to get to.
It's the safest location we could find. That's
why we keep the source of the cure here.
He is a mutant.
You understand our concern.
- We are in compliance with your policy.
- How long will you keep the boy here?
Until we can fully map his DNA. We can
replicate it, but we can't generate it.
And his power? What is its range?
You'll see.
Jimmy.
There's someone I would like you to meet.
Hello there, son.
- Hi.
- My name is Hank McCoy.
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
You have an amazing gift.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Extraordinary, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
Scott.
- Can you hear me? L'm still here. Scott.
- Stop.
- I'm here. Scott. Scott.
- Stop it.
- Scott. Scott.
I need you, Scott. Scott. Scott.
Stop!
Jean?
Scott.
How?
I don't know.
I wanna see your eyes.
- Take these off.
- No.
No.
Trust me. L can control it now.
Open them. You can't hurt me.
- What happened?
- No clue.
- Professor, are you ok?
- Get to alkali lake.
- You don't want to be here.
- Do you?
I can't see a damn thing.
I can take care of that.
What the...
Logan!
She's alive.
Jean.
The sheer mass of water that collapsed
on top of Jean should have obliterated her.
The only explanation of Jean's survival
is that her powers wrapped her
in a cocoon of telekinetic energy.
Is she gonna be ok?
Jean grey is the only class five mutant I've
ever encountered, her potential limitless.
Her mutation is seated in the unconscious
part of her mind and therein lay the danger.
When she was a girl,
i created a series of psychic barriers
to isolate her powers
from her conscious mind.
- Jean developed a dual personality.
- What?
The conscious Jean, whose powers were always
in her control, and the dormant side.
A personality that, in our sessions,
came to call itself the Phoenix.
A purely instinctual creature,
all desire and joy and rage.
- She knew all this?
- It's unclear how much she knew.
Far more critical is whether the woman
in front of us is the Jean grey we know,
or the Phoenix furiously struggling
to be free.
- She looks peaceful to me.
- I'm keeping her that way.
I'm trying to restore the psychic blocks
and cage the beast again.
What have you done to her?
- You have to understand...
- You're talking about a person's mind.
- She has to be controlled.
- Controlled?
Sometimes, when you cage the beast,
the beast gets angry.
You have no idea.
You have no idea of what she is capable.
No, professor.
I had no idea what you were capable of.
I had a terrible choice to make.
I chose the lesser of two evils.
It sounds to me like Jean
had no choice at all.
I don't have to explain myself,
least of all to you.
History will be made here today.
For the first time,
the so-called mutant cure
will be available to the public.
Reaction has run the gamut
with mutants on both sides of the line.
Some are desperate for this cure while
others are offended by the very idea of it.
Will secretary McCoy be a problem?
Hard to say. His political views seem
somewhat at odds with his personal issues.
Excuse me, sir. Your son's arrived.
Good. Bring him in.
Are you sure you want to start with him?
I think it's important. Yes.
- Hello, Warren.
- How are you, son?
- Did you sleep well?
- Yeah.
You know, I'm proud of you for doing this.
Everything's gonna be fine. L promise.
You ready?
The transformation can be a little jarring.
- Dad, can we talk about this for a second?
- We've talked about it, son.
It'll all be over soon.
- Everything's going to be fine.
- Wait. L can't do this.
Warren, calm down.
- I can't do this.
- Yes, you can.
- Just relax, son. Take it easy. Calm down.
- I promise you it will be fine. Warren, relax.
- Dad.
Warren, it's a better life.
- It's what we all want.
- No.
It's what you want.
Warren, no!
Told you so.
About time.
I've been busy.
Did you find what you were looking for?
The source of the cure is a mutant.
A child at worthington labs.
Without him, they have nothing.
Read off the guest list.
"Cell 41 205. James madrox."
This one robbed seven banks.
- At the same time.
- I could use a man of your talents.
- I'm in.
- Welcome to the brotherhood.
- Careful with this one.
- "Cain Marko. Solitary confinement."
Check this out.
"Prisoner must be confined at all times."
"If he builds any momentum,
no object can stop him."
How fascinating.
- What do they call you?
- Juggernaut.
- I can't imagine why.
- Are you going to let me out? L need a pee.
- Nice helmet.
- Keeps my face pretty.
I think he'll make a fine addition
to our army.
No!
You saved me.
Eric.
I'm sorry, my dear.
You're not one of us any more.
Such a shame. She was so beautiful.
Think resigning will make a difference?
That's no way to influence policy.
Policy is being made without me,
mr president.
The decision to turn the cure into a weapon
was made without me.
What happened on that convoy
was inexcusable. But your actions...
That was an isolated incident.
You have to understand
those mutants were a real threat.
Have you even begun to think
what a slippery slope you're on?
I have.
And l worry about how democracy survives
when one man can move cities
with his mind.
As do l.
You and I know
that it's only going to get worse.
All the more reason
why l need to be where l belong.
Jean.
- Hi, Logan.
- Welcome back.
Back where we first met. Only l was
in your place and you were in mine.
Are you ok?
Yeah.
More than ok.
Logan, you're making me blush.
- You're reading my thoughts?
- I don't have to.
It's ok.
- Wait.
- No.
Jean.
- This isn't you.
- Yes, it is me.
No. Maybe you ought to take it easy.
The professor said you might be different.
He would know, wouldn't he?
What? You think he's not in your head too?
Look at you, Logan. He's tamed you.
Where's Scott?
Jean?
- Where am I?
- You're in the mansion.
You need to tell me
what happened to Scott.
Jean, tell me what happened to him.
Oh, god.
Look at me.
Stay with me. Talk to me.
- Look at me. Look at me.
- No.
Focus. Focus, Jean.
Kill me.
- What?
- Kill me before l kill someone else.
- Don't say that.
- Please.
- Stop it.
- Kill me.
Stop it. Look at me. Look at me. Jean.
It'll be all right. We can help you.
Hey. The professor can help. He can fix it.
I don't want to fix it.
Voluntary? They put the cure in a gun.
I told you they would draw first blood.
- So what do we do?
- What do we do?
We use this weapon as a lightning rod
to bring countless more to our cause.
Come. We have an army to build.
I picked something up.
An electromagnetic force. Lt's massive.
It's a mutant.
Class five.
More powerful than anything I've ever felt.
More powerful than you.
Where is she?
Logan.
- Jean. Jean.
- What happened?
What have you done?
- I think she killed Scott.
- What?
- That's not possible.
- I warned you.
She's left the mansion, but she's trying
to block my thoughts. She's so strong.
It may be too late.
- Wait for me here.
- What?
I need to see Jean alone.
You were right, Charles.
- This one is special.
- What the hell are you doing here?
Same as the professor.
Visiting an old friend.
- I don't want trouble here.
- Nor do l.
So, shall we go inside?
I came to bring Jean home. Don't interfere.
- Just like old times, eh?
- She needs help. Jean is not well.
Funny, you sound just like her parents.
Nobody gets inside.
- I knew you'd come.
- Of course. I've come to bring you home.
- L have no home.
- Yes, you do.
You have a home and a family.
You know he thinks your power
is too great for you to control.
I don't believe your mind games
are going to work any more, Charles.
- So you want to control me?
- He does.
No. I want to help you.
Help me? What's wrong with me?
- Absolutely nothing.
- Eric, stop.
No, Charles, not this time.
You've always held her back.
For your own good, Jean.
Stay out of my head.
- I'm going in.
- The professor said he'd handle this.
Look at me, Jean. L can help you.
Look at me.
Get out of my head.
- Perhaps you should listen to her, Charles.
- Trust me. You're a danger to everyone.
- But l can help you.
- I think you want to give her the cure.
Look at Scott. You killed the man you loved
because you couldn't control your power.
No! Stop it!
That's it.
Jean, let me in.
No, Jean.
Jean!
Don't let it control you.
Charles.
My dear. Come with me.
No.
God!
We live in an age of darkness.
A world full of fear, hate and intolerance.
But in every age,
there are those who fight against it.
Charles Xavier was born to a world divided.
A world he tried to heal.
A mission he never saw accomplished.
It seems the destiny of great men
to see their goals unfulfilled.
Charles was more than a leader,
more than a teacher. He was a friend.
When we were afraid, he gave us strength.
And when we were alone,
he gave us a family.
He may be gone, but his teachings
live on through us, his students.
Wherever we may go,
we must carry on his vision.
And that's a vision of a world united.
Kitty.
Bobby.
- You ok?
- Yeah.
It's just... Xavier came to my house.
He was the one that convinced me
to come here.
Yeah, me too.
- We're all feeling the same way, you know.
- No, Bobby, we're not.
You have rogue and l have...
You know, I just miss home.
The first snow and all that.
- Kitty, get up. Come with me.
- Storm told us to stay in our rooms.
Don't worry. We won't get caught.
I mean, you can
walk through walls, you know.
Come on.
This place can be home too.
Thank you for this, Bobby.
You need a lift, kid?
No.
Where are you going?
You don't know what it's like
to be afraid of your powers,
afraid to get close to anybody.
Yeah, l do.
I want to be able to touch people, Logan.
A hug. A handshake.
A kiss.
I hope you're not doing this for some boy.
Look, if you wanna go, then go.
Just be sure it's what you want.
Shouldn't you be telling me to stay?
To go upstairs and unpack?
I'm not your father. L'm your friend.
Just think about what l said, rogue.
Marie.
Remember when we first met? Do you know
what I saw when l looked at you?
I saw the next stage in evolution
both Charles and l dreamt of finding.
And l thought to myself,
"why would Charles
want to turn this goddess into a mortal?"
I can manipulate the metal in this,
but you, you can do anything.
Anything you can think of.
Jean.
Enough.
You sound just like him.
Jean, he wanted to hold you back.
- What do you want?
- I want you to be what you are.
As nature intended.
That cure is meant for all of us.
If we want freedom, we must fight for it.
And that fight begins now.
She shouldn't be here with us.
- Her power is completely unstable.
- Only in the wrong hands.
- And you trust her? She's one of them.
- So were you once.
I stuck with you. Would have killed
the professor if you'd given me the chance.
Charles Xavier did more for mutants
than you'll ever know.
My single greatest regret is that he
had to die for our dream to live.
So what now? What do we do?
Xavier started this school.
Perhaps it's best that it end with him.
- We'll tell the students they're going home.
- Most of us don't have anywhere to go.
I can't believe this. L can't believe
we're not going to fight for this school.
I'm sorry. I know this is a bad time.
I was told that this was
a safe place for mutants.
It was, son.
And it still is. We'll find you a room.
Hank, tell all the students
the school stays open.
Rogue.
Hey, rogue.
- Hey, Pete. Have you seen rogue?
- Yeah, she took off.
Logan.
- Logan.
- Jean?
Logan. Where am l? Logan.
Logan. Logan.
- Logan.
- Stop.
Logan. Logan. Logan.
- Where are you going?
- Where do you think?
- She's gone, Logan. She's not coming back.
- You don't know that.
She killed the professor.
It wasn't Jean.
The Jean I know is still in there.
Listen, why can't you see the truth?
Why can't you just let her go?
Because you love her.
She made her choice.
Now it's time we make ours.
So if you're with us, then be with us.
We don't need a cure!
Getting the cure so you can go back home
to mommy and daddy?
I'm looking for someone.
Oh, l get it. Your girlfriend.
I figured she'd want the cure.
She's pathetic.
Come on, lceman.
Make a move.
Same old Bobby. Still afraid of a fight.
Today's attack was only our first salvo.
So long as the cure exists,
our war will rage.
Your cities will not be safe. Your streets
will not be safe. You will not be safe.
And to my fellow mutants,
i make you this offer...
Join us or stay out of our way.
Enough mutant blood
has been spilled already.
We're trying to track them, sir.
We're working hard.
- We cannot let him do this.
- You know l agree, sir.
This is now a national security matter.
Seize and secure worthington labs.
I want troops armed with cure weapons
deployed immediately.
And trask, you have to find Magneto
and stop him by any means necessary.
Magneto wants a war. We'll give him one.
Let's go. Keep it moving.
Turn in your old weapon. Turn in all metal.
Bayonets, magazines, dog tags.
Pick up your plastic weapons.
Pick up your cure cartridge.
Absolutely no metal.
We don't need a cure!
They wish to cure us.
But l say to you we are the cure.
The cure for that infirm, imperfect
condition called homo sapiens.
They have their weapons.
We have ours.
We will strike with a vengeance and a fury
that this world has never witnessed.
And if any mutants stand in our way,
we will use this poison against them.
We shall go to Alcatraz lsland,
take control of the cure,
and destroy its source.
And then nothing can stop us.
Jean.
I know the smell of your adamantium
from a mile away.
- I didn't come here to fight you.
- Smart boy.
- I came for Jean.
- You think I'm keeping her against her will?
- She's here because she wants to be.
- You don't know what you're dealing with.
I know full well.
I saw what she did to Charles.
And you stood there and let him die?
- I'm not leaving here without her.
- Yes, you are.
Ok.
Two minutes till rendezvous, mr president.
We have a satellite feed
of Magneto's base of operations.
- How did we find it?
- She gave us everything we wanted.
Hell hath no fury like a woman scorned.
Approaching target dead ahead.
Set for 360-degree incursion.
This is team leader to bravo one.
We are green to go.
Ok, send them in.
Ok.
Freeze, mutants! Get your hands in the air!
Hands in the air!
Ok. I give up.
Sorry, mr secretary, it was a decoy.
If he's not there, then
where the hell is he?
Worthington labs. Lt ends where it began.
- Are you sure the boy is still inside?
- 1 00%.
So how are we supposed to get there?
Cos l don't swim.
Leave that to me.
Storm. Storm.
What are you doing back here?
I need help.
- You found her.
- Yeah. She's with Magneto.
- Where are they?
- On the move. I know where they're going.
- You're saying you saw Magneto?
- We gotta go.
They're gonna attack Alcatraz.
- There are troops stationed on that island.
- Not enough to stop him.
Let's suit up.
Hard to believe this once fit me.
If Magneto gets that cure,
we can't stop him.
- Can you estimate how many he has?
- An army. And Jean.
- His powers have limits, hers do not.
- There's only six of us, Logan.
Yeah. We're outnumbered.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
But we lost Scott.
We lost the professor.
If we don't fight now, everything
they stood for will die with them.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Are you?
Then we stand together.
X-Men.
All of us.
We're in.
Let's go.
- They're ready.
- Yeah, I know.
But are you ready to do what
you need to do when the time comes?
Dad, what's going on?
It's an earthquake.
We're trapped.
Charles always wanted to build Bridges.
My god.
Fall back! Take cover! Fall back!
The boy's in the southeast corner
of the building.
- Well, then.
- Let's take it down!
In chess, the pawns go first.
Humans and their guns.
Plastic. They've learned.
That's why the pawns go first.
Target the bridge.
Fire!
Arclight, use your shockwaves.
Target those weapons.
- Oh, my stars and garters.
- Go into stealth mode.
- What about jets? Tanks?
- Against Magneto? He'll turn them inside out.
- Where are our ground troops?
- 30 minutes away.
Then god help us.
They're coming for him.
Don't ever do that again.
You men cover the doors!
Everybody get together! And hold this line!
Traitors to their own cause.
Finish them!
Not yet.
Go inside and get the boy. And kill him.
With pleasure.
Hold it!
He's going for the boy!
Not if l get there first.
Kitty!
Come on.
Grow those back.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm the juggernaut, bitch.
Going somewhere?
You're the guy that invented the cure,
right?
Yes, l am.
Girls.
No. Don't. Don't hurt him.
- No. Don't hurt him.
- Let go of me. L didn't do anything.
Calm down. Calm down.
Everything's gonna be ok.
- I thought you were a diplomat.
- As Churchill said, "there comes a time..."
Oh, you get the point.
Oh, no. Please, no, no, don't.
No.
No, don't worry. L'm here to help you.
I'm going to get you out of here.
This way.
- Oh, my god. What's going on?
- Your powers won't work with me.
- Stay close, all right?
- Ok.
I'm the wrong guy
to play hide-and-seek with.
Who's hiding, dickhead?
Don't. No.
Don't.
Please, don't do this.
I only wanted to help you people.
Do we look like we need your help?
It's time to end this war.
Take cover.
Get out of the way.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Move.
Go! Go! Go!
We work as a team.
Best defense is a good offense.
Bobby, think you can take out
your old friend?
Go ahead.
Storm, we're gonna need some cover.
Right.
You're in over your head, Bobby.
Maybe you should go back to school.
You never should have left.
This is it.
Hey.
Make it a strike.
You never learn, do you?
Actually, I do.
I'm...
One of them?
This is what they want for all of us.
It's over, Jean.
It's over.
No! Don't shoot!
No!
Everybody get out of there!
Bobby!
What have l done?
I'm the only one who can stop her.
Get everyone to safety.
Go.
Jean!
I know you're still there!
You would die for them?
No, not for them.
For you.
Save me.
I love you.
You're back.
I'm sorry.
I had to.
- This isn't what I wanted.
- I know.
It's what I want.
Hey.
Good to see you, buddy.
With the thanks of a grateful nation
I introduce our new ambassador
to the united nations,
and the representative to the world
for all United States citizens,
human and mutant alike,
dr Hank McCoy.
Way to go, fur ball.
Morning.
Hello, moira.