So this must be strange to you.
Not really.
Been awhile, but my dad taught me
to play when I was a kid.
Actually, I was talking about
you being here, with us.
I got what I wanted.
It's been a long time
since I had anybody
with a little skill
to play against.
I don't suppose
there's anything I could do
to convince you to stick around?
Relax Jack. Just an idle question.
We have a deal, I fully intend
to honor it.
Intend to, or you will?
Well, it's not entirely up to me.
If the island doesn't want you
to leave, it won't let you.
What, the...
The island's gonna sink the sub?
No. No.
I promise you, I won't do anything
to prevent you from getting home.
But if you do leave this place, the
day may come when you want to return.
Never.
I've learned never to say never.
And if that day comes, I hope
you remember this conversation.
It was a nice try though.