What's all this about moving from
the beaches, going to the caves?
Are you guys going to the caves?
They don't speak English, dude.
Oh. How about, are you going?
I don't know what you're
talking about, man.
I'm talking about the caves. Are
you gonna go to the caves?
Jack and that bald guy,
and, uh, what's-her-face,
they found some caves,
and they think
that actually we should move
from the beaches to the caves.
So, why shouldn't we?
Why sh...
Ok, A - number 1, moisture. Caves
are abounded with moisture.
Moisture breeds bacteria,
and attracts insects
that would lay eggs
in our mouths while we sleep.
I know that you don't understand me,
but if there is a vote
to go to the caves,
you two, you vote no!
Got it? No!
Hey, shouting at them is not going
to make them understand any more.
Dude, if Jack says
it's a good idea,
maybe we should,
like, trust him.
Why? You tell me.
Because he's a doctor?
Is that what qualifies him
for a leadership here?
How do we know
he's not a mental case?
Let me tell you something.
The other day I'm in the jungle,
and I'm taking a leak,
and Jack runs through the jungle,
crying for his Daddy.
Ok, fine, fine, you morons, you want
to go to the caves, good riddance.
I'm going to stay right here,
on the beach,
with all the people
who want to survive.
I'll, uh...
I'll see you guys at the caves.