Mummy!
Mummy! Mummy!
Yes? Where's Daddy?
- He's gone.
- What happened?
I don't know.
Danny!
I saw your car pulling in.
Are you trying to give
yourself a heart attack, or me?
New regime...two miles a day.
You need your head
examined and a cup of tea!
One of those I can do.
OK, you're on!
I'll get the tea later.
Good grief, it's Jimmy Saville!
- Tea, thank you, Jason.
- Herbal, or...?
Like builder's, two
sugars, as it 'appens!
There's nothing for you there.
Reported this morning, a woman whose husband
disappeared from the park on Downs Way.
One minute he's by the
swings with his daughter
- and the next minute, gone!
- Alien abduction!
I like it!
The daughter's eight years
old. She must be terrified.
Right, come on, Jason.
MJ,
the clinic got back to me.
This is the address they have for Ellen.
- Right.
- It's not far from here.
- I could buzz round there, check it out.
- No.
It's a bit out of the blue.
It has been a few years, MJ. It's
more than certain she's moved on.
All right. See if anyone can remember.
Hey, are you free tonight,
dinner after the show, my shout?
Mmm... missus out, is she?
Well, you know what she's like...
she doesn't go for exotic cuisine.
Exotic! You're on, mate!
An address for Ellen?!
You're getting close.
Too close. It's making MJ nervous.
Maybe I should have listened to
her and let the whole thing go.
It's not easy for her.
It runs pretty deep.
But she's relying on
you more than you think.
Maybe just let her set the pace.
Yeah, I will, thanks.
Right, last one down the
greasy spoon's a girl!
It's totally out of character.
He'd never leave Jess at
the park and just drive off.
Did he take anything... money, passport?
No, I've checked our bank account
online. It hasn't been touched.
And he didn't say anything, give
any hints something was wrong?
Jess saw something when he disappeared.
A man chasing Paul.
- No, Mum. Dad was chasing him!
- OK.
So what did he look like?
- I don't know, just a man.
- You go and play.
Thanks, Jess.
- Do you have any idea who it might be?
- Paul's a divorce solicitor.
One of his clients lost custody
of his kids, and blamed Paul.
What did he do?
Rang the house a few times,
threatening and abusive.
- He was drunk, of course.
- Was it just phone calls?
Paul saw someone a few
nights ago watching the house.
It was too dark to tell if it was him.
I'd like to check your phone accounts,
see where the calls are coming from.
- I need your permission to do that.
- Of course.
Look, Paul and I, we're very happy.
We've a holiday booked, in Mexico,
the three of us. He wouldn't...
Something's wrong, I know it.
Welcome back.
Been anywhere nice?
No, unless your idea of
nice is a student kitchen!
Ellen's place?
Not been for years.
I'm guessing the students
didn't have a forwarding address?
Better, much better.
Wonderful things, fridge magnets.
You found Ellen's mobile number?
- Have you ever thought of joining the police?
- I'm over-qualified!
Be careful with this.
- It's all right. I've written it down.
- No, I meant with MJ.
She can't make contact till
we've spoken to Ellen first.
Is that Cassie's phone list?
Yeah, I've been through it with her and this number
matches up with the times of the abusive calls.
It's registered to a Gary Nayland.
- Have you rung it?
- No answer.
Try the ex-wife, see if you
can find out where he is.
Has she identified any other numbers?
Apart from this one. I'm
trying to get a location for it.
OK, let me know.
One for you, Amy.
A woman called Layla Gudka.
I'm trying to find her father. She
hasn't seen him for over 20 years.
OK, I'll give her a call.
How did you get on at the house?
It's like I thought...
Ellen has long gone.
OK.
Oh, but...
she did leave this.
It's a phone number...her mobile.
- Have you tried it?
- No.
Thanks, Amy. Good work.
- What are you doing?
- What was I supposed to do?
She shouldn't have that number.
- It's Ellen decision whether she wants contact.
- Well, go on, then. Go and get it back.
Yes, you see it's not so easy, is it?
- She won't ring it.
- Of course she won't.
She knows the protocol but than anyone.
Hello, Mrs. Nayland?
My name is DC Doyle, I'm with
the Dover Missing Persons Unit.
We're trying to locate your ex-husband.
He seems to have gone off the radar.
Right, I see.
Did he?
OK. Well, thanks a lot.
Sorry to disturb you.
- Go on.
- Ibiza,
Ibiza, with his new tart, trying
to kid himself he's still 21!
Hello. Can I help at all?
I'm looking for Amy Garnett.
Hi, you must be Layla? I'm Amy.
If you'd like to take a seat.
So, when did you last see your father?
I lost contact with my
parents when I was 17.
Did they move away?
No, I left home.
I wanted to go to university,
but my father opposed it.
Can I ask why?
He's very traditional.
Doesn't think us women
should use our brains.
And how did your mother feel about that?
- She was very traditional, too.
- Was?
She died ten years ago.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please go on.
I was offered a place at Edinburgh.
The day before term started I packed my
bags, told my dad I was going and left.
That must have made him angry.
I've no idea.
I never spoke to him again.
So why now, Layla?
I work for a large charity,
been based in Geneva for years.
I've been posted back here again so I
thought now is the time to get in touch.
- So you've been trying to find him?
- For weeks.
I've tried everything you can think
of, but it's like he never existed.
Well, don't worry, we'll find him.
I hope so.
- Nayland's in Ibiza.
- Who?
Gary Nayland.
I just had a chat with his ex.
He's out the country, so it
can't have been him that Jess saw.
- Well, we've only got the ex's word for that.
- Believe me, she's not giving him an alibi!
What about that unidentified number?
Have you got a trace on that yet?
Yeah, it's a payphone at a
bail hostel in Medway Street.
- Bail hostel?
- It could be another ex-client.
The Probation Service are
sending me a list of residents.
Whoever it was only
spoke for 18 seconds.
- And Paul's car, has that shown up, yet?
- No, still no sign of it.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, fine, thank you.
I'll be in touch as soon as
I've done the basic searches.
If you would.
She's a right little
charmer, isn't she?!
Yeah. I bet her dad can't
wait to see her again!
Sarge, how many Garrisons do
you reckon there are in Dover?
Not many, why?
The bail hostel have just sent
me over a list of residents.
Room six, Jamie Garrison, released
from Strangeways last Wednesday.
Let's see if Cassie knows anything.
Jamie? Jamie is in Dover?
He's Paul's brother.
He called your house last
week. Paul didn't mention it?
No, no, he didn't.
And you don't think they'd been
in touch at all before that?
No way. They didn't get on.
Why now?
Jamie has just been
released from prison.
What? What for? What did he do?
Handling counterfeit goods.
When was the last time Paul saw him?
June the 8th, 2000... the
day Paul and I got married.
Right.
He had a problem with that, did he?
He was always jealous...
of Paul's career, success, happiness,
and then the big church wedding.
What did he do?
He turned up drunk, shouting at
Paul, sneering at his cosy life.
It was just so awful. Jamie always liked
to think of himself as a bit of rebel.
I suppose he was looking for a fight.
And he got one, did he?
Yes.
And that was the last
time they saw each other?
Yes.
He's agreed to come in and talk to
us, so hopefully we'll know more soon.
Cheer up!
I've done all the basic
searches and drawn a blank.
No mention of Layla's father anywhere.
Have you tried the Register Of Deaths?
He's not there, either. The house was rented
and it's changed hands three times since.
The trail is nearly as cold as she is.
Jason seems to think she's nice!
Yeah, and did he have drool
dribbling down his chin at the time?
Mmm, can't help himself!
Did you find out where
Layla's father worked?
The Council, I think.
Bureaucrats! I love bureaucrats!
They keep records of everything.
I bet they've got a file as
thick as that with his name on.
It's worth a try.
Sarge.
Mr. Garrison.
Can I get you a coffee?
Yeah, nice one. Got any croissants?
- Handbags.
- Counterfeit were they?
Well, I didn't know they were dodgy
but you try telling a magistrate that.
They gave me a year.
- And what did you do, six months?
- Yeah, good behaviour.
And you came back to
Dover, when, last week?
They put me in that hostel.
I've got to get out of there.
It's worse than prison.
And that's why you phoned your brother?
I haven't seen him for years.
We've all grown up a bit now.
I thought it was time to...
you know, extend the hand of friendship.
- And how did that go down?
- Just like the phone.
You can't be surprised,
not after the wedding?
You been talking to Cassie?
Of course.
What else did she tell you?
She told us that she last saw
Paul on the Sunday afternoon
when he took Jess to the park.
- Did you see him that day?
- No.
If you want an alibi,
ask anyone at the hostel.
- Reliable witnesses, are they?
- They've done their time, like me.
Well, thanks for coming in, Jamie.
Sorry about the croissants.
I'll get someone to show you out.
If you see Cassie and Jess,
give them my best.
Now just say
if any of these men look
like the man you saw, OK?
Yeah.
Mum...
I think, I think it was him.
Sweetheart, you go upstairs.
Do you want me to go?
What's going on?
What did Jamie say
when you spoke to him?
- Where's Paul?
- You can't stop me!
- Jamie!
- I came to see if you are OK.
Jamie, what the hell is
going on? Where's Paul?
Have you told them everything, Cass?
You haven't, have you?
My little girl saw you.
What have you done to him?
Do you know what's happened, Jamie, or do you
want to do this in front of your Probation Officer?
- Legenda não traduzida -
He attacked me, Cass. Do you know why?
- Because I told him about us.
- Stop it!
No...
I think we may want to hear this.
Yeah, Cassie.
These people need to know about
you seeing me behind Paul's back.
Cassie?
Eight years ago...
eight years.
Hang on. How old is Jess now?
- Jamie, come on...no.
- Don't worry.
Paul knows. I told him.
Why don't we have another little
chat down at the station, Jamie?
Is it true?
You were sleeping with Paul's brother?
You should have told us.
He knows.
Paul knows about Jess.
Sunday it was.
He was in the park, at the swings.
Sees me in the distance,
comes running up to me.
What happened?
He was livid.
Drags me away so Jess can't see.
Tells me he doesn't want me
anywhere near him or his family.
You did sleep with his fiancee, Jamie.
Yeah, that's what I told him.
- Why did you do that?
- Someone had to.
Cassie obviously wasn't going to.
Were you that jealous of his life?
His life was built on a lie.
That little girl that he
was trying to protect from me
- is my own daughter!
- Then what happened?
He went mad, lashed out at me.
You look all right to me.
I've been in prison, OK.
Someone is coming at you, you react.
What did you do?
- I hit him and he fell.
- Then what?
- Jamie!
- I ran!
Come on, I'm on probation.
It doesn't look good, does it?
So you've no idea where he went after?
None...
I swear to God.
We'll contact the hostel if
we need to speak to you again.
Paul didn't just happen to see
you in the park did he, Jamie?
Why were you really there?
She's my daughter.
I just...
I wanted to get a look
at her, that's all.
Find anything useful on Layla's father?
Layla's dad was the life
and soul of the office.
He organised the family party at work
and the annual summer outing for the kids.
Very sweet, but not very helpful.
No, but this is.
He names his wife Chandra as
beneficiary in his pension.
- Why wouldn't he?
- Because it's dated 2002.
Layla told me she died in 1999.
Do you think it might be fraud?
It might explain why he's
so hard to track down.
Run it past Layla.
Maybe she hasn't told you
everything about her father.
- Right, see you in the morning.
- Night.
- Sarge?
- Before you ask, I'm already spoken for.
Danny's buying me dinner.
No...it wasn't that.
The phone number for Ellen.
- What about it?
- You called it, didn't you?
It was off. I didn't leave a message.
If she'd answered it...
Imagine if it was me.
You wouldn't have let it go.
Thank you for your concern, DC Doyle.
Ellen, it's...
Hurry up! I'm starving!
I'm sure it is good for me,
but macrobiotic vegan is not my idea
of an exotic cuisine, that's all.
Does amazing things for
your digestive tract.
Too much information!
So Amy actually found
Ellen's mobile number?
- I wish she hadn't!
- Well, why not?
You've come this far.
Maybe I've come far enough.
From now on it gets complicated.
It's already complicated, MJ.
Once you realised there
was a chance of finding her,
you knew you'd have to see it through.
Jason's right.
I can't use the number, anyway.
It's against everything I believe in.
That's just an excuse.
Your team deal with this
stuff every day. Use them.
Let them treat you the
same as every other case.
But I'm not the same
as every other case.
I know you'll do the right thing.
Macrobiotic vegan!
I'm sorry... I shouldn't have
taken Ellen's phone number.
It's OK.
It's just hard to stand back.
Why don't you just carry on and
let me know what turns up?
- Are you sure?
- Sim.
It's just that I'm
running out of options, MJ.
All I can do is get onto
Ellen's phone service provider
and find out who she
has been in contact with.
If that's what you'd normally do next.
It isn't... not without the person's
consent, unless it was life or death.
- Legenda não traduzida -
Ellen has a history of
drug abuse. She could...
Sorry.
Just do what you think is best, OK?
It's Paul Garrison. He's been
to the school and taken Jess.
Get straight over there. Get
times, witnesses, the lot.
Amy, try and get number plate
recognition for Paul's car in that area.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah...just discussing the case.
Traffic, please. This
is Missing Persons.
I'm sorry, is this a bad moment?
So my mum was named as
beneficiary in Dad's pension plan?
- OK.
- In 2002...
seven years ago. She had to
have been alive at the time.
Yes.
Layla, you told me your
mother died ten years ago.
Did I say that?
Well, I've been out of the country.
I mean, I suppose if it says
it here it must have been.
So how did you know
she had passed away...
if you'd had no contact?
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Layla!
Layla, wait!
Cassie... He took her!
He just walked into
the school and took her.
It's all right. We've got people at the school and
every available officer is out looking for the car.
It was an hour ago. They
could be anywhere by now.
I'm sorry, I've got to ask you this.
Has Paul ever harmed Jess?
No.
But now that he knows she's not his,
what's he going to do?
Maybe he thinks he's going to lose her.
- But he's not!
- It's Jason,
he's at the school. Jess has returned.
- Is she OK?
- Yeah, she's fine.
Jason...
any sign of Paul?
OK. Bring Jess here.
We went to the cafe and had ice cream. It
was brilliant. And was your dad all right?
I think so. What did he say, sweetheart?
Just he was really sorry
for leaving me at the park.
He took masses of photos on his phone.
He said he loves me loads and
loads and gave me a big hug.
MOBILE RINGS
I'd better...
Did your dad say anything
about where he was going, Jess?
Going? Is he going somewhere?
That was Paul's law firm.
He's just resigned.
Layla shed any light on
her dad's pension scam?
It's not a scam. Layla's lying.
Are you sure?
She told me her mother
died ten years ago.
I checked, and her death
is not registered...
but guess where I did find her?
Surprise me.
Right here on our system.
She reported a missing
person back in 1992...
her daughter, Layla.
You're kidding me!
Two missing persons
looking for each other.
- That's a first.
- I don't know what to do,
cos Layla has been lying
to us about her mother.
Is she on the run for some reason?
If she was, we're the
last place she'd come to.
Don't say anything to her. Try
and locate the mother first.
She's got a right to know her
daughter is alive and well.
Cassie has agreed to go on Danny's show.
- What's Paul up to?
- Clearing the decks...
one thing at a time.
Leaving his job, saying goodbye to Jess.
And what's his last move, suicide?
It's possible,
that's why we've got to
try and find him first,
before he does anything stupid.
I still reckon he's high risk.
Let's hope he doesn't
involve the kid again!
He's a missing person, Jason.
It's our job to find him.
We don't judge, ever.
You rang, m'lady?
All right...maybe sometimes we do.
Come on.
Hypothetical question...
My favourite kind.
You've hit a dead end and all
you've got is a phone number.
- Is this?
- Hypothetical, I said.
OK.
Ok, get onto the phone company.
Get the numbers they called.
But they're not in any immediate
danger that you know of.
That kind of hypothetical question...
should I tell the phone
company a little white lie?
What would you do?
An amoral pig like me?
I'd do it in a flash, but
you're not me, are you, Amy,
and I don't think you want to be.
Hello, Customer Relations?
I'm ringing from Dover Police
regarding a mobile number
of a missing person.
Her name is Ellen Croft.
That's a great story...
adultery, violence, child abduction.
It ticks all my listeners' boxes!
You can't go into any of
that... just the live appeal.
- Is she up for it?
- Yeah.
Thinks it's a great idea.
- Apparently Paul listens to your show.
- Fantastic!
My first missing listener!
She says he throws things at the radio.
Well, at least it's a reaction.
No trace on Layla's mother.
Her last registered address
is the one Layla gave us,
but those cuttings might help.
A journalist on the local
paper took up the story,
ran a series of articles
over the yars, you know,
mother still searching for the
daughter she'll never see grow up,
that sort of thing.
Let's have a look.
Oh, yeah, Stella Stiles.
Do you know her?
She was a bit of a
legend on The Courier.
She had a steamy affair
with a junior reporter.
And would this junior reporter still
happen to have her phone number?
I'll see what I can do.
I've been joined in the
studio by Cassie Garrison
whose husband, Paul, has
been reported missing...
- How's Jess?
- Asleep at my sister's.
She thinks all of this
is a great adventure.
He was punishing me for
what happened with Jamie.
Cass, if Paul is listening, what
would you like to say to him?
Paul, please, please come back to us.
I know some terrible
things have happened,
but if we could just talk.
We love you, Paul.
We miss you.
Stay safe, keep warm,
come home.
Paul Garrison.
If anybody thinks they
know where Paul is tonight,
get in contact on the usual number.
I appreciate that you
are trying to help,
but I do not want police
resources to be wasted on me.
All I ask is that you make sure
Cassie gets my wedding ring.
With thanks, Paul Garrison.
Well, at least he's polite!
- Is that it?
- Yep.
Dropped it off at the radio station
last night. Danny gave me this for you.
Apparently he had to buy Stella Stiles a
couple of pints of Chardonnay to get that!
I'm sure he coped!
"Confined to a nursing home and
suffering from Parkinson's Disease,
"Chandra Gudka fears she may never
see her long-lost daughter again."
Any mention of her father?
None that I can see.
Oh, but they do have an
address for the home, here.
OK, get onto them.
See if she is still there.
I'd better get this back to Cassie.
This is really going to make her day!
Morning!
- OK, it's not what it seems.
- No?
Why should it be? Nothing
else is around here.
Listen, I've just checked
our bank account online.
Paul has taken some money
out, ten minutes ago.
He's in Westbourne.
Westbourne, it's only a few
minutes from here. On my way.
What do you expect me to think, Cassie?
He came round last night
to talk, to explain.
I'm not a fool, DS Croft.
- And where's Jess?
- She's still at my sister's.
And did he say anything worth hearing?
He told me he got in
touch with Paul last year
when he needed a solicitor.
Paul has friends,
contacts that could have helped him,
kept him out of prison,
but Paul refused.
- And Paul didn't tell you any of that?
- Of course not.
Come on, he must have
felt pretty guilty.
Jason?
I've found his car.
No sign of Paul.
OK, stay close, keep out of
sight, don't scare him off.
Might be too late for
that... Paul Garrison?
DC Doyle, Dover Missing
Persons Unit... Paul!
I just wanna talk, mate.
He ran off.
Sarge, I've got his satnav.
The last two journeys were to
and from a place called Sandford.
- Sandford...does that mean anything to you?
- St Mary's Church, it's where we got married.
Jason, get straight over there.
You want St Mary's Church.
Your mother's alive.
She's in a nursing home.
I spoke to them this morning.
Do they have any
information on my father?
No, but they...
I'm sorry, but you
thought your mum was dead!
- Don't you care that she isn't?
- This isn't about her.
She reported you missing.
She spent years searching
for you, so did this unit.
I just want to know where
my father is. That's all.
Well, fine. The best thing
I can do is talk to her.
No! Don't.
Layla, I have to! This
is still an open file.
I have a duty to inform
her that you've been found.
I don't want her to know where I am.
Fine. Then I won't breathe a word.
He's in the church.
All right. Wait here.
Paul?
Paul, I am DS Croft,
Missing Persons Unit.
I told you not to waste your time.
I'm only doing my job.
Cassie, no!
- Let me talk to him!
- No!
It has to be his decision.
Lovely, isn't it?
So peaceful.
I know what you're doing, Paul.
Quitting your job,
giving your wedding ring back.
It's easy...
getting everything
sorted out like that...
but taking that last step...
that's the hard bit.
I've made my decision.
I don't want to see Cassie again.
Cassie, no!
Paul!
- Cassie, outside.
- Paul, please...
Is it true about Jess?
Is she Jamie's?
Yes.
It was right here, do you remember?
You made your vows.
What was going through
your mind, Cassie?
That I loved you. That
I'd made the right choice.
I didn't even know there
was a choice to make.
I was young, Paul.
All that angry rebel stuff,
it was sexy
and you were always
working, always studying.
Qualifying, it's called.
I was getting married. I wanted
to give my family a stable future.
I've only got myself to blame, then.
I chose you.
You won.
I won?
I won? Jess isn't even my
daughter and you think I won!
Why do you think I didn't tell you?
Oh, gee, let me think.
- Because you were ashamed?
- I was...
I still am.
- I wanted to tell you.
- So why didn't you?
Because it would have destroyed us.
It's destroying us now.
But we love each other more than that.
Do we?
You were sleeping with him,
what, right up to the wedding?
Was it?
- Yes.
- No wonder he turned up
drunk, shooting his mouth off.
It was our wedding! That's
how much you loved me!
Jamie wasn't love, Paul.
I was a stupid, young girl wanting
everything in the sweet shop,
but I never loved him.
I only ever felt like that about you.
Maybe you should give
him a second chance.
You might be able to love him this time.
He might even be a brilliant dad.
Oh, please don't.
Let Jess have a
relationship with her real
- father.
- No!
I'm sorry, Cass, I can't do it.
I love you...
but I can't.
Paul!
You're ready are you, Paul?
To take that last step?
To never see your daughter again?
She's not my daughter.
No?
Who does she think her father is?
Have you asked yourself that?
You walk out that door
now, you'll feel great.
Everyone betrayed you but you've
walked away with your head held high.
But tomorrow,
when the doubts creep in...
it's hell, Paul.
Trust me, I know.
I didn't have a chance to give her this.
Jason.
I saw your mother, Layla.
She's very sick.
She'd really love to see you.
Does she have any news about my father?
Yes, she did.
He...
He died.
Four years ago, in India.
I'm really, really sorry.
He's really dead? Are you sure?
Yes.
What do you think is going on in there?
Well, I can't hear the tinkling
of stained glass breaking,
so that's a good sign.
The things you were saying
about doubts creeping in...
Did you mean Ellen?
It's just experience talking.
Are you OK, Cassie?
I'm just calling my sister,
let her know it's OK to bring Jess home.
We're going to talk.
I'd like to see Jamie.
You go home, and I'll bring him over.
When my father put on these parties,
he was happy, genuinely happy.
It was clearly his passion.
Oh, yes...
But it was a clever disguise.
The truth is, he was vicious.
He would beat my mum for anything...
spilt water, creased shirts...
sometimes for nothing,
just to remind her.
- Couldn't you do anything?
- If I tried, he'd beat me.
I wasn't going to stay.
I studied, passed my
exams, all in secret.
He would never have let me do that.
- Because it meant freedom?
- Exactly.
I only made one mistake.
I came home
and there he was,
the letter with my exam
results in one hand...
and his belt in the other.
That was the last time.
When you first came to see us,
you said that you'd
been trying to find him.
Was this true?
I'm sorry, Amy.
I knew you wouldn't take my case.
I did try to go to the house but
I was nearly sick in the taxi.
So why do you want to find him?
I'm going to be living here.
The thought of seeing him...
Layla, your mum really wants to see you.
She pleaded with me.
I pleaded with her once to
leave him, come with me...
But no. She thought it best to stay.
She was scared! Was
that really her fault?
How can I forgive her?
- She gave me something to give to you.
- What?
Wait here.
I've got your probation
officer's number in here.
You get smart, he'll
be here like a shot.
Hello, Jamie.
This is my exam certificate.
She kept it!
Mum kept it after all these years!
He threw it in the bin but
she must have pulled it out.
She spent so many years
trying to find you.
She just wants to say
she's sorry, that's all.
I was wrong about you, Layla.
- I'm sorry I lied.
- I understand.
I'm glad I stuck with you.
So am I.
Listen...the home she's in?
Thank you.
I was hoping we could,
you know, start again,
act like grown-ups.
- Won't be easy, will it?
- Course not...
- but I apologised to Cass.
- When?
We talked the other night.
- What?
- We were just talking, Paul.
He was here?
He just turned up. It was nothing.
Oh, no. Just like the old days!
Oh, come on, Paul.
Get out! Get out of my house.
I've spoken to a solicitor, Paul.
I want access...to my daughter.
Hi, is that the control room?
Yeah, this is Amy Garnett, MPU.
I've got a mobile number here
with a 999 call on it and I
just want to check the result.
Did we take it, or
did Fire or Ambulance?
Did you plan this? Is that
what you were chatting about?
No, Paul, no. I had no idea.
It's got nothing to do with Cass.
I decided. Oh, you decided, did you?
Congratulations! Is that what
you meant about being grown-up?
- How does it feel?
- It feels good.
I'm ready. I hope so.
- I hope you are.
- Paul, please don't!
- Daddy!
- Jess, sweetheart!
She's beautiful... just like her mum.
A couple of hours ago he was willing
to walk away and leave her to you.
Don't think he meant it.
I just wanted to see her that was all.
What did the solicitor say?
He said he hoped I had the
stomach for a long, hard fight.
Do you?
I'll walk back. Tell Cassie...
No, just say I've gone... for good.
Amy?
- I thought you'd be gone.
- This was just e-mailed.
It's a list of Ellen's phone calls.
- And, anything interesting?
- Big time!
She phoned St Margaret's Hospital
six times in the last three months.
and five of them were just this week,
and check out the last number on the list.
- 999.
- That call was made an hour and a half ago.
Does MJ know about
this? I just called her.
- What are you doing here?
- So she called 999?
It could have been anything.
This hospital has the largest
drug dependency unit in the county.
Let me go and find out what's happened.
No!
- You don't understand.
- I do, MJ.
She might say she
doesn't want to see you.
You meant well, OK?
Look, I won't go in there. I
just need to think things through.
Ellen?
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk