- Think I need to come up?
- It's more comfortable up here.
How's it going on The
Danny Hayworth Show?
Giving up fags has done nothing
for my performance on the mic.
- Or my waistline either.
- I'm pleased you took my advice.
- Did you call Craig?
- No, not yet. I will.
When?
What's with the inquisition?
What's with the procrastination?
The last time I saw him
he was smashing our wedding
china up the kitchen wall.
Just give him a ring.
What you got to lose?
All right. I'll call.
OK, so whose round is it then?
Well, the wife says if I have
another drink, she's gonna kill me.
Large gin and tonic it is then.
You fancy a quick drink?
Yeah, all right,
but only a quick one because
I'm meeting a mate later.
Nice.
Are you keeping on top
of all those files, Jason?
- Yip.
- Good.
- Don't fall behind.
- Night.
Doesn't look like you're going
to get out of here any time soon.
Do you want a hand with those?
Yeah. Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
Missing Persons Unit. Jason Doyle.
Can't it wait? I've got a ton of files.
OK. Give me the address.
She's gone. She didn't come
home. I don't understand it.
All right.
Are you OK to answer some questions?
How can she just disappear like
that? It doesn't make sense.
When did you last see your wife?
- It's Irene, isn't it?
- This morning. Earlier
What took you so long to get
here? Doesn't anyone care?
We do care, sir, I just need
to ask some basic questions.
I don't know. I woke up this morning
as usual. Had a shower. She...
I went to the office, she stayed
at home to work, and, um...
- When was that?
- I can't remember.
- Roughly what time?
- Please...
Please. I don't see how this is helping.
It's just procedure.
Just procedure? My wife is missing!
I'd like a bit more than procedure.
There are questions I need
to ask and it will help.
You need to get out there and
start searching for my wife.
- Which we will.
- When?
Mr. Laird, please.
All right, can we continue?
You're just wasting time.
My wife's missing and all you're
doing is just wasting time.
Do you know if she might
be with anyone? Friends...
I would've checked. Would not I?
What's that?
Have you had an accident?
I cut my hand.
There. See.
Have you been drinking, Mr. Laird?
- What if I have?
- Doyou mind stepping back?!
Would you mind helping me find my wife?
- I suggest you just calm down!
- I am calm!
Right.
I am arresting you for the
assault of a police officer.
You do not have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence
if you do not mention when questioned
something which you later rely on in court.
Anything you do say may
be given in evidence.
This is Craig. Please leave
a message after the tone.
Craig, it's MJ.
Long time.
I'm still looking for Ellen and
I need to talk to you.
Could you give me a call
when you get this, please?
Thanks.
Done. Happy?
You do wanna find her, don't you?
It's not that straightforward.
I haven't seen him since we split up.
Talking to Craig's just going
to drag it all up. Everything.
It's never as bad as you think.
You fancy a full English?
Swapping one addiction for
another wasn't the plan.
You worried you're going
to sound fat on the radio?
You should hear me
in horizontal stripes!
Hey, Jason!
Have you read this Cadzo file?
No, I thought you were dealing with it.
That's disgusting.
I missed breakfast. It was a long night.
You know it's an interesting case.
Martin Cadzo testified against his
father in a fraud investigation.
His father got three years
and Martin went missing.
He testified against his own father?!
And his family cut him off, except
now his aunt's looking for him.
What does the aunt want?
Her husband died last month
and left Martin a load of money.
So his aunt's got all this money
and she wants us to find him.
Jason, he made a stand. He helped
the police prosecute his own dad!
Put an ad in the paper:
" Martin Cadzo, your uncle's
left you a ton of money."
He'll be there like a shot. Right...
I have to fill in this report
after making my arrest last night.
So, DC Doyle,
a man calls in to MPU to
report his wife missing
and he ends up in a police cell.
- How does that happen?
- He assaulted me.
Any injuries?
He pushed me onto the sofa.
- Did you provoke him in any way?
- He was drunk.
- There was blood on the carpet.
- He went out,
had a few beers, came back
and his wife was missing.
- He was frantic.
- OK, well, maybe I over-reacted.
Right, I'll go and let Tom
Laird out of his cell, shall I?
DC Doyle won't be pressing charges.
Thank you.
It was the drink.
The worry.
The thought of Irene hurt or...
Do you have any idea
where Irene might go?
I spoke to her friends.
No-one's heard from her.
What about family?
There's no-one. Her parents are gone
and there's no brothers or sisters.
I hope you don't mind me
asking you this, but...
... did Irene suffer from
depression or mood swings?
No.
Never.
She's always so...
I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
- I'm so worried about her.
We do everything together.
Even the business.
And what about outside work?
Did you notice a change in her behaviour
or routine for the past week or so?
On Mondays, there's a book group.
The next night we
went out to the cinema.
Then Wednesday, she started work
on the garden. She's landscaping it.
She took a half day, and then we
met up and went out for a meal.
Apart from yesterday. I went out for a
drink with some colleagues, went back home.
That's when I realised. The
car was missing from the drive.
And all the photos of Irene.
They're gone.
There were none left behind?
There's one in my wallet at home.
Would it be possible to have it?
And her bank account details.
- We may be able to trace her that way.
- You will find her, won't you?
We'll do our best.
It was definitely Africa?
Thanks. You've been a great help.
University counsellor said
Cadzo was a brilliant student.
On course for a double first.
I don't think I'm
going to like this guy.
After the trial, he applied for
a sabbatical, which they OKed.
- Where did he go?
- Africa. Volunteer work.
He phoned the college to
confirm his place was open,
but he didn't show up when term started.
You could check passports and visas,
see whether he returned to the UK.
Good idea.
- He's cute, isn't he?
- He's not my type.
If you could get the account
details and the photo.
DCI Ford.
Thanks for your department's lead.
DC Doyle tipped us off
about the restraining order.
What?
12 years ago Laird's ex had a
restraining order placed on him.
DC Doyle didn't mention it.
I was speaking with the neighbours.
They heard rowing the night
before she disappeared.
Did he say anything?
No, he...
We are still looking
for a missing person.
Of course.
I just want to ask Mr.
Laird a few questions.
I'm not shutting your MPU
out of the investigation.
Let's keep this open, work together.
Of course, ma'am.
Don't worry, I'll keep you in the loop.
Mr. Laird, DCI Ford, I'd like
to ask you some questions.
What?
It's standard procedure.
- She's just doing her job.
- And whose job is it to find Irene?
Mine.
DCI Ford mentioned a row...
- the night before.
- That was nothing.
I'd just had a bad day
at work, that's all.
What can we do now?
How about contacting local radio?
how do you feel about
doing a live appeal?
I'll do anything, if
it helps find Irene.
Mr. Laird, can we go in?
Why didn't you tell me
you'd taken the case to CID?
I didn't.
Information about some restraining order
came out when I had Laird in custody.
A DS was down there and we
got chatting about the case.
And you didn't think it
would lead to anything?
Laird is now being investigated
as a possible murder suspect.
What?
- Sarge, I didn't...
- OK. Now, HE's under suspicion,
but we are still
investigating a missing person.
Is that clear?
Sarge.
I've checked the hospital's psych
wards and morgues, there was nothing.
Traffic don't have any RTCs,
they're giving me regular updates.
Ditto in PRS and PNC.
OK. See if there's any
activity on her account.
Amy, get this enlarged
and get it circulated, OK?
What about the missing photos?
Well, there's no break-ins, so
either Tom or Irene took them.
She's difficult to ID without a photo.
Maybe she took it,
doesn't wanna be found.
Or maybe it was him, he couldn't
bear looking at the woman he killed.
Why keep the one in the wallet?
I'm gonna see Danny,
see if we can get Tom
on his show tonight.
That was DCI Ford. She wants
to see you in her office.
Tell her I'll call in later.
I got the impression
she meant right now.
How can I help?
You don't think you're
wasting resources on this one?
Ma'am?
Did something come up
when you interviewed him?
Not him, no. We've spoken to the
ex-girlfriend about the restraining order.
- That was 12 years ago.
- She said he had mood swings,
a bit of a temper, as I'm
sure DC Doyle would agree.
He'd just discovered
his wife was missing.
His ex said he found it difficult to
accept that their relationship had ended.
Started drinking,
turning up at the flat.
She said it frightened
her to see him like that.
Anything from your end?
I'm thinking of getting
Tom to do a radio appeal.
Good idea. Is it sorted?
- I was just about to when you called.
- What time would I need to be there?
Well, it's an appeal for Irene. You
being there puts unfair pressure on him.
That's the point.
See how he reacts under pressure.
- He trusts me.
- I'm the senior investigating officer in this case.
Let me know when it's
organised and I'll be there,
DS Croft.
I found this from a search on the
internet. And passports and visas.
Cadzo re-entered the
UK 13th April 2003.
Hang on...
Paul Cadzo died without
meeting his first grandchild,
his estranged son Martin
did not attend the funeral.
When was that?
20th January, 2003.
So Cadzo returns from Africa
to find out his father's dead.
Came back too late.
That's gotta be why he
didn't go back to uni.
He must have guilt.
Guilt. And the money was his uncle's
way of acknowledging his sacrifice.
That's tough.
Choosing between your
family and your principles.
Exactly. And his uncle knew he'd
been out in the cold for too long.
And you get to be the one
to welcome him back in.
DCI Ford'll be here in five minutes.
I know what this is about.
She's waiting for me to crack.
- Confess to killing my wife.
- That's not...
She was asking me about my ex.
From 12 years ago. It was all lies.
Her and her new boyfriend
made it all up to get at me.
I wasn't a threat, not like that.
I turned up to talk to her and
he started on me. It was him.
Why don't they just come out with it?
Ask me what I've done with her body.
Tom...
- I need you to focus.
- I can't do this.
You can't back out now. It'll look
like you've buckled under the pressure.
Forget DC Ford, this appeal
is about finding Irene.
OK?
Just like any other morning,
you got up, you went to work,
and that was the last
time that you saw Irene?
That's right.
Can you remember what she was wearing?
Jeans, I think. Erm...
And a green V-necked jumper.
- Does she have any distinguishing features?
- She has a scar,
just below her ear.
Runs down to her neck.
And what would you like to say
to Irene if she was listening?
If...
If she was out there.
Tom's written Irene a message.
"If you're in trouble, we
can work it out, like always.
"More than anything, I need to
know that you are safe and well."
If you're listening, Irene, or
someone knows where Irene is,
please call 960 953.
There's some photos of
Irene on the website...
This is the Danny Hayworth Show.
Is Tom OK?
It threw him, having CID there.
She'll be even more suspicious now.
Craig got in touch.
He's coming in tomorrow.
How do you feel about that?
Ever since I started
looking for Ellen again,
I've had this terrible feeling of...
failure.
Why?
He blamed me for Ellen leaving.
Said it was my fault.
Said I wanted Ellen to leave.
And did you?
'Course I didn't.
Why did Ellen leave, MJ?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have asked.
Come on, let's get out of here.
- Did you get anything from the appeal?
- Nothing new. Still going through 'em.
What about you with Cadzo?
This guy seems to be able to live without
legally owning or renting property,
without paying taxes, getting
sick, or having a bank account.
- Psychiatric clinics?
- Checked.
- What did he do in Africa?
- He worked with orphaned children.
Kids, orphans, volunteering.
Come on, it's a no-brainer.
Local charities, of course!
I should check with the ones
that specialise with children.
Morning. Any news on Irene Laird?
Nothing on her personal account, but
maybe something on the business side.
There was some restructuring
just last month.
Sounds creative.
Well, Tom is now the sole
signatory on all the cheques,
and if anything should happen to Irene,
he's the sole beneficiary
of the business.
Things are stacking up against him.
Let's not be too hasty.
I've got an email here from the
radio appeal, from a Sarah Banberry.
She claims to be Irene's daughter.
What?!
She said Irene went
missing 18 years ago.
- Shall I let DCI Ford know?
- No.
This is OUR lead. She responded
to an appeal from Missing Person,
I wanna talk to her first.
This is my mother.
She was called Helen Banberry then.
That's all I've had.
18 years.
- Did you have any other photos?
- She took them all.
A week after she disappeared,
a box of them was found in the woods,
burnt.
Was she stressed, for any reason?
No, she...she'd just started
working up at the sailing club,
so there was a bit more money.
Dad said they'd even talked
about having more children.
He died five years ago.
Right until the end, he never
stopped believing that we'd find her.
We found Cadzo.
He volunteers for a local charity,
works with disabled children.
- He lives nearby.
- Get a uniform to ID him.
I thought I could go.
No, you find out when Irene
changed her name by deed poll.
But they won't give me that information.
Tell them it's a murder enquiry.
Irene left Sarah in 1991.
She was with Tom eight years, I wanna
know where she was for the other ten.
I thought we agreed
to share information.
I take it you're referring
to Sarah Banberry?
Why didn't you tell me you had a lead?
She responded to an appeal.
I thought she had
information about Irene.
Irene's gone missing before.
She left Sarah and her
dad, exactly the same MO,
took all the photographs...
I wonder what Tom would have
done if he'd found this out.
A wife with a secret past.
We know he has a temper.
Come on!
We've got no scene of crime,
no body, no forensics...
I have Irene Laird's burnt-out car
in a field half a mile from the A14.
My officers are there now,
searching the area for evidence.
So far, we've found the
remains of the photos,
and a pair of men's
gloves covered in paraffin.
And you're the one talking
about sharing information?
I called you in here to share
this latest development with you.
And as your senior officer, I'm reminding
you that I asked you for regular updates.
Any developments come straight to me.
I take it that works both ways?
Until I say otherwise.
- Would you like a drink, tea, coffee?
- No, I'm good.
Will she be long?
No, she's just in a
meeting. I'm sure she'll...
I'm sorry I'm late, I...
got caught up in a meeting.
You've got some news...about Ellen?
- We traced some money wires.
- Well, I sent her money.
How often?
She'd call a couple of times one week,
then I wouldn't hear
anything for six months.
Over what period of time?
I'm... I don't exactly... Six years.
- On and off.
- Why didn't you tell me?
We weren't in contact,
- remember?
- She's my sister, Craig.
I have a right to know.
What do you want me to
say? I'm not a mind reader.
You could have contacted me.
What was the money for?
It was always drugs-related,
getting away from people
who gave her drugs,
a deposit for a flat to
get her off the street,
- a fine for possession...
- Why didn't she come to me?
Well, look at it from her point of view.
God, you always took her side.
- You're still doing it now.
- No, MJ, I'm not.
I had to be a sister, a
parent, keep my career on track,
hold our marriage together, which wasn't
easy when Ellen wanted my attention
every second of every day.
You were jealous of Ellen?
Why did you stop sending her the money?
I suspected she was using it for drugs.
Did you tell her?
I said I'd send her food
and clothes, but no cash.
She gave me the address of
a halfway house in London.
London?
Yes.
She's in England.
I don't believe this!
I was helping someone I cared about.
Give me a break, MJ.
- Have you got an address?
- I called the number she gave me.
It was a telephone box
in Waterloo station.
She screwed me.
Interesting choice of word.
I came here to help, not to
rake up all this crap again.
Craig... Craig!
Craig!
Listen to me.
Craig, I was out of order.
Is this how little you trusted me?
It's just... I helped Ellen out
cos someone had to and you weren't.
If things were that desperate,
why didn't you come to me?
She begged me not to.
She hadn't forgiven you.
15 years later
and you're still going
over the same bloody ground.
Move on, MJ. Move on.
- Craig...
- MJ?
- Not now, Amy.
- It's really urgent.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, fine.
- Who's that?
- It's George Partis.
I did the checks you asked for and it turns
out that Irene, Helen Banberry at the time,
changed her name to Annette
Allan via deed poll in 1991.
I take it that was when this
George became her boyfriend?
I tracked Annette Allan
and found that she hooked
up with George Partis here.
I managed to contact him.
They used to travel a lot, keen sailors.
Then he wanted to settle down
and she gets a job running start-up
courses for up-and-coming businesses.
A year later, she's off
- takes nothing with her.
Apart from, let me
guess, all the photos?
You've got it. Exactly the same MO.
We're dealing with a
serial missing person.
There's a definite pattern.
Sarah Banberry said that her mum
got a job in the sailing club.
A couple of months later, she's off
on the high seas with George Partis.
While she's with him, she starts running
these business courses and meets Tom.
And bye-bye George.
I want you to check
out Irene's book club.
According to him, it was the
only time they were apart.
Are you gonna update the DCI?
- I'll let Jason do the honours.
- My pleasure.
I need to speak to Tom.
There might be something he thinks
of once I tell him about Irene's past.
MJ, patrol never made it
down to see Cadzo today,
so I thought I might follow it up.
I think I can accept
an ID off a non-uniform.
Good job, by the way.
Did I say that already?
I don't understand.
Earlier on...
the detective was asking
me about Irene's car.
They thought I'd burnt it.
I'm hoping that what
we've found out about Irene
will prove that you had nothing
to do with her disappearance.
I didn't. You do believe me, don't you?
Tom, I need you to try and think.
Is there anything you can tell me
that will help me find
out who Irene may have...
been with?
There's something I didn't tell you.
What you said about
Irene having affairs...
I started to get
suspicious a few weeks back.
Why?
There was a parking
fine, it came in the post.
She never mentioned it, which was odd.
So I started looking through her things.
I found a...dress.
It wasn't the sort she'd wear.
Can you describe it?
It was black and low-cut...
flimsy.
Is that what you and
Irene were rowing about?
No, I never mentioned that I'd
found it, or the parking fine,
just that...
I felt like she was losing
interest in me and...
when she denied it, I got angry.
I did something stupid.
What did you do, Tom?
I burned the dress and the letter
at the bottom of the garden.
I don't believe this.
What else aren't you telling me?
Well, nothing.
You do know how this is going to look?
- I thought you believed me.
- You withheld information.
I'm trying to help you
and you kept it from me.
- Please, I-I-I...
- I've got no choice, Tom.
I'm gonna have to call DCI Ford.
Hello?
Martin Cadzo?
Who are you?
Oh... Amy Garnett.
- Missing Persons.
- Who's missing?
You.
Is that me?
I look pretty good.
Well, I have some news from your family.
It's about your uncle, Steven Cadzo, and
and I'm afraid it's not good news.
- Is he dead?
- Yes.
He died on the 12th February.
He left you a considerable
sum of money in his will
and your aunt's been trying to find you.
Mr. Cadzo, what do I tell your aunt?
Do you want me to give her your details?
Yes, they're here. I'll do it now.
Please.. You know I didn't kill her.
Thomas Laird,
I am arresting you on suspicion
of the murder of Irene Laird.
You do not have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence if
you do not mention when questioned
something which you
later rely on in court.
Anything you do say may
be given in evidence.
Listen, you've got to
find Irene. P-P-Please...
you've got to help me!
I appreciate it must have been
difficult, arresting Laird.
What's going to happen now?
We'll be presenting the case to the CPS in
a couple of hours, then it's over to them.
But there's a strong possibility that
he'll be looking at a murder charge.
Thank you for all your work.
Come in.
Sorry, Sarge.
It's fine.
The CPS are looking at
the evidence right now.
How long have we got?
- For what?
- I think you might be right,
you find out about the
affair, you find Irene.
You confirm a motive, you mean?
I still reckon it's
worth searching for her.
I just heard back from the book group. She
didn't turn up to the last three meetings.
Let me ring the DVLA,
check out her parking fine.
I bet it was one of the nights she was
supposed to be with her Jane Austen mates.
OK, but we've got to act fast.
We've only got a couple of hours before the
CPS get back to Ford with their decision.
I thought we'd have been
able to make a fresh start.
I'd like that.
I'm sorry about before.
You did the right thing,
looking out for Ellen.
- I do appreciate it.
- There's something else.
It might be useful. I remembered
the last time she called.
For drugs?
Well, she said it was
for a counselling course.
She mentioned a
college, Winbeck College.
- In London?
- I don't know.
To be honest, I'd lost
it with her by then.
- Thanks. You've been a great help.
- Take care, OK?
I-I-If you find her,
will you let me know?
Of course.
Someone looks pretty
pleased with himself.
The DVLA...
Irene Laird's parking
fine from two Mondays ago.
But that's the night of her book group.
It must have been a page-turner
for her to forget about the car.
She hasn't been going. I knew it!
# I knew it, I knew it... # I'm assuming
that's because you've got a result?
The parking fine...
Ripley high street, 2046.
- The car parked at 1830.
- 1830 to 2046...
dinnertime!
Do you want us to get down
there and circulate her image,
- see if anyone remembers her?
- Yeah. That's what I was gonna suggest.
Great minds. Start with
the posh restaurants.
She was wearing the black
dress, going upmarket.
And we know Irene likes a man who
can provide a certain lifestyle.
Nothing, you? Yeah,
she came here on
Monday night with a man.
- Do they have the man's name?
- Paul Fallon.
I got his landline number,
so should be able to get the
address from the phone company.
Must have been a special occasion.
Maison du Pays, little black dress?
She left Tom a week later, so Paul
must have played his cards right.
What was the menu like?
Pig's trotter and
truffle. Not my cup of tea.
I'm a meat and two veg type of man.
Want some?
- How was Craig?
- He was OK.
Anything on her?
She was back in the country.
She applied for a college
course in Guildford.
They faxed me her application.
Her contact details were a drug clinic.
Got Amy looking into it.
What did the college say?
She seemed nervous, jittery.
Bit fragile.
But extremely bright.
Sounds like she was trying
to get her life back on track.
She couldn't afford the fees.
Wish I'd known.
How did you leave things with Craig?
Got a lot to be angry about,
but we cleared the air.
Thing is, Danny, I, er...
I accused Ellen of sleeping
with Craig before she ran away.
- Was it true?
- No.
No, she didn't. They didn't...
It was just me, and my
paranoia, and my insecurity.
Was that why you split up?
Sounds like we've all
moved on since then.
I'm trying to.
Oh, go on, let me have
one! Please. Please...!
No, look, have that. Go on.
Got it.
The phone number was registered
to Paul Fallon, Ripley Hill.
Got another one here.
Paul Fallon. Landscape gardening.
Irene must have met him when
he was doing work on her garden.
We've got a phone number and
address for Irene's new man.
Good work. Get over
there as soon as possible.
DS Croft. Missing Persons Unit.
You've been reported missing.
I haven't done anything illegal.
The problem is, Irene, I have
to officially identify you.
- You are still calling yourself Irene?
- I am Irene Laird.
Jason, call DCI Ford and tell
her we've found Irene Laird.
Your husband's being held
on suspicion of your murder.
But...Tom wouldn't hurt a fly.
I guess him being soft made
him easier to manipulate.
I'd like you to leave now.
- So what do I tell your daughter Sarah?
- I gave more than I took.
George was rich, but lazy!
He travelled the world with me.
Tom was terrified to take risks.
Today he owns a business
that employs 87 people.
And that makes it all right to
abandon him and ruin his reputation?
Must have been hard
remembering all those lies.
What about Sarah?
When I was young, my
parents moved around a lot...
Hardly the same!
It gives me a certain perspective!
You told Paul Farron
about your "perspective"?
He doesn't need to know.
I haven't broken any law. I have
the right not to be contacted.
Don't you think about the people
you left behind? A daughter...
she spent years wondering
what happened to you.
And Tom. He loves you. Don't
you think you owe him...
- some sort of explanation?
- What do you expect me to say
that wasn't made clear the moment
I walked out of their lives?
"I'm sorry"? No.
Certainly made it easier.
Maybe.
You've found me.
You've done your jobs.
I think it's time for you to leave.
- Congratulations.
- Ma'am?
It's been a difficult couple of days.
- For Tom Laird, you mean.
- Yes.
Thank you...and your team.
- Real dedication.
- Or a real pain in the neck.
You got the result, DS Croft.
We found Irene.
I don't think Tom will
see it as a result.
- She didn't want to know?
- No.
It's not your responsibility.
Doesn't make it any easier, though.
I guess not.
- Has Tom been released?
- Of course.
You were never a pain.
A bit of a challenge... But
you were right to pursue it.
Look, I'm not gonna keep coming round.
Just let me do my job and I can
let you get on with your life.
Your aunt's details.
I...
I can't imagine what it's like
sacrificing everything for your principles.
Personally, I think it was brave.
You stood up for what you believed in.
Your aunt and uncle knew it was
wrong for your family to cut you off,
and I know it's late. But this
is their way of apologising.
He controlled everyone by money.
Me... Mum...
Threatened to cut us
off if we crossed him.
Just got sick of it.
So I decided to play
him at his own game.
I threatened to call the police,
he just laughed in my face.
Thought I wouldn't
give up the easy life.
It wasn't about right
or wrong principles.
I did it out of spite.
Do you still wanna save me?
Well, I think you should stop hiding.
You could do a lot with that money.
Change lives.
I'm really sorry, Sarah.
I couldn't convince your
mother to contact you.
But you know where she is.
I can't give you her address.
Not unless she tells me to.
She doesn't have anything to say to me?
I'm sorry.
When I saw the picture on the
poster and I knew it was here, it was...
an amazing feeling, like
if all those years of hoping
hadn't been for nothing. She was alive!
But she doesn't want to talk to me.
Why would I want to hear
what she's got to say anyway?
What would be the point?
Just to have her say she
doesn't care, she never did!
- Sorry, I'm keeping you.
- No, no.
Well, at least I know.
Thanks.
- There you go...
- Thanks.
Brought you some sugar.
I'm all right.
I'm sorry about what happened...
- the other night...
- No, I was, er, upset.
- How you doing, Tom?
- Bit tired.
- Did you sleep?
- At least it wasn't in a cell.
Look on the bright side.
I just lay awake all night.
Totally still.
And then it was light again.
Nothing had changed.
I don't know what I'm supposed
to be feeling right now.
What do I do?
You need to take things slowly.
What... What do people think of me?
The neighbours, they...
think I'm actually capable...
You've done nothing wrong.
Then why did she leave me?
Doesn't even want to see me.
You mustn't blame yourself.
I just wish things could go
back to the way they were.
When someone goes missing, the effects on
the loved ones left behind can be devastating.
It can leave people
feeling depressed and angry,
and grief-stricken at the
loss of their loved ones.
But imagine if you're accused
of murdering that missing person.
Dealing with your own feelings and
the suspicion of your neighbours.
My question is: should the people
who go missing be held accountable,
or is it everyone's right to
live their lives as they wish?
My name is Danny Hayworth,
and the lines are open.
- I'm looking for Amy Garnett.
- Oh, hi.
Look, I'm no good at speeches,
I just wanted to say...
Thank you.
And I'd like to donate
some money to the MPU.
You do good work here.
My solicitors' details. Just let them
know who to make the cheque payable to.
Here's my...card. Just in case.
I'll keep it with the other one.
Good luck.
Thanks.
- Goodlooking bloke!
- He's not my type.
What is your type?
I like a "meat and two veg" kind of guy.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
- 2009
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk