You've not been returning my calls.
I've been busy.
MJ, this is me you're talking to.
She's in Dover.
I've seen her.
What, Ellen?
You've found her?
Got a list of her mobile calls.
Last number she rung was 999.
Traced it to the hospital.
There she was.
Are you sure it was her?
I called to her.
She looked right through me.
She wasn't expecting to see
you and she was in the hos...
It's all right.
I've seen her.
I can let it go now.
What, after all these years?
The case is closed.
Case? This is your sister!
Didn't stop you digging
it up on your show, did it?
I'd better go.
Back to the office?
No, home visit.
New case just come in.
Look, what I just said...
Did you say something?
I wasn't listening.
I went straight from work
on a girls' night out.
My boyfriend, Sam, was meant
to be meeting up with his mates.
Some of his stuff's gone.
This mate, can you give
us his number, Gemma?
Sam's not there. I checked.
He never even showed up.
I'm sorry to have to ask you this, but
- did you have a fight or anything?
- No.
In fact, we were... close.
Just yesterday morning, you know.
Which was nice, cos he's
been a bit distant lately,
since we found out about the baby,
cos it wasn't planned.
But he was as chuffed
as I was, er, at first.
At first?
Well, then he just clammed up
and whenever I mentioned it,
he just got quiet. Typical
bloke. Can't talk about feelings.
- You were going to get us a photo.
- Er, yeah, of course. It's in here.
Something wrong, Gemma?
My mum's bracelet. It should be in here.
Are you sure?
- Can you describe it?
- Gold, white gold.
Er, about that thick, with
rubies and diamonds on it.
It's the only good
piece I had. Erm, why?
Well, what does that mean, that look?
Well, he wouldn't steal it off me.
Look, erm...
He's in trouble, I
know he is, so just...
Please, you've got to find him.
What happened to the
trackie and trainers?
Too much like hard work.
- If you want MJ, she's not here.
- I know, I've just seen her.
She told me she's just
closed Ellen's case.
She's in bits.
Look, I have to come up with
some way to put things right.
How?
She mentioned a list
of telephone numbers.
That is police business!
Well, won't you just let me see it?
For MJ's sake.
Please.
I don't know, Danny.
What if you were to leave the room and you
just happened to leave the file on your desk?
I won't go further than the car
park. I'll bring it back, I promise.
I'm just going to pop
to the canteen.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know me, just poking me nose in.
Your new case, I've got a
slot on the show tonight.
Danny, I'm busy.
If I need ya, I'll let you know.
His mate said Sam had
real money worries.
Seems Gemma didn't want
to wait for anything.
See the house.
The house is like a shrine
to the Shopping Channel.
Jason.
Sam tried to borrow money off him.
Said not to tell Gemma.
It's not the only
thing he kept from her.
I talked to his boss.
Sam was made redundant three weeks ago.
Even opted to work out his notice.
So he wouldn't have to
tell his wife presumably?
I think we're talking
serious financial pressure.
Maybe marital problems?
Don't think so. She said they were
close yesterday morning.
Well, it could've been
his way of saying goodbye.
That how you say goodbye, is it?
The boss said he was edgy. He went
out for lunch, never came back.
Do we know where he went?
Usually goes to a cafe on Farthing
Street. I'll get over there.
Get on to the council, see if there's
any CCTV coverage for that area.
Amy, call Gemma, see if we
can see the bank details.
And run a check on Sam's number plate.
Missing Persons Unit.
Yeah, let me get my coat
and I'll be right down.
So?
I called the most
frequently used number.
Turns out it belongs to
Ellen's boyfriend, Simon.
- And you know this because?
- Well, I spoke to him.
Look, don't worry! I just said that
I was a friend of Ellen's sister.
And?
Ellen did recognise MJ at
the hospital last night,
but won't talk about it, so he wouldn't say
where they live. Maybe that's your answer.
- Legenda não traduzida -
No, he wanted to, Amy, I
know he did. I could tell.
You're not going to
let this go, are you?
Look, here's the number.
Now you could find out the address
it's registered to, couldn't you?
If you do this for me,
I won't ask you for anything else.
Ever.
Yes, you will.
Sarge!
I've got footage of the cafe
from yesterday lunchtime.
It was after one o'clock.
This is where he was last seen.
The manager said he
came in with another man.
Apparently, they had an argument.
Sam shouted something
about owing him money.
That's Sam in front.
And the other guy slammed
his fist on the table.
Manager asked him to leave
or he'd call the police.
Let's see if we can get him coming out.
Sam was pretty shaken up after this.
Another customer went over to him,
but he pushed past and rushed out.
That's the man he went in with.
There he is.
That's the customer who followed him.
A do-gooder according to the manager.
Amy, get some print-outs done.
See if Gemma knows the bloke.
A "please" would be nice.
- Are you sure?
- Well, who is he?
We don't know.
He was seen having an argument with
Sam in a cafe near where he works.
Well, what about?
Money.
You didn't know he'd
been made redundant?
Well, he never told me.
This just keeps getting worse!
Shall I order a facial recognition?
When your office called,
I phoned the building society.
They say he was four months
behind on the mortgage payment,
but that he paid it off three weeks ago,
in cash.
Over two thousand pounds.
I mean, where did he get
all that cash in one go?
Why didn't he tell me instead
of just taking the bracelet?
He's running away from something,
but I don't think it's you.
Look, I don't care what he's done.
I'll do anything to get him back.
Anything?
Sam, if you're listening...
I love you so, so much and, erm,
whatever's wrong,
we'll get through it, right.
Just please, please come home.
So if anybody has any
information on Sam Winter,
please get in contact
on the usual number.
And just to remind you, Sam was last seen coming
out of the cafe on Farthing Street at 20 past one.
Perhaps you were there and saw him,
or perhaps you've seen him since.
If you've got any information,
then please call in.
- Ellen?
- Yeah?
I'm a friend of Mary Jane Croft.
Are you the guy that phoned Simon?
Yeah, yeah.
Danny.
- Danny Hayworth.
- Look, I'm not interested.
I just want five minutes of your time.
Please.
She's beautiful.
- What's her name?
- Sarah.
Is she all right now?
I mean, you took her to the hospital.
One of her asthma attacks.
I probably overreacted,
but it's best be safe.
Look, I'm sure you're not
here to talk about Sarah.
No. I, erm...
I was hoping you'd
agree to meet up with MJ.
Mary Jane.
Did she send you here to ask me that?
No, no. She doesn't even know I'm here.
Well, she's a really good friend
and I care about her.
Look, I'm sticking my neck out
here. She'll probably kill me.
Please.
Ellen...
she's your sister.
Whatever went on in the past...
If you could meet her
and talk things through...
It's complicated.
It might be easier than you think.
You see, MJ knows what
happened after you left.
She knows about the abortion?
I couldn't believe it,
cos I'd seen him in the cafe.
When I heard his name on
the radio, I knew it was him.
When I saw his picture on
the website, I had to come in.
I don't usually listen
to that radio station.
This is...
Hi, Ryan Long, I'm here to
help with the Sam Winter case.
- Hi.
- He heard the appeal last night.
Yeah, that's right. I
was expecting DS Croft.
You're getting DC Doyle instead.
Would you like to come this way?
- Do you want to take a seat?
- Yeah, this is the guy. Sam, is it?
And that's me. Er, how did you, erm...?
CCTV.
Right. Well, it was the raised
voice that made me look over.
- Can you remember what he said?
- Yeah. "You'll get it."
Or, "I'll give it back to you."
Something like that.
- And then?
- Well, the manager
goes over to their table
and tells this guy to leave,
so I go to Sam to see if he's OK
and he just rushes past me.
- And then you followed him
outside? Yeah, that's right.
Why?
See if I could help.
A total stranger?
I'm a financial consultant. I
could have offered a way out.
What, give him a loan?
Consolidate his debts?
- Could work something out.
- Did he say anything to you?
No, he got in the car
and just drove off.
If there's anything you want me to do.
If you're organising a search party or...
No, it's fine.
Thanks for coming in, Mr. Long.
If you'd like to wait here, my
colleague will be in shortly.
Anything?
Nothing we didn't already know.
He's an ambulance chaser.
You couldn't do me a favour?
Could you take his details?
Cheers.
Hey! You shouldn't be looking at that.
Sorry. I just find this
thing so fascinating.
I thought about joining the force once.
I watch police
documentaries all the time.
All right, Mr. Long,
can I have an address?
Er, yeah. 32 Greenford Road.
And a phone number?
07802 420 006.
So in a case like this, I suppose
you just check out all the hospitals?
That kind of stuff.
Standard procedures.
- Still no news?
- No, not yet.
Right. Thank you for taking
the trouble of coming in.
Oh, no, no trouble at all.
I'm on a training course.
My hotel's just a five-minute walk.
- We'd better let you get back.
- OK.
I'm taking the rest of the day off.
I've said to your colleague if you
need any help, just let me know.
You will call and let me know
if you find him, won't you?
Yeah.
Good.
I'm going for lunch with Danny.
He says it's important.
You know what he's like.
I bet he's after a favour.
You're a cheap date, I'll give you that.
What do you want, Danny? I'm on a case.
I saw Ellen last night.
I went to her house.
Didn't I make myself clear?
- I just thought...
- What?!
That I don't mean what I say?
That I don't know what I want?
MJ, please.
Please what? Say it's all right
for you to go behind my back?
Someone had to get you
two together, all right?
She told me something you need to know.
Now, do you wanna hear it or not?
Facial recognition's come through.
And I've got another witness.
She phoned in to say she
saw Sam leave the cafe.
- Are you listening to me?
- Yeah.
Go on. I'm riveted.
Well, she then mentioned Ryan Long.
That finance guy from earlier.
How could I forget?
So any way, Ryan follows Sam to
the car, tries to speak to him.
- But Sam just gets in.
- Trying to escape, no doubt.
Ryan holds the door open trying to talk to
him, but Sam drives off and leaves him there.
- I mean, doesn't that strike you as odd?
- No.
These finance guys are desperate.
Yaeh. But he never told
us they had a conversation.
I think it's worth talking to him again.
Well, can't you do it?
You're took the interview.
Don't think you should be...?
Amy, look!
I've just had a major breakthrough.
You see this guy. Lenny King.
He calls himself a businessman,
but he's a loan shark.
Yeah, maybe he is, but to
us, he's just a witness.
What with a criminal record for GBH?
He's coming in for a chat.
Jason, you're taking a statement,
remember? Not making an arrest.
Yes, Sarge.
I'm sorry, MJ.
She didn't know she was
pregnant when she left.
It was just some boy she was seeing.
She phoned him to tell him,
but he didn't want to know.
I know it's a lot to take in.
It's the thought of her on her own.
Pregnant, frightened, no money.
Why couldn't she just come home?
Come on, don't blame yourself.
She couldn't, could she?
Not after I'd accused her of sleeping
with my husband. She couldn't come home.
She never mentioned any of that.
- I need to see her.
- You have to.
Do it. You know it's what you want.
- Wait in here.
- How long's this gonna take?
Till I'm satisfied with your answers.
Hi. You want to sit in?
I'll pass, thanks. Before you go in,
about this Ryan Long business.
His phone's switched off and the
address he gave us is nonexistent.
I tell you what,
you worry about little details,
I'll go deal with the bad guy.
All right, MJ?
What's up with her?
Yeah?
Is everything all right?
I agreed to you
investigating my sister
on condition that you would
call a halt when I said so.
- I'm sorry.
- For what it's worth,
Danny didn't shop you.
I figured out he could only have
got the address with your help.
I'm really disappointed in you, Amy.
You were one of the last people
to see him before he disappeared.
So?
So I wanna know everything
that was said at the meeting.
Could you remember everything
you said two days ago?
How do you know him?
- We had a business arrangement.
- What you've got a contract?
An understanding.
Don't try and be clever.
I've got witnesses in the cafe.
You were with Sam Winter
and you were leaning on him.
You've got no idea how
bad this is looking.
I don't give a toss how this looks.
So you've got no idea
what's happened to him?
No.
I don't give a toss about that either.
Even though he owes you money?
- He doesn't.
- What?
Owe me money.
- But you said...
- Yeah, he cleared it, didn't he?
What, all of it?
I'll say.
Put that through me letterbox.
- When?
- Well, I dunno.
I wasn't at home, was I?
Well, where were you?
I left the cafe and I
went to a friend's house.
I've just been to have that valued.
That is the real deal.
- Can I go now?
- Hold on.
How do I know you didn't steal it
from his house or from Sam himself?
Where is it?
It's here somewhere.
There it is.
Well, don't you want it, then?
"This covers what I owe.
"Don't get in touch with
me again. Sam Winter."
I think that kinda changes
things a bit, dunnit?
It seems like Sam used the bracelet
to clear his debts with Lenny King.
Didn't want to leave
Gemma with too big a mess.
Which makes sense, I suppose.
We're off to Gemma's house.
See if we can get her
to ID this bracelet.
That witness, Ryan Long.
I found the hotel where his course was
and they're getting me his address.
- You still on about that?
- Well, you know what they say?
The devil is in the detail.
Even the little details.
Amy's right.
Everything's worth checking,
even the small things.
Just leave it on my desk
and I'll deal with it later.
You probably need to lie
down after all that hard work.
Gemma?
Call an ambulance!
Gemma!
Gemma, it's MJ. Can you hear me?
- Sarge. There's one here already.
- Blimey, that was quick.
I'll go with her. You
speak to the neighbours.
See if they saw anything.
Get on to the ambulance service.
See who called them in.
It's all right, Gemma. Ambulance
is here. You're gonna be OK.
You're a very difficult
man to get hold of.
Can I come inside?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thanks.
They won't let me speak to her.
She's still sedated.
There's been some bleeding.
They're concerned for the baby.
How did you get on?
No witnesses, I'm afraid.
But I got the phone number
from the emergency services.
Any lead?
The mobile was switched off. I
checked Sam's, but it wasn't him.
See if the phone's registered,
then go back to square one.
Re-examine everything, CCTV,
witness statements, everything.
Where's Amy? She
should be here for this.
- I don't know.
- Well, chase her up!
Well, where are you...
going?
Hello.
Let me get this one settled.
How long have you been here?
About a year.
And you didn't think to call?
I didn't want to do this.
Danny told me what you'd been through.
I'm sorry...
... for accusing you and Craig of...
So is that it?
You say sorry, then we hug?
You walked out on me, Ellen.
I didn't know where you were.
Didn't know if you was all
right, if you was alive even.
I was OK.
Don't you dare tell me you was OK!
Do you know how much you hurt me?
I said I'm sorry.
I'm not talking about Craig.
There's other stuff.
Mum.
Do you remember you used to drive
me to school just after Mum died?
Yeah.
I was sitting in the back
and I started to cry.
And I caught your eye
watching me in the mirror...
... but you looked away,
like you hadn't seen.
I'm sorry.
Sarah.
Your witness has got it wrong. I've
told you everything that happened.
But, she said you tried to talk to him.
Then she made a mistake.
- If there's nothing else...
- There's one other thing.
Why did you give us the wrong address?
That's my brother's address.
I sent him a birthday card last week.
Well, if that's all?
I don't want to keep you
from anything.
What happened to your hand?
I had an accident.
- Accident?
- Yeah, why do you ask?
- I'm just concerned.
- Listen, what do you want?
I can't let you answer that.
It's OK. She's fine.
I thought it was the right thing.
I thought it best
just to try and get on.
- I was just trying to look after you.
- And you resented that, didn't ya?
I was worried about you.
I don't know you any more.
I'm fine now.
I've got Simon. I've got our baby.
Why would I need you?
- You're my sister.
- I'm really sorry, but
I don't know what that means any more.
I'd better go.
Oh, yes, I know why you're here.
Is his girlfriend all right?
Gemma? You've done something to Gemma?
- It was an accident!
- I know nothing about it, I swear.
I went round to her house.
I had to speak with her.
I didn't expect her to
reacted way she did, just...
I just had to tell her the truth.
Just go in there!
Sit down. Sit!
This is a beautiful
picture. Is this your son?
Don't you touch that!
You can't leave here.
Look... that will be them.
They're looking for me.
They'll get suspicious if
I don't answer the phone.
Please, Ryan.
Why are you doing this?
He killed my son.
Amy, it's me again.
Where the hell are you?
Look, you wanna be getting back
here before the sarge gets in.
Just call me back.
She was getting an
address for Ryan Long.
My guess is, she went to see him.
There's no way.
I told her to leave it on my desk.
It's not here, so why
would she go on her own?
Maybe she thought she had
to prove something...to someone.
The phone that called the ambulance, it's
pay-as-you-go, so it's not registered.
Don't change the subject.
Phone Ryan Long.
You know, she probably needs saving.
Chances are he's trying to
sell her a top-up mortgage.
Switched off.
Do I have to remind you that
Amy is not a police officer?
Hold on.
Where is it?
Look at this.
That's the number that called 999.
And that's Ryan Long's.
They're exactly the same.
Run him through the databases.
Sam Winter's real name
is Alex Steel.
I recognised him straight off.
We were mates. We lived
on the same street.
Rory...
... he was four.
Saturday morning,
we go to the park to play.
I took my eye off him just for a second.
He just, um,
he just ran into the road.
I put Long's name into
the system and this came up.
He saw his son killed in an RTC.
Look who the driver was.
Sam's got a new identity.
He was convicted of causing death by dangerous
driving while under the influence of alcohol.
Been at a stag party the night
before. Pleaded guilty. Got four years.
This, a couple of years ago.
This is serious.
Amy's with Ryan. She
could be in trouble.
You get a trace on her phone.
Circulate the photos,
alert all units.
I'll speak to Gemma, see if she
knows anything about Ryan Long.
I'll call if I get a lead.
You've never heard of
Ryan Long before today?
Not till...
... I told him I didn't
know where Sam was.
He wouldn't believe me and he
just kept on at me and then...
Then he starts ranting.
Calling him a murderer.
So I screamed
and he grabbed my arm
and he pushed me and I fell back.
We've got everyone out
looking for him.
You know, Sam was always nervous
about moving to Dover and, um,
now I know why.
Do you think he was
worried about our baby,
cos of what happened
to that poor little boy?
I think when he saw Ryan
in the cafe the other day,
he got scared.
He's scared!
I nearly lost my baby today.
Gemma, listen to me, please.
Sam needs you.
If he thinks you can forgive him,
I believe he'll come home.
You get some rest, yeah?
Sam, it's Detective Sergeant Croft.
Please, please get in touch.
Gemma knows your past and
she wants you to come home.
You're not in any
trouble with the police
and we promise we'll
protect you from Ryan Long.
- Have you heard anything from Amy?
- She'll be all right.
Sorry.
- What about the phone trace?
- It'll be another 30 minutes.
I called Ryan on his old
address. His ex-wife lives there.
- Does she know where he is now?
- No idea.
She told me where he works.
I'm waiting for someone to call me.
You need to chase them up.
Could be them.
Missing Persons Unit.
It's Sam.
Sam, it's Detective Sergeant Croft.
Tell Gemma I'm sorry.
Tell her I'm coming home.
- Sam, just tell us where you are and we'll...
- No!
I'll come myself after...
After what?
'I'm being a coward. I've
always run away. I need to...'
Sam. Sam, please.
I need to face him.
Sam?
If he gets to Ryan before we do and
Amy gets caught in the crossfire...
Sam?
All right. Um...
It's Ryan's boss.
OK.
Open that drawer over there.
There's a letter in it. Go on.
I had a total breakdown.
- Lost my wife, my job...
- I'm really sorry...
I was just starting to
get my life back when...
He sends that letter. No!
Read it out.
"Dear, Ryan. This is Alex Steel.
"I hope it's OK me writing to you.
- "The thing is, I just got out of prison..."
- Out!
Should have got life!
Go on.
"What I did to Rory, I'll never
be able to forgive myself for.
"He was a great little kid and I
just hope that you can understand..."
That day,
he's there in the cafe.
And I know he saw me because
he ran and I went after him.
And he's in his car
white as a sheet.
I told him that I would
find out where he was living
and I would hunt him down and I
would waste his life like he did mine.
And I would never ever stop!
I can't imagine
what you've been through.
It's exhausting.
You've already called them.
- You called the police!
- No! I didn't! Help!
Help! Let me go!
Please help! I'm in here.
&lt; Ryan, it's me. It's Alex Steel.
- What?
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Calm down.
- I'll calm down when I've got Amy out of there.
Oi, I said calm down!
The last thing I need
is some hot-headed,
macho cop throwing his
weight around, all right?
All right?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
All right, let me do the talking.
I don't want any of your macho stuff.
Listen.
Stand back.
Amy!
All right?
Oh, MJ, thank God! Sam's
in there. Ryan's got him.
You took everything away from me!
- Please, just listen.
- No, no!
No!
You stay out of this. You stay back!
It's all right, Ryan. It's all right.
Listen to me. You can't do this. You can't.
Stay back!
- Put it down.
- I can't.
Today, you left his wife on
the floor. She's pregnant, Ryan.
What?
You nearly killed an unborn child.
Is that what you are, Ryan?
- Is he all right?
- He's fine.
He'd like to see you if
that's all right with you.
Yeah, of course.
Is the baby all right?
Strong heartbeat. No more bleeding.
I'm so sorry, Gemma, for everything.
Why couldn't you tell me?
I... I've made such a mess
of everything. All the debts.
Well, you should have told me.
I... I just wanted you to be happy.
I'm so sorry.
Well, just promise me...
... you won't keep
anything from me again.
I promise.
You OK?
I was pretty scared back there,
but I'm feeling better now.
What will happen to him?
He'll be facing charges.
Two for assault, one for
holding you against your will.
Poor man.
I feel sorry for him.
Well, at least he'll get
the support he needs.
If you want some time
off, then just ask.
You don't have to decide now,
but we will have to do
a debrief at some point.
I think today the devil
really was in the detail.
Sorry.
Hey, we never got that drink.
Are you free tonight?
Yeah, could be. But you're buying.
After today, I reckon you owe me one.
What, just the one?
Don't push it.
MJ, fancy joining us?
No, you're all right. I promised
Danny I'd go on his show.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Good night.
- Night.
Oi, you two.
I don't want you in late tomorrow.
If you know what I mean.
No chance.
Things didn't work out.
- We won't be keeping in touch.
- I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I was a bit hard on you before.
You were just trying to do a nice thing.
So thank you.
We're on.
You're listening to Danny Hayworth.
Just to remind my listeners,
I'm here with DS Croft, who
is ready to take your calls.
Now, we have a caller.
I understand you would
prefer to remain anonymous.
Yeah. But I would like
to speak to DS Croft.
Hello, can I help you?
I was recently reunited with
my sister after 12 years.
And how did it go?
Not well.
That's often the way with first
meetings after long separations.
People have changed.
They can seem like strangers, becuase...
because they're not part of
each other's lives any more.
But if you give it time...
If you work at it,
it'll be worth it.
Does that make sense?
It does. Yeah.
I think you should give
your sister a second chance.
I hoped that's what you'd say.
Good luck, caller.
Subtitles By Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk