2011256258.
201125...
6258.
2011256258.
Yep.
Sorry, I'll have to call you back.
Dover Missing Persons Unit.
Sorry, DC Doyle's not
here at the moment.
256258.
2011256258.
Amy Garnett's phone.
She should be in any minute.
Yaeh, I will. Thank you.
It's 20 past nine!
2011256258.
- 2011...
- All right, son?
You OK there?
We'd better not go in
together. People might suspect.
Wait a minute before you follow me.
Please tell me your name.
Have you run away from home?
Morning, Sarge.
The officer will take
you to our interview room.
Would you like a drink?
Juice or something?
Cheers.
Where was he picked up?
Wandering along Kingsway.
He won't, or can't, tell
us his name and address.
Can't?
Hasn't said anything apart
from a sequence of numbers.
Drugs? Shock?
I don't know.
Someone's looking for him.
Let's find out who he
is and get him home.
- Sorry I'm late...
- I'm really not interested, Amy.
You clock in on time
like the rest of us.
That applies to you, too, DC Doyle.
I want you to take MPU as
seriously as you did Vice.
You never know.
You might learn something.
Bring Amy up to speed. I want to
find out who that young man is.
We need to find out where you
live so we can take you home.
Can we take a look in your bag?
Won't your family be worried?
Is there someone we could contact?
There's nothing, apart
from this key ring.
AT, these your initials?
Alan?
Andrew?
Alex?
Can I take a look at your book?
Wow. These are great.
I checked the PNC. No-one matching
his description is missing.
Anthony Taylor.
Is that your name?
I'll go through the electoral roll.
Have you run away from home?
Don't worry. We'll soon
find out where you're from
and get you back safely.
Oh, MJ, I did some research on
the symptoms that Jason described.
Difficulty communicating,
verbal repetition.
He could have a form of autism.
I'll make some calls,
get some expert advice.
- You contact the LEA and social services.
- Will do.
Jase, when you're finished here,
fire escape. Bit of privacy.
No record at all of an Anthony Taylor?
Right.
Would you expect to have details
of everyone in the area with autism?
OK.
All right. Thank you. Bye bye.
Mary Jane!
How's my favourite detective
sergeant in the whole wide world?
How did you get past front desk?
With a friendly smile.
It's meant to be authorised people only.
They all know me.
Dover Radio mug!
It's a freebie just for you, and
I've got mouse mats and pens as well.
What are you after, Danny?
Well, it suddenly struck me
that you would be the perfect
person for my show tonight.
Your guest has dropped out.
Well, it's a blessing in disguise.
You'll be fantastic.
I'm not going on the radio.
And I certainly can't be
bribed with a...free mug.
- But it's my first show.
- No!
I thought you were happy
being a crime journalist.
What does Liz think about
you packing it all in?
She thinks it's a great idea.
She hopes I'll spend less
time drinking with coppers.
Probably just trying to humour
you through your mid-life crisis.
After the favours I've
done you over the years!
You've had your fair
share of exclusives.
I'm not going on your show.
We've known each other a long time, MJ.
Yes, too long, Danny. Out you go.
Out you go. Bye.
Look, um... Last night.
Don't get me wrong, it was...nice.
- Yeah?
- Probably. I mean,
we were really, really drunk.
Anyway, it was just a one-off. Right?
Um... OK.
- From now on, we're just good colleagues.
- Yeah. It's no problem.
- No need for any awkwardness.
- No!
- Right, I'll see you...
- Inside.
Yeah.
- OK.
- Yeah, it's cool.
It's cool.
OK.
Thanks.
Bye.
Any luck?
Broughton High School had a
pupil called Anthony Taylor
up until four years ago.
He was withdrawn by his mother, a
Sandra Taylor, to be taught at home.
Kent Autistic Family Support don't
have an Anthony Taylor on their books.
You found anything?
I have an Anthony Taylor and a
Sandra Taylor at 45 Bankshire Road.
There's a phone number.
Bankshire Road?
That's only five minutes' walk
from where Anthony was picked up.
It's looking likely, then.
Answer machine.
She's probably out looking for him.
Hi, this is Amy Garnett at...
Want me to go over?
I'll see if the neighbours
have Sandra's mobile.
No. No, I'll take it.
Are you OK?
Something's happened to my fiance,
Etienne. I don't know where he is.
- What's your name?
- Jan. Jan Morgan.
OK, Jan.
DC Doyle will take the
details. Through there, please.
Amy, I want you to sit
in on this interview.
Bit of female support?
No, I think Jason is fully in
touch with his feminine side.
Your fiance's full
name is Etienne George?
He's from St Lucia.
We should be on a flight
on our way over there now.
He was to pick me up hours
ago, but he didn't.
You've missed your flight?
I've tried calling him but
there's no answer on his mobile.
When did you last speak to him?
- Last night.
- How did he sound?
A bit stressed.
He still had things to sort out.
Have you checked at Etienne's place?
We've both given up our
flats to move to St Lucia.
So he's been staying with a
friend, but he's not there.
We're getting married next week.
Come on.
Look, I can't leave
you here on your own.
Please?
This is your house, isn't it?
OK. You stay there, right?
We met at work. I'd
been there for ten years.
Spent nine of them
thinking about leaving.
Boring office work.
Then Etienne started. He
was on the reception desk.
I didn't know what to
say to him at first,
but eventually he plucked up courage.
Never have much luck, you see.
Tend to get a bit carried away,
thinking I've met the one, only
only to find they're not
really into me in the same way.
Etienne's different.
So lovely.
When I got made redundant,
we thought "Let's do it.
Let's move to St Lucia."
Everyone says it's so
beautiful out there.
Do you have any photos of him?
Yeah.
Here's one taken at my leaving party.
Hates his photo being taken.
He's very good looking.
Yes.
Hello?
Anyone at home?
Sandra?
Has he got any friends
or relatives over here?
I've spoken to all his friends,
but no-one's heard from him.
All of his family live in St Lucia.
We're staying with them
until our house is finished.
- You're having a new house built?
- Yeah.
Things are so much cheaper
out there, Etienne said.
We put a deposit down.
It should be ready after the wedding.
Look.
Etienne's cousin's a property developer.
Can I borrow this,
to check if Etienne's
cousin has heard from him?
Sure.
Got your flight number?
Yeah, somewhere.
Why?
We need to check Etienne
wasn't on the plane.
He wouldn't have left without me.
We need to check everything.
Cheers.
Please.
Help me find him.
We'll do our best.
For goodness' sake, Anthony! You
nearly gave me a heart attack.
Do you know what happened here?
2011256258.
2011...
Anthony, where's your mum?
Have the numbers got
something to do with your mum?
2011256258.
Jason?
Sandra's left her mobile phone
and her keys in the house.
Either she left in a hurry,
or something's happened to her.
Our missing person isn't Anthony.
It's his mum, Sandra.
I called the airport.
Etienne wasn't on the flight.
See! I told you he
wouldn't go without me.
There were no flights
booked in your names.
You must have made a mistake.
We went to the travel agents together.
I called them too.
Etienne went and
cancelled. He got a refund.
They must have misunderstood.
We were meant to be leaving today.
His relatives are expecting us.
We were going to see the
new house for the first time.
How did you pay the house deposit?
That was me. I had my
redundancy, didn't I?
I gave the money to Etienne and
he sorted it with his cousin.
Do you mind me asking how much it was?
Four thousand pounds.
Can you give us a second?
You know the expression love is blind.
Seems he cleared her back account.
He cancelled the flights.
Why isn't she suspicious?
We need to check out his cousin.
He might shed some light on it.
Yeah, I'll look into it.
Good call asking about the
deposit. I was gonna do that.
Yeah, but I beat you to it.
We need to search the surrounding areas.
Go door to door, talk to neighbours,
see if they've seen or heard anything.
We're now treating Sandra
Taylor as a missing person.
I want her located urgently.
OK.
Cheers.
Is this your mum and dad, Anthony?
Do you know where your dad lives?
Don't worry. We'll find him.
St Lucian Land Registry have
no record of the development.
The plot of land doesn't exist.
What about Etienne's cousin?
They've never heard
of him, or his company.
But you saw the brochure!
There'll be an explanation.
Apart from the money you
lent him for the deposit,
- was there anything else?
- Yeah.
I gave him 3,500 pounds to
get the rings and a suit,
something nice for the wedding day.
But I saw them!
He couldn't resist.
I told him I wanted it to be a surprise,
but Etienne was so excited
he showed them to me.
- Even put the suit on.
- Where did he buy them?
The suit came from that
department store in town.
He said he got the rings from
one of those jewellers nearby.
But it was all my idea. I
forced him to take the money.
He was embarrassed. We just
wanted to do things right.
I understand what you're thinking,
but Etienne wouldn't do that!
Don't worry.
We'll keep looking.
Thank you.
How are you doing with Jan?
She's a bit calmer now.
I don't think we'll get the
romantic ending she hopes for.
Sounds intriguing.
It's all in hand, MJ.
I'm assuming this is
Anthony's father and Sandra.
According to marriage
records, he's Edward Taylor.
They got married in 88, divorced
three years ago. Track him down.
And Anthony kept
repeating these numbers.
It's not a phone number.
Bank account or computer password?
Maybe he plays bingo!
Your jokes are as bad
as your timekeeping.
See what you can come up with.
We've got an Edward Taylor
in for assault four years ago.
He was fined and bound
over to keep the peace.
Same date of birth.
- Got an address?
- Yeah.
Go and see him.
Morning.
DC Jason Doyle, Dover
Missing Persons Unit.
- I'm looking for an Edward Taylor.
- I didn't even know I was missing!
- Are you Edward Taylor?
- Yeah.
Sorry, couldn't resist. Eddie.
Are you related to Anthony
Taylor of 45 Bankshire Road?
Yeah, he's my son. Is everything OK?
He was found on his own
earlier this morning.
Can I ask if your son's
autistic, Mr. Taylor?
He is. Where was his mum?
We're trying to locate
her. We hoped you'd help.
It's over a year since I've seen them.
We'd like you to come to the station.
We need to find out what's happened.
Sorry, I've got a two-month-old
baby and a business to run.
Anthony's on his own there.
Look, Sandra made it clear
that she and Anthony wanted
nothing more to do with me.
Why's that?
I've got a baby to see to. Sorry
I couldn't be of any more help.
Your son needs you.
Sandra would never
leave Anthony on his own.
- He'll have wandered off. She'll be looking for him.
- I don't think so.
You really need to come with
me to the station, Mr Taylor.
Now.
I have to make sure Karen
and Daisy are OK first.
Not now, Danny.
If there is one thing I learned
in all my years of reporting
crime, it's persistence.
I think I said no.
You'll regret it if you don't!
Look, It's great PR for
the Missing Persons Unit.
- You sound desperate.
- No!
- Of course not.
- Get someone else, then. Bye.
No, don't go. Don't go.
OK. I'm desperate.
You didn't ask me first.
Now you ask me because you
want to get out of a hole.
- You'll make me suffer for this.
- Of course.
Please?
I promised my producer I'd
get someone for the show,
and it's not looking good. Come on, MJ.
OK, what time?
Oh, fantastic!
Well, get there about 8 o'clock
and I'll show you the ropes.
Don't worry. You'll be
brilliant. The public'll love you.
Hello?
How are you getting on with
Anthony and those numbers?
I've ruled out phone
numbers and bus numbers,
but to be honest,
they could be anything.
OK, well, stay on it.
According to the Inland Revenue,
Sandra was self-employed.
She sold jewellery online.
- That throw up any contacts?
- No.
The company that suppliers the material
haven't spoken to her in months.
Ok, get uniform at the house.
Get her bank and credit card statements.
Find out how the business is doing.
Any news on Etienne yet?
We're still chasing a few angles and
waiting for St Lucia police to reply.
Excellent.
Hello, son.
What's happening, eh?
Where's your mum?
Anthony!
Thanks for coming in, Mr Taylor.
Anthony, why don't you do your
colouring while we talk to your dad?
I've never seen him so withdrawn.
What do you think could have upset him?
Breaking his usual routine.
Being apart from Sandra.
Has it been hard for you,
being excluded from his life?
- What's that got to do with anything?
- You must be bitter...
- and angry.
- Jason!
When was the last time you saw Sandra?
More than a year ago.
And you've no knowledge of
who would smash up her house?
What?
November 2004, you admitted a
charge of actual bodily harm.
I gave a loudmouth a slap for
taking the mickey out of Anthony, ok.
I've been at home with
Karen and Daisy all morning.
Instead of having a go at me,
you should look for Sandra!
If you could just wait a sec.
A word, please.
Jason, in this department,
we deal with people whose friends
and loved ones are missing.
They are not suspects.
He's her ex, and he's got
a previous for violence.
It was worth a go. No, it wasn't!
You need to brush up
on your people skills.
That's why you were transferred
here in the first place.
Someone get their wrists slapped?
Don't worry about it. Get a
bite to eat. It'll be fine.
- I'm not really doing food.
- What?
You're not hungover?
Canteen cappuccino. Works every time.
DC Doyle gets a bit carried
away at times, but he means well.
We need all the help we
can get finding Sandra.
What can I do?
Tell me all about her.
How long were you together?
Since we were kids, really.
She was my first serious girlfriend.
What happened?
Grew apart, like lots of couples.
I'm sure you were both
under a lot of pressure,
bringing up Anthony.
She... We decided to treat his
autism as a manageable condition.
That's easy to say with
a young boy, isn't it?
Sandra was determined we could care
for Anthony without
outside help, but I disagreed.
Was it hard, leaving your son?
We decided it would be best
for me not to be involved.
You don't sound too sure.
I love my son.
Having a kid with a disability...
changes everything.
I don't see what any of this
has to do with finding Sandra.
Everything helps. Believe me.
The only thing that Anthony
has said since we found him
is a series of numbers
he keeps repeating.
Any idea what they could mean?
He's been obsessed with
numbers since he was a baby.
One year it would be train timetables,
the next year, flight numbers...
2011256258.
Sorry.
What do these numbers mean, Anthony?
Have they got anything
to do with your mum?
Have you hurt yourself, Anthony?
I just want to check that you're OK.
No! Anthony!
No one's going to hurt you, Anthony.
I just want to check you're OK.
Anthony! Look, no, leave.
There's nothing wrong, all
right? Everyone's going.
He...he just gets a little upset
if there's a lot of people around.
Leave him alone. He'll
calm down in a few minutes.
OK.
He's always had a temper.
Just got worse as he grew older.
Our GP said there was medication
we could give him to keep him calm.
Sandra was furious. Said I wanted
to turn him into a vegetable.
I think we've got to assume that
Anthony caused the damage at the house.
There's no sign of forced entry.
Anthony's bruised.
- Legenda não traduzida -
Is he capable of harming Sandra?
Doesn't know his own strength.
20...11...256258.
2011...256258.
2011256...25...8.
This is starting to look more
serious than just a missing person.
What'll happen to Anthony?
Let's just try and find Sandra first.
I might need to talk to CID,
but I don't want to
jump to any conclusions.
From the St Lucia police.
What do you reckon?
- Are you OK after Anthony?
- I'm fine.
What have you got there?
Two property scams. Slightly
different MO to our Etienne.
Two couples bought holiday homes
over there that didn't exist,
but the company involved
had exactly the same
PO box number as the
one in Jan's brochures.
Got any other leads?
Jan lent him money to buy wedding rings.
Amy's been looking into it.
Good teamwork.
Yeah. She's a fast learner.
And it normally takes me
so long to pick things up!
Really good teamwork!
I'm sorry. That came
out wrong. It was...
How's that hangover of yours?
Well, I thought it was getting better.
He's had about 15 minutes. He'll
probably be a bit calmer now.
He can take as long as he likes.
Might be good to check
in on him, serious.
Whatever you need to do.
Thank you. For being so understanding.
Sandra's bank card was used
in the chemists 20 minutes ago.
Medistores chemist.
It's at the very end of the High Street.
Get over there with a photo
of Sandra. Ask for witnesses,
any indication of her state of
mind or where she was heading.
I've been going through
Sandra's bank statements,
and business isn't exactly booming.
Credit crunch.
Her personal account's
not much better either.
Her overdraft is maxed.
So on top of everything else, the poor
woman's up to her eyeballs in debt.
Where's Anthony? He's
not in the interview room!
It's my fault. I told you to leave him.
- He can't have got far.
- He's not been out through reception.
Fire escape.
This is all we need.
We've got all units
out looking for Anthony.
We've circulated the description,
we should pick him up soon.
I shouldn't have left him.
Anthony is clearly distressed.
It wasn't your fault.
I never make the right decisions.
- Any idea where he may have gone?
- He'd normally be with his mum.
Look, can I...step out
and get some fresh air?
As soon as I hear anything...
Thanks.
I had a call from Jason.
He's at the chemist.
Sandra bought a packet
of paracetamol and
then tried to buy three
more, but they refused her.
- She apparently looked distressed.
- That doesn't sound good.
I'll make some calls, see if
she's tried other chemists.
If she's that desperate,
she'll try and get more.
2011256258.
- Anthony.
- 2011256258.
- 201125...
- Anthony.
You need to come with me, Anthony.
- 2011256258.
- Come on.
Let me take you back to your dad.
You OK, son?
I was really worried about you.
Anything on Sandra?
Not yet.
I just left the chemist.
He wasn't that far from where
we picked him up this morning.
- I think he knows where she is.
- Why's that?
It can't be a coincidence.
We now know Sandra
was on the High Street,
and now Anthony was on the same route.
I think you're on to something.
And the numbers he's repeating
definitely means something.
I've got patrols on alert. I'll
check if she's bought more tablets.
I spoke to the jewellers. The assistant say that
Etienne returned the
wedding rings this morning.
Any idea where he went?
No, but we've the opportunity
to catch him red-handed.
Aparently he's got to go back there
at 5.30 to get the money off the owner.
The assistant can't give refunds.
Brilliant.
Do we tell Jan?
No, we need to be careful.
If he's a no-show at 5.30, we don't
want to have made any promises.
But she's downstairs.
We let her know we've
got a promising lead,
but the rest, we leave till after 5.30.
Someone matching Sandra's
description just bought
two packets of paracetamol
at a chemist's 20 minutes ago.
Where's the latest shop?
Vale Road, not far from town.
- What road was he found on this morning?
- Kingsway.
What number?
B2011.
Road numbers.
And I found him again on the A256.
Which leads to the A258.
She could be heading that
way. Route out of town.
The Heritage Coast
Trail runs along there.
Sandra was packing a picnic.
Make a list of all the
picnic spots around there.
Get patrols to check them
out. I'm gonna head over there.
She's on the Heritage Coastal
Trail, just past the visitor centre.
She looks OK. But send an
ambulance, just in case.
Sandra?
I'm DS Croft.
Dover Missing Persons Unit.
We've been looking for you.
Anthony's really worried.
- Is he OK?
- He's fine.
I've made such a mess of things.
It's OK.
I've really let him down.
What happened?
I got him the wrong colouring book.
He...he got into one of his tempers.
I told him to calm down,
or we wouldn't go out.
He slammed the bathroom door shut.
He didn't know I was right behind him.
We saw the blood.
He was so angry.
I was screaming at him,
threatening to go without
him just...just to punish him.
It was so silly.
Going on a picnic when...
when I've got all these debts.
You've had a really tough time.
Anthony doesn't mean
to be such a handful,
but...it's just so relentless.
Anthony's at the station with Eddie.
I genuinely think he wants
to help out, and financially.
Well, he's gonna have to now.
Sandra?
Sandra, have you taken any tablets?
Sandra!
Sandra, come on.
How many have you taken?
Sandra, tell me, please!
Yeah, that's him.
Etienne?
I'm DC Jason Doyle. I'm with
the Dover Missing Persons Unit.
Jan Morgan asked us to find you.
The police?
It's my fault. Please, I'm so sorry.
Where's the money, Etienne?
That's all there is.
I told them to make it out to her.
I'm going to get the
money back on the suit.
The least I can do is get
her back her 3,500 pounds.
What about the 4,000 pounds?
My cousin took it.
He said trust him.
I persuaded Jan.
I love her.
- Am I going to be arrested?
- No.
But I think you need to
explain to Jan what happened.
You owe her that more than any money.
- Thanks, Doctor.
- No problem.
They managed to pump her stomach
in time, but it was close.
- They're keeping her in.
- How's Anthony?
He's calm now.
If Sandra agrees, he can
come home with us tonight.
Of course.
- How are you feeling?
- Not great.
I had no idea things had got so bad.
I tried too hard.
Thought it was for the best.
You were right.
I couldn't cope. You're not to
blame. I struggle with Anthony.
What else could you do?
I'm sorry.
Please, I...I want to
make it up to you both.
She's in here.
I just wanted to say how sorry I am.
- I trusted you.
- I know.
Why, Etienne?
I sent the money to my
cousin, but he lied to us both.
- He'd taken it all.
- Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted it to be perfect.
I never thought this would happen.
You agreeing to marry me,
move to St Lucia, everything.
I didn't even think you would go
for a drink with me, let alone...
I've messed it all up.
- No.
- I didn't know what to do.
I took the money for the
flight and hired a solicitor,
and he confirmed what I already knew.
He said I should go to the police.
It is my fault.
I let you down.
You shouldn't have run, Etienne.
I am so sorry.
You should have trusted me.
Not gonna take a punt on this one,
but I reckon the wedding's still on.
I knew there was a reason
you were a detective.
Very funny.
Certainly used to be.
It may not be Vice, but it still
feels like a good day's work.
- Thank you.
- Both of you.
It's our pleasure.
You fancy a drink? Just
good colleagues and all that?
Sorry, Jase.
It's probably best we give it a
miss, you know? Maybe another night.
Yeah. No problem. I understand.
I can't tonight anyway.
MJ's just called.
She's ordered me to take part
in this radio show she's doing.
She thinks they'll be interested
in all my techie palaver.
Sounds like she wants some support.
Probably. She's really nervous.
I've always wanted to go
on the radio. Can't wait!
So, after you've successfully reunited
a missing person with their loved ones,
does your department have any
more involvement with the family?
No. We're just charged with
locating the missing person.
However, there are support
groups and charities
we can refer people
to if they need help.
What if the person who you found
doesn't want any contact
with their friends and family?
If they're an adult,
there's nothing we can do.
We can let them know that they're
being looked for, and then we can
let the person who reported them
missing know that they're OK.
Thank you, DS Croft.
After the break, we'll be straight
back with your calls. So, tell us.
Have you got any questions on
what the Missing Persons Unit do?
Or perhaps you'd like to find out more about the
technical side of the investigations from Amy.
Or perhaps there's somebody you'd
like to find, and you need some advice.
We'll be right back with your calls.
How many callers have we got?
None.
Great!
Well, hopefully they'll
start phoning in soon.
You were brilliant.
Maybe we should swap!
Going back on air.
It looks as though all you folks
are still watching the match!
So, Amy, how big a part do computers
play in these investigations?
Well, there's the ANPR,
which is the automatic
number plate reader.
And the AVLS,
which is the automatic
vehicle location system.
Er, and there's, um...
DS Croft, um...
..I know that you've got some personal
experience regarding a missing person yourself.
I'm not sure the listeners
are interested in any of that.
Well, it's a fascinating story,
the head of the Missing Persons
Unit with a missing relative herself.
My sister ran away a few years ago.
She was missing for a while, yeah.
It must have given you a hidden insight
into the emotions of those left behind.
No, not really.
I like to keep my personal life
and my work life totally separate.
But surely you can empathise more,
having been through it yourself?
I suppose so.
- Your sister...
- Ellen.
She was very young
when she ran away, 17?
We lost our mother when she was
young and I looked after her.
So she just went missing
and she went abroad?
I didn't know that at the time.
I tracked her to France.
But you spent the better part
of a year searching for her.
All that uncertainty
must have been hard.
Very.
Could you tell us why Ellen ran away?
I know it's hard.
Ellen was living in a
squat and it burnt down.
She was...presumed dead, is that right?
They told me she died in a fire, yes.
Thank you, DS Croft.
I know it couldn't have
been easy talking about it.
But hopefully, your honesty
will inspire my listeners
to be brave about their own experiences.
What the hell do you
think you're doing!?
I'm sorry, MJ. I didn't know
what to ask. It just came out.
- It was emotional. It was brilliant.
- You had no right, Danny!
But it worked, MJ!
It could help somebody.
My personal life's not entertainment!
Maybe I pushed it a bit too far,
but I think you're over-reacting.
You're out of order, Danny.
MJ, look, I'm sorry!
MJ!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk