Lindy?
Thanks, sorry to call so late.
What's up?
She hasn't come home.
Well, this is nice!
I don't make the laws.
You don't have to smoke either...
Addict.
Look, MJ, I know you are upset with me.
I'm not upset, Danny, I'm furious.
You sat there and dragged
up all the details of
my sister's disappearance
live on your radio show.
They told me she was dead, Danny.
Dead.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have done it.
But people really
responded to the story, MJ.
My job is to find missing persons
not to entertain your audience.
So, let me help you.
I got thousands of listeners, every
one of then your eyes and ears.
I'll think about it.
DS Croft.
All right.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Gotta go.
A teenage girl run away
from home last night.
Perfect...
For the show.
Oh, forget it.
They'll be talking again, right?
You're in early.
- What?
- You got ketchup on your face.
What's that?
Is that Ellen Croft?
Yeah.
It's MJ's sister, I aged up the photo.
You'd better get rid of that
before the sarge gets in.
Now look, I did some digging
and I found these newspaper stories
about the squat fires in Marseilles.
No, no, don't involve me in this.
I went through a list of all the people
reported dead and found
all sorts of discrepancies.
Basically It was almost
impossible to say who died.
There's this guy,
he left the squat minutes
before the fire started.
He had no idea people
thought he was dead until
he came back to the UK two years later.
This is Kieran Russell.
He knew Ellen. I e-mailed
him and he just replied.
She didn't die. MJ has got it wrong.
Ellen survived the fire.
Are you gonna tell her?
Cos if you do... Jason,
stop flirting and get your coat.
We've got a case and I want to
talk to the family straightaway.
Initial checks please, Amy.
Her name as Alison Hughes,
aged 16, 24 Branscombe Gardens.
She didn't come home last night.
Hospitals, traffic,
morgues, the usual. You know.
Maybe she just got drunk
and crashed at a mates house.
Isn't that what
16-year-olds do?
No, that was just you.
Thanks.
Is your husband out at work, Lindi?
No, he's out looking for Ali.
Something's happened.
Ali has never stayed out all
night without our approval, never.
Did she always tell you where she's gonna be?
- Yes, always.
Where does she normally go?
Shopping, her friends' houses.
- What about bars, clubs?
- No, Ali doesn't drink.
We don't allow it. Carl
and I don't drink so...
Sorry, what's this got to do with it?
What about her friends,
do they drink or use drugs?
Drugs?!
We're just trying to build up a picture
of Ali's world, her group of friends.
Is it possible to have a
look at her room, please?
Look,
we are a close family.
If Ali had been offered
drugs she'd tell me.
Her room's up here.
Any more theories, Poirot, you
share them with me not her, OK?
Sorry!
- Can I help you?
- So sorry, it's Frank.
- Amy.
- Stan.
- Who's Frank?
- Sinatra.
They sent me up here,
I'm trying to find Missing Persons.
You found it.
Have you got a recent photo
of Ali we could borrow?
Yeah.
You won't find it under there, mate?
Find what?
This.
Vodka. Let's hope she
took some tonic with it.
It was in Ali's school bag.
Hello?
Up here.
- Did you know?
- No.
Nothing...
Carl...
- So who's missing, Stan?
- My brother.
- We're twins.
- OK, and what's his name?
We lost touch ages ago
but our mother passed away a
few weeks ago and I wanted to...
You know.
Stan, his name?
That's the thing, I'm not sure.
You don't know your
twin brother's name?
I can't even be sure I've got one.
- What was she even doing with them?
- Someone must have given them to her.
Any idea who?
- Mr. Hughes?
- No, I don't.
Just wait till she gets home.
I know you're upset but try
not to be to angry with her.
Does Ali have a computer?
We gave her a laptop for Christmas.
Can we have a look at it, please?
Most girls her age have
at least tried a drink.
Look, my old man was a boozer.
I've seen what it does to people.
And what does Ali think about that?
- Does it cause any tension?
- No,
she understands.
Shouldn't you be out
there looking for her?
It's always nice to feel welcome.
Come on, Jason.
He feels helpless, he
needs someone to blame.
- Great, so he picks us.
- His daughters missing.
We can't do enough.
I'm worried she hasn't at least
rung with parents like that.
Maybe because she's
scared of Mr. Angry.
Let's just concentrate
on finding it, shall we?
Mum suffered from dementia
for the last three years.
She used to ramble
on, all these memories.
Then she said something that made
the hairs on my neck stand up.
She told me I had a twin brother.
- And you never knew?
- Not a clue.
- Your dad, is he...?
- I never knew him.
He was killed in France, 1940.
I don't want to seem rude,
Stan, but you said your mum...
No, yeah, maybe it was
just more of her gibberish
but it might not have been.
And now I need to know.
Have you looked for a birth certificate?
Mum was a bit of a hoarder.
I can't even find mine let alone his.
The thing is, it's not really our thing.
We specialise in finding people
we know exist in the first place.
But you're my last hope
really I... Look, I've done all this.
This family tree back as far
as my mum's great grandfather.
That's amazing!
Yeah, but it's not given me any answers.
Look, there's one or
two things I can try
but I'll have to get my boss's
approval so no promises, OK.
I'll call and let you know.
I like your new boyfriend.
Family Tree Trace Your Roots.
I know, I know.
He's searching for his lost twin.
Tell me this is a joke.
He was a really sweet old guy.
Did you tell him to try the library?
His mum's just died.
All right, but don't
spend too long on it, OK.
Right, I need you to get into this.
You're looking for anything on
where their owner was last night.
- I'll get that photo blown up.
- There's something else actually.
- What?
- Can I have a word?
What's this?
In your office.
Amy, what the hell are you
doing, this is my sister's file?
Please, you really need to hear this.
No, this can't be
right. She died. She...
Kieran definitely knew her.
I didn't use your
surname and he knew it.
What gives you the right to go
digging about in my personal life?
I really wanted to look into
it, I thought it could help.
I've asked him to call me.
What?
You have no right to
be doing any of this.
But we don't know what happened
to Ellen after the fire.
You're talking about my sister, Amy.
I thought she was dead.
You don't know what
I've been through.
- I thought you'd want to know.
- Well, you thought wrong.
This ends. Now.
What's that?
It's a photograph... I aged it up.
Danny is downstairs. He said
he'd wait outside for you.
Oh, come on, MJ. I've sold
my producer hard on this.
I told her I was planning
a teenage runaway special.
Danny, Ali Hughes' mum is
out of her mind with worry
and all you want is a
juicy item for your show.
We could help you find her.
No means no.
Look what happened last week.
Now I've got Amy digging around in files
- telling me Ellen's still alive.
- What?
So what are you going to do, are you
going to start looking for her again?
No.
They told me she was dead, Danny.
I followed so many leads, I
spent so many months searching.
And then the fire...
You need to end this.
You need to know.
Let Amy help you find her.
- She hasn't sacked you then?
- Funny.
You cracked it yet?
There's a website she uses,
I just need the password.
- Have you tried Ali 1?
- I've tried Ali 1 to 999.
Same for Alison Hughes,
street name, school name.
All right. Mine's Attila.
- It's my hamster.
- You've got a hamster?
No, when I was a kid.
Pet names.
Ali has got a rabbit, I saw a photo...
You got anything from that?
Some stuff, yeah, I just
need to crack the password.
If this Kieran Russell
does get in touch,
I want you to inform me immediately.
And if I want you to stop
at any time I'll tell you.
No questions asked.
Right.
Do you want me to
formally reopen the case?
Yes. Thank you.
Ali Hughes.
A runaway,
an abduction, an accident?
Runaway. Family row.
Slow down, we've got no evidence.
The bottle of vodka, the angry Dad.
He was at work when she went missing.
What does he do?
Private hire driver. Drive suits
around for one of the big taxi firms.
He was on shift till 2.30am.
Something might have happened
that morning or to the nigth before.
Let's just concentrate
on where she is for now.
Bingo! I'm in! Thank you, Robbie...
Ali's pet rabbit.
The night she went
missing, just after seven,
she was chatting on-line
with Karen Leyland, or Kaz.
She's four years older than Ali
and here's her mobile number.
I haven't seen her.
Kaz, we know that you were the
last person that Ali chatted to.
- I haven't seen her.
- She's been missing for two days.
Look at her, Daddy's little girl.
What do you mean?
Kaz?
I think you know where she is.
- I don't have to be here.
- Kaz.
Kaz!
- Kaz!
- Get off me!
Listen to me, please.
I just need to know where
she is and if she's all right.
I can't make her do anything
she doesn't want to do.
She's upset, you know.
I can't force her to go home.
If you want to get rid of me
then just let me see her, please.
This is wonderful!
I hardly scratched the surface.
This is what I wanted to show you.
Your mother's cousin, Sheila
Crook. You know she had a son?
I couldn't find anything about him.
What was his name?
Neil. Neil Crook.
Here's his birth certificate.
4th September, 1940.
Good grief, that's my birthday!
Ali? I'm DS Croft.
You promised, you promised me.
Ali, it's fine really.
She's the police!
Ali, you're not in trouble.
Ali, just listen, she's
not gonna make you go home.
She just needs to know you're all right.
So I pulled up a list of everyone
born in Dover on the same day as you,
and looked for matches
with your extended family.
- That's where Neil came up.
- But surely he's my cousin?
If what your mum said was true,
then she was left
alone with twin babies.
You think she put one of us up for
adoption? I checked all the agencies.
It wasn't unheard of for
extended families to help out.
Unofficial adoption, that sort of thing.
Neil Crooks. So...
So, you're saying he's my brother?
He might be.
Probably turn out to be
a complete coincidence,
so please don't get your hopes up.
Missing persons.
Speaking.
Kieran... Kieran Russell?
Can you just hang on?
Stan, I'm really sorry but
I have to take this. Kieran.
- Legenda não traduzida -
Yeah, thanks for calling me back.
I'm desperate to find
out anything about Ellen.
What are your plans, Ali?
-I'm gonna stay here.
- So what happened?
Is it about your dad?
We had a row. What about?
When did this row happen Ali?
I thought you said I wasn't in trouble.
Your dad's not angry, Ali, he
just wants you to come home.
So, we sent you to fetch me?
Your mum's worried sick.
Don't.
OK, I'll tell her you
won't be coming home then.
You're over 16 now.
You just say the word and you'll
never have to see her again.
All I know as she loves you very much.
Ali!
I'm sorry, Mum.
My God, look at you.
You're OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
How about a hug?
You saw the way they
were with each other.
What did you expect him to do?
She said they had a row. How
come he never mentioned it?
Guilt. We see it all the time.
People who are ashamed of something
they said in the heat of the moment.
I think she's terrified of him. There's
something going on in that house.
Do you think we did the right thing?
Don't get carried away.
He's just strict, that's all.
My guess is there will be a hell
of a row in that house tonight.
I hope that's all there is.
Hi, Stewart.
Busy lunch break?
I've got one lead but I'm worried
Stan is pinning all his hopes on it.
- I don't suppose...
- What?
You couldn't get him on
Danny's radio show, could you?
He'd be a great guest and
he certainly likes to talk.
If you think it will help.
And it'll get Danny off my back.
Oh, MJ...
He called. Kieran.
Where did he and Ellen
go after the fire?
Barcelona.
Is she still there?
It's complicated.
Erm... They were drug users.
What kind of drugs?
Heroin.
Kieran got busted, he did
some time in a prison in Spain.
- And Ellen?
- They lost touch.
He said she was in a bad
way the last time he saw her.
I've checked the EU databases and
there's a couple of court appearances.
The last one was four years ago.
Is that it?
There's not many records kept of
people... Of people like Ellen.
Junkies, you mean?
MJ, I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
You're listening to the Danny
Hayworth show on Dover Radio.
Tonight, we're talking to a man
who's searching for a twin brother.
His name his Stanley Marsh.
He was born here in Dover
on 4th September, 1940
and lived in the Hadden Street area.
So, Stan, it's a bit of a long shot
after all these years, isn't it?
We think we might have
found him, actually.
Well, I hope not, Stan,
because there goes my show!
- But go on, tell me more!
- His name's Neil Crook.
But we don't know where he is now.
So, DS Croft, that's a
bit of a breakthrough.
Is this case cracked?
No, no, I wouldn't say that.
I mean, this Neil Crook
is a possibility, Stan,
but without concrete proof,
we need to keep on looking.
The thing is, we share a
birthday. 4th September.
All right, so, if anybody remembers
this Neil Crook,
or if that date rings a bell,
get in contact in the usual
way or log onto the website.
This is the Danny
Hayworth Show, Dover Radio.
What's with the tap, tap, tap?
Are you trying to put people off?
Sorry.
Producer won't let me smoke in here.
- It's driving me nuts.
- Oh, what a fascist!
It's a workplace, Danny.
Smoking is illegal.
I told her, I'm not going
two hours without a fag!
Stop the world!
Dan the man needs his fix!
What's your problem?
She's a junkie, Danny.
My little sister's a heroin addict.
If it hasn't killed her yet.
Sorry.
I was all she had.
I could have stopped it.
Maybe if we find her,
we can get her some help.
Why don't you do us all
a favour and pack up.
Someone sent this in
straight after the show.
And she said she was in
Neil's class at school,
and I think that's him.
That's Neil!
That's of me.
Look at that! We could be twins!
Are you sure, Stan,
it's a 50-year-old photo.
We share a birthday.
The woman who sent this in said
that Neil was mad about climbing.
Why don't I check out all
the mountaineering clubs.
Sarge?
It's Ali, she's gone again.
I haven't seen her. Seriously.
So, where is she?
I knew this would happen.
What's happened, Kaz?
Did she tell you anything
about this row with her dad?
She didn't really talk
about it. She was upset.
She said she couldn't go home.
Is that who you're
protecting her from? Her dad?
Kaz, this is really important.
I can't.
It looks like you had a heavy night.
I'm a police officer, Kaz, if I open this,
I'll have to deal with whatever I find inside.
Don't do this. Please.
Look, she started seeing this guy.
We need a name.
Mark. Mark Stone.
Who is he?
Where can we find him?
- I don't know.
- Kaz?!
Please! I've given you his name,
now just leave me alone!
All right. Cheers.
Mark Stone. Who is he?
No arrests. No convictions.
Amy's checked him out. He's clean.
Kaz is lying.
She knows who he is and
she's terrified of him.
I'm gonna give Danny a call.
If this Stone's got
history, he'll know about it.
- Mark who?
- Stone.
Has Ali ever mentioned him at all?
No. Not to me.
Carl?
I thought she was with this Kaz.
Did she say anything last night?
Well, like I told you...
Sorry...
I was asking your husband.
Say anything about what?
I don't know, Carl, your
daughter has run away twice now.
Seems she'd rather be anywhere than home
and I can't help wondering why that is.
- What's he saying?
- What's that supposed to mean?
Ali told us she had a row with you.
There was no row. I was out working.
- What do you do to your daughter?
- Nothing.
- DC Doyle!
- Let's just worry
about where she is, OK?
Thanks for your help.
We'll be in touch.
- What the hell was that all about?
- I think he's abusing his daughter.
Yes, you made that quite clear.
Look how he acted.
He's hiding something.
His daughter is missing, DC Doyle!
He and his wife came to us for help.
You're in MPU now, not Vice,
sorry if you don't like
the way we do things,
- but you'd better get used to it.
- Sarge, there's something...
I am THAT far away from putting you
on report, Jason! So don't wind me up!
Forget about them.
Get back to the office and see
what you can dig up on Mark Stone.
Sarge.
I'm so sorry, Stan.
A climbing accident in the Alps.
What a terrible way to go.
Neil's death was
registered in France.
That's why it didn't show
up on any of our searches.
The Kent Mountaineering Club
had that in their archives.
So, my brother was dead
before I even knew he existed.
Well, we don't know for sure
that he was your brother, Stan.
And we don't know that he wasn't.
Tell you what, why don't I keep
looking, something else might come up.
No, no, I think I'll leave it.
Actually, I'm very grateful
for everything you've done.
I'm sorry.
Stan! Look, Stan, wait!
- Got you a coffee.
- Cheers.
Mark Stone!
You're keeping classy company, as usual.
What was you able to
find out about him?
A mate of mine,
contact from the good old days
when I was out fighting crime...
You were a crime reporter, Danny.
... says he's got a club here
on the harbour on Gable Lane.
It's legit, but he uses it as a front.
- What for?
- Escorts, mainly.
Class A's all the way
down to contraband fags.
Vice can't find a way
in. Nobody's talking.
- Any idea how I can find him?
- Well, you could try the club.
They won't give you anything.
Home address, anybody's guess, sorry.
- Thanks all the same.
- Always a pleasure.
Here, this is for Amy!
It's more information about Stan.
He's quite a star, you know.
Hmm, you wanna watch they
don't give him your slot!
Look, can we go in now, I'm freezing.
I meant it, you know, what
I said about you quitting.
You're beginning to
sound like my producer.
She's not gonna knock the edges
off Danny Haworth, neither are you.
Kaz?
Kaz? Yeah...
What's the matter?
He'll come back.
He's just a bit shocked.
I hope so. He's convinced
himself that Neil was his brother.
- Was he?
- I don't know for sure.
And how's it going with Ellen,
you found out anything more?
Not a lot.
One last court appearance about
four years ago. Possession, again.
- She get sent down?
- No, she paid the fine.
1,500 euros. How does a smack
head get that kind of cash?
That's what I was wondering.
Maybe she was on the game.
Amy, unless she looks like Keira
Knightley, a junkie prostitute's
- barely gonna make that in a month.
- So...
So, maybe she had a guardian angel.
What, someone was giving her money?
You could check the money wires.
Well, she won't have had a bank account,
but you don't need
one to be wired money.
If you've got a name and a city,
you can try a reverse trace
with all the big firms.
See if anyone has sent any money to her,
if they did, you can track it back.
Thanks, Jason.
How's it going with Ali Hughes?
Oh, it's a brick wall.
Erm...MJ asked if you could see if
there was anything on her dad, Carl.
What kind of thing?
Benefit claims, unpaid parking fines,
credit card history, the works, really.
Leave it with me.
Mark Stone.
He found you, did he?
- No, I went to his place.
- Why?
To get Ali away from there.
She's too young.
For what?
I was Mark's girlfriend, once.
I ran away from home, just like Ali.
There he was, all
smiles and cash, and...
Something to help you relax?
It was exciting. Something else.
Then, he wants you to
meet some of his friends.
Sadly, I'm not his girlfriend any more.
I work for him.
You know?
Is that what Ali is now?
Mark's girlfriend?
I warned her, but, she saw what
she wanted to see, just like I did.
So you went round to try and talk to
him.
Do you wanna press charges?
32 Elwood Court.
Just leave me out of it, all right?
Mark Stone?
DS Croft, DC Doyle,
Missing Persons Unit.
I was just making some coffee.
- Would you like some?
- Lovely.
Ali Hughes.
Yeah, I know her. Sweet kid.
And no, I haven't seen her, but if I do,
I'll tell her you're looking for her, eh?
Have you got her number?
Yeah.
Hello again, Ali.
- What do you want?
- I think you know.
Let's go back to Kaz's
for a chat, shall we?
No.
I live here now. With Mark.
And she's 16.
I think she can do what she wants.
And is this what you want?
- Yeah.
- Good luck to you.
Good girl.
Is there nothing we can
do to get her out of there?
Where to? Back home?
I thought her father
was the problem.
So what are you suggesting?
Ali won't leave Mark
Stone till she wants to.
Yeah, but she doesn't want to.
No, I think she does.
This is from Danny. Some more
information for your friend Stan.
Oh, thanks. And that stuff
you wanted is on your desk.
What stuff?
On Carl Hughes.
You wanted me to check him out?
Did I?
I asked her to do that, actually.
After I gave you a
clear order to drop it.
Well it might have turned something up.
It did.
He lost his private
hire licence a year ago.
Right. So he's working illegally.
Tell traffic. Not our problem.
What else you got?
He was questioned a couple of nights ago
about an incident involving
a group of drunken lads.
A couple of nights ago?
That's when Ali went missing.
- Any more details?
- Hang on.
Yeah, he refused to take them in his car
and it was on Gable Lane.
That's where Mark Stone's club is.
Question is, what was
he doing in his car
outside Stone's club,
the night Ali ran away?
Could be a coincidence.
Let me just check the CCTV,
see if there's any connection.
Or, should we just ignore it?
All right. Get on it.
Jason, this close...
Cheers. I owe you one.
Yeah, small point,
next time you're thinking
of lying to me, don't!
This is from the camera that
covers Stone's club two nights ago.
That's Carl going into the club.
Said he'd never heard of him.
Well, have a look at this.
There.
That's Karl and Mark Stone together.
Where did that bag come from?
Looks suspicious.
Yeah, and if it's drugs,
that's Carl Hughes' courier.
This is where it gets
really interesting.
Yeah, there's our little friend, Ali.
The row!
There it is.
Right.
Let's see what Carl's
got to say for himself.
You knew.
You knew! Our daughter is out there with
this man, and you knew all along.
- Lindy...
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Lindy, I couldn't.
- Who is he?
What is he doing with her?
Lindy, please.
Let's just hear what he's got to say.
I jumped a red light up by the
motorway and nearly hit someone.
I lost my private hire licence.
You what?
One of the other drivers
told Mark Stone about it.
- He offered me some work.
- But that's illegal.
We needed the money, Lindy.
He needed drivers.
Because he couldn't use
legit drivers, could he?
- Not for that.
- Not for what?
What's he mean?
I was...
he needed me to take
people to this place he had.
There were prostitutes, love.
That's what he does.
Oh God, my...my little girl!
What's in the bag, Carl?
- I don't know.
- Carl!
- It's cocaine.
- Cocaine?
He said if I said anything,
he'll send people round here.
He threatened to hurt you.
- To hurt Ali.
- And what about Ali?
When did you know about her?
- Two days ago.
- Oh, the night she went missing?
I didn't know she was seeing him!
But then I saw her at the club.
I tried to get her
home, but she was just...
she just got really angry.
Can I blame her?
There's me working for Mark Stone,
and telling my daughter go
home and be good with her mum.
She told me she hoped
she never saw me again.
- What could I do?
- You could have told me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Well, do something. Get her back.
How can I, now?
- Talk to us.
- If it gets him away from her, you have to.
Nah. She'd hate me even more.
I don't think that's possible.
Do you?
Someone was sending
her money every month?
Can you tell me who?
OK, well what about a location...
Kersley?
That's in Kent.
Yeah, I found it, thanks.
Amy.
Stan! I've been trying to
get hold of you all day!
Well, I haven't been at home.
I had to go and have a think.
Just me and Frank.
There was another
call from the radio.
No, no. Look, I'm sorry, Amy.
Neil is dead, I just
came to collect my books.
No Stan, listen.
It's not Neil.
There was this woman, she phoned in,
she worked for a doctor, a GP, and she...
- she sent this in.
- Oh please, Amy.
No, Stan, the dates match, just listen!
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
Stan, please! Her name is Cora.
She was a housekeeper for a doctor who
lived on Hadden Street, a Dr. Lacey.
Dr. Lacey?
He was our GP.
She said he and his wife
brought a baby home one night.
Cora knew it was a patient's, but it was
never spoken of and they raised him as her own.
- When?
- The first night of the Blitz.
Stan, I checked the date.
The night the Blitz started?
7th September, 1940.
Three days after my birthday.
Oh, and I found him on the registry.
And...
I found his birth certificate.
"Dear Lottie.
"I just received your letter.
"Twins, that's wonderful news.
"I hope to be home
before they arrive".
My father wrote it three
weeks before he was killed.
"If they're boys, we should name them
after our grandfathers, Stanley and...
- "and David."
- That's the name on here!
David.
Oh... Two of us, I mean, how could
she cope? With my father gone.
Oh, what a terrible choice.
- Poor Mum.
- Stan.
David's alive,
he lives right here, in Dover.
You don't all want coffee, do you?
You're funny.
Where is she? Ali! Ali!
It's all right.
- Who are your boyfriends?
- They're for you.
Sorry there's only two of them,
but the rest are down your club,
turning it over. Jason.
I'm arresting you for possession
of a controlled substance.
This is harassment!
You do not have to say anything,
it may harm your defence
if you do not mention when questioned
something which you later rely on in court.
Just wait here, I'll be back.
I don't think so.
What's going on?
He's a drug dealer, Ali.
Your dad told us the truth.
This is because of my dad?
He gave us a statement. He wants
to talk to you, to apologise.
Oh come on, Ali.
Whatever he's done, he's still your dad.
- You going to be all right?
- Yeah.
So, what do you wanna say?
Whatever it is you
were thinking I did...
is true.
All those things I was
telling you not to do...
Drinking?
Mark Stone threatened me.
He threatened your mum.
Our family.
You must know the sort of
people he hangs about with.
He's a dangerous customer, Ali.
I liked him.
I was driving around his girls.
They're no older than you are.
They're his clients,
he knows what they want.
- He was using you.
- No!
He wasn't going to...
I couldn't stay at home any more, Dad.
You were just so angry with
me, all the time, for nothing.
I just didn't want you to
mess your life up like I...
Like you?
I'm not stupid, Dad. I'm not a kid.
I know.
Sometimes I just really find it...
hard to let go.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm really sorry.
- Mum, is she OK?
- No.
She wants to kill me.
But most of all, she would
be really glad to see you.
Good result?
Admit it. I was right about her dad.
You were half-right.
And half-wrong.
Kersley.
That mean anything to you?
Where d'you hear that name?
From Capital Express.
Someone from Kersley were
sending money to Ellen.
When? Amy, when?
Every month, until about four years ago,
and then it stopped, suddenly.
A few hundred pounds each time, but
it's just a village, I just don't see...
Kersley.
That's where Mike's husband lives.
I'll take over now.
Amy...
thanks.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd