Timing and Subtitles brought to you byGone with the Shirts Team @ Viki
♫ Don't be upset when the moon is covered by clouds ♫
♫ That's just the wind showing its love ♫ b
♫ If the stars are the sea of sky ♫
♫ Then the moon is what the tide hopes for ♫
♫ When the clouds scatter ♫
♫ The moonlight shines upon the haze of this world ♫
♫ The world becomes still at this moment ♫
♫ Let go of everything ♫
♫ Who is infatuated to the radiance of freedom ♫
♫ Loves carelessly, then abandons love ♫
♫ Maybe a vow can last like the sea ♫
♫ As long as the heart doesn't change ♫
♫ That is the last thing I will worship in my life ♫
♫ Who is playing a song about love ♫
♫ Anyone would want to have it completely ♫
♫ Burn the dusts of darkness ♫
♫ When the wind pushes away the clouds ♫
♫ He will return with the melody ♫
Green Hill Fox Legend
The Charming Fox: Heng Niang
Master Liu, even though these refugees have starved for days,
but don't you worry, we've already brought a shipment of food here from Jiangnan.
I agreed to come to the human world with you because you can play with me.
But I didn't expect you,
looking so honest,
to be a liar!
You didn't see me these days. Did you miss me?
I missed you so much.
No, no, no...
Master Liu...Master Liu?
No, no...
Master Liu.
You said that we have to open the granary and give out food, right?
-Okay, let's do that.-That's right.
Master Liu, I see that your mind is drifting away. It must be because that you have traveled too much these days and haven't had enough rest.
I will be holding a feast at Jade Flower House tonight.
I hope Master Liu would come and relax a little bit.
Master Liu, what do you think?
-Jade Flower House?-Yes.
The music at Jade Flower House
is well-known around here.
Yes.
Music?
Okay, then. I could get to know the culture of this place.
Good, then I'll be waiting for Master Liu at Jade Flower tonight.
We'll definitely get drunk with Master Liu tonight.
What am I doing?
Why am I thinking about that bookworm?
Tao Heng, focus on your game of Go!
What are you thinking about?
My Go board!
Mistress, what has happened to you today? We've never seen you being so ill at ease.
Yeah. Mistress was repeating something to herself just a minute ago.
I think...she is missing Master.
Who... Who is missing him?
Stop guessing!
I think I also heard Master's name just a while ago.
You... Do the two of you have any manners?
Let's see how I'm gonna take care of you!
Mistress won't allow us to say the truth.
Exactly. Mistress, please don't hit us.
We'll pretend like we didn't hear anything.
Go, go, go. Get out of here. I don't want to see the two of you.
Yes, yes, yes. Mistress, we'll leave then.
You just stay at home and think about Master quietly.
It can't be.
That's impossible.
What level am I, a nine-tail-fox, at?
How can I possibly be obsessed with him?
It's impossible for a nine-tail-fox to be obsessed with anything.
Not to mention a dull person like Liu Changyan.
A stunning beauty like you...
With one glance, a city falls for her.With another glance, a country falls for her.
It's impossible for anyone to forget about you.
Your Highness.
Darling, it's you?
I've learned something from the cook
and made this goodwill cake myself. Please try it
with the Longjing tea.
Darling, you seem to be in a good mood today.
Okay, I will try some.
How is it?
Darling, you are really skilled at this. It's delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
As long as you can be happy,
I'm willing to learn a new trick everyday to surprise you.
I see that you are in a really good mood today.
Is there anything to celebrate for?
I just made a new friend today. Her name is Ying'er.
She's clever and sensible. I'm very fond of her.
Moreover, she is very beautiful and so is her dance.
She is a lovely girl.
I really like her.
Could there really be a beauty like that in this world?
Even the Duchess would appreciate her?
Your Highness, I don't usually praise someone.
It's just that this girl is really lovely. Even I fell for her.
Then she must be a stunning beauty, right?
Your Highness, this girl is congenial to me.
How about I invite her to come to our house someday
to view the moon, have a little wine,
and dance a little bit? Your Highness, what do you think?
Good. Of course.
Since you like it,
go ahead and do it immediately.
Okay.
I'll prepare for it right away.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byGone with the Shirts Team @ Viki
How come I'm so bored?
I feel upset.
What's he doing right now?
I have nothing to do anyway.
Why don't I transform and go see him?
No.
I'm using magic too often. If he knows about it,
he will definitely give me another lecture.
Then...should I go or not?
Yes.
No.
No. Yes.
If you really miss Master, we could go see him.
Who misses him?
She won't admit it.
You said that...
we could go see Master?
Yes.
You mean that...we could see Master in person?
Of course! We could sit in a carriage.
That's right. Why didn't I think of that?
Go pack up right now.
I'll leave immediately.
Li Zi, come quickly!
-I'm coming, I'm coming.-Why are you so slow?
-Quick, quick.-Mistress, this is the first time I've seen you in a hurry.
-What?-Nothing.
Mistress, be careful.
Maid, where is your Mistress heading to?
Our Mistress is going to see Master Liu in the countryside.
They are that close?
It's such a long way, yet she's going to visit?
Of course.
God is helping me. Why don't I just take care of the Ninth Duke
while Tao Heng is not in the capital?
It's just burning incense to worship Buddha.
What's so mysterious about that?
Master, what did you just say?
Nothing.
Oh, Master,
the Ninth Duke have a feast in his house tonight. The Duchess invited me to dance for them.
How did you get to know the Duchess?
If Master could get to know the Ninth Duke, why can't I make a friend myself?
You can. Of course, you can.
Oh, be careful with what you say and how you act.
Make sure you don't offend anybody at the Duke's place.
I understand. Thank you, Master.
Maid, quickly. Bring out all of my pretty clothes.
You look really beautiful.
Why are you just standing there, Master?
Today, I brought a bottle of vintage wine to share with you.
It's already been a long time
since the last time we've drank together.
I remember that when I first met you,
I wanted to hold your hand everyday
and talk while we drank.
How many years have passed since then?
Yeah.
Age has mercy over no one.
With the blink of an eye, so many years have passed.
I still remember that,
when I first met you,
you were sitting by the river, staring blankly, like a goddess.
I was thinking then that I had to marry you.
It was all arranged by God.
When I got home, I realized that our families had been friends for generations.
Coincidentally, I would always run into you in my backyard.
You really think that happened by chance?
It didn't happen by chance?
Ever since I had met you,
I would always think of various excuses to go visit your family.
Then I would stay in the backyard for a whole day
just to see you.
After that, I would miss you for a whole month,
and wish for our next meeting to come soon.
Actually...
I would always go to the backyard, thinking that maybe I would see you again.
Really?
Then why didn't you tell me?
What's so important about this?
-Master.-I'm here.
From this day on, you can let Master Hong stay in your room.
But you can't let him decide this. You must take control.
You have to reject him a couple of times and leave him wanting for more.
What is it?
I'm feeling sick all of a sudden. I'm afraid that I can't drink with you anymore.
If you're sick, then I should stay by your side.
Someone come here! Find a doctor!
No, no, no. It's okay.
Why?
I've already promised the Buddha that
I will have three days of abstinence. I'm afraid that I can't stay with you in the same room.
Please go rest, Master.
I won't go with you any further, Master.
Please rest early.
You rest early, too. I'll come and see you again after a couple of days.
Okay.
She is my wife,
yet she's acting like someone else's wife.
Someone come here.
-Master.-Where's Second Mistress?
The Duchess took Mistress to her home.
I forgot about that. Ying'er is going to dance at the Duke's house tonight.
Okay.
You go fetch some water for me. I'm gonna wash up. I'll sleep here tonight.
Yes, Master.
I remember that I took Ying'er in
because she danced well.
Now when I think about it,
that's the only merit she had.
My wife is better.
Qin (an instrument), Go (a game), calligraphy, and painting. She knows them all.
Moreover, she is educated, reasonable, clever, and virtuous.
She is also more graceful than Ying'er.
Now we're like this.
It's all my fault.
Heng'er is here?
Heng'er is here!
Heng'er!
Your Highness, I didn't lie to you, right?
Isn't she lovely?
Ying'er is as beautiful as a flower and her dance is so graceful.
It's hard to find someone like her even in the capital.
Come here, Sister. Come and meet His Highness.
Your Highness, I'm not that good. Her Highness praises me too highly.
Exactly.
This girl does look pretty.
But when it comes to appearance and posture, Mrs. Liu, Tao Heng, should be number one in this world.
Duchess, how can this friend of yours compare with her?
-Your Highness!-Your Highness!
Not only does Ying'er dance well, she can also drink.
Come here, Sister, drink with His Highness until he is content!
-Yes.-No need for that.
I'm not in a good mood tonight.
Let's end here.
Your Highness!
Tao Heng,
I will definitely return this shame to you someday.
My beauty...
I miss you so much...
Liu Changyan,
how can you deserve such a beautiful wife?
Someone come!
Your Highness, those who can rule the world are kings.
Those who have power get to dominate.
You are from the royal bloodline and have authority over the court.
Don't you have the courage to kill all gods and demons?
Anyone who is preventing you from having that beauty
should be killed.
Your Highness, what do you think?
Kill them all!
Then I can have my beauty.
That's right.
Kill him.
Kill him!
That way you can have the woman that you've lost your soul to.
Your favorite! Favorite!
Kill him...
Kill him.
Kill Liu Changyan.
Then I can have the woman I love the most.
Liu Changyan...
I'll make sure that you never come back.
Here, here, here. Cheers...
Here, Master.
Please drink.
Very nice.
Good.
Very nice. Very nice. Very nice.
Good. Look at that body.
Good!
-Nice dancing.-Good.
Very nice.
Come here quickly. Drink wine with Master Liu.
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you for dancing for us.
I still have to discuss some matters with these officials.
You may go now.
Looks like Master Liu has gotten used to the beauties in the capital.
The beauties in a small town like ours
are not attractive at all.
-Yeah.-No, no, no. I don't mean that.
I'm really thankful for this feast and dance
you've prepared for me.
It's just that my wife has warned me at home,
and also I'm not interested in prostitutes.
I can only appreciate your kindness and decline your offer.
Master Liu, since you respect your wife so much,
Mrs. Liu must be extremely virtuous and beautiful.
Not at all. Not at all.
My wife is more than extremely beautiful...
Since Master Liu is not interested in the beauties,
then we'll drink with Master Liu.
Here, Master Liu, I'll drink a toast to you.
We won't leave until we're drunk tonight.
-Toast to you. Toast to you.-Here. Please drink.
Liu Changyan, you dare to drink more?
You have been so disrespectful to senior!
You still have to save the entire fox clan and you're drinking now?
And you even have feelings toward...
I'm a bastard!
I'll drink a toast to Master Liu and Mrs. Liu.
-Here, here, here. Cheers.-Cheers.
Cheers.
Masters! Let me, let me!
You must be tired.
Thank you for sending me home. You can go back now.
Okay, Master Liu, you take rest.
-We'll leave then.-Goodbye.
-Goodbye, goodbye.-Be careful!
-Master...-Let's head home, too.
What's wrong? Why do you look so worried?
Mistress is here.
-Who's here?-Mistress, Nine-Tail-Fox senior is here to visit you!
Heng- Heng'er is here?
Wh-where is she?
You go in first.
-I'm not going in there.-You're a good for nothing...
You're a good for something; you go in!
Fine, I'll go in!
-Do I look like I'm drunk?-Uh-uh!
Don't push me!
Heng'er, why did you come here?
What? Is this a bad time?
Did I interrupt something good for you?
No, no, no! This is a great time, a great time!
You stayed out all night?
You arrived here last night?
If I hadn't, were you going to lie to me?
Of course not. Why would I lie to you?
Alright.
Tell me the truth, where did you go drinking?
Drink? No, no, no, I didn't drink.
The local magistrates held a welcome party,
and I couldn't refuse, so I went.
I just had a few cups...
and just got home from the party.
Welcome party?
You are really considerate!
Was it really with a few magistrates?
-Yes! Yes!-You're still lying to me!
Very good , Liu Changyan! You usually look very earnest,
but I didn't expect that, after pretending to be human for a few days,
you‘d gotten better at everything except for drinking!
You even learned how to lie!
Heng'er, I really didn't!
You know how much I can drink. I only took a few sips. I didn't even touch the fingers of those dancers...
Dancers?
Other than drinking, you're even accompanied by dancers?
Heng'er, I swear, I didn't even touch the fingers of those dancers!
If I did anything that may hurt you,
I will be struck by lightning and die a painful death!
And I was worried about you!
I was afraid that you wouldn't get used to the bitter life in this small town.
I didn't expect that you were enjoying it here!
I realize now that you have gotten more and more used to the life in the human world!
Heng'er,
-please believe in me...-Don't come over!
I feel very tired right now. I need to rest. Get out!
Then I'll get out...
This lad right here, who are you?
How come you look familiar even though I've never met you before?
I'm the Second Mistress!
What? You don't recognize me?
Second Mistress? Are you joking?
But somehow, you look alike...
Of course! That's me!
But you're a man!
I...
I was a man from the very start!
Then...then...then...how come...
Come here. Come here.
Our Master, he...
has a weird hobby.
He let me dress as a woman and live in the Liu's house.
Master?
You and Master?
-Su Xi!-Ah?
What did you say?
No...no...nothing...
-Mistress! He and Master, they...-I know!
Su Xi!
Actually...it's not like that!
I'm actually Master's bodyguard!
I was pretending to be a woman and protecting Master secretly!
Bodyguard?
That's right!
I don't think so...
It's because that I'm intelligent and respond quickly!
And I'm also very loyal.
It's very hard to find someone like me in this world.
A person like me usually has a crucial effect at critical moments.
Is that really so?
If you don't believe me, ask Mistress.
Okay, stop playing around.
-I'm hungry. Go get some food for me.-Yes, Mistress.
No wonder Master never rests at your place.
Su Xi, where is Liu Changyan?
Master went out very early this morning.
He said that he's going to express sympathy to the those in the disaster. He will also take a look at how bad the farmlands are.
He's really serious about it even though he's such a minor official.
Do you know where the disaster area is?
Yes, I know.
The consequence of this disaster is really severe. We need to order the guards to come here and help us.
Master Li, please take care of that matter.
-Okay.-Master Zhao, see if the victims of this drought need anything.
Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
Husband!
Wife, why are you here?
You must be very tired after working all morning, right?
I came here to look after you.
Look, you're sweating so much.
Master Liu is indeed a lucky man.
Your wife is not only beautiful but also gentle and caring.
Yes. Yes.
Gentle, caring, and very considerate.
-Yes. Yes.-Not at all. Not at all.
Master, you give me high praise.
My husband came home in the middle of the night last night.
Everyone must have been working hard for the disaster zone.
You must take care of your health.
I won't keep you from your work.
I'll head back for now.
Alright, travel safely Madam!
Heng'er, I'll send you home.
Heng'er!
Heng'er! You really misunderstood me last night!
You keep saying that.
You knew I was angry and you didn't stay home. Why did you run away?
Heng'er, the court sent me to investigate disaster conditions. If I don't investigate and understand it personally,
how would the court give us funds?
If you really felt anything for these refugees,
why did you go drinking? Don't you know that
a cup of wine can feed a family of three for a day?
What you say is right.
Heng'er!
The fault is all on me.
I didn't understand the situation before attending the banquet and created all this misunderstanding.
I'm really angry.
You should be... You should be.
I'm not joking with you!
I don't dare to joke with you, too.
Come on, Heng'er, you know that I'm not very good at talking. Please don't give me a hard time anymore.
Who's giving you a hard time?
Did you think I came all the way here just to interrogate you?
If I didn't think that you really cared about the people, I wouldn't have bothered to come.
Alright, Heng'er. Let's not talk about this for now.
How about we talk about our real business?
Oh, so now that you've placated me, you want to talk business?
I haven't had news of the Hong couple lately, and I've been worried.
Fine, then I'll tell you. That couple are now stuck together like glue.
Like a newlywed couple.
Really?
Then when will they be able to have children?
Liu Changyan, you look like such a straight-laced person normally.
How come you keep abruptly saying things only perverts would say?
That...
When will that couple share a room, have a "good time," have children,
you can ask these things without blushing?
N-no.
That's not what I meant.
Madam must be tired, would you like some water?
No need for water.
But I am a little hungry, is there anything to eat?
There is! Wild vegetable porridge! I'll bring some out for you.
Wild vegetable porridge?
Do you eat wild vegetable porridge every day?
Heng'er, it might sound bad, but it actually tastes pretty good.
Those officials that welcomed you with a banquet
didn't send you any meat and vegetables?
I distributed them to the refugees when I went on inspection.
Didn't you see them? They are really in a pitiful state.
They are pitiful? Aren't you pitiful eating wild vegetable porridge every day?
Why don't you taste it first, it really tastes pretty good.
Madam, wild vegetable porridge.
Here, I'll fill a bowl for you.
Here, taste some.
I'm not eating; you go ahead.
Heng'er, you haven't eaten all day. Why don't you have a little?
We'll be heading back to the capital the day after tomorrow.
But I'm a little tired, I'm going to take a nap.
Heng'er...
You will need to do this skillfully.
Make it look like disaster refugees rioting against corrupted officials
and take care of Liu Changyan for me.
-Yes, your grace.-Only...
Mrs. Liu must not be harmed in any way.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
In any case, this time,
you must make sure that no one knows.
Yes!
If you can, you must show Lady Nuwa how cruel and ruthless
those she cherishes and protects are.
Willing to kill each other for the greed of a beautiful woman.
What is there to protect?
Why not let the exceptional Fox Clan rule over all
and save you pitiful villains?
Should I try for Madam's room again tonight?
By my count, the three days of abstinence have passed.
Tao Heng, you are nothing.
I won't be satisfied until I get rid of you.
You can't even pour tea now?
I was thinking of what to prepare for you for a night snack.
There's no need.
I will be sleeping in First Mistress' room tonight. Why don't you rest early.
What's going on lately?
Rejections all around.
I remember when we were newlyweds, you did this all the time.
Getting water for my wash.
If I didn't see you all day, then
I wouldn't be able to sleep well.
Good times will always fade away.
Since then, even without me,
weren't you just fine?
Madam!
It's all my fault. I shouldn't have looked for something new and married Ying'er.
I neglected you.
It isn't all your fault.
I didn't bear the Hong family a boy or a girl.
-I almost violated the seven rules- No! no!
It was all my foolishness.
Will you give me another chance?
Will you forgive me?
Then...can we rest now?
Where did this chicken come from?
I saw that you haven't eaten these couple of days,
so I had Su Xi buy it from the villagers.
What... What is it?
What are you doing?
I...I... Nothing.
The chicken is cooked!
-Really?-I'll tear you a piece
Wonderful!
Here, have a taste.
Is it good?
Mistress Nine-tail is so adorable!
Oh heavens, what am I doing now?
Have I gone crazy?
Have I developed feelings for my senior?
Where is your sense?
Liu Changyan!
Aren't you eating?
Yes! I'm eating, I'm eating!
Eating!
Delicious!
I guess my senses, from the time in the mountains when she started tormenting me,
have been lost
It smells wonderful!
You ate it all!
And left me the chicken's butt!
What noise is that!
Quick, let's hide.
What are you doing?
-My power isn't working!-Not working?
Get behind me.
Hide.
Who is the bastard Liu Changyan? Come out and die!
It's your responsibility to protect the clan leader, right?
Go out, go!
Sir, he is Liu Changyan! We're all just servants.
Please let us go!
What are you talking about?
You are Liu Changyan?
Sir, the one who is sleeping in there is Mrs. Liu.
Please let us go.
You, go!
You, tie him up!
Let's go!
Yo! You look really pretty!
Let me touch you...
Open your mouth!
Do it quickly! I don't want new problems to rise!
Let's go!
Go! Go! Quickly!
Go! Quickly!
Heng'er, are you alright?
What can go wrong for me?
I feel like there's something unusual about these thugs.
You just said your magic doesn't work anymore. Why is that so?
I have no idea. That never happened before.
But even if my magic doesn't work, we can still use your magic.
We're not allowed to use magic in the human world.
Didn't you already use it just then?
That... That was an emergency.
There's order in the human world. We can't disrupt it.
What rule is that?
The 93-rule of the fox clan. Any fox traveling in the human world cannot use magic.
Anyone who disrupts the order of the human world will stay in the human world forever
and cannot go back to the Green Hill.
Senior, you are a nine-tail-fox. Only nine-tail-foxes won't be restricted by the rules of the fox clan.
I wonder who set that rule.
The elders and my father.
The son is just like his father. I finally understand that phrase now.
Okay, let's stop talking about these useless things.
We have to think of a way to untie these ropes.
But they are too tight.
How can we untie them if we cannot use our magic?
Untie...?
What are you doing?
Nine-tail-fox, as long as you can be heartbroken like the other foxes,
and give me one teardrop,
this magical fruit will ripen.
-Grey-eared-fox?-You destroyed my face and my eye,
and forced me to cut my own tail...
Today, I'm going to make you pay twice the price!
Oh woman!
Won't you drop even one tear for him?
Look at him.
Die!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you byGone with the Shirts Team @ Viki