Timing & Subtitles brought to you by Gone with the Shirt Team @viki
Opening Song: "To Ask the Moon" by Yisa Yu
♫Fret not that the clouds cover the moon♫
♫It's just the wind showing its love♫
♫If we say the stars are the ocean of the sky♫
♫then the moon is the longing of the tides♫
♫When the clouds scatter♫
♫The moon lights up the earth's haze♫
♫The world stops in this moment♫
♫and forgets all its wins and losses♫
♫Who has been beguiled by freedom's radiance?♫
♫Loving freely then leaving willfully♫
♫Maybe vows are like the oceanas long as the song stays the same♫
♫That is the last worship of a lifetime.♫
♫Who is playing the love of the world?♫
♫Anyone would want to be brimming with joy♫
♫To burn up the ashes of nightThe wind pushes the clouds aside♫
♫and he will follow the sound of the piano home♫
Enchanted Fox Chapter: Heng Niang
Move!
Yo! You're very pretty!
Let me touch you some...
Open your mouth!
Hurry up, I don't want any complications.
Move!
Move, move! Quick!
Move! Quick, quick!
Heng'er, are you alright?
How wouldn't I be alright?
I think there's something odd about these bandits.
You said your magic failed, what was that about?
I don't know why either; this has never happened before.
But even if my magic's not working,
yours still works.
We can't randomly use magic in the human world.
Didn't you just use it?
Th-That was an emergency.
The human world has its own rules, we can't break them.
What rule is this?
The Fox Clan's 93rd Rule: Any Fox clan member who travels the human world is not allowed to use magic.
If we disrupt the human order, then we must stay in the human world forever and never return to the Green Hill.
Senior you are a nine-tailed fox. Only a nine-tailed fox is not restrained by the Fox Clan's rules.
I'd really like to know who made this rule.
The Elder, my departed father.
The fruit does not fall far from the tree. I understand now.
Alright, let's stop talking about these useless things.
We need to hurry and think of a way to loosen these ropes.
But these ropes are tied too tight,
and neither you nor I can use magic. How do we untie them?
Untie them...?
What are you going to do?
Senior, what are you going to do?
Senior?
Senior!
Senior!!
That's ticklish! Senior!
Could you please stop?
Even though you can't use magic, you should still be able to handle those bandits right?
Yes, without magic, I still have my martial arts.
If I hadn't been worried about you getting hurt, I would have fought them.
It's alright, you don't have to explain.
Let's go after them.
Hold on, they've already gone so far, how will we find them?
Don't be a fool.
We're both foxes. Even if we don't use magic, we can find them with this!
That's right, I am a fool!
Over here! Sit!
Why aren't we killing them?
What do you know? We'll wait for their family's ransom money,
-and kill them then!-You so smart!
Don't be afraid, Taozi. I'm here!
B-But they are ruthless killers,
what if--what if they kill us?
Then I guess we'll just die!
Then in another 18 years I'll be a man again!
Anyway, you have me for company.
You won't be lonely on the way to the underworld.
But I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die...
But you're not dead yet!
What are you crying about!
You won't die. Don't worry, I'm a bodyguard!
Really?
Really!
Are you really a bodyguard?
I really am a bodyguard! I'll protect you.
Clan leader made me swear not to use magic.
Now look at us. What to do?
Do I use it or not?
Will a suave, distinguished fox, such as I,
die here
at the hands of such ugly bandits?
No way, definitely not!
I must use a little magic!
Who goes there!
Master is here!
Master is here?
Does master know martial arts?
I guess you didn't know, master is...
a martial arts expert hiding in the government!
Master, I knew you were going to come save us!
How did your ropes get loose?
Oh, those bandits didn't tie me tightly enough.
Master, who did you offend that had them chase you all the way here?
Lately, disasters have spread. The surrounding bandits are rising; claiming to kill corrupt officials.
On the surface it looks like the work of bandits.
Even so, it doesn't look that simple.
We can't bother with that now.
We shouldn't linger here too long. While the news that Master Liu has been captured by bandits is traveling,
we should quietly head back to the capital on the safe side.
I think these bandits were following orders.
I wonder whose orders.
Who have you offended as a minor official?
I don't think I have.
Even if the citizens asked, it wouldn't be necessary to plot my death.
There must be some explanation.
Hey, Su Xi! Master was able to defeat the bandits by himself,
why would he still need your protection?
Even if you're great at martial arts, you still need to sleep. Right?
Oh, that's true.
Also, Su Xi, where did you learn to disguise yourself as a woman?
I grew up among piles of girls
and I couldn't even tell.
Oh, that was nothing.
I just learned a few things from street entertainers.
Did you grow up traveling the world?
Yeah! A good man should see the world and not be tied down in one place!
That's true. I like men like you.
Y-You like me?
Uh, no, I just mean I like men like you, not like master.
Oh, you like my type, and you don't like master.
Don't misinterpret me!
Even if you had feelings for me, we may not be fated.
Wh-What do you mean?
You wouldn't understand.
But, Taozi, do you really like me?
I'm not talking to you anymore!
You're making fun of me. I'm going to look for madam.
Tell me!
You can whisper it to me. I've never had anyone like me.
I don't know what it feels like to be liked.
If you keep saying that, I'm going to ignore you.
Alright, I'll stop! I'll stop. Don't be mad, Taozi.
Are you alright? Did you twist your ankle?
What do you think?
I'll help you over there to sit a bit.
Here, have a seat.
Which foot is it?
Please, be gentle.
Is this the spot?
What about this?
Much better.
Your bone shouldn't be hurt; nothing serious.
Without magic, everything is difficult.
I just wanted you to take care of one person! What have you done?
Your subject has failed! Please, forgive me!
Fools! All of you are fools!
Send out a search team and find them immediately!
Protect Mrs. Liu and kill Liu Changyan!
Yes!
I figured you would fail.
But your failure will give me a hand.
This magic fruit
is just missing one drop of fox tears.
Nine-tailed fox, you only have to have your heart broken like the other fox spirits.
And give me one drop of your tears.
This magic fruit
will ripen and break open.
How did we get to this state?
Four people squeezed into one little broken house.
Ah, Su Xi! Su Xi, your life is hard!
Come, Su Xi. A man should be flexible.
I am being flexible!
But if you want me to sleep on a wooden bench, I might as well sleep outside on the ground.
Look, you're thinking of yourself again.
What about the Missus and Taozi?
Su Xi, how about you sleep on the floor and I'll sleep on the bench?
It's dangerous outside at night.
Don't you go out there!
Taozi, you treat me the best!
If you want to like me, go ahead!
-I won't say anything!-Who says I like you!
I don't like you!
Ah, our Suxi is so pitiful.
Looking after us all this way, and now he has to sleep on a wooden bench.
That's right! All this way I've suffered the most!
Hubby, let's ignore them.
Let's rest.
Su Xi, it's late.
Why don't you rest, too?
Then you rest, too.
Timing & Subtitles brought to you by Gone with the Shirt Team @viki
If you squirm anymore, you'll fall off.
If you fall off, won't they laugh at you?
I don't want to crowd you.
This blanket's a little thin.
If we cuddle together, it'll be warmer, and I won't be cold.
And we're foxes.
Animals snuggle for warmth. It's nature's way.
Su Xi
Sleeping like that is so uncomfortable.
Why don't you squeeze in here with me?
Shouldn't men and women not have any contact?
Forget it then.
Wait, I'm not that particular.
Taozi, you're so good to me.
Customers, sorry for the wait!
Here are the noodles you ordered.
I'll split some with you.
I'm not hungry; you eat.
These past few days you haven't eaten much.
Just wild vegetable porridge everyday. I've already eaten half a roast chicken,
and you just had a little.
I'm so hungry my eyes are blurry, how could you not be hungry?
You eat. I'm really not hungry.
Though my magic is sealed,
my inner energy is still there
even if I don't eat, I can carry on for a while.
That reminds me.
I just lost my magic, why have I become like a human
and unable to withstand hunger?
You're a woman, I'm a man;
naturally we're different.
What's different? When you first came to the valley to find me,
you couldn't defeat me.
That's because I couldn't simply make moves on you.
You're my senior after all.
You forgot I was your senior when you were so affectionate.
I didn't force you to do anything with me. Why do you keep using words like "senior" "junior" all day?
Heng'er!
Don't eat then!
Hey, do you even see that I'm here?
What was that?
Nothing!
Su Xi, I'll give you mine!
Aren't you eating?
I'm full!
Taozi, you're so kind!
Have you seen a couple around 25-6. The man is handsome, the woman especially beautiful?
I haven't!
Everyone listen up!
We are the Ninth Duke's men! We are looking for Master Liu Changyan who is missing!
Anyone who has any leads will be heavily rewarded!
Sir! Sir!
Don't let Taozi reveal where we are!
Sir, is there really a big reward?
You saw them?
No. But if there is a reward, I'll look extra hard for you!
Step aside!
Su Xi, why didn't you let me tell those guards?
I'm not too clear either, but madam made me do it.
Come on. Let's go find Madam.
The kidnapping happened the day before yesterday.
The news should be that Master Liu was kidnapped.
If that's so, the guards should be looking for news of the bandits.
That's right. It has only been a day since we rescued Su Xi and Taozi and fled through the night.
Even if they caught the bandits and got a confession, it should be that Master Liu was rescued.
And not that Master Liu has gone missing.
And I was just thinking,
who could a minor official like you have offended.
Looks like it's that Ninth Duke.
But the Ninth Duke is not a ruthless man, why would he do this?
I... I can't figure that out either.
With the Ninth Duke's power and position, there are many ways he could deal with you,
and openly remove you.
But he chose the lowliest method to take your life.
It's not at all like something he would do.
Oh, I understand now.
You're saying that the Ninth Duke is trying to kill us!
But hasn't the Ninth Duke always thought highly of our master?
Don't you know that the Ninth Duke likes our madam?
When you were sent to survey the disaster,
Ninth Duke especially invited our madam out to ingratiate himself.
I knew he liked our madam.
I guess, he wants to kill our master,
and have mistress for himself!
How dare he try to snatch our master's woman! He must be tired of living!
Don't be reckless!
If it truly is as we guess and it is the Ninth Duke,
we will need to stay hidden and be careful on our way.
It's alright. Since we now know who is behind all this,
it's much better than being ignorant.
We will just need to be more careful.
Go chase after them! This way!
Do you want to rest a little?
Let's get back to the capital first.
I was thinking that, too.
But...
Oh no. Su Xi, you block them first.
-No problem!-Let's go!-Su Xi, why are you going?
Taozi, you go with master first. I'll be fine!
Su Xi!
Now I have no choice!
Keep moving. I'll deal with them.
Use magic, use magic!
I can't use magic on humans!
You idiot!
Hui Er!
Liu Changyan,
we meet again!
You ruined my face and slashed my eye!
You forced me to cut my tail. Let me repay you twice!
Stealing the magic fruit and breaking heaven's laws.
You put the Fox Clan in danger.
You still dare to make excuses?
Why can't I?
I am the one who will dominate the Fox Clan and lead it to glory!
I am the one that will be the Fox Clan's
pride and glory!
Liu Changyan, DIE!
Nine-tailed fox, your magic disappearing is heaven helping me!
Why don't you watch him die!
Oh, woman,
aren't you going to drop even one tear for him?
Liu Changyan, I tell you, I am not going to drop one tear for you,
but I will avenge you!
He will die without a corpse!
Oh, you cold-hearted woman!
Then watch him!
Watch him!
Die!
Liu Changyan, are you alright?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
You're wounded to this extent, what do you mean you're fine?
Don't worry, this little injury I can handle.
Can you?
You're just a six-tailed fox, how do you have this ability?
I may only be a six-tailed fox,
but Grandmother and the others all say, I am a fox that's rarely seen once in a thousand years.
Most six-tailed foxes need a thousand years of practice. How long have you been practicing?
Only three hundred.
Three hundred years!
And you're already a six-tailed fox!
That's why I'm the 79th clan leader.
It must have hurt a lot.
You spit out your inner core to save me.
You must be very weak, too.
I said those things then,
are you upset?
I know you were just harsh on the outside, but soft on the inside.
How could you bear for me to die?
Nine-tailed fox!
I-I...
How am I going to get your tears?
Stop! Come back.
Su Xi, isn't master seriously hurt?
-How is he alright already?-You were mistaken.
The blood on master belongs to those guards.
Master's martial arts are very strong; of course, he's fine.
That's true.
Alright, let's stop talking and enter the capital.
Alright.
You.
-They're in, let's go!-Wait, wait!
It looks a little bad,
but if we can fake our way through, it will save a lot of trouble.
How ugly could it be?
However ugly I get, I'm still Master Liu's beloved and pampered first mistress.
My wife speaks the truth.
-Let's go!-Let's!
Stop!
Ugh, you smell! Move!
Move!
Stink!
We're finally back!
Does it feel like a different world?
It didn't feel that way before.
Now it feels like this place we call home
is especially important.
Home?
That's right, we're home!
I don't understand.
You are neighbors with Master Liu, and your wives are so close. How can you have no news?
Your Grace, I have sent people out everywhere for information,
but there is no news.
-Your Grace! Your Grace!-You dare!
Don't you see I am talking? Who allowed you in here?
Your Grace, that Master Liu is here to see you!
Liu Changyan?
This...
Let him in!
Yes, Sir!
Liu Changyan?
Master Liu!
-I am here to see your Grace-Never mind the formalities.
Master Liu, I heard that you met with bandits, and I have been very worried about your safety!
Thank you for the Ninth Duke's concern.
Master Liu, it's good that you are fine.
-I'm fine-Now that I see you are safe and sound, I've worried for nothing!
Master Liu, how did you escape from the bandits?
Go and see the Ninth Duke, and tell him a little lie.
Tell him that when we were kidnapped, I suffered from shock.
That my health was especially affected. I guarantee that duke will be especially concerned about me.
He will forget everything else.
As we were being kidnapped, we were saved by a hero.
But my wife is suffering from shock.
She is recovering at home.
Mrs. Liu suffered from shock!
Is she alright?
I tell you, Mrs. Liu is so precious; you must get a doctor for her.
Make sure you don't delay! No, no, no!
Now that I think of it, you must have a royal physician see to her.
My thanks, Your Grace.
Daye, hurry and summon the royal physician!
-Yes-Hurry!
That's strange. Why is today's chicken so unappetizing?
This was prepared by a famous chef from the capital.
But it's not as good as the chicken Liu Changyan roasted for me in the village.
Fragrant and tender.
Where did he learn to do that?
How did it go? Did you do what I asked you to?
What was the Ninth Duke's response? Was he especially worried for me?
Of course, he was worried about you. He immediately made a fuss about having a royal physician coming to see you.
As I expected.
Heng'er, what are you planning?
Liu Changyan, you and I may have had a one night's relationship, but I don't have to tell you everything, do I?
What you say is true. But, but you and I...
What?
Heng'er.
Stop "Heng'er Heng'er" ing already.
I said I would complete the Fox Clan's business, and I definitely will.
So don't ask me anymore. Right now, there's something even more important.
Can you help me do it?
What is it?
I don't know why, but since I ate that chicken you roasted, I can't eat anything else.
But.. But...
-But what?-When I was at home, my parents hated my cooking!
But I like it!
I tell you, if I can't have some today,
I'll be in a bad mood!
Hurry, hurry!
I'm starving! This is much more important than the Ninth Duke!
Where's the master? Why hasn't he been here today?
The master is at the first mistress'
admiring flowers with her.
That Madam Zhu!
A lowly yellow-faced old woman.
Dares to seduce the master behind my back!
These flowers blooming so beautifully
are all the result of your meticulous care.
Mrs. Liu taught me well. Now she's back but is in a bad mood.
I'd like to pick some flowers to comfort her.
Wife, all day I'm either looking for Master Liu or the Ninth Duke.
I'm running around all day, don't I need comfort, too?
You've worked hard.
I don't want those
simple words.
How old are you now, yet you're still acting like a child?
All that's in your head is love and passion.
That's not all that's in my head.
You're the only one in my heart.
Little sister is here.
I never thought that at this age,
you still have the inclination to pretty yourself with flowers.
These flowers are beautiful, but not everyone looks good with them.
Aren't you worried your looks will fade?
Ying'er, watch your mouth.
Master, I wonder where she learned her seductive ways.
Trying to be all foxy.
I said to watch your mouth!
She's the one who's being shameless at her age!
Thinking of all the ways to entwine herself around you.
Vile, shameless!
Shut your mouth! You--!
Why have you become like this?
Speaking out of turn as a concubine!
No respect, no common decency!
I am like that! I want to be like that!
You, right now... You!
Behaving like this, how can anyone look well on you?
I won't punish you today. Go, think it over in your room.
Master!
Why are you so angry at me?
I told you to go to your room, didn't you hear me?
Then are you going to stay with her tonight?
I'm going to be reading tonight!
Reading through the night!
-Master...-Dismissed.
-Master!-Dismissed!
Wife! Wife!
I don't know what tricks she played;
she's managed to lead him around in circles!
It's Tao Heng.
It's that vile woman!
If it weren't for her, I wouldn't be in this position!
How is she?
Master Liu, congratulations!
Mrs. Liu is with child!
Congratulations!
Thank you, Doctor, and Ninth Duke's concern.
Husband, why don't you invite the Duke and the royal physician to retire in the front parlor.
Right.
Master Liu, I will write a prescription for Mrs. Liu to stabilize her fetus.
You just need to have someone follow the prescription.
Thank you, Sir.
I shall not disturb you
and take my leave.
-This way.-Take my leave!
No wonder I suddenly lost my magic.
I'm pregnant!
I have a child with Liu Changyan!
Do you have something to say?
Heng'er, is this child real?
Do you think I'm lying to you?
No, that's not what I meant.
This child wasn't diagnosed by me.
That royal physician said so.
Also, I don't have any magic right now. How could I lie to you?
Heng'er, don't misunderstand.
It's just this happened so suddenly.
I'm not ready at all!
-This child is here at a bad ti...-That's enough, Liu Changyan
I know right now you want to list all of your big reasons.
But in the end, in your eyes, I'm just a trouble maker.
Stopping you from achieving your great goals.
Heng'er, you really misunderstand.
You don't know what kind of task we need to do.
With Hui Er putting obstacles in our way,
the Fox Clan is facing annihilation, the Green Hill will quite possibly no longer exist.
-Having a child at this time-That's enough!
Don't say anymore. I don't want to hear it.
You have many things to deal with. This child is mine.
And it's my business, alright?
It's also mine!
That's right. Actually, as your senior,
I shouldn't fight with you.
But this child is mine,
and is yours.
No matter what, based on your identity, position and power, I should be the one who should raise this child.
There is no need for you to do anything.
Heng'er, you're angry so I'm not going to take those words seriously.
I'm not mad. I will complete what I agreed to do.
When I go back to the Green Hill, I will live my life freely.
And you can continue being the Clan Leader.
Heng'er, I said some foolish words. Please don't take them to heart.
If I can help the Fox Clan through this trial,
I will come back for the both of you.
Forget it.
There's no point talking about this now.
I'll go make some dinner for you both.
Idiot.
Mrs. Liu's pulse is very odd.
I've practiced over 20 years, and this is the first time I've felt such a strange pregnancy pulse.
I think it may have something to do with the fetus being unstable.
I'd better prescribe some nourishing medication for her,
so that Mrs. Liu can be nursed back to health.
No.
You should prescribe abortion medication.
Get rid of Liu Changyan's child, and make sure no one finds out!
Your Grace, this, this...
What do you know? I've long since disliked Liu Changyan.
He is nothing but a useless minor official.
Sooner or later, he'll be removed by His Majesty.
I'm just helping His Majesty.
I understand.
Why are you standing there? Get moving!
Right, I will go right now.
Liu Changyan, Liu Changyan.
You're not fit to have a child with Heng'er.
You keep pacing up and down, are you trying to starve me?
Heng'er? Heng'er are you asleep?
Just come in. Why are you dithering out there?
Heng'er, I made you some soup.
Would you get up and have some?
Leave it. I'll drink it when I feel like it.
You're mad.
Heng'er, what happened yesterday and in the past are all my fault.
I hope that you will take care of yourself.
Don't trouble yourself for my mistakes
and hurt yourself.
So what happened yesterday and in the past,
are they all mistakes?
Heng'er, I can't put things together as well as you do. Could you not pick out the faults in my words?
Please?
Heng'er, it's all my fault.
What's your fault?
Making you mad is my fault.
It's good that you know it.
Then can you forgive me?
Forgive which time?
Didn't you say you made many mistakes?
This time.
I'm hungry.
Heng'er, I simmered this soup for 4 hours.
I'm not sure if it will suit your tastes.
If you don't like it, I'll make it again.
If you make it again, I'd have to wait another 4 hours. Wouldn't I starve?
This is raw the first time and ripe the second time. If I did it again, it wouldn't take as long.
Come, taste a little.
How is it?
It tastes a little odd, but tolerable.
Really?
You lie. It's pretty good! Have a bite!
Let me tell you. Now that madam is pregnant,
we will have to make chicken soup for her every day. Her food must be nutritious.
Also, whatever she does, you must keep her company. She must never go out alone, understand?
I know all that.
-Do you?-Of course, I do!
Pregnant!
Now that you are pregnant, you must remember to drink medicinal soup every day.
Why don't I take care of your food and drink?
I couldn't trouble you.
My health has always been good, eating a little more or less won't affect me.
Little sister, what are you saying? We are like close sisters.
And now that Master and I are on good terms again,
you are my savior and I can't thank you enough.
It's just that... you are so young,
how do you know men's hearts so well?
To this day, do you still not understand the reasoning behind it?
I understand a little.
But I don't understand some as well.
In this world, no matter man or woman,
are naturally attracted to those who are outstanding.
But most women, after they marry, they begin to forget themselves.
All the advantages they had, they discard one by one.
In the end, they become someone they themselves don't like.
I just helped you find the best of yourself again.
The one that others like the most.
In the beginning, putting you in the worst position,
didn't make you likable.
Even though your husband wouldn't even look at you,
but when you went on the tour with the duchess and he suddenly saw you，
it's as if he hadn't seen you in a long time.
Do you know the feeling of meeting again after a long time,
can lead a person back to memories of the past.
That day, when we went out together,
you changed from a dirty farm wife into an elegant beauty.
That's why when your husband saw you, he wanted you,
wanted to get close to you and understand you again.
And from that time on?
From then on, he thinks of me all day.
Just when he wants to be with me, I draw him in slowly;
yet, I don't satisfy him immediately.
That's right.
An old love can be young again, and all his thoughts are on you.
In fact, these are all just strategies.
If the time comes when you don't want to be threatened by the concubine again,
you must remember to be the you that others will like.
These principles...
If you hadn't said them to me, I might have already been set aside.
In the end, it's up to whether this man is worth your effort.
If he's not worth it, then you might as well let it go.
I can't be as free as you.
As the saying goes, ten years practice and you can take a boat together. One hungred years practice and you can share a pillow.
Since we have the fate to be husband and wife, of course, we should grow old together.
How can I just let go by saying so?
With this unexpected fate between he and I,
I wonder if we can grow old together, too?
Little sister.
Little sister!
What's the matter?
It's nothing. Why don't you come with me to my room? I have a magic weapon for you.
A magic weapon?
Master Liu.
Like this.
Right.
And like this.
This is called Charm through the Smoke.
Charm through the smoke?
Husband, what are you doing?
Heng'er, I was looking at my fan.
-Your fan?-That's right!
Look, how well these words are written.
The words are well-written.
Madam, the Hong family's Second Mistress is here.
You're dismissed.
Yes.
-Go on.-Yes.
I hear you are expecting.
You're quite well-informed.
Such joyous news, of course, I would know.
Have you called me here
to show off?
Show off?
You are quite capable.
Causing my husband to distance himself from me,
seduced by that yellow-faced hag, every day going to her room.
-This is my fault?-Are you claiming innocence?
The path of husband and wife is paved in sincerity.
If you really love your husband, you should respect his first wife
and not fight for his attention.
If you aren't sincere and are only seeking power and position,
then it's simple.
Since your mistress has won back your master's heart,
then you should submit to defeat.
Submit to defeat?
That's right. When it's time to retreat then retreat.
If you are determined to snatch his love,
then you are just looking for humiliation.
Looking for humiliation?
There's nothing that is certain in this world.
Men are naturally fickle.
It just depends on which girl has the best moves.
Is love really so shallow in your eyes?
Men rely on women for prestige.
Women rely on men for an easy life.
This world has always been about give and take.
Stubborn and untamable.
What did you say?
The fact that I'm willing to teach you is your fortune.
These evil thoughts of yours will lead to your own destruction.
Lead myself to my own destruction?
Mrs. Liu, listen well.
You've repeatedly ruined my plans
and cost me years of hard work.
I'd love to pluck out your muscles
and peel off your skin.
Looks like this was a useless gesture for me.
It's true I am not the good type.
Anyone who offends me, I will pay back ten times.
If they want me dead, I will definitely drag them down to hell with me.
Since you will not listen to my counsel,
then please leave.
Mrs. Liu, this is not over.
That ruthless Ninth Duke!
He dares to have medicine sent to abort my child?
I was going to ignore you,
but since you just had to mess with me,
then don't blame me for returning the favor!
Really shameless!
Husband, who are you talking about?
Of course, I'm talking about the Ninth Duke!
It's clear that we are a happily married couple, yet he still sends this medicine for you.
He's clearly currying your favor!
Did you and I get married?
I'm afraid we aren't even husband and wife.
How did we become a happily married couple?
Heng'er, we're about to have a child.
Why does that matter?
Aren't you a master of etiquette?
Between the two of us, our parents have not spoken for us,
no matchmaker has either.
So we are even skipping the wedding ceremony.
And you're criticizing the Ninth Duke.
I don't think you're much better than him.
I-I-I-I'll definitely make it up to you!
Make it up to you.
Ah, child,
your dad is quite a blockhead.
You must definitely not take after him.
Mama's teaching you...
If one day someone tries to take your woman, you must teach him a good lesson!
You must have no mercy!
Don't let your woman be like your mom,
and have to teach the bad guy a lesson herself.
-Su Xi, you're awesome!-Let's have another!
One, two, three!
Amazing! Again!
Su Xi!
Come here a minute.
What do you wish, Mistress?
Su Xi, tell me honestly.
Do you like Taozi?
I am a little attached to her.
But you know the rule that Liu Changyan set.
If you want to be with a human,
you will have to give up years of practice.
And be a normal person like them.
Slowly experiencing old age and death, with no going back.
I'm willing! I'm willing to stay here.
Even if I grow old and die with Taozi, I'm willing.
-Really?Really!
The way Taozi treats me well,
can't compare to anyone else.
But even if you want to stay with a human,
based on Liu Changyan's personality, won't he take you home by force?
Mistress, you must never tell the Clan Leader!
If I don't tell him, how are you going to stay?
Um...
However, you know my relationship with your clan leader.
If I can put in a good word for you, it might all work out.
Mistress, you're really going to help me?
I can persuade him for you; however,
you must agree to help me with something.
Of course! Senior, please tell me!
Timing & Subtitles brought to you by Gone with the Shirt Team @viki