Subtitles by DramaFever
[Final Episode 20]
Everything was a lie.
Friends...
are really nothing special.
Me...
I want to be over this damn guilt
I feel every time I look at you!
You were right.
Friends really are nothing special.
and Yeo Kyung...
We both lied
about things that we never
should have lied about.
We both told lies
we would definitely regret forever.
There's no such thing as a friend
who isn't really that special.
When a person is forced to face
the death of their friend...
it entrances
that person with shock and sadness.
What do we do now?
The pain brought on by sadness only
disappears after the trauma has set in.
In a way, that's consolation
in and of itself.
Even if...
you're not necessarily friends.
[Seven Days Later]
What are you trying to pull
right now, Head Chef?
You've been ignoring the
kitchens for a week now!
The kitchens are a mess,
and customers are unsatisfied!
At this rate, we'll be
forced to shut down!
Shut it down then.
What's even weirder
is that we're still open.
What?
Who would eat noodles that
were once made by a murderer?
Shut this place down until Kim Gil Do's
presence is erased from here forever.
That's the right thing
to do in this situation.
What happened to your
parents is truly a shame.
Finding out that Kim Gil Do is a killer
was as shocking to us as it was to you.
But why do the consequences
have to be suffered by Goong Rak Won?
It took so much for us to get this big.
I will not stand by and watch it crumble.
I cannot accept that.
I refuse to watch it crumble like this.
Step down from your position.
You're the one who is most
responsible for our current state.
You should be trying to fix this
situation as much as possible.
But look at you.
Leave this place right now.
I can't do that.
I have to protect this position.
Kil Gil Do will definitely be back here.
Whoever ends up dying, I have to see this
through until the end, no matter what.
Why, you...
My friend died.
I got so distracted with my raging need
for revenge against Kim Gil Do
that I didn't even think of my friends.
My friend...
came into this living hell because of me.
Tae Ha...
I might as well have killed him, myself.
Madame Seol. Let me give you a warning.
Do not make me
redirect my rage towards you.
You definitely will not
be able to handle that rage.
So just stay put
and keep quiet until Kim Gil Do is dead.
Let me give you a warning too.
Don't drag people
who have nothing to do with you,
into your damn revenge plot.
From this point forward,
I do not consider you Head Chef.
I'll use whatever means necessary
to get you
thrown out of here.
He just does whatever the hell he wants!
He's like this as a head chef
imagine how much worse
he would be as Master!
Madame Go. Are you just going
to sit and watch this happen?
Hello? Are you listening to me?
Geez...
Why are you so damn insensitive?
His friend just died.
You have to give him time to grieve.
It's not like you're a major shareholder.
Why are you being so nosy,
like a truffle-sniffing pig?
What?
What did you just call me?
- Hey--
- Am I wrong though?
Now that you've got Master Ha's shares...
Geez, aren't you just
on a major power trip?
Can you be considerate
of others, just this once?
Noodles are important,
but not as important as people.
Geez...
Um...
I guess you don't actually
get motion sickness.
I do
if I don't eat.
Let go
before I start screaming.
You're the thief here, not me.
Hey!
You smell like cars.
And sweat.
And...
dumplings.
Do you know what it smells like,
when you mix all of those together?
It smells like Tae Ha.
Why are you here?
What's this?
Tae Ha's stuff.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
I keep tearing up, looking at this stuff.
Tae Ha...
Don't misunderstand.
I'm just using you as a garbage can.
I have a request for you.
Please remember
my scent.
It looks like Chief Park had
a big impact on a lot of people.
I think I know how empty it must feel...
at least from what I remember about
how I felt after my father died.
You have to just cry it out.
What else can you do, really?
There's something that
I've really wanted to tell you.
When I said that dirty blood
flows through your veins...
How could I still be considered human,
after saying such a terrible thing?
I mean, it's not like
my blood is much cleaner.
What I said back then has been
stuck in my heart like a thorn
and it hasn't left, no matter
how hard I tried to dig it out.
I'm sorry.
I truly am, Da Hae.
It's okay.
I knew that you didn't really mean it.
About Moo Myung...
I know he that he's going
through a rough patch.
Madame Seol is only making
things worse by pressuring him.
I'm sure that his entire life
has been a living hell
so we should protect him.
I know...
that no matter what anyone says
he truly loves noodles
and he truly loves making noodles.
I'll be
a source of strength for you.
I know that we can't
go back to the times when
we ate noodles together so comfortably.
But even so...
do you think we could lend each other
a shoulder to cry on
when we're going through tough times?
I think that would be
really nice, if we could.
I'll do that, Madame Go.
Also...
Thank you.
[Park Tae Ha]
[Beloved father]
[Senator So Tae Sup of the Liberal Party
confirmed tour.]
Prosecutor.
Did something happen?
It was all my fault.
Stop putting on a show,
you son of a bitch.
Take him in.
Still not here?
They're on their way.
I'm sorry.
My body was acting up.
Can we get started right away?
Of course.
I've been living for this day.
Let's go, then.
You remember Chief Hwang Sung Rok, right?
How could I possibly forget him?
You look good.
You look like you've lost some weight.
Seems like you've
been through quite a bit.
No, not really.
People were asking me for autographs
while I was on the run.
It felt like people weren't
as interested in me as I thought.
I'm sure that they'll be much
more interested in you soon.
Let's start with the incidents
that you were both involved in.
Mr. Kim Gil Do.
On May 27, 2014
you ordered for Mr. Hwang
to be killed under a bridge. Correct?
What do you mean?
Why would Master Ha try to kill me?
What's written here is what
you said, word for word.
I'm sure that there
must have been an error.
Or I may have felt threatened
by a certain someone when I wrote that.
To be honest with you
I don't even remember...
ever making such a claim.
What are you trying to pull right now?
We have everything documented,
recorded and filed as evidence!
There was no pressure
placed on you, and I'm definitely
not mistaken.
What would happen if I were
to change my witness testimony?
Did you two...
by chance...
I do not wish to testify any longer.
I'd like to change my witness testimony.
Please take Chief Hwang Sung Rok away.
You even ruined our witness...
for your escape plan?
Just take things as they are.
Don't let your imagination run wild.
You damn monster.
Prosecutor, you seem a bit worked up.
Allow me to
take some pressure off of your shoulders.
Regarding that incident involving
Senator So's old housekeeper...
It's true that I killed her.
Yes, it is.
However...
the murder of Ha Jung Tae and his wife...
The only evidence against me for that
is Choi Soon Suk's eyewitness testimony.
And unfortunately, the statute
of limitations on that has expired.
And...
regarding the murder of
Professor Chae Il Hwan....
Raymond Holdings' CEO
Lee Jung Bum
was behind that one.
It had nothing to do with me.
But that doesn't matter now,
since he's been acquitted of all charges.
You also said that I'm being
charged for escaping authorities.
But I didn't escape.
I just got lost
from the trauma...
that I suffered, from the accident.
And what about Tae Ha?
You killed Tae Ha!
You killed Tae Ha so you
could hide your secrets!
Again with that wild imagination.
A prosecutor should make judgments
based solely on evidence.
That damn imagination of yours
is why things happened like this.
You son of a bitch!
Prosecutor, you can't.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung.
Listen very carefully.
Tae Ha. I didn't kill him.
I don't care whether or not
you believe me.
But that's the honest truth.
Chief Hwang.
Go ahead.
I'd like it if you could
do one more thing for me.
You do realize that
this is the bathroom...
inside of the prosecutor's office, right?
I need something.
It won't be easy to get,
but I need you to get it for me.
Getting things is a matter of money.
What is it, though...
that you want?
So all we did was help Kim Gil Do
find a way out of all of this?
We were publicly humiliated after
getting an emergency warrant out for him
and we had our witness
change his testimony.
Correct?
Please, give me more time.
If I just dig deeper--
And if you do?
Do you think you'll find some
secret evidence basket, then?
In seven days, he has managed to
buy out our only witness,
and get rid of all of the evidence.
Within those seven days, you did nothing!
I'm sorry, sir.
I received a report about
you receiving a bribe.
I also know that all that money
was donated to an orphanage.
I also understand that you had
no choice, due to the situation.
However
a crime is a crime.
You can choose one of two options.
One, be terminated.
Or two, be tried for the crime
of accepting a bribe.
I'll choose to be terminated.
From this point forward
until you get your termination letter,
you will be off of active duty.
Using any of your privileges
as a prosecutor is forbidden.
[Goong Rak Won's Former Master
Kim Gil Do Acknowledges
Murdering Senator So's Old Housekeeper,
But As For Other Charges...]
That vermin...
Should I take care of him?
I shouldn't keep scratching...
at a festering wound.
I'll become the leader of my faction,
and then I'll shoot for presidency.
After all, we can kill vermin, any time.
Please let me know if you
change your mind, sir.
But that being said...
increase the number of bodyguards I have.
Kim Gil Do has enough wrath in him
to try to do something.
Senator
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung is here.
Send her in.
Senator.
You let Kim Gil Do go?
Our witness decided to recant
his testimony against him.
He's been declared innocent now
so all you really did
was do him a favor.
Please give me one more chance.
Didn't you already get fired?
Just forget about all of this now.
Start fresh somewhere else.
You're smart, so you'll have no problem
making a living, wherever you may go.
I can't just give up now.
You must help me.
That's
the only way that you won't face
any issues from this point forward.
Wow, you've sure changed your tune.
Are you threatening me, right now?
If that's how it sounds to you,
then yes, it is a threat.
That isn't just any kind of threat.
This here, is called an empty threat.
Do you
even have the secret document?
Of course.
You sure?
Are you sure about that?
[Dear Yeo Kyung, the stars lingered near
my window for longer than usual today.]
Whenever I got a letter from you,
I always wrote a reply letter.
I kept telling myself I had to send it,
but I was afraid of affecting you
so I folded them up
and put them away.
Read them whenever you think of me.
That's enough to make
me happy, Yeo Kyung.
Kim Gil Do.
Do you know what the best place
to stab someone is?
Their back. You shouldn't show
your back to others so easily.
Get the hell out, right now.
When people feel fear,
their pupils dilate.
That way, they can analyze a situation
better, to get themselves out of danger.
And their lips part slightly too
as they prepare to scream
"Save me!"
And that's exactly what
you look like now, again.
There really is no easy way out
this time either, right?
Tae Ha.
So Tae Sup killed him.
So, choose.
Will you choose So Tae Sup,
who killed Tae Ha
or me, who planned
the murder of your parents?
If you choose So Tae Sup
you and I
will be on the same side, soon enough.
But if you choose me,
you'll have to keep fighting until
a person who is even more
important to you dies too.
There are no other choices.
We have to end this annoying relationship
between us, in one way or another.
Give me evidence that
So Tae Sup killed him.
I won't believe anything anymore
unless I see the evidence for myself.
So Tae Sup sent me that photo...
after he kidnapped my daughter, Da Hae.
And this...
You'll basically be trading
your death for your daughter's life.
Isn't that fair?
Anyway, there's a warehouse in Incheon.
I'll send you the address,
so come there.
Isn't it only fair that we trade
your death for your daughter's life?
He also made the same call to Tae Ha.
Tae Ha got to the
warehouse before I did
and that's why he died.
So Tae Sup.
I will kill him.
And in order to do that,
I need your help.
One... two... three.
Sorry...
but I'm not sorry at all.
Kim Gil Do!
Shut up!
If I wanted to kill you, I could
have done it a hundred times already!
It's not over yet.
So you just wait.
My father was a monster
who killed two people.
But I didn't become a monster.
Saying that you became a monster because
of your terrible past, is just an excuse.
You don't know anything about me.
I saw your true colors
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
at the crematorium that day.
You said that you were just acting...
but you can't fake those kinds of tears.
Please retain that last shred of
being earnest that you might have left.
The only one who can
pull you out of this hell...
is you.
Shut up!
[Kil Gil Do]
Gil Do, have you been doing well?
I've been through quite a bit,
all thanks to you.
You've sure been through
a lot in your life, haven't you?
So why did you have to be so greedy?
If you had just lived a nice quiet life,
these things wouldn't have happened.
You're not the only one in this world
with a lion's share of greed.
It's not because I was greedy.
It's probably because
I'm weaker, that I keep suffering.
Is that right?
May I come in?
Da Hae... Why did you kidnap her?
I thought that it was the only way
I could get you to come to me.
I never imagined that you would
even ignore your own daughter.
And why did you kill Tae Ha?
It's not like I planned to.
He came to be killed.
He thought he had to die for Da Hae
and Prosecutor Chae to live.
He's a completely different
person than you.
Why didn't you just take the
secret document, and let him go?
And you? Why didn't you just steal
your friend's recipe, and leave him be?
Why did you have to go and set
two people on fire after that?
Everything happened after I met you.
That's where I went wrong.
Now I've veered off to the point
of no return, all thanks to you.
That's right.
There's no way you can make
things the way they once were, now.
So Tae Sup...
I will kill him.
To do that... I need your help.
[Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung]
The number you have dialed,
is unavailable at this time...
What brings you here?
I have a request to make.
Help me meet Senator So.
That's not hard. But...
you have to tell me what this is about.
Tae Ha... So Tae Sup
is the one who killed him.
I'll never forgive that bastard.
You'll be in danger, Yeo Kyung.
If you get in any deeper,
you won't be able to climb back out.
I've already lost Tae Ha.
I don't want to lose you too.
Who will you hold back next,
after you lose me?
I can't just sit and watch
like this anymore.
Yeo Kyung!
Tae Ha...
I can't send him off
in such a lonely way.
We really can't do that,
no matter what, Moo Myung.
I don't think I could ever
forget this scent!
Do you have any idea how much
I was craving lotus noodles?
I should have made them
for you more often. I'm sorry.
Oh, don't say stuff like that.
If not for you, I could never
eat such luxurious noodles.
Um, Senator.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask you.
Go ahead.
I'm happy to listen
to any request from you.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung
wishes to meet with you.
How do you know her?
I've been summoned by her a couple of
times regarding the case with Kim Gil Do.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
asked you for that.
- Please ignore what I just said.
- No, I'll see her.
If she really wants to see me that bad,
then I have to see her, right?
Da Hae.
Yeah?
Take a break once in a while.
You'll pass out, at this rate.
Some people make hundreds
of servings on their own.
Geez. I just feel so damn bad,
just watching you.
Noodle-maker Kim.
One order of royal court court style
quail buckwheat noodles, please.
You have to give the order
to the sous-chef first.
What is it? Did you call for me?
The customer wants you, specifically
to make them and serve them.
What?
Put it here, please.
I'm here as a customer today.
Your kneading has gotten a lot better.
The elasticity is just right, and you've
maintained the buckwheat smell nicely.
With this level of skill
you could serve your noodles
anywhere... with pride.
Tae Ha...
Who killed him?
Tell me.
Did you kill him?
Is that what happened?
No, please, tell me that it isn't true.
Tell me that you didn't do it!
Please tell me you didn't do it!
It wasn't me.
Who did it, then?
Who killed him?
It's someone that you don't know.
And it must stay that way.
It's because of you.
It's all because of you!
Why didn't you pick up my call?
If you did, I never would
have gotten kidnapped!
Tae Ha...
He died trying to save me!
He died because of me...
No...
If you just didn't commit those crimes,
he wouldn't have died.
You should have been the one who died.
Why did you go and commit crimes
but have someone else
atone for your sins?
Why?
Why? Why?
Oh, geez...
It's been a while, Ms. Prosecutor.
Have you been well?
Yes, thanks to you.
I'm sure you didn't call me
because you missed my pretty face.
So tell me,
what is this about?
Ms. Da Hae...
I found out who kidnapped her.
And he's the one
who killed Tae Ha too.
And who would that son of a bitch be?
Allow only Chae Yeo Kyung up here.
Stop anyone else who
tries to come up here.
Yes.
There's no use.
Nobody can help you now.
What the hell are you doing right now?
Tae Ha...
was a very dear friend to me.
And then, my dear friend,
Tae Ha... you killed him.
And now what?
You're going to kill me
because of that now?
No.
We're not capable of murder.
Not Tae Ha, not me.
Be a bit more honest with yourself,
even if you don't live honestly anymore.
Is it that you won't kill me,
or is it that you can't?
I'm a person who has
this country by the reins.
You know what will happen to you
if you lay one finger on me, right?
If you do, you two will disappear
without a trace. You know that, right?
Since you put it that way
let's just say that we "can't" kill you.
But, you know...
there are plenty of people
who aren't like us.
Then...
What the hell are you saying?
The number you have dialed
is not available at this time...
The moment I met you...
thirty years ago...
started the downward spiral
that ended up ruining my life.
I wonder how my life
would have turned out
if I just hadn't seen the ad
for a tutor that day.
You probably would have just...
stolen someone else's identity somewhere.
Isn't that right?
After all, you steal everything you like.
I thought about ways that
I could get a new lease on life.
But I couldn't think of one that easily.
I've grown too weary of everything.
Everyone in this world knows
that you're a murderer.
So how could you possibly start fresh?
That's why I figured
I'll just call it quits now.
Hey, Kim Gil Do.
If you have qualms, we can
settle them through words, right?
You wanted the Gold Senator's Badge?
Here, I'll give you one.
I'll give you ten, if you want!
Hey, calm down, Gil Do. This isn't right.
This is all a big misunderstanding!
Stop!
I think I'll have to live like a monster
for just one more day.
Have a safe trip to the other side.
Were you waiting for me?
What are you doing?
Something that a coward like you...
could never do.
Ha Jung Tae.
Park Tae Ha.
So these two are being laid to rest
where I was once born?
I've felt that emotion called guilt
just once in my entire life.
When I made your father...
Ha Jung Tae...
fall off of that cliff.
I've lived under many names...
but I was happiest
when I lived as Ha Jung Tae.
As if
it was my real name,
from the very beginning.
You made me live through hell
for the sake of your happiness.
I'm sorry
but I'm not sorry at all.
All I did was
try my best to survive.
Is that
really so wrong?
You damn monster...
I even considered pretending to be
someone else and surviving that way.
But it...
wore me out way too much
to keep on living like that.
That's your father's notebook.
The one that I stole from him.
That
became the framework for Goong Rak Won.
This last bullet...
will be used either
to shoot me...
or to shoot you.
For someone to die where
they were once born...
Is that an ill fate?
Or a good one?
No.
You shouldn't be allowed
to die so easily.
Moo Myung...
No, Soon Suk.
Your revenge isn't what led to this.
I'm doing this on my own volition.
I'll always make all of the decisions.
From the beginning, until the end.
I make the decisions.
No!
No...
No.
Ah...
Oh, Prosecutor Chae!
Have a seat.
You don't have to come in
if you've been fired.
I came to confess.
Confess?
Confess as in, turn yourself in, confess?
I was the one who truly committed
the murder that took place
on November 10, 2007, at Love Orphanage.
No... What... the hell are you saying?
Furthermore, as a prosecutor,
I got rid of the evidence.
I've also committed other crimes, such as
accepting bribes,
and accessory to another murder.
[Head Chef Moo Myung]
So it looks like
everyone leaves in the end...
one by one...
My father wrote these
noodle-making techniques
and devoted his entire life to this book.
Your father stole this from him
but I'm giving it to you now.
Why would you give this to me?
Please protect Goong Rak Won.
And make noodles that have been earnestly
created, with more than just hands.
Only you can do that.
I'm begging you.
[Three Years Later]
I am Chef Kim Da Hae.
As you may know
Goong Rak Won has been encompassed
by many unpleasant circumstances.
Our scars from that time
still haven't fully healed
and we are still going
through many hardships.
However
if we put all of our strength together
we can definitely overcome this.
And of course, I'll do my very best.
Okay.
From this point forward, everything I say
is not a request, but rather, a command.
I will not accept talking back.
I will not accept disobedience.
From this point forward, everything I say
is not a request, but rather, a command.
I will not accept talking back.
I will not accept disobedience.
Let's begin with two servings of royal
court-style quail buckwheat noodles.
Let's begin.
Geez, what took you so long?
Look at how much makeup you caked on.
It's so that I look pretty. What?
Get in.
What are you doing?
Why are you sitting in the back?
Am I your driver?
You're the Chief of Management.
And I am
the interim Master, and the major
shareholder, with half of the shares.
I could fire you for this, you know.
What a dirty, rotten...
I was going to make sure
that I didn't cry.
I...
didn't run away.
I faced everything head on,
like you told me to.
And I'll keep doing that, from now on.
So...
Please watch over me, Tae Ha.
And...
over Mom, too.
I'd like a bowl of noodles, please.
And what kind of noodles
would you like, Valued Customer?
Shouldn't you look at your customer's
face when you're taking their order?
Looks delicious.
It tastes good.
So...
back here again in the end...
you're here...
and I'm here.
It took too long.
Yeah.
Do you remember?
The noodles that all four of us
had at the Chi Myun Restaurant?
Those noodles were so delicious.
- Can we eat?
- Yeah.
Let's eat.
Hey, give it here.
This tastes so good.
Looks like you're eating that
with a side dish of hair, Yeo Kyung.
- Yum! It's good.
- Hey, you got it on your clothes.
Oh, really?
- Hey, there's more, you know!
- Give it to Yeo Kyung, already!
- Hey!
- I'll make some more, you guys.
Gil Yong!
Come on!
- Hey, Moo Myung!
- Hey, come on!
Let me have some too!
- This tastes so good!
- Let me have some too!
Here, have some.
[Thank you to all of the viewers
who enjoyed Master: God of Noodles]
Just come over and see me
when you're hungry, okay?
[Master: God of Noodles]
Subtitles by DramaFever