(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Final Episode 20)
Everything we said was a lie.
Friends...
mean nothing.
I lied.
I want to stop feeling guilty whenever I look at you.
Friends? It means nothing.
Yeo Kyung lied, too.
We both said something we never should've said.
Something we would regret for the rest of our lives.
Tae Ha, you'll meet new friends here.
Friends are never meaningless.
It's always shocking...
to face...
the death of a dear friend.
What should we do?
You start feeling grief...
once you recover...
from the shock.
Even if...
it wasn't the death of your friend.
(Seven days later)
What do you think you are doing?
You haven't shown up in the kitchen for a week now.
Everything is out of order. Customers are complaining.
If this goes on, we'll soon be closing the restaurant.
Close the restaurant.
It's weird for it to be still open.
What?
Who would want to eat...
noodles that were once cooked by a murderer?
Close the restaurant until people forget about him.
That's the right thing to do.
I'm sorry that he killed your parents.
The fact that Kim Gil Do is a murderer...
was also a big shock to all of us.
But what does Goongnakwon have to do with anything?
We all worked very hard to get here.
I can't just stand by and watch it go down like this.
It's unacceptable. I won't allow it.
Resign from Master of Noodles.
You are the one who messed up Goongnakwon.
You were supposed to protect it,
but you ruined it instead.
Leave right now.
I can't do that.
I have to keep my place.
Kim Gil Do will definitely show up.
Even if someone has to die, that's when it'll end.
Stop it.
My friend died.
Burning with vengeance against Kim Gil Do,
I didn't even care about my friends.
I'm the one...
who led them into this mess.
I'm...
practically the reason why Tae Ha died.
Ms Seol.
Let me give you a word of advice.
You don't want my anger firing towards you.
I don't think you'd be able to handle it.
So just sit tight.
At least until Kim Gil Do dies.
Let me give you a word of advice, too.
Don't get innocent people involved in your revenge.
From now on,
you're no longer the top head of noodles to me.
I will drag you down from that position,
no matter what it takes.
He thinks he can have everything his way.
How worse will it be when he becomes the noodle master?
Gang Sook, aren't you going to do anything about it?
Are you even listening to me?
My gosh, why are you being so cold-hearted?
His friend just died.
We should give him some time to grieve.
What's your problem? You're acting like a dictator.
What? A dictator? Hey!
What? I didn't say anything wrong.
After getting the shares from Mr Ha,
you're poking around here and there.
Just try to understand others.
I understand the restaurant is important,
but nothing is more important than people.
My goodness.
I guess...
you don't get carsick.
I do, if I have an empty stomach.
Let go of me before I scream.
You're the thief, not me.
Stop it.
Oh, no! Hide.
You smell of sweat, car...
and dumplings.
But when all that combines together,
do you know what it smells like?
It smells like Tae Ha.
What are you doing here?
What are they?
They're Tae Ha's stuff.
I can't believe this.
I keep crying every time I say his name.
Tae Ha...
Don't flatter yourself. I'm just throwing it away.
Please do me a favour.
Please remember my smell.
Mr Park left a big hole in everyone's hearts.
After my father passed away,
I realised how hard it is to miss someone who left me.
You have no choice but to cry as much as you want.
Something has been bothering for a long time.
I once said you have bad blood in you.
I can't believe I had said such a hurtful thing.
It's not like my blood is any cleaner.
What I said to you kept weight me down...
the whole time.
However hard I tried, I couldn't get it out of my head.
I'm sorry.
I really mean it, Da Hae.
It's okay.
I knew that...
you didn't mean it.
Myeong will be going through a tough time.
Ms Seol will make it even worse.
He'll feel like he's being attacked from all sides.
We should protect him.
I know.
Whatever they say,
the person who loves noodles the most...
is Myeong.
I will do what I can to help.
I know very well that you and I...
can't go back to the day we cooked and ate together.
But...
when we're going through a tough time,
we could lend each other a shoulder.
Wouldn't that help?
I wish that were possible.
I'll do that, Ma'am.
I'd like to...
thank you.
(Park Tae Ha)
(So Tae Seop is most likely to represent his party.)
Ms Chae.
Is something wrong?
I'm at fault.
Quit putting on a show, you jerk.
Take him.
Any news yet?
He's on his way.
I'm sorry.
I'm disabled, you see.
Can we begin right away?
Of course.
I lived waiting for this day.
Come with me.
Do you remember him? Mr Hwang Sung Rok.
How could I forget him?
You look great.
You lost some weight.
Were you under some stress recently?
Not at all.
I even signed autographs...
while in hiding.
People don't care about me...
as much as I thought they would.
They will now.
We'll start with a case you're both involved in.
Mr Kim Gil Do.
On May 27, 2014,
did you order Mr Hwang's murder under a bridge?
What are you talking about?
Why would he want me dead?
These questions...
are based on the statement you gave us.
There was a mistake.
Or maybe...
I felt threatened during the interview.
To be honest,
I can't really remember if...
I made such a statement.
What are you doing?
Every interview is taped and preserved as evidence.
There was no misunderstanding or threats.
What happens if I change my statement?
It can't be.
Did you two...
My previous statement is invalid.
I want to revise it.
Get Mr Hwang out of here.
Did you bribe a witness...
while you were on the run?
Take things in the way they are.
Don't imagine things.
You beast.
I think you're a little emotional.
Let me help you out.
Congressman So Tae Seop's domestic helper.
I killed her.
That was me.
But the murder of Ha Jung Tae and his wife.
You only have Choi Soon Seok's statement and no proof.
And unfortunately, the statute of limitations...
for both cases have expired.
Then there's the case about Congressman Choi's cheques.
That's on the CEO of Raymond Company.
His name is Lee Jeong Beom.
You decided not to indict him,
so it has nothing to do with me.
You also said that...
I disappeared for a week during my arrest.
I didn't disappear.
I was in an accident and the shock left me panicked.
I lost my bearings.
What about Tae Ha? You killed him.
You killed him to hide your secrets.
Stop imagining things.
A prosecutor should work with evidence.
All your creative guesswork got you in this mess.
You jerk.
Don't, Ms Chae.
Ms Chae.
Listen carefully.
I didn't kill Tae Ha.
I don't care if you believe me or not.
But that's the truth.
Mr Hwang.
I'm listening.
Can you do me one more thing?
Do you realise that we're in...
the Public Prosecutors' Office?
There's something I need.
It will be hard to get,
but get it for me.
People don't procure things.
Money does.
What is it you need?
Does this mean you let Kim Gil Do off completely,
while making us look like...
we arrest the innocent and coerce statements from them?
- Is that right? - Please give me more time, Sir.
- If I look into... - What then?
Will you find evidence you couldn't before?
In just seven days, he bribed a witness...
and destroyed evidence,
while you sat and did nothing.
I apologise.
I heard you accepted a bribe.
I also know you gave it all to an orphanage.
I understand that you had no choice at the time.
But...
a crime is still a crime.
You can choose 1 of 2 options.
Be dismissed...
or be arrested for accepting a bribe.
Dismiss me.
You're now suspended until you're officially dismissed.
You are forbidden from working as a prosecutor.
(Goongnakwon's Kim Gil Do Appears Voluntarily)
This little insect.
Shall I deal with him?
We can't get into trouble...
right before an important event.
I will take over the party convention...
and then run for president.
I can kill an insect whenever I want.
Tell me if you change your mind, Sir.
Instead,
hire more bodyguards.
Gil Do...
will come for me.
Ms Chae Yeo Kyung's here to see you.
Let her in.
- Sir. - You let Gil Do go.
The witness changed his statement.
Good for him.
I bet he got off, too.
He must be happy.
Give me another chance.
Weren't you dismissed?
Forget all about it...
and find a new job.
You're a smart girl. You'll manage to make a living.
I can't give up now.
You have to help me. Only then...
will you be able to achieve your goal with ease.
You've changed a lot since we first met.
Are you threatening me?
If that's how you feel,
then yes, this is a threat.
The threat you just made...
is an empty threat, not a loaded one.
Do you even have...
the confidential document?
I do.
Are you sure?
I asked if you're sure.
(Dear Yeo Kyung)
(I wrote a reply to each letter you sent me.)
I wrote a reply to each letter you sent me.
I meant to send each of them,
but I didn't because I was afraid of distracting you.
Read them whenever you miss me.
That...
is all I want, Yeo Kyung.
Kim Gil Do.
The back is the best spot to stab a person.
Don't show it to just anyone.
Get out.
When one is afraid, their pupils dilate.
That helps them focus on the attacker.
Their mouth also drops open.
Instinct prepares them...
so they can shout for help.
That's what you're doing.
Nothing has changed. You're still the same.
Tae Ha's death...
is on So Tae Seop.
Take your pick.
So Tae Seop who killed Tae Ha.
Or me who instigated your parents' murders.
If you pick So Tae Seop,
you and I will become allies for a brief period.
But if you pick me,
we must fight until one of us dies.
There's no other way.
Don't you think we should end...
this ill-fated relationship?
Show me proof that So Tae Seop killed him.
I won't believe you unless I see it.
These are photos of Da Hae...
that So Tae Seop sent me when he kidnapped her.
And there's this.
Exchange your life with your daughter's. It's simple.
There's a warehouse in Incheon.
I'll text you the address. Come over.
If you die to save your daughter,
wouldn't that be a fair trade?
He made...
the same call to Tae Ha.
Tae Ha reached the warehouse before I did,
and that's how he died.
So Tae Seop.
I'll kill him.
To do that,
I need your help.
One.
Two.
Three.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not sorry at all.
Kim Gil Do!
Shut your mouth!
If I wanted you dead,
I'd have killed you hundreds of times!
It's not over yet.
So be ready.
My father was a monster who killed two people,
but I didn't become one.
Blaming your unfortunate past for becoming a monster...
is just an excuse.
What do you know about me?
I saw your truth...
at the charnel house...
You said it was an act,
but no one can fake such tears.
Your last ounce of truth.
Stay true to it.
The only one who can stop this...
is you.
Shut it.
(Kim Gil Do)
Gil Do, how have you been?
Thanks to you, it wasn't easy.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Why were you being so greedy?
If you just lived your life the way it was,
things wouldn't have come this far.
I can't dare to compare my greed to yours.
It's not that I'm greedy.
It's just that I have no power.
Is that how it works?
May I go in?
Why...
did you kidnap Da Hae?
Because I thought you'd come to get her.
I didn't know you'd even abandon your own daughter.
Why did you kill Tae Ha?
I didn't purposely kill him.
He came to me to die.
He thought it was the only way for him...
to keep Da Hae and Prosecutor Chae alive.
He is completely different from you.
You should've taken just the confidential document.
You should've just taken the secret recipe.
Why did you have to...
burn two people to death and let things come this far?
Everything started from...
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
when I met you.
Everything went wrong from that moment on.
And I can't undo anything.
You're right.
You can't...
undo anything any more.
So Tae Seop.
I'll kill him.
To do that,
I need your help.
(Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung)
The number you have dialled is not available...
Why are you here?
I want you to do me a favour.
Let me meet with So Tae Seop.
That's not hard.
But I need to know why.
He's...
the one who killed Tae Ha.
I will never forgive that jerk.
It's too dangerous, Yeo Kyung.
There won't be a way out.
I've already lost Tae Ha.
I don't want to lose you.
Who will you stop next when I die?
We can't put up with this forever.
Yeo Kyung.
I can't...
send Tae Ha like this.
We just can't...
do that to him, Myeong.
I couldn't forget this scent.
I really wanted to eat lotus flower noodles.
I should have served you the dish more often.
- I'm sorry, Sir. - Please don't say that.
If it weren't for you,
I would never have had the chance to try it.
Sir.
Yes?
I have a favour to ask of you.
Tell me.
I can do anything for you.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Kyung wants to see you.
How do you know her?
I was summoned a few times for Kim Gil Do's case.
Maybe I shouldn't have said that.
- I'm sorry, Sir. - You don't need to be.
If she wants to see me that desperately,
I should go see her.
Da Hae.
Yes?
Go get some rest.
You look very tired.
There are people who work harder than me.
You look so pitiful.
I feel so sorry for you.
Gosh.
Ms Kim Da Hae.
We got an order for royal pheasant buckwheat noodles.
You should tell Deputy Head of Noodles about it.
What? What do I need to do?
The customer wants you...
to cook it and serve it to him yourself.
What?
Put it down here.
I came here as a guest today.
You did a good job with the dough.
It has a good consistency.
And I like the fragrance of buckwheat.
You are skilled enough...
to serve noodles...
on your own.
Who killed...
Tae Ha?
Tell me.
Did you kill him?
Was it you?
Please tell me it wasn't.
Please tell me that...
you didn't kill him.
I didn't kill him.
Then who did it?
Who killed him?
Someone you don't know.
Someone you shouldn't know.
It's your fault.
It's all because of you.
Why didn't you answer my call?
If you had answered my call,
I wouldn't have been kidnapped.
Tae Ha...
got killed while trying to save me.
He was killed because of me.
No.
If you didn't do bad things, Tae Ha wouldn't have died.
You're the one who should've died.
You're the one who committed all the crimes.
Why does Tae Ha have to be the one to get killed?
Why?
Why? Why?
My goodness.
It's been a while, Prosecutor.
Have you been well?
I've been well, thanks to you.
You wouldn't want to see me for no reason.
What's going on?
I found out the man who kidnapped Da Hae.
He killed Tae Ha, too.
Who is that worthless jerk?
Send up Chae Yeo Kyung only.
Block everyone else from entering.
Yes, Sir.
There's no use.
No one's here to help you.
What do you think you're doing?
Tae Ha...
was a dear friend of mine. But you...
killed him.
So what?
Are you trying to hurt me?
No.
Tae Ha and I...
don't kill people.
You should use the correct vocabulary.
It's not that you don't. You just can't.
I work for this country.
You know what will happen to you...
if you lay a finger on me, right?
You'll all be gone without a trace. Do you know that?
Let's just say that I can't kill...
since you insist on putting it that way.
But...
there are also people who aren't like us.
Goodbye.
What are you talking about?
Your call has been forwarded...
The moment I met you...
30 years ago,
everything got ruined.
What would've happened to my life...
if I hadn't come across that flyer?
You'd probably be somewhere...
mimicking someone else's life.
Then, if you like...
what you have, you would steal that life completely.
I thought about living a new life,
but it's not that easy.
I'm too tired.
The whole world knows that you're a murderer.
How can you possibly live a new life now?
That's why I'm thinking of giving up.
Gil Do.
We can talk this out.
You want the gold badge, right? I'll give you one.
I'll give you 10 if that's what you need.
Calm down, Gil Do. Calm down.
This is not right. You've misunderstood something.
Stop it.
I will live as a beast...
for one more day.
Goodbye.
Were you waiting for me?
What are you doing?
Something that a coward like you...
can never do.
Ha Jung Tae.
Park Tae Ha.
You two are dead in a place where I was born.
In my life, there was a time...
when I felt guilty for the first and last time.
It was when...
I pushed...
your father, Ha Jung Tae, off of a cliff.
I've lived by many names,
but I was the happiest when I lived as Ha Jung Tae.
It felt as if...
I was born with that name.
We had to live in agony...
because of that happiness of yours.
I'm sorry,
but I don't feel sorry at all.
All I did was do my best...
to survive.
Is that...
so wrong?
You are a beast.
I thought about mimicking another life again.
But...
I am too tired to do that now.
I stole...
your father's recipe note.
That was...
the beginning of Goongnakwon.
I have one bullet left.
I either shoot you...
or...
myself.
It's either one of the two.
How many people do you think...
get to die in the place they were born?
Is it an unfortunate thing...
or a fortunate thing?
No.
You can't die that easily.
Myeong.
No, Soon Seok.
This isn't you getting your revenge.
It's me putting and end to this myself.
The beginning and ending...
is always judged and decided...
by me.
No!
No.
Hey, Prosecutor Chae.
Take a seat.
You don't have to report your expulsion.
I came to turn myself in.
Turn yourself in?
Are you saying you committed a crime?
On November 10, 2007,
there was a murder case at Sarang Orphanage,
and I'm the murderer.
What? What are you talking about?
I've also committed crimes as a prosecutor.
I destroyed evidence, took bribes, assisted murder...
and did many more.
(Top Head of Noodles, Moo Myeong)
Everyone is leaving.
One after the other.
My father put his entire life into these recipes.
Your father stole it,
but I am giving this to you.
Why are you giving this to me?
Please keep Goongnakwon going.
You're the only one who can make noodles...
with your heart, not just with your hands.
So keep it going.
(Three years later)
Hello.
I am Kim Da Hae, Head of Noodles.
As you know,
there has been many complications...
at Goongnakwon for the last few years.
We haven't fully healed from our scars,
and we still have many problems.
However,
I believe we can overcome this...
if we all work together as one.
I will also do my best.
From now on, everything I say is an order,
not a request.
I will not take any objections,
and I won't tolerate disobedience.
From now on, everything I say is an order,
not a request.
I will not take any objections,
and I won't tolerate disobedience.
Let's begin with two servings of...
royal pheasant buckwheat noodles.
Let us begin.
Why are you so late?
Look at you, putting on make-up and everything.
I wanted to look pretty. Is that bad?
Get in.
What are you doing? Why are you riding in the back?
Am I your driver or what?
You're my manager...
and I'm the next Master of Noodles...
who also has a 50 percent share of Goongnakwon.
I might just fire you.
My goodness, this is unbelievably lousy.
(Park Tae Ha)
I wasn't going to cry.
I...
didn't run away.
I fought everything just like you told me to,
and I'll continue to do so.
So...
please watch over me, Tae Ha.
And...
you too, Mum.
(Kim Seon Joo)
Are you okay?
Look at your hands.
May I have a bowl of noodles?
What kind of noodles would you like?
Shouldn't you look at me when you take my order?
It looks good.
It's good.
So...
we're back.
Both you...
and me.
It took too long.
You're right.
Do you remember...
the noodles the four of us ate at Chimyeon Restaurant?
That was really good.
A bit more.
Just enough of this.
Here.
Some sesame seeds.
- Can I eat? - Yes.
Let's eat.
- Give me that. - He ate too much.
It's really good.
You're eating your hair, too.
- It's good. - Your shirt's dirty.
Thanks for the bow.
- There's more. - Let Yeo Kyung finish it.
- It's mine. - I'll make you more.
Gil Yong.
Will you hit me?
Hey!
Myeong!
- It's mine. - I want more.
- It's good. - It's nice.
- I want more. - I haven't eaten yet.
- Stop it. - Gosh.
Hang on.
Hey.
What?
It's so good.
- What? - Try this.
Eat up.
(Thank you for watching "Master of Revenge".)
Don't they feed you at Goongnakwon?
I guess so.
- How funny. - Come to me if you're hungry.
Okay? I'll buy you a snack.
No thanks.
Yeo Kyung's eating everything.
(Master of Revenge)