Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Noodle Masters @ Viki
Last Episode
Everything was a lie.
♬ It's bitter world. ♬
Being the best...
♬  It's bitter world. ♬
There's actually nothing much to it.
I, too...
I want to stop feeling guilty every time I see you. I'm sick and tired of it.
Friends... there's not much to it.
...and Yeo Gyeong.
We both lied about things we shouldn't have lied about.
Lies that will make us regret doing forever.
Tae Ha, this is where...
♬ My mother died.  ♬
♬ There is nowhere left to hide ♬
♬  I can't deny  ♬
There are no such things as useless friends.
♬ Photographs  ♬
When you're faced with a friend's death, always...
shock and sadness precede the death.
What now...
♬ Good bye, good bye my love ♬
♬ There is nothing left I can say ♬
Sadness... only after the shock wears off...
sweeps over.
Even if you weren't friends.
♬ Why did it have to be me? ♬
♬ Tell me why ♬
♬ Good bye my love... Good bye ♬
7 days later
♬  It's not enough for me ♬
♬ How long insanity was ♬
♬ Why did it have to be me? ♬
Prime Noodle Chef, what are you trying to do right now?
You've abandoned the kitchen for a week now!
The kitchen is a mess and the customers' complaints are pouring in. Goong Rak Won will close down this way!
Close it down. It's stranger to keep business running.
What?
Who would eat noodles prepared by a murderer?
Until Kim Gil Do's trace has been erased from Goong Rak Won, close it. That's the right thing.
It was unfortunate your parents passed away in that manner.
The fact that Kim Gil Do was a murderer is as big of a shock to us as it is to you!
But why should Goong Rak Won be hurt by that?
Somehow it's come this far.
eI can't see it fall apart like this. I will not ever stand for that. I can't watch that happen.
Quit the Prime Noodle Chef position. You are most liable for making Goong Rak Won this way.
You should've embraced it and covered it up. You dug up a wound.
Leave at once.
I can't leave. I have to protect this position.
Kim Gil Do will appear.
Whoever dies, we'll have to see the end to it then.
You, really...!
My friend died.
Because I was blinded by my desire to destroy Kim Gil Do to take revenge...
I didn't consider my friends at all.
My friends came into this hell because of me.
It's the same as if I killed Tae Ha.
Madam Seol, let me give you some advice.
My anger... don't let it be directed toward you.
You won't be able to handle it.
So, just stay put. At least until Kim Gil Do dies.
Should I give you advice, too? Don't drag in innocent people into your revenge.
You're not the Prime Noodle Chef to me anymore.
I'll do anything in my power to drag you down.
Everything is his way or no way.
He's acting like that as the Prime Noodle Chef. How much worse could he be as the Noodle Master?
Are you going to stay put? Are you listening to me?
Seriously, how can you be so heartless? His friend died.
We should give him time to mourn.
What in the world... it's not like you're a pig with an armband. Why are you so frustrated?
What? A pig with an armband? Hey!
What? Did I say something wrong?
Just because you got a few shares from the Noodle Master,
gosh, you're excited to go around causing a ruckus.
Think of other people. No matter how important noodles are, it's not more important than people.
It...seems like you don't have motion sickness.
I do, if I don't eat.
Let go, before I yell.
You're the thief, not me.
What? What happened?
The smell of sweat, cars, and dumplings.
Do you know what they smell like in combination?
It smells like Tae Ha.
What are you doing here?
What is this?
Tae Ha's things.
This is driving me crazy...Just saying his name is making me cry.
Tae Ha...
Don't misunderstand. I'm throwing it away to you.
I have a request.
Remember my scent.
Secretary Park left quite a trace.
After my father passed away like that,
I know better than anyone else what an empty place a person leaves behind.
There's no other way. You cry your heart out if you want to. What can you do?
There's something I said that's stuck in my heart like a thorn.
When I said you have dirty blood in you...
How could I have said such a thing as a human being?
My blood isn't all that clean, you know.
What I said, just like that...
it's stuck right here. No matter how hard I tried to pull it out, I couldn't.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Da Hee.
It's okay. You weren't being genuine...
I knew it.
And you know Moo Myeong... he must be struggling so much right now.
Madam Seol will shake him up quite a bit.
His life must've been hell all around. Shouldn't we protect him?
I know.
No matter what anyone says... the person who genuinely loves noodles in Goong Rak Won is...
Myeong.
I will become a source of strength as well.
You and I...
I know very well that we can't go back to the time we used to eat noodles together.
But still...
Whenever you guys go through a hard time, can you sit next to each other like this and comfort each other?
I would really like it if you guys did that.
I'll do that, Madam.
Also,
thank you very much.
Park Tae Ha
Private Bank
Korean Freedomn Party's Head, longest incumbent Assemblyman Seo Tae Seop...
Prosecutor Choi Yeo Gyeong
Prosecutor.
Did something happen?
Prosecutor, it's my fault.
Stop this act, you son of b*itch.
Arrest him.
He's not here yet?
He's on his way.
I'm sorry. Due to my disability...
Can we start right away?
Of course. I've lived for this day.
Let's go.
You remember, right? Secretary Hwang Seong Rok.
How can I forget?
You look good.
You've lost some weight.
You seem to have suffered a little.
What suffering?
Even in hiding, I've given out my signature.
People didn't have much interest in me as I had expected.
People will now have more interest in you.
We will start with your relationship to each other first.
Kim Gil Do...
May 27, 2014. You ordered Hwang Seong Rok's murder under a bridge, right?
What are you talking about?
Why would the Noodle Master want to kill me?
These questions were formed based on your testimony.
There must've been a mistake.
Or the coercive mood could've been present during the time of my testimony.
Whether I made that type of testimony or not...
I can't really remember.
What are you doing right now?!
All the testimony procedures are recorded and remain as evidence.
The mood was not coercive and there was no mistake.
What happens if I retract my testimony?
Don't say that you guys...
I have no intention of maintaining the same testimony.
I retract my testimony.
Take away the reference witness Hwang Seong Rok.
Did you tamper with the witness while you were on the run?
Just take things as they are.
Don't imagine things.
You animal.
You look upset, Prosecutor.
I'll lighten up your load.
You know Assemblyman So Tae Seop's housekeeper from the past...
I did kill her.
I did kill her, yes. But Ha Jung Tae and his wife's murders...
You only have Choi Soon Seok's testimony, but no evidence.
And unfortunately, the statute of limitations on both cases have expired.
And Assemblyman Choi's case on the checks that were issued...
CEO Lee Jeong Beom of Raymond Company did that.
And since the Prosecutors' Office dropped that case, I have nothing to do with that.
And you said I ran away for seven days while I was being arrested.
It's not running away...
It was an accident. Due to the shock, in the state of panic...
I got lost.
What about Tae Ha? You killed him!
You killed him to hide your secrets!
That's just you imagining things.
A prosecutor should only use evidence. She must not use speculation and her imagination.
You son of a b*tch!
Prosecutor, you must not.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Gyeong, listen carefully.
I did not kill Tae Ha.
Whether you believe me or not, I don't care.
But that is the truth.
Secretary Hwang.
Say it.
I'd like you to take care of one more thing for me.
Are you not aware that we are
in the restroom of the prosecutors' office?
I have an item I need. It's hard to come by it, but I really need you to get it for me.
Would a person be able to come by it? It's only through money you can get it.
What is it that you want?
Then, are we forced to acquit Kim Gil Do?
We've been embarrassed due to conducting a difficult exigent arrest and coercing testimony that's been retracted.
Is that right?
Give me a little more time. If I dig a little more...
If you dig...
does nonexistent evidence appear?
Only in seven days, the bastard manipulated the witness and even obtained evidence.
During those seven days you relaxed!
- I'm sorry. - I received a report about you accepting a bribe.
I know all of the money went to the orphanage.
I understand you had no choice but to accept it to get to Kim Gil Do. But...
A criminal is a criminal.
You have two choice. One, dismissal.
The other choice is to be arrested for accepting a bribe.
Why don't you dismiss me?
You're suspended from this moment on until you receive a formal dismissal.
You're prohibited to conduct any business as a prosecutor.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Noodle Masters @ Viki
That insect like man.
Should I take care of it?
There's no need to make my rash even bigger by scratching it before the upcoming event.
At the political convention, I'll get the control of the party.
I'll enter the presidential election right away.
You can always clean a bug, don't you think?
If you change your mind, let me know.
Instead, increase my security.
That Kim Gil Do... he's more than capable of coming to get me.
Assemblyman, Prosecutor Chae Yeo Gyeong is here to see you.
Tell her to come in!
- Assemblyman. - Kim Gil Do got released?
The witness retracted his testimony.
The witness played you. He got his case dropped.
He must be so happy.
Please give me another chance.
Weren't you dismissed? Now, just forget everything and...
look for a new line of work. You're smart, so...
you won't have a problem making a living wherever you go.
I can't give up here.
You have to help me so that
in the future when you do big things, there won't be any problems.
Look at this girl, you've been soaking in shit water. Are you threatening me now?
If you feel that it is a threat... then yes, it is a threat.
What you're doing right now... it's not just a threat. It's called bluffing.
You... do you even have the classified document?
Of course.
Are you certain?... I'm asking if you're certain?!
Yeo Gyeong, there are so many stars by the prison window tonight...
Whenever I received a letter from you, I wrote you a reply.
I've been meaning to mail it to you. But I put them away because I didn't want to shake you up.
Read it whenever you think of me.
That's enough for me, Yeo Gyeong.
Kim Gil Do.
The best spot to stab is your back.
You can't turn your back too easily.
Get out immediately.
When someone feels threatened, their pupils dilate.
That way, they can better see dangerous situations.
And their mouths slightly widen.
They're getting ready... to scream 'save me'.
That includes you as well.
You haven't changed a bit. Then and even now.
Tae Ha was killed by So Tae Sub.
Choose now...
So Tae Seop who killed Tae Ha. I, who ordered your parents' murder.
If you choose So Tae Seop,
you and I will work together on the same side.
If you choose me, we have to fight until one of us dies.
There are no other options.
We have to end this tiresome unlucky fate somehow.
Give me proof that So Tae Seop killed him... until you show me, I can't believe it.
It's a picture of my daughter Da Hae kidnapped by So Tae Seop.
and this...
We're exchanging your daughter for your life. It's simple.
There's a warehouse in Incheon. I'll give you the address. Hurry up and go there.
You die and let your daughter live. Isn't that a fair trade?
He made this same call to Tae Ha.
and Tae Ha arrived at the warehouse first...
that's how he died.
I will kill So Tae Seop.
I need your help to do that.
One... Two... Three...
I'm sorry, but I'm not sorry at all...
Kim Gil Do!
Shut up!
If I was going to kill you, I could've done it a hundred times over!
It's not over yet. So look forward to it.
My father was a monster who killed two people.
I did not become a monster.
To say you've become a monster due to your unfortunate past...
that excuse is not allowed.
What do you know about me?
I saw your sincere feeling at the ossuary that day.
You said that you were acting. But you can't cry like that falsely.
Please keep your last shred of genuine intentions.
The only one that can end this hell... is you.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Shut up!
- Gil Do, have you been well? - I've been suffering a bit thanks to you.
You're going through a lot in your old age. Why are you so greedy?
If you live a grounded life, things like these would not have happened.
How could it be compared to your greed?
It's not about my greed. It's because of my lack of power that I had to let myself be manipulated.
How can you say that?
Can I come in?
Why did you kidnap Da Hae?
Only then will you show yourself.
I can't imagine that you would be nonchalant about your own daughter.
Why did you kill Tae Ha?
It's not that I wanted to kill him,
it's that he came to me to be killed.
He thought that his death would ensure Da Hae would live, and that Prosecutor Chae could also be saved.
He and you are two entirely different persons.
Wouldn't it be enough for you to take away the classified document?
Wouldn't it have been enough for you to steal the noodle recipe?
Why did you have to kill? Even to burn two persons to death, and causing all that commotion?
Everything started after having met you, Assemblyman.
It all went downhill from then onwards.
There's no turning back since.
That's right. There's no turning back now.
I want to kill Assemblyman So Tae Sub.
To do that, I need your help, Prosecutor Chae.
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Gyeong
The person you are calling is unable to take your call
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Noodle Masters @ Viki
Why are you here?
I have a favor to ask of you. Help me to meet Assemblyman So Tae Sub.
That won't be difficult.
But you have to tell me the reason.
Tae Ha was killed by Assemblyman So Tae Sub.
I definitely cannot forgive him.
That's dangerous, Yeo Gyeong. If you fall deeper, you will not be able to climb out of it.
I already lost Tae Ha. I don't want to lose you too.
After losing me as well, who are you going to obstruct next?
- We can't continue to endure and suffer in silence.
We can't let Tae Ha leave in such a lonely way.
At least for us, we can't do that.
How can I forget this fragrant smell?
Do you know how much I longed to eat Lotus Flower Noodle?
I should have offered it to you often. I'm sorry.
Don't say stuff like that.
If not for you, when can I find an opportunity like this to eat such a precious noodle?
Excuse me, Assemblyman.
Yes.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Tell me. Whatever it is, can I say no?
Prosecutor Chae Yeo Gyeong wants to meet you.
How do you know Prosecutor Chae?
I have been summoned several times because of Kim Gil Do.
It looks like I shouldn't have uttered those words. Please take it as if you didn't hear them.
No, it's not that. Alright, since she wants to meet me so badly, I should meet her.
- Da Hae. -Yes.
You have to pace yourself. If you continue this way, you will collapse from exhaustion.
There are people who could make 100 bowls of noodles by themselves.
I don't like this. I'm going crazy with worry because of you.
Noodle Chef Kim Da Hae, please make one palace pheasant buckwheat noodles.
You should give the order to the Assistant Noodle Chef first.
Oh? What? I'm the Assistant Noodle Chef. What is it?
The customer wants you personally to cook and serve him.
Pardon?
Over here.
I came as a customer today.
Your skill in kneading the dough has improved quite a bit.
The stickiness is just perfect and the smell of buckwheat is perfect as well.
With this level of your skill, you won't be ashamed anywhere out there.
Who killed Tae Ha?
Tell me.
Did you kill him? Is that the case?
Tell me that it isn't. Please tell me that you didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
Then, whose doing is it?
Who killed him?
Someone you don't know. You shouldn't know who did it either.
It's because of you. Everything is because of you!
Why didn't you answer your phone that time? If you had answered, then I wouldn't have been kidnapped.
Tae Ha... He died while trying to save me.
I said he died because of me.
No. If you hadn't done anything bad, then Tae Ha wouldn't be dead now.
You should've died.
You're the one who committed the crime. Why did an innocent person have to die?
Why? Why? WHY?
Aigoo... It's been a while, Prosecutor.
- Have you been well?  -Thanks to you.
You didn't call me because I'm nice, so what's the matter?
I found out who kidnapped Da Hae.
That person killed Tae Ha too.
Who is the bastard?
Only allow Chae Yeo Gyeong to come up here.
Block the rest.
Alright.
There's no use in that.
There is no one to help you.
What are you doing right now?
Tae Ha is a friend like my life.
That Tae Ha was killed by you.
So... are you trying to kill me?
No. We don't kill people.
Tae Ha and I both.
Even if you get things crooked, say the right thing.
It's not that you don't kill, it's that you cannot kill.
I'm a man who moves a nation.
If you lay your finger on me,
you do know what's going to happen, right?
Then you guys will disappear without any trace.
Because you said that, let's just go with that w can't kill people.
But it seems there is someone who's not like us.
Then...
What are you doing?!
The caller could not pick up the phone.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by  The Lucky Team @ Viki
Thirty years ago,
the moment that I met you,
everything became a mess.
If I hadn't seen a flyer for a tutor...
How do you think that my life would have been?
You would've gone elsewhere and...
lived imitating someone else's life.
And if you liked something of his, you would've stolen everything from him.
I've even thought of living a new life.
But it doesn't seem so easy.
I became too sick of it.
The whole world knows that you're a murderer.
Living a new life... do you think that that is possible?
That's why now... I'm wondering if I should give up.
If there's something that you're upset with... use words!
You want an assemblyman's gold badge, right? I'll give you one. No, not just one. I can give you ten. Hey!
Calm down, Gil Do!
This is not it! There has been a misunderstanding!
Stop!
Today, once more, it seems I have to live as a monster.
Goodbye.
Were you waiting for me?
What are you doing?
Something that a scaredy cat like you couldn't do.
Ha Jung Tae. Park Tae Ha.
You died because I was born.
As I lived life,
there was one moment I felt guilty.
When I pushed Ha Jung Tae, your father
off the cliff.
I've lived with many names.
When Ha Jung Tae disappeared, I was the most happiest.
Like that name was mine from the beginning.
Because of that happiness,
we had to live in hell.
I'm sorry but I am not sorry at all.
In order for me to survive...
I just did my best.
Is that wrong?
You monster.
I thought of living under pretense another time.
but, doing that got me so bored.
Your father's notebook... I stole it.
That was the beginning of Goong Rak Won.
One bullet left.
To use it on you,
or use it on me. You decide.
Because I was born,
how many more people will die?
Is that a misfortune or being lucky?
No.
You can't die so easily.
Myeong... no, Soon Seok...
this isn't you taking revenge.
I'm ending it myself.
The beginning and end... I always form my own judgment and...
I decide.
No!!
No.
Prosecutor Chae. Have a seat.
You don't have to notify me before your dismissal.
I came to surrender myself.
Surrender?
As in "Surrender yourself and live in light?"
November 11, 2007. The murder case from Sarang Orphanage. I'm the culprit.
I mean... What are you saying right now?
Other than that, I committed evidence tampering, accepting bribery, ordering murder...
etc. as a prosecutor.
Prime Noodle Chef, Moo Myeong
In the end, everyone is leaving. One by one.
It contains secret noodle recipes my father compiled throughout his life time.
Your father took it, but I'm giving it to you.
Why... give it to me?
Take care of Goong Rak Won.
Noodles made with genuine heart, not hands...
Only you can do it, Da Hae. I beg you.
[3 Years Later]
I'm Noodle Chef Kim Da Hae.
As you know, there have been many difficulties Goong Rak Won faced in the last few years.
The wounds have not been healed yet and we're still struggling.
But if we all work together, I believe we can definitely overcome it.
I will give my best.
What I say from now, isn't a request, but an order.
I won't accept any type of objections and disobeying my orders is not allowed.
The palace pheasant buckwheat noodles. Let's start with two servings. Let's begin.
What's taking you so long? It's not like we're going anywhere nice. Look at you with makeup.
I wanted to look pretty, why?
Get in.
What are you doing? Why are you sitting in the back? Am I your driver?
You're Director of Operations.
I'm the next Noodle Master and 50% shareholder. I can fire you so easily.
Wow, so disgusting...
Park Tae Ha
I wasn't going to cry.
I... didn't run away.
As you said, I fought and I'll do the same in the future.
So, please watch over me, Tae Ha.
Also,
please do the same, Mother.
Thank you to Channel Manager:pilar_velasquez
Are you feeling okay?
Thank you to our segmenterss:pilar_velasquez, xomachi, kitty100, bjohnsonwong, shms, xiennora
Thank you to our segmenters cont.:whit_eonni, cgwm808, wanttogo, tess6, eards, marykarmelina
Thank you to our Korean-English subbers:jo_p66, ecocare123, jellly, geneva68, jadecloud88
Thank you to our Korean-English subbers cont.:jhyunmi, superwoman123, imashl3y, nutrient, soyummay
Thank you to our Korean-English subbers cont.:clara_kim_544, icedthy, icantsayrural, sophie2you
Thank you to our Korean-English subbers cont.:sheilawendy, eereene, sarahson2, wheelykpopeonni, saralee21
A bowl of noodles please.
What kind of noodle should I serve you, customer?
Shouldn't you be taking anorder by looking at the customer?
Thank you to our Editor:heidi_lyon
It looks delicious.
Thank you to our Chief Editor:cgwm808
Thanks to all The Noodle Masters moderators and subbers
It's delicious.
In the end, I came back to the place.
You and I, both.
It took a long time.
I know right?
Do you remember?
The noodles we shared with everyone at Chi Meon Restaurant.
That was really delicious.
Page Designer:bespark
Thanks to all viewers
Eat.
Let's eat.
Give it.
He's eating well.  Give it.
It's really good.
You're eating your hair, too.
It's good.
You got something on your clothes.
Give me some.
No.
Gil Yong!
You're going to take it away?
Hey!! What is this?!
Don't do that!
♬ My mother died ♬
Hey!-I want to eat too.
♬ There is nowhere left to hide ♬
Seriously!
♬  I can't deny  ♬
♬ Photographs  ♬
What did you say?!
♬ Inside my head,  ♬
♬  Nothing else  ♬
♬  is mine  ♬
Thank you for watching Master: God of Noodles.
Hey, at Gong Rak Won, you don't feed him?
♬ Good bye, good bye my love ♬
When you're hungry, come to me.
♬ There is nothing left that I can say ♬
♬  It's not enough for me ♬
Master: God of Noodles♬  It's not enough for me. How long insanity was ♬
♬ Why did it have to be me? ♬
♬ Tell me why ♬
♬  Goodbye, goodbye my world  ♬ ♬  There is no one left by my side ♬
♫  I can't stand this loneliness. The fear inside my head... ♫