"Five hundred dollars for
the death of Chen Kuo-Wei."
Hey, Friend!
Your style's not bad.
But take it easy, you look beat.
You must be the Four Door Fist Champion,
Chen Kuo-Wei?
Yes I am, and who might you be?
I'm Yen Tieh-hsin.
I've heard of your devil's kick,
It's famous in the Kung-Fu world.
It has never been defeated...
And it never will.
I suppose I should warn you.
I've been given good money to kill you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Someone's paid you to kill me?
I'll give you twice as much to kill him!
You could, only my honor comes first.
You must realize I'm paid to kill.
The contract's sealed.
- So you must die.
- Don't be so sure of that...
For I, champion of the four Door Fists,
have never yet been defeated!
I don't care who you are,
I'll break every bone in your body...
and send you to hell.
"Wong Kei-Ying Martial Art School"
Kai Hsien!
- What's the matter, Master?
- I'm going out, keep an eye on them.
Yes, sir.
Stop!
We won't practice this today.
Let's practice the Fist of Five Styles
which I taught you a few days ago.
He's so lame...
- Three-legged cat.
- Four-eyed rat.
Start now.
Dragon Sees Tiger.
Tiger's rear, Snake's Tongue Darts Out.
Panther Sees Fire,
White Crane Spreads Wings.
Hold it!
Your wrists are too weak.
You can't learn it well, understand?
I suppose you think that was funny,
playing tricks on your teacher!
We'll see. Take that! And that!
- It wasn't me!
- Who was it? Tell me.
Who was it?
Wong Fei-Hung.
Even though Master Wong is your father,
you don't have a right
to cause trouble here.
You think Kung-Fu
is just a performance.
You're telling me my Kung-Fu is bad?
Not too bad, but bad enough.
Show me exactly what's wrong with it.
Look at your Panther Sees Fire.
Well what's wrong?
You've exposed your body.
It's easy to attack you.
And that Horse Stance is
bow-legged. Just a kick...
and you'll fall.
Shut up! Shut up you turkeys!
You'd like to test your
teacher's Kung-Fu, would you?
We can all learn from each other.
I can stand almost anything, you bum!
But I've taken enough of this bullshit!
You've exposed your body again.
Do you know that, teacher?
Your hat!
Here you go!
Pork belly, shut up!
Look! Right foot! Snake stance!
Bastard!
Wong Fei-Hung,
you've taught Hsien a lesson.
We all feel very happy about it.
He's too arrogant, I can't stand it.
You really showed him!
That's great...
Eat more then!
No, I'm talking about that girl.
That perfect frame she's got.
Really sexy!
- How much?
- 30 cents.
Not bad!
I'm willing to trade 10 years
just for a kiss by her!
Kissing is for children.
I could get her to hug and kiss me.
I don't believe you!
You want to bet on it?
I'll bet you a whole dinner.
Deal.
She's hot, she wouldn't
look at you twice!
All right! A whole dinner then.
Just watch.
He's looking for trouble.
This flower is beautiful.
Trust me, try it on.
- Excuse me!
- My eye hurts.
What can I do?
Something got into my eye.
Help me get rid of it, miss. Please, hurry.
Harder.
- He did it!
- Did you see that?
Thanks. Snake!
Don't be afraid...
I'll kill it. Don't be afraid.
That's a great technique.
That's great. I must try
that on your sister.
What did you say? My sister?
Thought you could take advantage
of my daughter, did you?
Me touch her? She was asking
for it, that dumb bitch.
Mother!
You wanted to lay your
filthy hands on her.
On her? That's a laugh.
She's much too ugly.
Think you're real smart, huh?
Well, I'll teach you a lesson, boy.
So you want to play Kung-Fu? Try this!
The old bitch is tough.
Come on, you guys! Hey!
Some friends they make.
You're nothing but a skinny old woman,
so I'll let you win.
Excuse me!
Watch where you're going!
Stumbling about like a drunken stooge!
Antique jade!
Mister, want to buy?
You sure it's real?
Of course.
It's a family heirloom.
It's worth the money, sir.
- How much?
- 10 dollars.
That's too expensive!
It's worth it!
Only 10 cents?! Hey mister!
Mister, I can't sell it that cheap.
Please give it back to me. It's all I have!
I couldn't sell such a
valuable piece for only 10 cents!
Then I'll keep the jade and the money.
Hey, give me back my jade.
Mister, you broke my jade!
Pay me back!
You expect payment from me? Take this!
Father...
- Please, at least give me something.
- No!
What happened?
He's broken my jade and
then he refused to pay me!
Shithead. Piss off.
Who're you calling Shithead?
I'm calling you!
Hand over that man's money!
Pay? Not before I put you in the ground.
It's too bad you feel that way.
There's nothing been going right today,
so you caught me in a bad mood.
Now, I'm gonna have to
teach you how to pay!
Get up!
Wanna kill me?
This is dangerous!
You barely missed my knuckles!
- This is for you, now get going!
- Thank you, sir.
I'm doomed, I'm dead!
Don't be afraid,
it's just the blunt end.
I have no intention of killing you...
yet!
Don't...!
That one really came close.
And watch what you're doing.
Drop dead!
Fists have no eyes, knives have no heart!
Sometimes I can hit by mistake!
I chop, chop, chop... the meat!
I slice, slice, slice... like a cucumber!
I beat, beat, beat... you like garlic!
I'm glad I came across you.
You sure have brightened my day!
It's been ages, brother.
You still look great.
Your brother is old now.
What a beautiful niece I've got.
She's still a kid. Just a bit naive.
Where's Fei-Hung?
He went out.
This naughty boy always goes out to play.
He's a young man now.
I think you may not recognize him.
This time, stay longer.
Fei-Hung, don't go away.
Come greet your auntie and cousin.
Come here, now.
Coming...
Shit!
Say hello.
Auntie, cousin.
- Cousin.
- Fei-Hung.
What happened to your neck?
I... I slept without a pillow.
Without a pillow? Let me help you.
- No thanks, auntie.
- Come on, relax.
Auntie.
Mother!
Feel better now?
Yes.
Brother,
Fei-Hung really looks smart.
He's quite tactful and clever.
Brother, you're really a good father.
Yes, I'm very strict to him.
No wonder I heard people praising
him as soon as I came here.
Really? What did they say?
The son of Wong Kei-Ying is very smart.
He's also a man of justice.
I'm very proud of him.
Come here, my son.
Sit down.
But there are many sex
maniacs in this village.
That's right.
One of them harassed your
niece on the street just now.
When I went to rescue her,
he even attacked me.
You mean to tell me both of you
were attacked here in my own town?
Could you recognize him?
As if I could forget.
Yes, I'd recognize him.
Good, let's find him now.
I'll teach him a real good lesson.
Fei-Hung, come with me.
Uncle! You don't have to go out.
Why?
That guy is right here.
He's standing in this very room.
Who? Where?
Standing right over there.
He's your son Wong Fei-Hung.
You...
Son-of-bitch!
Kneel down!
Father...
You bastard!
You have dishonored me.
Wong Kei-Ying!
I'm doomed.
Wong Kei-Ying.
Master Li, what has happened?
I'll tell you what.
I'm looking for your son.
Why?
Because he's nothing but a wild animal.
He attacked my son for no reason,
breaking his legs, arms, and skull.
He really beat him up.
He looks like a dumpling.
Wong Kei-Ying! I want justice!
- You beast, I must kill you.
- No, Dad... No...
Brother, you mustn't kill your own son.
Yes!
I must kill him, he's a disgrace!
Sounds bad for a teacher of your
standing to flog his own son to death.
Mr. Li didn't come to witness
how you punish your son.
If he must be punished, I suggest
that Mr. Li here is quite capable.
Stop him!
I'm responsible for what I've done.
So let him punish me.
Take this.
Now, I promise I won't fight back.
You dare make fun at this time?
Wong Kei-Ying, what are you gonna do?
As from this moment, I disown him.
This slime is no longer mine.
Do what you like with him.
Mr. Li, I have a proposition.
Let Fei-hung take ten strikes
without any resistance.
Ten strikes should be enough.
Now, Mr. Li, do you approve?
I don't need ten strikes
to kill him, three is enough.
Master, listen.
I'm going to fix that squirt.
Master Chao, be sure you leave
him looking just like I look now.
The Divine Eight.
That palm style of yours,
it's really something.
I'm only getting started!
I'm not dead yet!
You want to cut off my posterity?
Enough!
You've made your ten strikes, Mr. Chow.
You said you would kill
me within three strikes.
Snake and Crane together.
Strike the vital points.
Let's try your Divine Eight again.
I told you I've got style.
Hey! My jacket's getting dirty, take it!
You regret not paying
for that jade now, huh!
- It's me!
- You hit your master.
- Young Master, are you alright?
- Young master, are you okay?
Master, now I look just like you.
Wong Kei-Ying,
you win with your smart tricks.
I'll get you back.
Let's go!
You watch out!
Careful with my son, hurry.
- I'll get you yet!
- So don't come back!
Careful, careful.
He came in with one cripple
and left with two.
You fight well, I give you that.
- But I'll still kill you!
- Brother.
It's useless to beat him anymore.
Let's punish him by Kung-Fu practice.
I've tried with that bastard.
Right!
From now on, you are forbidden
to leave the house.
We'll start with five
hours of Horse Stance!
Now don't move.
Have some more boiling water, bastard!
Hey, are you comfortable?
Are your legs shaking, are they aching?
You know, I feel sorry for you.
Poor little chicken!
You feel itchy? Want me to help you?
Stop. Don't do that!
I'm just carrying out my orders.
See, it's your father's idea.
He says for every bowl you break,
you stay another hour,
you bastard!
Master, you're back!
Yes, his stance appears
to be pretty steady.
- Did he slack off?
- No, I've been watching him.
Really?
Finally some progress.
Yes, I'm very tired.
- Are you really that tired?
- I am, sir.
But you've got a chair, right?
What? A chair? Let me see!
Damn it, a chair...
You dare cheat me
when I'm punishing you.
I really can't do anything about you.
I'll ask your uncle to come
tomorrow and fix you.
Who's he?
Beggar So.
Help me, To Tao!
Hurry!
Practicing your Kung-Fu upside down, huh!
- I'm dying!
- Here, I brought you food.
I'll go get something to drink.
My neck!
Get me down, quickly.
Come on, get up.
You came down so quickly.
Untie me!
Eat this.
Hey, is it true So Hui
is gonna fix you?
- That's right.
- That's bad news for you.
Why?
Do you know anything about Beggar So?
I heard he's very cruel.
All his students have if not
broken arms then broken legs!
Really?
I'm telling you the truth.
Nui was his student and you
know what happened to him?
What?
He lost all his teeth and hair.
His nose got twisted.
Even his own father
couldn't recognize him.
That monster gets pleasure out of
torturing people, he's a real sadist.
- What should I do then?
- You think about it yourself.
You've got to help me,
I don't know what to do!
- Escape, that's the only way!
You're clumsy!
You should try to pay more attention!
- Just go.
- I'll leave now.
"Yue He Restaurant."
Sir, here are the dumplings.
Please have a seat.
Excuse me, do you mind if I sit here?
No, sit down. Go on.
You're by yourself, good.
I don't like to eat alone.
The food here is very good.
Everything looks and tastes great.
Real good smell, really fantastic.
What can I get you, sir?
Why you're alone? Where's Old Shang?
- What's that?
- No, go ahead, eat.
What would you like to eat?
A bowl of shark's fin as appetizer.
- Sorry. We got no shark's fin.
- That's too bad.
Then I want a roasted goose leg. The left
one. A chicken and a steamed grouper.
- Sorry, we have no grouper.
- Then any fish will do.
Also a stewed abalone and
shrimp noodles. Hurry!
And half a catty of
Shaoxing wine, hurry!
One wine!
You have a great appetite.
It is necessary to eat
well to become strong!
Here's the left goose leg, chicken...
- Half litter of Shaoxing wine.
- Yes... no thanks.
- Have a little wine. Be my guest.
- Really, I...
Here, just taste that.
Eat up!
Go on, don't be shy.
Help yourself to what you want.
Enjoy yourself.
Don't stand on ceremony. Here.
Drink...
Go ahead.
I eat...
Drink...
You must be starving!
Very nice.
They sure know how to cook here.
That meal was really something.
I'll pay the bill, don't refuse me.
I'll go and pay it now.
Buy me lunch tomorrow.
I'm leaving. I'll pay today.
You must finish your dinner, okay?
See you tomorrow. Bye for now.
Take care, see you tomorrow.
That will be exactly $1.05.
Someone else will pay the bill.
Really? Who?
The old man over there.
You know him?
He's my father.
Your father?
How many fathers do you have?
He's the boss of this
inn and I'm his son.
That makes you a bastard.
So you just want to eat and run?
Look there.
"PAY OR DIE!"
I ain't poncing meals from you.
Forgot my money, that's all.
I'll come back tomorrow
and pay you then.
"PAY OR DIE!"
Gorilla, beat him up!
Tiger's Claw.
No, hold it, stop. Let's talk.
Stop it.
Go ahead, beat him.
I'll get back what you've eaten.
Now!
Roasted goose's leg. The left one.
And the fish.
That's enough.
Also half a catty of Shaoxing wine.
Now that you emptied my belly,
I feel hungry again.
Hey, that's enough, or do
you want to kill the boy?
No, it's not enough. He is to
do the toilet cleaning for us.
You wanted something to clean?
Thanks old man.
Old bum! How you dare
interfere with our business!
Just look how strong I am.
Watch me jump!
Jump then!
Now you're jumping all right!
This is how to wash your face.
Damn you!
Stop eating!
- We're friends, remember?
- Okay, let's be friends.
You've got arms of iron,
but you've brains of straw.
Stop that, let's get out of here!
This way...
You know what?
I can't help wondering
how old you are.
For your age, you sure are tough.
A necessity.
I've had to be tough to be
able to survive to this age.
Just look at you.
You're weak and useless.
Today was just a bad day.
If I hadn't fallen into the trap,
I'd have beaten them.
Sounds like an excuse.
I forgot to ask why you
couldn't pay for your meal.
That's a long story.
Old man, may I know your name?
I'm Mr. So.
Hey, there's a fellow with the
same name screwing up my life!
It's all his fault!
- Who are you talking about?
- He's this creep named Beggar So.
My own father asked
this guy to train me.
So you're afraid of him?
Afraid? Of course not!
I have heard rumors.
He's very cunning, violent and mean.
But I'll Show him!
That old fart. Wait until
I see him, I'll tear him apart.
You'll show the fart, huh?
Hey, just where do you come from?
The sky is my roof and
I sleep where ever I may.
- So you're a bum?
- Everyone calls me Beggar So.
Your name is Beggar So as well?
Beggar So?
That's the name.
That was close. Good thing I'm fast.
Not fast enough!
You can't escape from me!
Your father paid me well to train you
and that's what I'm going to do!
How long will this take?
- One day?
- One year exactly.
I'll never make it!
You already have your cash,
so you can relax.
I wouldn't do that.
I'm going to enjoy this!
I'll see you in hell!
You're strangling me.
Well, you're just a stupid old fool.
You're just an old beggar who likes
to pretend you're a real tiger.
I'll show you what a tiger's about!
I see your tiger's got a bad paw, huh?
Tiger-Fist!
It's still there!
All that Kung-Fu looks like dancing.
The Crane attacks!
Crane's Beak. Angry Crane.
Crane eats the Shrimp!
- The Crane Flies.
- How's your head?
Your fingers are
stronger than my teeth!
I'm coming to get you!
You scared me!
Climbing trees to get away now, are we?
What? I'm just using Monkey Kung-Fu.
Ready to learn?
Answer! Answer!
Please stop, I want to learn.
But I don't like your
style of recruitment.
Let me down!
I don't want to die like this.
I thought you were
supposed to be a teacher.
But you are trying to kill me.
All students with style
must learn how to fall.
That was only your first lesson.
Trying to escape?
I just wanna take a piss.
So do it there!
From the right jar to the left jar.
The back jar to the right jar.
The back jar to the front jar.
Left jar to the right jar.
The right jar to the front jar.
Left jar to right jar,
right jar to left jar.
I can never finish it!
Continue!
This is torture. Fine!
Fei-Hung! Fei-Hung!
Have a good wash, you old bastard!
Hey you, get out of here.
Do you hear me? Are you deaf?
Are you blind? Can't you see I'm busy.
No hanging around you bum.
Move your ass.
Is this your place?
What if I refuse to move then?
A big mouth and a wet ass.
It should be taught some manners.
How does it feel?
Nice and dry?
Right you twerp! I'll give you dry!
I'll shove you in the head first.
Come on...
What's that supposed to be, Kung-Fu?
Who taught you that load of shit?
Who's your master?
No-one calls my father's Kung-Fu shit!
Judging by that, your old
man's Kung-Fu stinks.
I wouldn't ask him to clean my shoes.
I think you'd better call me father.
Go to hell!
Sit down!
Get up! Sit down again!
All my dogs must obey.
Quit playing!
Take my shoes.
What...?
I don't even need to use my hands.
You'd better use them, I'm not scared!
Had enough?
I won't stop until I send
you straight to hell!
Don't come here!
Ah shit!
You've become a cowardly turtle!
Your skull's like butter.
You could study kung-fu for the rest
of your life and still not beat me.
Killing a nobody like you...
would only ruin my reputation.
Crawl between my legs...
and then go home to your pig-sty!
Crawl!
Wait!
Aren't these your pants?
Judging by that, your old
man's Kung-Fu stinks.
I wouldn't ask him to clean my shoes.
Your skull's like butter.
You could study kung-fu for the rest
of your life and still not beat me.
Killing a nobody like you...
would only ruin my reputation.
Crawl between my legs,
then go home to your pig-sty.
Crawl!
You idiot, this wine is very expensive.
It smells good!
Master, enjoy your wine,
I'll dry your clothes.
Hey, Why are you so sexy?
- The clothes caught fire...
- It's on fire!
Oh god! You've burnt
my best cloak I have!
My back!
- My wrists!
- Your wrists are not strong enough.
More rabbit food...
and the tea's weak & cold.
Stay quiet and eat.
Master, you're giving me a headache.
Eat your meal.
What's wrong?
You're so tired you can't
even use your chopsticks?
Master, I'm finished.
That was quick.
Now, use these smaller
cups to empty it again.
Go on.
I wish I'd known about this part first.
This is killing me.
- Hey, Hung...
- Yes?
Crack this walnut for me.
No, you break it like this.
Now you try.
Please, Master!
Haven't I cracked enough?
Master, why don't we go for a walk?
All right...
Open now...
- Master, you're good!
- Of course.
Observe well... place your bets!
Old man, you should leave now.
Leave?
How can I buy good wine
with so little money?
I've still got more money to win.
Come on, bet...
Trust me, bet there!
Turn it over!
Hurry up!
Quit shouting!
You're amazing, Master. You did it again.
That's great.
Put down your bets.
We're getting rich. It's easy!
You were lucky.
I'll play with you...
in one go!
Right, this is my lucky day.
Come on.
- Choose.
- No problem.
Turn it over.
It's not there.
You think you're quick, huh?
Well, my eyes are quicker.
- So, you're trying to cheat, huh?
- So you're a swindler.
Police is here, run!
You're a dirty thief.
Give me back my money!
You'll never get your money back!
Do you know who I am?
Who cares!
I'll tell you who I am,
I'm Iron-Head Rat.
I'll show you with this brick.
Very hard indeed!
Scared?
Hey. baldy!
Give me back the money!
I don't care who you are! I'll beat you.
I warn you, shitface,
I choose who I bury next!
You don't mind to get hurt, do you?
I'll let you try my iron head!
Master, his head is too hard!
Don't give up!
Let's see you stop my iron head!
This is fun!
Good, very good.
Bet you never guessed you'd
end up in someone's pants!
An iron hammer for an iron head?
Can you take it?
That's enough, please!
Master, my wrists are breaking!
- Lazy!
- No.
My hands are gonna break!
No more exercises.
Go fetch me some wine.
Yes,
"Ru Yi's Restaurant."
Waiter!
Corning. What do you want?
- Some wine.
- Shall I fill it up?
No, three cups will be enough.
Three cups?
Hurry up, don't just stand there.
Damn it! Where's that
stupid boy with my wine?
Idiot!
That's him!
Old man, who are you?
Who's asking?
Old man, have you heard
of the King of Sticks?
Yes, I have. Have you ever
heard of Beggar So then?
Beggar So?
In person!
Let's go!
Don't go. He doesn't
look like Beggar So.
- What?
- Look.
He's trembling, he can't
be the real Beggar So.
So you think you're being funny?
I'm not fooled that easily.
But I'm not lying, I am Beggar So!
Master.
Give me the wine!
It's water!
Idiot! Now see what you've done!
Master!
They're lucky!
If I ever meet them again,
I'll kill them both. Let's go!
Cheer up, eat something.
Master, it's all my
fault you were beaten.
It seems bad luck follows you around.
I've been through a lot of things,
but until this day...
I've never suffered such
humiliation like that!
He wasn't better than you, but you've
no strength without your wine.
You sure can talk.
True, but if I had been taught better,
I could've beaten that jerk.
You mean to say I'm not
teaching you right?
You're just pushing me around.
You're teaching me how to get beaten.
Your father is without question
an excellent martial arts Master.
His methods are among the best.
So why would he ask me
to teach you my style?
He wants you to torture me.
He asked me because he knows
I've got a secret style.
What's that?
The Eight Drunken Gods.
It's nothing special.
That shows your damned ignorance.
Many people have asked me to teach
them but I turned them all down!
Don't be fooled by my staggering,
there's power inside to kill.
It looks real enough, yet it isn't.
Pretending lets you win.
Clever, isn't it?
Why haven't you shown me it before?
Didn't your father tell you that...
foundation is very important.
I do this because I want you
to have a good foundation.
I think you're ready now.
Really?
To study my style, you'll find it
easier if you have a drink first.
Drink up.
Have another cup.
Fei-Hung, have you ever gone to school?
I've spent a few years
in a private school.
"Drink up the wine."
- "May our cups never rest."
- "For I'll sing you a song."
"I'll put your ears to the test."
"Power and wealth are no avail to us.
When only drinking prevails."
Boy, enough, enough.
"Sober men and sages are
lost through the ages."
"All our brave drinkers
shall never die."
"All our brave drinkers shall never die."
"Shing Fung produces
the finest of wines."
"The best soldiers of Shien
Yang are always young."
"Even the King couldn't
stop my drinking."
"Let's drink a toast to
our ship that's sinking."
"With uplifted cup,
I say to the full moon."
"Why does my shadow appear to swoon?"
"Wine in a radiant cup you see."
"Put down that cup the
horses are awaiting thee."
"Fallen on the battlefield, the
soldier says, who will remember me?"
"Who will remember me?"
The God Lu, the drunkard
with inner strength.
The God Li, the drunken cripple
with the powerful right leg.
The God Jun, the drunkard
holding a pot in his arms.
The God Ian, the drunkard with
the sudden deadly waist attack.
The God Chan, the drunkard
with the swift double-kicks.
The God Tso, the drunkard
with the powerful throat lock.
The God Han, the drunken flute
player with powerful wrists.
The God Miss Ho, the drunken
woman flaunting her body.
Concentrate! This is serious.
Isn't this style for women?
Miss Ho is a woman, yes,
but she is strong. Watch me.
Do like I do!
Continue practicing!
Okay, I will.
Practice hard!
This is for sissies. I won't do it!
Wong Kei-Ying!
Why do you persuade the Bull Head Hill
villagers not to sell me their land?
What was your reason for it?
Was it because of that
business over your son?
That's a personal issue.
It'll be settled in good time.
I'm not responsible.
What is your game?
What is yours?
Mr. Li, why do you want to buy the hill?
As you wish to know, I'll tell you.
That old graveyard up there has been haunting
us for centuries, disturbing family spirits!
They'll get more than $20 per lot,
it's good money for that land.
Then you butt your nose in
where it isn't wanted!
You mean you want to buy the graveyard?
Don't you believe me?
There's a curse on the name of Li!
And it must be exorcised.
I've got three mistresses without children!
I'll be content with a chicken egg.
But they can't produce that!
Maybe you've just become impotent.
You can't hide anything
from me, Mr Li.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Li Wan-Hao, I think you just
want what's hidden in the hill.
What would that be?
- The coal.
- The coal?
Bull Head Hill contains
a rich coal deposit.
You secretly deal with the Coal Company to
make profit from the selling of the coal.
You can fool the villagers,
but you can't fool me!
Since you know it, I won't deny.
If you don't interfere,
I'll give you 20% of the profit.
20%? You'd spend so much on me?
Listen, Li Wan-hao,
the hill belongs to the villagers.
No one can take it away,
get out of here!
Wong Kei-Ying,
you're trying to go against me,
No matter how good your Kung-Fu is,
you are going to pay for this!
$1000 for the death of
Wong Kei-Ying of Fushan.
Wong Kei-Ying?
"Teacher's Birthday Ceremony."
Master.
- Is everything ready for tonight?
- Yes.
Hurry up, there will be
many guests tonight.
Hey, Master Hsu.
Big Funeral?
Are you a dumb masochist?
Coming here looking for more punishment?
Didn't you suffer enough last time?
I just wanna have something
to eat and someone to beat.
Alright. I'll make you
an extra special dish!
Master, what would it be?
Bamboo shoot and pork.
- Go get my stick.
- Okay.
Pork?
I'll have a piece first.
Right, it tastes good!
Master.
Cheers.
Wow, your teeth are sharp!
They bit right through the bowl.
Now what?
Be careful now, toothy.
Take it easy.
I did tell you to take it easy.
Sit still!
A fart for the King of Sticks.
This is 'Hungry Dogs Eats Shit!'
Not quite!
You like it?
He's drunk!
The old man will like this.
Master, the King of Sticks gave
us wine. It's free of charge.
Master.
Fei-Hong, one year has passed...
and it's time for us to
go our separate paths.
I have taught you all the techniques
and the magic of kung fu.
Practice diligently,
master each technique...
The Eight Drunken Gods
is the ultimate Kung-Fu.
My home is the world.
Try not to miss me.
Go home and be a good son.
Remember this, If you ever need me,
I'll be there. Beggar So.
Master...
Master!
Higher!
- Harder!
- Master Wong!
- Master Wong...
- What is it?
Master Wong, Li and his men
are digging on Bull Head Hill!
Really?
Tell the men I'm going there. Quick!
This way! Quick!
Wong Kei-Ying,
Your skill in Kung-Fu is
renowned, I compliment you.
Who are you? I don't know you.
Why do you want to kill me?
I'm Yen Tieh-hsin.
I kill for money.
Today I have a worthy opponent,
I'd like to pay you my respects.
I've heard of you. The cold-blooded
assassin who'd sell his own brother.
That's me.
But killing me,
you won't find that so easy.
Then I suppose you'll
want to wish me luck.
Hands are for door knobs
and legs break down doors.
30% from the hands,
the rest are from the legs.
Wong Kei-Ying. Are you
ready to meet your death?
Master.
Father, are you alright?
Idiot, you're back?
It's alright. Don't be afraid. I'm here.
He dares to attack my father?
I'll give him a good lesson!
You again?
Good. You can help bury
your old man, shitface.
Master Wong, it's too bad
you have such a disgraceful son.
You watch out, or you'll
have a body with no ass!
Dumbass, go and clean pig-stys
or I'll have to kill you too.
I won't die, bastard,
but the worms'll grow fat on you!
Okay, I give a discount today,
killing two for the price of one!
Up yours!
Wait... wait for me.
Master, what are you doing here?
How can Beggar So
miss a great fight?
Beggar So, it's none of your business.
Go away!
You are mistaken.
This is very much my business.
But don't worry, I'm not
going to fight you.
He is good enough to do it.
Come. Drink first.
Master, this wine is strong.
What kind is it?
San Pien Wine.
I'm drunk!
I'm the God Lu, the drunkard
with inner strength.
The cripple Li!
The drunk with a strong right leg.
The God Ian!
A sudden attack to the waist,
the God Jun!
Holding a pot in his arms,
Han's gone mad!
Well done, the Eight Drunken Gods...
Patience, you've not seen it all yet.
The God Han.
He's the flute player
with the powerful wrists.
Impressive!
Your flute is bent.
The God Tso,
- drunkard with the powerful...
- Throat Lock.
Now your lock is broken.
The Devil's Shadowless Hands.
Yes, you're very observant.
The God Chan!
The God Chan won't reach old age!
Where's the drunken Miss Ho?
Miss Ho... Ho...
Wait!
- Master, there's a problem.
- What?
I didn't bother to learn this!
- Can you teach me now?
- It's too late!
Fei-Hung!
She'll appear without a shadow,
just perform the actions.
Combine the other 7 styles,
and make your own Miss Ho.
Ho? You want Ho? Sure.
This is called Widow Seeing Lover off.
Woman sitting on a toilet Seat.
You don't sit right!
Putting on Make-up.
Pretty girl looks in the mirror.
These are the famous
Eight Drunken Gods?
So, you think that you're
the only master here.
Everyone has different styles even
they learn from the same master.
The goddess wants a drink.
Come on!