TopTeo.com
Five hundred dollars
for the death of Chen Kuo-Wei
Friend
Please stop, you're wasting your energy
Are you Chen Kuo-Wei with
Quadruple Door Heavy Fists style?
Yes, who are you?
I'm Yen Tieh-hsin
So you're the Hades Kick
The kick which has never been beaten?
You're right
Someone paid me to kill you
You and I haven't met before
Who wants kill me?
I can pay you double to kill him
You can, but killing is my profession
I have to honor my word
So I must kill you first
You're too arrogant
I've never lost before
You may not win
I don't care what kind of fists you have
I'll break your hands first!
醉拳
DRUNKEN MASTER
Wong Kei Ying
Martial Art School
Gai Hsien
What's the matter, master?
I'm going out, keep an eye on them.
Yes, sir.
Stop!
We won't practise this today
Let's practise the Fist of Five Styles
which I taught you a few days ago.
Messing up again!
Cheeky!
Pointless!
Start now.
Appearance of Dragon & Tiger
Two Tigers inside,
White Snake signaling.
Panther watching Fire,
White Crane flashing wings.
Hold it!
Your wrists are not firm at all!
You can't learn it well, can you?
You mud head!
How dare you fool me?
- Fooling me...
- Not me!
Who's he?
Say it
Fan Dou Hong
(Naughty Panther)
Naughty Panther
Though Mentor Wong is your father
you should never cause trouble here.
All because your kung-fu instruction
makes no sense!
You mean that my instruction is wrong!?
Not all wrong, just a little!
Huh? How wrong is it?
Your Panther Watching Fire...
Excuse me!?
You've exposed your body
easy to be attacked
Your foot-work is too loose.
Just a sweeping kick
can knock you down!
Just wait!
Shut up! Shut up you turkeys!
Oh! you'd like to test
your teacher's kung fu, would you?
A nice person can fly, can't he?
Aha! I can stand almost anything, you bum!
But I've taken enough of this bullshit!
Right! Come on!...
You're wide open.
Do you know that, teacher?
What?
Come to...
Over...
See how good his Horse Stance is?
Pork belly, shut up!
Hah! Look! Hah! Look!
Right foot!
Bastard!
Chick... Chicken Stance!
Naughty Panther
you've taught Hsien a lesson.
We all feel very happy about it
He's too arrogant, I can't stand it
You've vented our anger
That's great...
If so, eat more then...
No, I'm talking about that girl
What a charming face
very pretty indeed.
- How much?
- 30 cents.
Not bad!
I'm willing to trade 10 years
for one night with her!
That's easy
I'll make her hug and kiss me
Liar I won't believe you
Let's take a dinner to bet then.
Deal.
Be careful!
You'll be sent to jail if she sues you.
Just watch out. Don't worry.
Just watch.
He's dead man.
This flower is beautiful.
Trust me, try it on.
I'm sorry, sir.
My eyes hurt.
What can I do?
Something got into my eyes
Help me get rid of it, miss. Please, hurry
Not yet.
Yes good.
Thanks.
Snake.
Snake?
Don't be afraid...
I'll kill it. Don't be afraid.
It's great
I'll do the same thing on your sister.
My sister?
How dare you flirt my daughter!
I didn't, she hugged me first.
Mother
Save it, I saw everything over there.
Who'll flirt an ugly duck like her!
Time to teach you a lesson.
Good, not bad
You're good fighter
Watch out
What a fierce woman
Come on, you guys! Hey!
You're all ruthless bastards!
Man won't argue with bitch, excuse me!
What's your game, huh? Stumbling
about like some drunken stooge.
Don't answer back, there!
Hey! Jerry!
Come to buy. Ah, see, mister.
Jade antique.
Is it real?
But of course, sir. It's an heirloom, mister.
It's worth the money, sir.
- How much is it?
- Ten bucks, sir.
That's very expensive!
Here.
Just ten cents!
Hey!
Hey! Hear me, sir!
You can't give me this, it wouldn't
buy an old plate, you know that.
I couldn't sell such a
valuable piece for only 10 cents!
If you don't want to sell,
give me my money back.
Hey, give me back my jade.
Mister, you broke my jade!
Pay me back!
Pay? No way!
Father...
- You must pay me.
- No!
What happened?
He's broken my jade
but refused to pay, yet beat me.
Beast, get lost!
Who're you calling beast?
I'm calling you!
Pay him immediately.
Pay? I don't know how to pay.
Good, I'm just looking for some way
to vent my anger.
Let me teach you how to pay!
Get up
Wanna kill me?
Oh, wow! You almost kill me!
Wow, my knuckles are barely missed!
This is for you, now get going!
I'm doomed, I'm dead!
Don't be afraid, it's just the dull edge!
Me uncle don't want to kill
you boy, so don't move.
Don't...!
Please spare me...
Not hit yet...
Got you now
Drop dead!
Fists have no eyes, knives have no heart!
Sometimes I can hit by mistake!
Watch this!
I chop... chop meat.
I slice... slice a cucumber.
I beat... beat garlic into paste.
Nice to see you! I wouldn't know
how good I am if we didn't fight today.
Oh gosh! So do I!
It's been ages, brother.
You still look great.
Your bro is old now.
What a beautiful niece I've got!
Not really. She's still a kid.
Where's Hung?
This naughty boy always goes to play
He's grown up now.
I think you may not recognize him.
This time you visit, stay longer.
Fei Hung, don't go away.
Come to greet your auntie and cousin.
Come here, now.
I'm coming...
Shit!
Come to greet your auntie.
Auntie, cousin.
Cousin.
Fei Hung
What happened to your neck?
I... I slept without a pillow.
Without a pillow? Let me help you.
No thanks, auntie.
Come on, relax.
Auntie
Mother!
Feel better now?
Yes.
Brother, Fei Hung really looks smart.
He's tactful and learn fast.
Brother, you really know how to raise a son.
Yes, I'm very strict to him.
No wonder I heard people praising him
as soon as I came here
Really? What did they say?
The son of Wong Kei Ying is very smart
He's also a man of justice
I'm very proud of him.
Come here my son, come here.
Sit down
But there're many sex maniacs
in this village.
A bad guy harassed your niece
on the street just now.
He beat me too.
Who dares do this to my relatives?
Can you recognize him
if you see him again?
Sure I can.
Good, let's find him now.
I'll teach him a real good lesson
Hung, come with me.
Uncle
You don't have to go out.
Why?
That guy is here.
Who?
He's your son Wong Fei Hung.
You...
Son-of-bitch...
Kneel down.
Father
You bastard, I'm so angry.
Wong Kei Ying
I'm doomed.
Mentor Li, is someone looking for cure?
I'm looking for your son.
Why?
Your son beat my son irrationally
You see the bandages? He hurts so badly.
It's just a waste to heal him
Wong Kei Ying, we want your son?
You beast, I must kill you
No, Dad... no...
Brother, you'll kill him
Yes, because I'm too angry
But they'll think that
you won't have your son tortured
Mentor Li doesn't come to witness
how you punish your son
but to punish him with his own hands
Don't move...
It's all me
I'll let your son beat me back
Take this.
I've given you a chance
It's you who let it go.
You dare say this at this time
Wong Kei Ying, you indulge your son
I'll just abandon him
Just do anything you want
Mentor Li, how about let Hung
stand this mentor's 10 strikes
without any resistance?
He deserves it if he dies
If not, just put it into an end
I don't need 10 strikes to kill him
Young Master
I'll take the revenge for you
Mentor Chao
beat him to be as badly as I'm
TopTeo.com
The Divine Eight, that palm-style
of yours is really something.
Ha! I'm only starting.
How many strikes already?
You want to make me childless?
Stop it
It's already 10 strikes
You said you'll kill me within 3 strikes
Crane Chasing Snake On River technique.
Secret Strike on vital point
I'll fight back if you don't stop
I told you I got style.
Hold it!
My clothes get dirty, take it
You comes for the revenge?
It's me
You hit your master
Young Master, are you alright?
Young master, are you ok?
My baby, are you alright?
Young Master Go to hell
Young Master
I hurt as badly as you now
Wong Kei Ying, you're somebody
but I ain't ordinary person
just wait and see
Let's go!
You watch out!
Take Young Master home, hurry
Do come back
Be careful
Now two of them are badly hurt
Are you very proud of yourself?
I'll kill you now
Brother
It's useless
to beat this naughty panther
Let's punish him by practising kung-fu
You really piss me off
From now on, you can't go out
and do 6-hour foot-work!
Don't move
Be careful, this water is hot
So, feeling good now?
You're trembling, I feel very happy now
So happy...
You feel itchy? Let me help you
Stop, don't go too far!
I don't, your father asked me
to keep an eye on you
You'll have to stand 2 more hours
if you break one single bowl
You deserve it
Master, you come back
Your foot-work is fine
Did he slack off?
No, I've always kept my eyes on him.
- Really?
- Yes
Show progress finally
Yes, I'm very tired
Are you really tired?
- But you got a chair
- Yes
What? A chair, let me see
Damn it, a chair
You dare cheat me
when I'm punishing you
I really can't do anything about you
I'll ask your uncle to come tomorrow
and fix you
Who's he?
Beggar So
It hurts!
Hurry up pinhead,
it's choking me!
Won't be a second.
Oh, hurry!
Wow! Practicing your kung fu upside down, huh!
- I'm dying!
- Here, I get you something to eat.
Wait till I get some water.
Just take this thing off my ass.
- OK.
- It's killing me!
Hurry!
Get up!
Eat
Master's asked Beggar So to fix you
Yes
You're miserable then!
Why?
Do you know anything about Beggar So?
He's very cunning
All his students have
if not broken arms then broken legs!
Really?
If not believing, then you can try.
A guy named Bull was his student
and you know what happened to him?
What?
He lost all his teeth and hair!
His nose is twisted
even his father can't recognize him
That monster really likes torturing people!
What should I do then?
You think about it yourself
Shit! You got to help me.
Among the 36 tactics,
running away is the best!
What are you doing?
You're clumsy!
Hurry up! Run!
- I leave now.
- Just go!
Yue He Restaurant
Have some pork buns...
Come in please.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I sit here?
Yes... You from Chaochow?
Are you Chaochowese? Me too!
- I'm also from Chaochow...
- Please, sit...
The food is very good
They all look good and taste good
Really good
Good
Sir...
Why you're alone? Where's Old Shang?
You eat first, eat
What would you like to eat?
A bowl of shark's fin as appetizer
Sorry, we got no shark's fin
It's too bad
Then I want a roasted left goose leg
Left leg...
A chicken and a steamed grouper
Sorry, we got no grouper
Then any fish will do
Also a stewed abalone
and big shrimp noodle
Yes
Half litter of Shaoshing wine, hurry.
Half litter of Shaoshing wine
You have a big stomach
Of course, or I won't be so fat
Here's the left goose leg, chicken...
Half litter of Shaoshing wine.
Yes... no thanks
Cheer... just feel free
Eat... very delicious...
We're friend... feel free to eat...
Drink...
Go ahead
I eat...
Drink...
He must be starving
Very nice
I mean the food is really good
Really good
I'll pay the bill, don't refuse me
I'll pay it now
Buy me lunch tomorrow. I'm leaving
I'll pay there
Let me pay, just enjoy it
I've to go, see you tomorrow
Take it easy, goodbye
Excuse me, goodbye... Enjoy
Sir, 1.99 dollars please
Someone will pay the bill
Who?
The old man who's eating with me
You know him?
He's my father
Your father?
How many fathers do you have?
He's the boss of this inn
and I'm his son
So you're his illegitimate son?
So you just want to eat and run?
Look there.
Severe punishment for not paying
(嚴懲白食)
Eat and run? No
I've just forgotten to bring the money.
I'll come tomorrow and I'll pay you then.
Kingkong, beat him!
Tiger's Claw
Stop it, let's talk
Stop it
Don't fight, we're friend, don't fight
It's okay to beat friends.
I'll get back what you've eaten
Beat him!
Roasted goose's leg
One on the left
Soyed pork
Damn it
Also half a litter of Shaoshing wine.
No... I'm dying.
Stop it! That's enough!
Do you really want to kill people?
Enough?
He's to do the toilet cleaning for us.
I can't stand it anymore.
Thanks.
Old bum! How you dare
interfere with our affairs!
Just watch, I can jump.
Take it
Now he's jumping all right!
Here is how to wash your face.
You've eaten enough, you thief!
- Stop, Let's be friends!
- Who's your friend?
You're looks well built, but stupid!
Hey, bad boy, let's go!
This way...
TopTeo.com
Sir, it's amazing at your age,
you're really tough!
Oh well, without it how can I
survive in this world?
Unlike you, looking tough while
letting people thrash you around!
It's just an accident
If I hadn't fallen into the trap
I'd have beaten them
It's just an excuse
How come you're so miserable?
Couldn't pay the bill?
That's a long story
May I know your name?
I'm So
I feel very angry
when I hear the name So
It's all his fault
Who're you talking about?
It's that Beggar So
My father asked him to come
and fix me up
So you're afraid of him
Afraid? Of course not
It's heard that
he's vicious and cunning
That old bastard...
I'll teach him a lesson someday
You'll have the chance
Well, where do you work?
Me? I have no work
So you're a beggar?
Yes, I'm Beggar So.
I see...
Beggar So?
Exactly
Better go now
You can't go now
I've received your father's money
I've to do my job
You can't go away
How long do I need to learn from you?
A day?
A year
I'm doomed then
I quit and you've got the money
Profits are all yours
You wanna quit? I wanna teach you
You old bastard
Do you dare release me?
don't ever underestimate me
Let me show you Tiger-conquering Fist
This is Tiger-conquering Fist?
Tiger-like Fist
It's great, isn't it?
Tiger-conquering Fist?
I think it's Conquered-Tiger Fist!
Crane Fist
Cool Crane's Beak
Well-Fed Crane's Soul
Crane Hunting for Shrimps...
Shrimps... Flying Crane
Your fingers are stronger
than my teeth?
Ahh! It's broken!
I'm coming!
You scared me!
You're scared to climb up a tree
What? I'm just using the Monkey's Fist
Wanna follow me?
Answer me. Answer me!
Please stop
Answer me, now!
Okay...
Nobody should find a student by force!
Let me down!
I don't want to die yet!
I suppose you're supposed to be a teacher,
you'd break a gorilla in half.
All students with style
must learn how to fall, right?
That was only your first lesson.
Wanna escape?
I just wanna piss.
Do it there.
From right to left
Then back to right
Back to the front
Left to the right
Right to the front
Left to right, right to left
I can never finish it
Just go on
So harsh to me? Fine!
Fei Hung...
Old guy, wash yourself
Go away, kid
Do you hear me? Go away
Can't you see I'm busy
What a stubborn bastard
Is this your place?
How about if I don't leave?
You're so cheeky
and so naive about the world
Comfortable?
No, you're a wicked person
I'm good at fixing wicked people
Come on...
You shouldn't be too arrogant
with such bad kung-fu
Who's your master?
My father teaches me
Then
your father mustn't be a good fighter
Maybe I'll let him be my follower
I think you'd better call me daddy!
Go to hell!
Sit down.
Get up
Sit down again
It's good you obey daddy.
Go suck mommy!
Take my shoes
Oh...
I won't even need
my hands for you, stupid!
Ah, you dare use them!
I'm not scared!
Well, shithead, had enough?
I won't stop until you sink in hell fire.
Don't come here!
Ah shit! You've become
a cowardly turtle!
I surely beat you now.
No matter how hard you train, you never
could beat me with this suck kung-fu!
Killing a nobody like you...
would only defame my reputation.
Crawl between my legs
then go back to your shit hole!
Crawl!
Wait, is this your trousers?
With your kung-fu that bad,
Then
your father mustn't be a good fighter
Take my shoes.
I surely beat you now.
No matter how hard you train, you never
could beat me with this suck kung-fu!
Killing a nobody like you...
would only defame my reputation
Crawl between my legs
then go back to your shit hole!
Crawl!
You idiot, this wine is very expensive
It smells good!
Master, enjoy your wine,
I'll dry your clothes.
Why are you so sexy?
Oops! The clothes caught fire...
On fire...
Oh god! You've burned
the only decent clothe I have!
My back!
My wrist!
You're not strong enough.
The food has no meat,
and the tea's too cold!
Cold...
My head hurts, master.
Have your meal.
Are you too tired
that you can't even use your chopsticks?
TopTeo.com
Master, all the stuff is done
So quick?
Take it back from upstairs
Hurry.
I shouldn't have made it so full!
Oh my god!
- Hey, Hung,
- Yes?
help me to break walnuts.
You break it like this
Yeah, like that.
Master, it's too hard even for a monkey!
Let's go for a walk outside.
All right...
Open now...
- Master, you're good!
- Of course.
Observe well... Make your bets!
Old guy, you should leave now.
Leave?
How can I buy good wine with so little money?
I got to bet when luck's with me.
I bet on this.
Come on, bet...
Trust me, bet there!
Open it... What?
Don't dare
Open it...
Scared? Shut up!
Open it.
You're amazing, master Sure!
That's great
Put down your bets...
We're getting rich. It's easy!
Lucky you!
I'll play with you
in one go!
Alright, we'll make a good fortune today.
Come on.
Bet!
Good.
Open.
I'm sorry!
What's it?
You're nimble
but I got good eye-sight too.
So you're a swindler.
Police is here, run!
You filthy thief, give me back the money.
You can never get back your money
from a swindler!
Do you know who I am?
I think you're a rat!
You're quite clever
for knowing I'm an old rat!
People call me Iron-head Rat!
Really like clay-head indeed!
Very hard indeed!
Scared?
Don't go!
If you don't return my money,
no matter you're a rat
or a tiger, I'll beat you.
Around here no one dare say this to me
You don't mind to get hurt, do you?
I'll let you try my iron head.
Your heart.
Your lung.
Master, his head is too strong!
Don't give up
Now you know how good I am.
It's fun.
Good, very good.
You've knocked into my trousers.
Watch out...
A hammer for an iron head, all right?
How can you bear?
It's unbearable!
Master, I can't bear...
- Want to be lazy?
- No...
My hands are gonna be broken!
Let's stop now, buy me some wine.
Yes, buy wine...
Ru Yi's Restaurant.
Waiter.
What do you want, mister?
- Give me three...
- Three litters of wine?
No, 3 cups of Shaoshing wine, hurry!
3 cups?
Hurry up, don't just stand here!
Right.
What takes that kid so long
to buy some wine?
Idiot!
That's him!
Old guy, who are you?
Who are you then?
I'm King of Stick Hsu Ching-tien
Have you heard about me?
Yes, I have
You ever heard of Beggar So then?
Beggar So?
It's me.
Go.
Don't go, he doesn't look like Beggar So.
What?
Look.
He's trembling
he isn't the real Beggar So.
Well, how dare you cheat me
impersonating beggar So!
What's for?
I'm really Beggar So.
Still so stubborn?
Master.
Give me the wine.
It's water!
Idiot, you harm yourself.
Master!
They're lucky!
I'll get them next time!
I sure will break their bones, let's go!
What happens?
Are you too badly beaten to eat?
Master, it's all my fault
that you were beaten.
It's all because of you.
Me beggar So throughout
10 years traveling everywhere
I've never had such humiliation like that!
It's not because you couldn't beat him,
just you didn't drink enough.
Now you know.
But I'm so useless
or I'll surely
kick the King of Stick out.
Then you're blaming me
for not teaching you?!
You've taught me minor things only
and how to stand beating.
Your father Wong Kei Ying is an expert
of all kinds of kung-fu.
How can I teach his son?
He wants you to torture me.
Your father's given you to me
because he knows
I have good kung-fu skills
What skills?
The 8 Drunken Gods.
What special? I've learned Drunken Fist
when I was first introduced to kung-fu!
You won't understand how great it is
Many people asked me
to teach them in the last decade
but I turned them all down.
Don't take my drunken-like footwork lightly.
It hides the killing strike.
Camouflage the moves. Appear weak to
beat the strong. Use defeat to snatch victory!
How?
Why don't you teach me then?
Didn't your father tell you that...
it's bad to just practice the moves
without building up a solid foundation?
I do this because I want you to have
a strong foundation.
It's really the right time now.
Really?
You should be a bit drunk
to learn the Drunken Fist!
Have a drink first.
One more.
Fei Hung, have you ever gone to school?
I've spent a few years
in a private school.
(From the poem "Let's raise a toast" of Li Pei 李白)
"Let's raise a toast!
"Don't rest the cups.
"I'll sing a song for you.
"Lend me your ears.
"Power and wealth are not worth much.
"I only wish to be always drunk, not sober!
Enough!
"Since ancient times sage men are forgotten.
"Only great drinkers are remembered!"
Only great drinkers are remembered!
(From the poem "Young men song" by Wang Wei 王維)
"Shing Fung's fine wine costs 300 a cup.
"Many Shien Yang's good men are young...
(From the poem "Eight drinking immortals" by Du Fu 杜甫)
"Refusing to board a boat
despite the king calls.
"Saying: '' I'm one of the
drunken immortals, your lordship!'' "
(From the poem "Drink alone under the moon" by Li Pei)
"Raising the cup,
offering to the bright moon
"Counting my shadow
makes three of us drinkers.
(From the poem "A Song of Liangzhou" by Wang Han 王翰)
"Fine wine poured in a radiant cup
"Ready to drink, but marching music
is urging to board the horses.
"Please don't laugh at those
lying drunk on the battlefield!
"Please don't laugh!
The immortal Lu, the drunkard
strong like a thousand men.
The immortal Li, the cripple with a powerful leg.
Han, holding a pot in his arms.
Lan, a sudden attack at the waist.
Chan, the superior double kick.
Tso, wine-offering hands locking the throat.
Han, blowing his flute while
holding one's wrist and kicking at his chest.
Lady Ho, using drunk footwork
while attacking at the waist.
Be more serious when training!
This style is so sissy!
Miss Ho is a woman. Watch.
Follow me.
Do it yourself
Okay, I will.
Practise hard!
Only women practise this, not me!
Wong Kei Ying
Why do you persuade
the Bull Head Hill villagers
not to sell me their land?
What are you thinking?
Was it because of
that business with your son?
That's a personal issue
that will be settled in good time.
I'm not responsible.
What is your game?
What is yours?
Mr. Li, I'm most interested to know
why you want to buy Bull Head Hill.
As you wish to know, I'll tell you.
Metal graveyard up there
has been haunting us for centuries,
disturbing family spirits!
They'll get more than $30 per lot,
it's good money for that land.
then you butcher nose in
where it isn't wanted!
You mean you want to buy the graveyard?
Huh? Don't you believe me?
There's a curse on the name of Li!
And it must be exorcised.
I've got three mistresses without children!
I'll be content with a chicken egg.
But they can't produce that!
Oh, my chilled nut be...
becoming a little seed ah?
You can't hide anything
from me, Mr Li.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Li Wan-hao, I think you just want
the thing hidden on the hill
Huh? What are you bullshitting?
- The coal.
- The coal?
Bull Head Hill contains a rich coal deposit.
You secretly deal with the Coal Company
to depress the price
and make huge profits.
You can fool the villagers,
but you can't fool me!
Since you know it,
OK, I won't deny.
If you don't interfere,
I'll give you 20% of the profit.
20%? You spend so much on me?
Listen, Li Wan-hao, the hill belongs to the villagers.
No one can take it away,
get out of here!
Wong Kei Ying,
you're trying to go against me,
No matter how good your kung fu is,
I'll find someone to handle you.
A 1000-dollar warrant
to kill Wong Kei Ying of Fushan
Wong Kei Ying?
Teacher's Birthday Feast.
Master
- Is everything ready for tonight?
- Yes.
Hurry up
there'll be many guests tonight.
Hey, Master Hsu.
Funeral?
You ugly boy,
Haven't you had enough last time?
Itching for more again?
My body is not,
but my hands are.
Alright
I'll make you an extra dish tonight
Master, what would it be?
- Bamboo shoot and pork, give me a rod
- Yes.
Pork?
I'll have a piece first.
Right, it tastes good!
Master
One bowl.
Wow! Your teeth are so strong
to break a bowl!
TopTeo.com
Well?
Watch out for the teeth!
You look quite miserable now!
Sit still!
Push off!
Ass against the King of Sticks.
This is 'Hungry Dogs Eat Shit!'
Not quite.
Got it?
Are you drunk now?
Master, there's wine to drink now.
Master, the King of Sticks gave us wine
free of charge.
Master
Fei Hong, we've been together for a year,
it's time to say good bye.
Master can only show the techniques,
learning depends on the pupil.
You've to work it out,
practice makes perfect.
Make the Drunken Fist
becomes part of your self
The world is my home,
don't miss me, go home.
I'll come when you need me.
-- Beggar So.
Master
Higher
Come on
Master Wong!
- Master Wong...
- What's it?
Master Wong, Li and his men
are digging up on Bull Head Hill.
Really?
Tell people I'm going up there.
Be quick!
It's right ahead, quick.
Wong Kei Ying, you really deserve the fame
being Grand Master of the Great Fist school.
Who are you? I don't know you.
Why did you ambush me?
I'm Yen Tieh-hsin.
I kill for money.
Meeting a renown opponent like
Mr. Wong, I won't try to be polite!
So you're the cold blood killer
Yan Tieh-hsin.
Correct.
But against me,
you won't find that easy!
Then you must show me your best today.
The hands are the doors,
the legs are for attack.
30% from the hands,
the rest are from the legs.
Wong Kei Ying,
I must kill you today.
Master
Father, how are you?
Are you alright?
Idiot, you're back?
It's alright. I'm here.
You dare attack my father?
I'll teach you a good lesson.
You again?
So you come to bury your father.
You...
Master Wong, it's too bad
you have such a disgraceful son.
Careful, you will give birth to
a deformed child!
Good kid,
go back and clean the pig-stys
or I'll kill you too.
Don't mind about the hogwash,
I'll break your bones now.
Okay, I give a discount today,
killing two for the price of one!
Wait... wait for me.
Master, why you're here?
How can I miss a great fighting?
Beggar So, it's none of your business.
Go away!
No, you're wrong! I love to
stick my nose in people's business!
But don't worry. I myself don't need
to touch people like you!
He's good enough.
Come. Drink first.
Master, this wine is strong.
What kind of wine is it?
Three-Immortals Wine.
Good wine!
The immortal Lu, the drunkard
strong like a thousand men.
The immortal Li...
the cripple with a powerful leg.
Lan...
a sudden attack at the waist
Han...
holding a pot in his arms
That's great... the 8 Drunken Gods...
Thanks... there's more
Han Hsiang-chi...
blowing his flute while
holding one's wrist and kicking at his chest.
It's amazing!
Even the flute would twist
Tso, drinking wine lock...
Throat Lock
I lock...
Lock...
Bow...
I'll make you bow.
Shadowless Hand!
Yes, you're very smart.
Chang
I must kill you!
And Miss Ho? Show it now.
Miss Ho... Ho...
Wait!
Master, I can't stand it anymore.
Why?
I haven't learned it yet!
Can you teach me now?
Of course not!
Fei Hung
It seems invisible but it's visible.
Combine the other 7 styles, and relax.
Well, I'll create another Miss Ho.
This is Sexy Girl's Fist
Twisting the ass...
You don't sit right!
Putting on cheek blush
and facing the mirror.
Is it the 8 Drunken Gods?
Everyone has different styles
even they learn from the same master.
The goddess wants a drink,
Come on.