Go!
Brother, this is your favorite tea.
Come on; drink it while it's hot.
Hey, there, Pao.
Your cough better?
Yes, a lot.
Good. Your health is everything.
Please be careful.
You hear?
Don't make me worry.
I won't.
I should go check up on Bull.
He's tending the horses, right?
Well, this mission is critical.
I should go check.
You understand, right?
Go ahead.
Bull.
Hello, Pao.
Hey, listen,
why don't you take a rest?
I'll handle it.
Thanks, Pao.
Don't mind if I do.
He said be careful.
Don't worry.
Someone's coming!
Pardon me.
My name's Hung Yat-fu.
I know who you are.
You're Bill Man.
Detective?
Yes. Government orders.
I was working an opium case.
Except my cover was blown.
So I came here to borrow a horse.
You mean--
Wait!
I'm a detective.
Stop!
Take it.
Thank you!
Hold on!
Brother, that horse is mine!
Let him go.
- Run!
- I'll return the horse!
Don't move!
Chun-yuen Delivery Service!
I think he means it.
Brother, let's get them.
Quiet!
I think we should let them be.
Let's go.
- Brother!
- But they--
Go!
Man, come on!
- Come on, let's--
- All right.
Pao, we'd better leave now.
- I agree. Let's ride!
- Right!
Boss.
Boss, you're back.
Here, I'll take that.
Mr. Luk.
Mr. Luk, please.
This way, if you will.
Check it, please.
Paper.
Check it.
It's correct!
Chun-yuen Delivery is always trustworthy.
Master Yu.
In here, please.
Yes, Master Yu.
It's correct.
- Show them out.
- Yes.
Mr. Luk.
Thank you, Master Yu.
- Good-bye.
Bill. You've worked hard.
It's my duty.
Pao?
Feel all right?
I'm fine, thanks.
- Wine for all.
- Yes!
- Drink.
- Cheers!
Well done.
Tell me!
How could you possibly lose it?
Master Yu, I wasn't expecting this.
Oh, really!
Listen!
I mean it.
You get it back now...
or you see that bag?
That's you!
Master Yu.
So he took the horse...
and he's got the opium...
there's no way that he's gonna find us.
Anyway, that detective
is a long ways away.
There's nothin' to worry about.
What about Robinson?
What will you tell him?
We'll pay his loss.
Double it, if that's better.
You think he wants money?
Don't worry.
I can fix it.
Just trust me with this.
In a day or two, it'll disappear,
I swear.
Don't tell your older brother about it.
Brother, why did you get up so early?
Master Man.
What is this?
Opium?
No, wait!
You don't understand!
It's for the servants!
You know. Come on.
My brother...
we have been together...
for a lot of years now.
I know you well.
I've taken care of you...
looked after you.
But... I won't stand here
and watch you destroy yourself.
Do I make myself clear?
And also--
- Listen.
- Hey!
I've been hearing
that you're having lots of women...
and gambling, too.
How do you afford this?
Look...you have to trust me.
That's bullshit!
You smuggling?
There's...no way I could.
No? Then what's this?
This opium I found on your horse!
You used our good name to smuggle it in!
No!
You go to the police and surrender!
No! Don't take me to the police station!
- Just let me go!
- Forget it!
No, Bill!
Bill, why?
Please listen.
He has his whole family here to look after.
You can't send him away!
Enough!
What about our family name?
I can't let him ruin that.
Let's go!
No! Please!
Brother...
Okay. I'll go with you.
May.
My son.
Let me hold her.
Listen.
The kids are still young.
Please take care of them for me.
Brother Bill,
they can't live without their dad.
Tell your brother that you'll go straight!
Tell him!
She's right.
I will!
Stop!
Stay alert.
Bill, go take a look.
Okay.
Brother...
I'll do it.
Pao, you be careful!
Right.
Pao!
Pao, why did you do that?
Because... I don't want to be
a deliveryman for the rest of my life!
Since I was a kid,
no matter how hard I tried,
I've always been the little brother of Bill!
I want to be rich!
Pao has betrayed us.
I know that.
So you and he are partners!
Freeze!
Why? Why did you join forces to trap me?
You! You have ruined the corporation!
- Search!
- Yeah!
Yu Hoi-yeung!
Toss him in the river.
Now rest.
Rest well, Bill.
Rest in peace.
I'll hold a funeral in your honor...
and make you a grave to worship...you.
Pao.
You're overdoing it a little.
You surprise me a bit...
like you care.
I'm over it now.
You did well.
No one can stop us.
We can do anything.
Now you get Bill's job.
I will not be a deliveryman forever.
What about our friend?
Robinson?
I'll handle it.
- Watch out!
- Move out!
Move! Move! Move!
I'm moving here.
Hey, Ma! Come here!
What? What's wrong?
What's the matter?
It's not what I want.
So, what do you want?
It's just not right!
He's done the monkey
a lot of different ways.
His legs are spread apart.
That's not the monkey.
Bring it to me.
Get out!
Ma! Make it real.
Raise your legs!
And pull back.
Monkey on the cloud.
Monkey pisses.
Somersaults.
1...2...
3...4!
Ma, don't overdo it!
Okay! Choose any gesture you want.
Yeah!
Monkey on the ground.
Monkey gets the peach.
Monkey looks right.
Monkey looks left.
Now!
It's not right!
Try again!
Monkey looks at the moon.
Monkey on the cloud.
That's not bad. Go on.
Hey, you think you can do something
that we haven't seen before?
Sure!
Monkey in the water.
Bring him up.
- Right!
- Yes! Higher!
- Wait! No!
- Higher!
Not yet!
No hands!
Do it! You got it!
Act more like a monkey.
Rise!
Lazy monkey yawns!
Last stance!
Monkey climb.
Monkey runs!
Faster! Faster!
You got it now!
Son, keep drawing!
Okay. When you're done,
clean up there, too.
Keep goin'!
Keep goin'! Keep goin'!
Keep goin'! Don't stop!
Faster! Faster!
Master is back!
- Get away!
- Now just--
The Master's home?
The Master's home!
My God! My father's here!
Tidy up now!
Hurry up!
Move the paper off this desk!
Take away that ladder!
Close the door!
Reset the curtains!
Master, you're home.
Why did you return so early?
I've already finished my work,
so I came home early.
I miss all of you.
It's gorgeous!
I thought you would really like it,
so I bought it for you.
Where is Ka-yip?
Master?
Do you like it?
How do I look?
Very nice.
Now, where is Ka-yip?
He is studying.
Studying?
All right, stop stalling.
Where is my son?
He is inside.
Wait! Wait!
- Hello, nephew.
- Uncle.
Hurry up. Hurry up!
I want you to study hard
and take over my business,
but all you do is paint!
But, Dad, I'm creating a handbook
of Monkeyish Fist.
- A what? What is that?
- Master...
Can you make money from that thing?
You do nothing at all
to prepare for your future
in the business world
except stay home
and draw monkeys all day!
Master, don't get angry.
Father, please listen to me.
I only need eight more stances
to finish my handbook.
Get down on your knees.
Father, I'll become truly famous
if I publish this handbook.
And then I'll become
a great teacher as well.
- Yeah, he's right!
- No! No!
It's all right here in your head!
I must punish you thoroughly
in front of our ancestors.
It is my duty.
- Bring it to me!
- Yes, Master.
Stop!
What's the matter?
It's family business.
And so is that.
What's wrong with this?
You just encourage the kid.
Look, can I ask a question?
What do you call me?
I call you Uncle.
And what is our relationship, huh?
I'm your oldest brother's son.
Please take it out.
Chan's family tree.
My dear nephew, listen.
Turn to the first page, if you will.
It's clearly written that... many...
Many years ago...
Many, many years ago,
the ancestors of the Chan family
swore to become truly famous.
Now, I'm your uncle, I believe.
Isn't that correct...Chan Sing-kam?
So...what are you saying?
On your knees!
And you...
Yes?
... refer to me as what?
Uncle-in-law.
Listen... if I die all of a sudden,
I would become your ancestor,
just like the others.
I want that respect now.
The respectable uncle.
Who's the senior here?
It's you, Uncle.
I couldn't hear you.
I said, who's the senior here?
Of course it's you, Uncle.
I'm sorry.
Good.
Now, I know you want Ka-yip
to succeed your business.
He's done nothing wrong.
I mean...
why do you beat him like that?
Because all he ever wants to do is paint.
Don't you see that it's his dream
to finish the sketches?
Is there anything wrong in that?
If you force him to quit now,
to give up on that dream...
well, something tells me
that's not exactly your style.
Meaning what?
You always finish your work. Right?
And you'll do whatever it takes
to get it done,
won't you?
I've heard it all.
All right. Look...
I know you don't like us to practice.
Here we are...
my dad and l...
so poor that we have to live here.
I'll not forget...
...all you've done for us.
- Uncle.
However, Dr. Sun Yat-sen
was once heard to say
that Chinese kung fu
is our country's heritage.
That's right!
Good speech!
Then let Ka-yip publish his handbook.
I want him to follow me.
He will study hard.
- The Chan family will be famous!
- Yes!
I hear that you like to draw the monkey.
Then draw this.
All right, go ahead!
I know Monkeyish Fist.
That hurt!
Watch out!
Move! It's urgent!
Come on!
Over here!
Good one.
Wait. You shouldn't use this to...
hurt anyone.
Well said!
He's bluffing again.
Oh, man.
Here, catch.
So... how would you guys like to...
play a little ball?
Are you...scared?
So, what kind of game do you like?
How about fighting?
Grand Uncle, you're good at that.
Grand Uncle?
So, where's your beard, huh?
So. All grand uncles have beards.
- Let's say that--
- Allow me.
Let's say your sister marries
my grandfather
and they have a son.
How should my son greet
your sister's son?
I'll tell him.
"Grand Uncle."
What?
- Grand Uncle!
Oh, Grand Uncle?
Are you makin' fun of me?
Let's get him!
I'm hungry!
We're late for dinner.
Eat later!
Kid, I want to fight with you alone!
Well? You afraid?
I told you I haven't eaten!
If you want to fight, let's save some time
and do it together.
Come on!
I'm in a hurry here.
Hit me! Here!
Go ahead!
Oh, no!
Your breath stinks!
Wow! What a move!
Father, our students are always active.
They love extracurricular exercises.
No matter-- football, basketball,
every kind of ball game.
They're good at swordplay, too.
It develops camaraderie
and healthy competition.
Super Rod!
And they especially love
anything to do with baseball.
Why haven't you learned
the Chinese sword?
You're a traitor!
How 'bout that?
Isn't that right, Father?
So, you see,
we intend to build a church
here on the campus.
But the funding could be an issue,
you know?
Well, don't worry.
Wait!
It's the curve ball that can't be hit!
Good hit!
Are you hurt?
Have you been hurt?
- You're okay?
- You're sure?
I'm fine.
Don't worry, Mom.
Grand Uncle, are you all right?
Everything is all right.
So, no one was injured.
May the Good Lord bless you.
Amen!
Gently.
Who was it that hurt you?
I did.
You want all the glory.
Did you fight?
Let me show off once, okay?
Me.
He used a bat on you?
No...
- A ball?
Nephew, listen to me.
- I didn't plan to hit him.
- Of course not.
I just wanted to hit the ball.
- Then ball hit him. The ball hit him.
- That's right!
Yes, of course.
It makes sense.
So then...it was an accident.
You didn't intend to hurt Father Ma.
That's right!
It was solid contact!
A good hit!
A good hit?
Well, what is the matter with you?
Please stop hitting my son!
I hit him because
I want him to be good.
I have to teach him a good lesson!
Don't you see?
Mom!
[Music] If you hit him again [Music]
[Music] I won't let you sleep in our room [Music]
- [Music] I won't let you sleep-- [Music]
- Keep quiet, won't you?
[Music] You can sleep alone
in the sitting room [Music]
Shut up!
Oh, God!
What is it, husband?
What's the matter?
It's a notification.
- Of what?
Some kind of ritual or something?
You're both being sent to another school!
- What?
- Sweet!
What famous school is it?
Canton High School.
Oh, no!
Wow!
- Oh, yeah!
- Oh, great!
Good morning, Mandy.
Good morning, Uncle Wah.
Thank you.
Grand Uncle!
- Stop!
Hey! What did I tell you?
You promised not to call me that anymore.
I have a name, right?
Yes, Tak. I promise.
Now, we didn't go to Canton,
but got off in Shao-xing.
Are you sure we can find him?
We haven't started looking yet.
Gotta give it a chance.
I know. But, Grand Uncle--
Right. Tak.
It's gonna be hard to find him.
Look.
At least we have to...to try.
I mean, come on!
We're here, aren't we?
I mean, you want to finish your book, right?
- Yeah! Of course!
- Well, all right!
That's what I want to hear,
Grand Nephew.
Wait!
Let's be fair.
You call me Ka-yip.
Okay, Ka-yip.
Down to business.
We're here is to find
the famous kung fu master
who plays Monkeyish Fist.
Bill Man.
That's right.
So, where do we begin?
We're here.
Let me help you.
Get the luggage, okay?
Mind my paintings!
Do you know Bill Man
who plays Monkeyish Fist?
No!
Are you sure?
- Ask him.
- Hey!
Doctor.
Come on, show me your tongue.
Listen, I just need to know,
have you treated any monkey--
What? I'm not a vet.
But-- Wait, wait, wait.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Have you treated a guy around here
named Bill Man
who plays Monkeyish Fist?
No!
No. Wait. Wait. No.
Get out!
You'll get all you need here.
Come on, everyone's welcome!
We have different schools
of kung fu play
from both the north and the south.
All are worth watching
and at a very cheap price as well.
If you want to watch, follow me.
Come on.
Wow! It's Chinese kung fu!
Hey! A show there, too!
- You're there, I'm here.
- Okay.
You can eat all kinds of crab
in Shing's Restaurant.
Only the freshest, see.
You can have it extra spicy,
which is just that way I like it.
Or no spice at all.
There's a whole selection of fresh fruit
if you go to White Cloud Temple.
An array of appetizers
and dessert is included.
You'll be satisfied.
- Hey, please stay.
- Hey.
If you don't like veggies,
you can eat meat.
- I came for Bill Man.
- You mean with crab sauce?
Oh, sure.
We can make that for you.
No! He's a kung fu master!
You mean king crab.
Yeah, we've got that.
My God!
I just want the kung fu master!
Sister, someone is having an issue here!
He's playing Monkeyish Fist!
Monkey jumps.
Monkey jumps again.
Stop!
- Okay.
- Teach him a lesson.
Monkeyish Fist.
He's drawing you!
Wait. Don't go!
Lady, it's great!
Don't run so fast! I can't follow you.
Slow down!
You stop following me, or I'll jump.
Oh, you're kidding!
I'll draw it, too.
- Nice job!
- Perfect!
Thank you, hero.
You there!
Still want to draw?
I suppose not.
See ya!
Wait a minute!
Look, you're in my way!
Move it!
Hey! Ka-yip!
I'm coming down!
Never mind me!
Just go after the girl!
Girl? Where?
The one in blue!
She plays excellent Monkeyish Fist.
Okay! I'll go now.
Hurry up!
I want to draw her!
Over here!
Lots of vegetables!
Uncle Fook, how are you today?
- Did you come for the fruits?
- Yes.
Wow! The bananas are great.
The bridge.
It's the girl!
Here, Mandy, take some apples.
All fresh!
Over here! Over here!
What's the big deal?
What am I afraid of?
Hey, you!
Does it smell good?
Oh, yes!
- Want a taste?
- Sure.
Go!
Wow!
That's great!
I'll take two.
Okay.
Here's two.
Hey!
Watch out!
Look out!
Don't block my way!
Hey! Watch out.
Hey, listen.
Catch that girl for me, can you?
Please, no.
I'm too busy.
- Will this do?
- Let's go.
Don't get too close.
Catch it.
- It's no good.
- Oh, no?
Then, here!
Wait. Stop wasting the wine.
But you said it's not good.
- I was only joking.
- My head hurts!
You old monkey!
It's broken!
I told you not to waste my wine, didn't l?
But you're the one who broke it!
You could have stopped it with your hands.
Yeah, but how?
Here. Look.
Just like this.
Just like this?
Or like this.
- Or like this.
- Or you could have done this.
- Look at him...
- Shake...
Monkey's claw!
Here it goes!
Lazy monkey yawns.
Monkey runs.
Monkey doesn't care.
Wait!
Ghost!
Stay back!
- It's cold!
- I know Monkeyish Fist!
It's cold!
I'm gonna kill you!
- You'd kill your Grand Uncle!
- Grand Uncle?
I'm sorry!
You stink bad.
What are you two doing there?
Get lost, don't touch!
Next time come to my country,
I would love to show you around.
That'll be great.
Definitely, you have to come
to my country.
Yeah, I'll definitely...
You get out.
Is this Chun-yuen Delivery?
Get out.
- It's Mr. Man's horse.
- Get out!
Hey, Rocky!
He's a friend.
It's all right.
Be polite.
Rocky, rain's coming.
Let's go.
Let's go inside.
Tend to the horse.
Please.
Mr. Hung, after my brother
lent you the horse,
he was killed later that night.
I couldn't even find his body.
Bill was so unlucky.
I feel like...
I was responsible.
Listen. You weren't.
It wasn't your fault.
All deliverymen...
...are prepared for the risk.
Tell me why this is now a trading firm.
I didn't want my men
taking that risk again.
And I don't want Pao
to feel upset for Bill's death...
so I have to trade with the foreigners.
The company's now become a trading firm.
I came here to bring the horse back...
...and to watch Master Man
playing Monkeyish Fist.
I'm afraid I will not have that honor.
Can you show me?
No! I do not want to play Monkeyish Fist.
Well, is he a match for that girl?
All I know is that she is as powerful
as her father is.
How good are they?
Don't push it.
You hear?
What is that?
Come here.
Here's how it looked to me.
I have no idea what you're doing.
Here, take it.
Hold it tightly.
- I recognize that.
- Wow!
That's great!
Was that One Palm, Four Stances?
Please tell me.
- It's you.
- It's none of your business!
Who is your master?
Why should I tell you?
It's important that I know.
Okay! Bill Man is my Master.
So what?
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Let go of me!
I knew it.
Bill Man.
Can you take me there?
Wanna fight?
Oh, this is good!
My friend...
it seems you're new to this.
Right?
You're absolutely right.
He's just learned it.
Your master.
Take me to where he is.
Trouble is, he likes to roam around a lot.
If I see him, I'll tell you.
- Come on! Let's get outta here!
- All right, then.
Do that.
Clean up.
Pull down the curtain. Hurry.
Sir, I'm sorry.
It'll be okay soon.
What's the matter?
Detective.
What's he doin' here?
I'm not really sure.
But don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
- Just watch out.
- Yes.
You see, once I fought with Master Man.
I know his stances very well.
That young lad,
he didn't play well at all.
He's a rookie.
That's strange.
Bill's the only one to play
One Palm And Four Stances.
And that's what I saw.
Mr. Hung...
do you think my brother is still alive?
That's right.
When I asked them
where Bill was to be found,
they wouldn't answer.
Very secretive.
I had to tell you.
Do you want me to follow the case?
- Yes.
- Yes. We'd be grateful.
Thank you.
Find out what you can.
I'm going now.
And halt!
What's wrong?
I was wondering.
What if it's not really Bill there?
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
It has to be Bill.
If it's not, then it's his student.
We should make him our master.
Of course!
Otherwise, how can I finish my handbook?
Yeah! Anyway, we've him brought
so many presents!
He'll be moved to tears.
Let's go!
Thank you, everybody.
Bye. Thanks.
- See you later.
- All right, bye.
Well! What's up here?
We're new students.
- What are these?
- Presents for our master.
You want to be my students?
- Uh, no.
- No, not exactly.
Why'd you come here?
- Mandy. Inside.
- Right.
Hey! Come on!
How do you know them?
I met them in the market the other day.
You showed them your kung fu again?
- Oh, no, no, no. I did not.
- No?
- How about some more tea?
- Open!
So, what now?
Well, he just has to see that we mean it.
Yeah! We have to prove it to him.
Right!
So knock again.
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe we should kneel.
Stupid fool!
Just kneel when he opens the door.
- Forget about them.
- Yes.
Open up!
One last thing.
There was a guy looking for Bill.
Oh, yeah.
Who wants to see Bill?
I don't know.
This guy who saved me.
- He's a kung fu master.
- Yeah! That's right!
Hey, hey!
Why'd you come here?
To be your students!
What? Get up.
Come on.
Master Bill.
Good to see you.
Hung Yat-fu?
Then you are Bill Man!
Please! Take us as your students.
Hey! My dad lives in seclusion.
Leave him alone.
I see.
But Pao said you were dead.
He said you were killed by thieves.
- Mandy.
- Yes.
Show these lads to the door.
Right. Come on.
Time to go.
- Please.
- Give us a moment.
- No, no, no.
- Please wait.
- No, no.
- This way. This way.
- Out. Out!
- Get out.
Go! Go!
- All right!
No, I said out!
Have you heard?
Chun-yuen Delivery
has become a trading firm.
It has nothing...
to do with me.
Freeze!
Listen.
I'm warning you.
Don't come back here. Go!
What a pity.
Now I have no chance
to see your Monkeyish Fist again.
How can you live
in seclusion like this?
Master Man, you fought for justice.
I think that it's best to let it go.
If I don't show it...
then all will be safe.
I see.
Master Man, you're a man of compassion.
It's truly an honor knowing you.
You are the light that I must follow.
Let's enjoy the wine together.
Hey!
Stop!
My arm!
What happened?
They took Mandy!
What is it?
It's Pao.
He's taken Mandy.
Will you be all right?
I'll be fine!
Go save her!
Mandy?
Are you okay?
Wake up!
What's wrong?
Mandy.
Opium water?
How much was it?
Only a little.
Just two bottles.
It's much too much to drink!
Oh, I don't know.
The opium water can kill her.
What are you doing?
Now then, dear brother...
some folks say
that a woman is your better half.
So then...she's a lot more than that.
She saved your life!
Pao, you have to end this.
You're guilty of smuggling opium.
You will be hanged!
So what?
I deal in opium.
Not so bad.
Besides, I've got the foreigners
backing me up.
Why should I be afraid?
But...there is one way...
that you could help me.
Detective...
if you help me, I'd be grateful.
I'm listening.
Kill him!
I'm an officer, not a murderer.
Well, you don't have to.
Arrest him
as the opium smuggler,
and he'll be the one to be hanged,
and you'll be a hero.
Forget it!
What's wrong with you?
I'm not stupid.
You won't let me go!
That's right.
- Stop! Stop now!
- No! Don't!
Come on!
- Kill him!
- Leave her alone!
Mandy!
- Don't touch her!
- Don't do it!
Bastard! Stop!
Pao, don't you do it!
Don't hurt Mandy!
- What are you doing?
- Kill him!
Do it!
Hung Yat-fu, what are you waiting for?
Kill me!
I said do it!
I won't do it!
What are you doing?
- Where are you taking her?
- Let her go!
Leave her alone.
I mean it.
Do it now!
No.
Do it! Die!
Kill him!
Why did you stop?
Keep going! Kill him!
Drink this!
If you drink wine, it will kill the pain.
Now, you can do it!
We have to get her out!
Take Mandy away!
Hung Yat-fu!
Run!
Go!
Death means nothing to real heroes.
What's with you?
Save me!
You mean... he's still not eating?
He hasn't eaten for three days.
And how is the girl doing lately?
I'm not allowed to see her.
But you could have tried to sneak a look.
I wasn't able to.
You mean that you didn't
even bother to try, did you?
Grand Uncle, you're not better yet.
It's best that you stay in bed.
Ma, I got to admit
that I'm worried for Mandy.
We both are!
And Bill as well.
We understand.
Take it away.
It's just, when he said he'd care for her,
we swore we wouldn't interfere.
We must not break that oath.
Ma, Bill needs us now,
you know, to take care of him.
Yes, I know.
He's hurt pretty badly, too, you know.
Let us take care of him.
But you two are also hurt.
- We are young.
- Able.
We'll take the pain.
Ka-yip!
Grand Uncle!
Now, remember, stay quiet.
Okay.
Mandy. Mandy!
Master Man,
you better eat something.
Don't you want to help Mandy?
You can't if you don't stay strong.
- Wake up.
- Master Man.
Wake up!
If you eat, you'll be strong.
We'll be glad to care for Mandy.
How about it?
You haven't recovered.
Your body needs time.
Your mind does, too.
- Yeah, that's right.
- All right?
Madam Chan, you promised
not to bother me.
Leave us alone.
- Just--
- Grand Uncle. Ka-yip.
Let's go.
Madam, Master is home.
Dear, has it all been handled?
It has, my dear.
I've buried Hung Yat-fu's body
in the forest behind our house.
- He is at peace.
- That's great!
Master Man,
you need not worry any longer.
Hung has been buried.
Master Man, you don't have to--
I heard.
Mr. Chan, your kindness is appreciated.
Master Man, one request.
My son, won't you take him on
as your student?
I'd be grateful.
So he could finish his book.
All right!
Mandy, we need you to wake up now.
You hear?
Mandy, I need a model for my book.
Listen, Mandy, your business,
well, that's our business, too.
We'll get revenge for Hung Yat-fu.
- Wait.
- Wake up.
Are you serious?
Well, I said that just to wake her up.
Let's say she does wake up.
Then what?
So? Don't take it so serious--
Master, she's awake!
- Come in here!
- Mandy's awake!
Come quick!
Mandy.
Mandy, you're awake.
I'm glad that you're awake.
- Mandy.
- Old Monkey.
I'm glad.
Death....
Death means nothing to real heroes!
All right!
Now then, Master,
you have two new students!
- Master!
You have our respect!
Now they can learn...
Monkeyish fist.
Oh, man.
Madam.
Lesson one!
Mandy, are you all right?
Come on. Come on.
No, I'm okay.
It hurts!
It really hurts!
Master Man, how about they take a rest?
Yeah, how about it?
Go rest.
Finally.
Not you.
Continue!
Monkey gets peaches!
Every finger should be powerful.
Understand?
Am I clear now?
Yeah.
I need to change now.
No.
Continue.
Monkey rolls the ball.
Stop.
Look, you have to play
the fist with strong eyes
and you have to be quick
because your enemy
is right over there!
You're kidding.
What did I do?
I wasn't talking about him!
A monkey is wise
and with special potential!
Master, I'll test it out on you.
Come on.
Your fingers aren't strong enough.
Let's go!
Using only your forearm
and shoulders is not enough.
Again!
The power should...
come from your waist!
Good drawing!
- Grand Uncle, you're great!
- Yeah, I know.
Back to work!
Wine can raise your energy.
It will also make you brave.
If you match it with your fists,
you'll find it far more powerful.
Don't stop drinking.
Makes you be strong.
- I should always be drunk!
- I hope I never wake!
Let's clear our sorrows together.
This is great!
Master.
Well?
Let's go!
- Master!
I, Bill, have no regrets...
There's trouble!
Master Man!
Master, we have trouble.
Ka-yip and Grand Uncle have disappeared!
Fred, wait.
- It's them.
- Yes.
Take him down.
Right.
- Would you like a light?
You two, clear out.
- Yes, sir.
Gentlemen, what would you
like to deliver, if I may?
A package.
And where is it?
Right here.
"For Mr. Yu of Chun-yuen Delivery."
That's right.
What's in the package?
A couple of items he might be interested in.
For Yu Hoi-yeung and Pao Man.
He's in the office.
He's our manager.
I'll take it to him now.
Don't bother.
We'd be glad to take it.
It's personal.
Oh. Then follow me.
After you.
Right this way.
You sure this is the way?
Mr. Yu and Mr. Pao live a sheltered life.
They're afraid, I bet.
It's a trap, then.
We're not afraid.
We're ready for anything.
Hey, don't show off.
Master said to keep yourself hidden
in front of your enemies always.
That's right.
I forgot.
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
If you move left,
I'll attack on the right.
And vice versa.
If you move your head, I'll kick your ass.
If you turn, I'll show you the knife.
If you run, I'll still attack.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don't have any idea
what you guys are talking about.
- So? Neither do we.
Follow me!
Hey, delivering, too?
See you later, then.
Hey, you're blocking the way.
The problem is we didn't ask nicely.
Move it!
See? It's a trap, just like I said.
Come on!
Here's to you!
Drop something?
He hasn't had enough.
Then neither have we.
- Here's lookin' at you!
- You okay?
- I'm not sure.
Squeeze the vein.
Return dagger.
Lazy chicken flies.
My brother is nothing but a fool.
I see his students
are just as foolish as he is.
Tell me something.
You realize we can't let you leave.
At least not in one piece.
Pao, as Bill's successors
you know we are sworn to kill you.
Let's see how much you've learned
in your training.
Can you hang on, Ka-yip?
Sure.
I'm a successor of Monkeyish Fist.
The kid's an amateur.
So, you want Monkeyish Fist so bad?
Well, here's the real thing!
It's not in the book!
That's not Monkeyish Fist.
Tak!
Attack!
Kill them now!
- Master?
- Mandy.
- Are you okay?
- Let go of me!
We're fine.
Where's Master?
Man Pao!
Yu Hoi-yeung...
how have you been?
Master, are you doing better?
Master, you shouldn't be here.
Then, who would save you two?
Enough!
Four more ounces.
Master Yu, this will be easy.
His wound has barely healed.
Master, let me fight.
Pao, stay where you are!
Those who are not involved,
go away now!
You haven't had enough.
Four ounces more!
Had enough?
Okay, then.
Rod stance.
Okay, you can release the power now.
Go ahead!
Monkey's tail!
Master!
Fierce monkey turn.
Two Palms, Eight Stances.
Lazy monkey piss.
Man Pao!
Master.
Monkey grabs fruit!
4 palms, 16 stances.
Why, Master?
- Master.
Brother...
Let's go.
Brother!
Let's ride!
- Yes!
Take the flag!
Good morning, Master.
- Uniforms.
- Yeah.
Take it.
Let's ride!
- Yes!
I saw that!