"MASTER
A COPACABANA BUILDING"
A building in Copacabana,
one block from the beach.
276 studios home...
to some 500 tenants.
Twelve floors,
23 units per floor.
We've leased a studio
there for a month.
Three film crews shot the
building's life over a week.
- I was 1 when I moved in.
- So all your 49 years, you've lived...
Here.
all my 49 years!
In one building.
- In one apartment?
- No. I've already lived...
I first moved into #813.
Then I moved to #715.
Then to #714.
I've lived in #1102, #306...
#209, #123...
#117...
- Your mother lived in...
- 28 apartments.
'Cause we'd rent them and...
the owner okaying it,
she'd sublet them.
She'd furnish a studio,
People liked it...
you know...
so we'd rent it out.
Regularly.
We lived like gypsies...
only within one single building.
This place used to...
I'll draw the general picture first,
then I'll go into details.
This used to be a seedy dive.
There's been suicides,
doormen killed...
assassinations.
This used to be quite seedy.
- In the hallways?
- There used to be hookers...
and lines, see?
Men and women waiting for...
clients to exit,
so they'd have their go.
There used to be lots
of madams here.
There were natural deaths, too.
I remember...
Sure you wanna hear this?
A friend died in #608.
- The studio we've in?
- That's right.
The building's been revamped.
The indecorous people have
moved out.
There's lots of decent people
here now.
Thank God,
this is a family building now.
Welcome to the Administration.
I'm glad, I'm really glad,
cause...
I've been in charge here
since April'97.
I was reelected last March...
until 2003.
I hope to be able to do
much more...
but my goal is not, let's say...
I wanted this place to be
nice- looking and decent.
Thank God, I succeeded.
I use a lot of Piaget.
Otherwise, I resort to Pinochet.
That's reality, huh?
People say I'm the King
of sayings, so...
"Reality is the funeral
of illusions."
So when they flip out,
I bring them back to reality.
They come to their senses,
shocked with reality.
That's how I deal with them:
I start with Piaget. I'm polite, I'm kind.
I give love and expect
to get love...
but I can't demand
love from them.
Like I say: "One can't demand
love; only conquer it."
Go on, Eliska.
Go, go, Eliska.
Hi, Ms. Maria do Céu.
How do you do?
- Fine. Welcome.
- Thank you.
Come on in.
Before Sergio's tenure,
at the wee hours...
that lobby there...
became the hang out place
for us, ladies...
to drink with the doormen
all night...
every night.
I used to join them, too.
About 1 am, I'd get insomniac,
so I'd go down, too.
We all ate, the doormen drank...
got drunk, then one of them
would go to sleep...
on a foldable beach chair
out of sight...
and the lobby would then
be deserted.
You say it with such fondness!
Look, it wasn't all that good.
Only when we were having fun,
but things could turn sour.
First, some woman would show up,
throwing a fit.
Then someone else,
waving a pocketknife.
It'd go on like this.
So the cops were called.
When fights broke out,
the cops would come, and go up.
Out front, there was a scaffold,
for the facade was being painted.
So someone would rappel down
the scaffold ropes.
Then, a second person
would rappel down...
from the 7th or 8th floor.
Then a third one. I'd say:
"What the hell is this?"
all night long...
In the morning I'd say:
"Who's giving the scoop
of what happened...
you or me, Conceição?
About what we saw last night?"
We'd give each other the scoop,
saying it was a news flash.
Before Sergio, this was hell,
but thank God, all's calm now.
all's great,
but the poor fellow suffered...
to chase out of here
the transvestites...
prostitution, the massage parlors.
Good Lord! He kept going
down to the district...
the poor guy suffered.
We would go testify...
and so would the doormen.
Now it's better. all's fine.
We're here.
This is our crew.
I'll see myself in, okay?
How are you?
This is Jacques.
This is Coutinho, the director.
- You look smart, huh?
- Yeah, but one should look smart?
My favorite objects?
My portraits!
Definitely!
- Tell me why.
- Cause I love myself.
We should all love
ourselves, right?
If I don't love myself,
who will?
Except when you have a boyfriend.
Then you love your boyfriend,
of course!
I began posing for portraits
after my divorce.
I started working as a seamstress
for the high society.
I worked for
Roberto Marinho's famlly...
Othon Palace Hotel's ,
and Niemeyer's family.
I had to polish my act.
I learned many great things
with the high society.
Then I started posing for portraits,
cause I fell in love with myself.
And to this day, I've got portraits
on my phones and about everywhere!
We live in one of Rio's
postcards: Copacabana.
It's very violent here, though.
How was your mugging,
Ms. Esther?
- Here?
- Yeah.
I was on Siqueira Campos St.,
near here...
when a guy and a woman
approached me.
I got quite frightened.
Then...
he took his piece out of
his pocket.
When I saw the gun,
I panicked.
He said: "Be quiet,
and don't look sideways."
"Where do you live?"
When I came in here,
I got so scared...
really scared of him.
Such a handsome man! White...
really well- dressed.
He said:
"Where's your bank card?"
I said: "I don't know!"I shook
so badly, I was speechless!
I opened up a drawer,
emptied it on my bed...
kneeling on the floor, looking
for it, but couldn't find it...
being under gunpoint like that.
I had to crawl on my knees...
grab his leg,
and beg him not to shoot me.
Then we left for the bank.
He cashed all my money,
R$ 8,OOO reais.
He had the gun on me all the time.
I think the branch manager
was in it with him...
cause he paid right up. For you
to cash a couple thousand reais...
a 24- hour notice is required.
I came back home,
in such a state!
I couldn't stop crying.
He handed me a damn bag
that's still here!
It's here, that damn bag!
He said: "Keep it.
I don't need your money."
I thought the money
was really there.
Boy, what a letdown!
The bag's here.
Here's the damn bag.
I find it disgusting.
Look, he did all this!
It's disgusting.
all nicely folded up,
so I'd take it for my money.
I got desperate,
when I saw myself alone here...
pacing up and down,
debt- ridden at C&A, and Ponto Frio...
At 4 am, I got dressed and decided
to jump out of the window.
I was going to jump.
It'd been two years my late
husband had died...
and left me alone.
But I...
didn't go through with it.
People always teased me:
"You didn't jump because of
C&A and Ponto Frio?"
I said: "Yes", cause I'm not
like those who say:
"The dead don't have to honor
their debts."
When I die,
I want to go in peace!
Not owing a dime to anyone.
Now I have a really
great boyfriend.
I'm very happy.
One shouldn't be alone.
We should all have someone.
I'm not dead yet.
Men and women need companions,
don't you think so?
We all need a partner.
You spend your daytime with
your friends, and that's nice.
Then you come home,
and Iock your front door...
My friends tease me, saying:
"If you dislike being alone within 4
white walls, paint them in colors!"
It's easy for them to say so,
cause they're not in here.
Solitude hurts a lot.
It hurts a lot.
- My boyfriend is American.
- What's he like?
Christopher? Oh, God,
he was a godsend, a glory.
Calls me everyday.
Must be nuts my cel phone's off.
- Where's he?
- He lives in Greenville, a city in the US.
He's bought me a home, and
proposed. I pIan to move there.
I just wanna wait a little,
cause he's too eager.
Everyday he sends me e- mails,
calls, wires me money...
- How do you call him?
- "My chocolate baby", he calls me.
I call him "my chocolate white".
He's really cool.
AIways joking, you know?
No one would say he's 42.
He's the chairman of one of the
US' most famous organizations.
- Is he single, married, widowed?
- He's single, and he's mine!
He's got a beautiful son,
who loves me dearly!
- Does his son know you?
- Yes, he does.
I know his mom.
His son came to visit, she didn't.
She sends me e- malls.
It seems he has a huge house,
and his wife left him.
My poor baby,
his wife was a neurotic.
She took off with a lover,
and left him with their son...
and a huge trauma.
He's been separated for 2 years.
I think he found in me
what he'd been looking for.
I have a dream, cause when
I Ieft home, my mom said:
"You wanna move in with
your cousin? Fine!"
"You'll be back in a week,
begging for a plate of food."
As I'm really proud, I said:
"Mom, apart from being a hooker
or a killer..."
"I'd sooner starve to death
than ever come back here."
- Why?
- Cause I had a boyfriend...
She was so liberal with my friends,
I thought with me...
Then I got pregnant.
And I'm through and through
against abortion.
My mom was worried about
what People'd say...
what the neighbors would say.
That upset me even more.
When she got her paycheck,
she took me to this...
Spiritist Center, where a lady,
like, induced miscarriages.
You go there, she does her thing,
and the next day, you miscarry.
only I didn't .
So, I had an internal infection.
I kept the dead baby
in my womb for 3 days.
On the 4th, my temperature
was, like, 1O7 F.
When I recovered, my mom said:
"Let's go home."
I said: "Maybe you forgot
you'd told me...
that I couldn't stay home
with a baby."
"So, even without one,
you won't want me there."
"I love you, but..."
I couldn't bear to see
my mom cry, I'd cry, too.
Now I'm Renata, and that's it.
I'm #1 in Brazil.
Nobody will ever let me
down again.
My music keeps me entertained.
I've already played a little
keyboard today.
I enjoy singing.
I used to sing a lot.
When a radio station in Maranhão
was founded...
I sang in one of their
talent shows.
My family disapproved of it,
but I loved it.
I've lived by myself for quite
a while, and am used to it.
But I have children.
I've had 4 children:
one of them passed away.
I have 3 children...
two married girls
and 8 grandchildren.
My daughters say: "Mom,
People have CDs now, not LPs!"
Oh, c'mon, my LPs are beauties!
Once in a while, I sit there...
play my LPs, and fly!
I'm not sad,
I'm not unhappy either.
No sir, thank God.
I face my probIems...
naturally.
I'll sing, if you want. I'm not
self- conscious, did you notice?
Never,not even if
my world ends
Neither in God's name
Not even then
Will I evertake you back
Never! When our illusions
Are shattered
Our hearts end up buried
As I have buried mine
Nostalgia
Go and tell him
Please
How happy my love was
And how much I loved him
long ago
Nostalgia
Don't forget to say, at last
That you bring me sleep and rest
So I can live in peace
Your 1st anniversary?!
How has it been?
Thank God, all's fine.
Why did you eye him like that?
Be honest.
Why?
Aren't we fine?
Honestly?
Since December...
in January and February...
Until January, all was fine.
In February, we had a fight.
I thought of jumping out
of that window.
We fought all night.
In the morning, he saved me.
If I'd seen him coming,
I'd have jumped.
I sat down on the windows,
and said: "So be it..."
"I can't stand it anymore."
"When I meant to jump,
he threw me on the floor."
- She's sick with jealousy.
- So is he!
That fight, back in February,
was out of jealousy.
I'm honest. I'll say whatever
I pIease to his face...
anywhere.
Whenever he's with a woman.
Say I'm a guy, with a date.
I won't check out other women
passing by.
She's paranoid,
says I'm gawping at them.
- Do you look at them?
- She says I do...
Do you love each other?
I love her, but I don't know if
she loves me. I think she does.
I used to be crazy about him.
That love I felt for him...
I first got married at 42...
and I'm never
getting married again.
Did you have children?
Ready for this?
You won't believe me.
I have a 23- yr- old son.
I've had 22 children...
15 abortions.
I didn't get it. Come again?
How many children have you had?
22. Total, with 15 abortions.
As a child, were you poor?
Yeah, I can't say I was rich.
I was raised...
and lived in a slum.
But he didn't .
His life...
His life was better.
Thank God,
I've had a good life.
My dad gave us an okay life.
But my mom and I lived
in a slum.
My dad left me with her
to be raised.
I'd spend a year
with each of them.
My mom had a rather
improper life...
if you know what I mean.
I was 13, 14, and she rented out
rooms for trysts.
- With you there?
- I was there.
- Do you like Copacabana?
- No.
I've worked here for years,
and never liked it.
What did you use to do?
I'm not ashamed of saying it:
I was a housemaid.
- For how long?
- Years.
You've worked for a family
in Copacabana...
so you know the neighborhood well.
- Why don't you like it?
- Because.
You know why?
I feel caged in.
Of her own choice.
I aIways invite her to take walks
on the beach.
I don't like it.
You know why?
I'm an oId lady. Why sit and watch
oId foIks stroll by?
I don't mean that!
Just for the sake of walking.
You know what I really like?
To do the samba, to dance...
but he doesn't .
I love him more than he loves me.
- Is it a love contest?
- Yes, it is.
We're good for nothing,
but we love each other.
I've told his daughter:
"Next time he misbehaves...
I'll kill him first, and then
I'll kill myself."
Your hair grows longer
Your look goes downhill
You grow older,
Time doesn't stand still
A minute can contain
a lifetime,or more
Within that minute,
What's in store?
Love stories do not
exist anymore
And they were only lies
of yore
She showed her bellybutton
Herworld spinning there
Look beyond your bellybutton
See time go by, by,by
She showed her bellybutton
And herworld spinning there
Look beyond your bellybutton
And see
Have you ever made money
with your music?
We have. If we played covers,
we'd earn a llving with it.
But if money was my only concern,
I wouldn't be a musician.
ReaI money,
not pocket money here and there.
Or eIse, I'd be home in Curitiba,
playing at bars.
We used to play every week,
Thursdays thru Sundays.
But we don't want to play
musak at such venues.
We want to play concerts,
go on tours, play for reaI.
How do you like llving in
Copacabana for 6 months?
It's cooI.
I like it here.
- Why?
- It's great. We go down...
to the corner bar,
everyone's happy, sipping beer.
You go to the beach,
everyone's jogging.
How much is your rent?
Rent R$ 35O, taxes R$ 135.
And how do you make ends meet?
They both work, and I study,
so my dad send me some dough.
- What do you do? Can he speak?
- No.
He works at a Chinese restaurant.
Won't he ever answer me?
When he's in that outfit,
he's isn't allowed to speak.
ExpIain it to me.
Well, he's in our band as
a visuaI message.
He expresses, physically, what we
want to convey with our music.
So if he taIked, it'd be
meaningIess, cause he's an image.
He's meant to be a visuaI message,
not a taIking one.
- How was your 1st marriage?
- I had two chlldren.
How long did it Iast?
I was married for 9 years
before I got divorced.
I spent some time by myself,
then got married again.
After 9 years,
I became a widower.
- Was your 2nd marriage good?
- Excellent.
- Haven't been married since?
- No.
We've been llving together
for 13 years now.
And were you separated,
or a widow?
- A widow.
- How long untll you met him?
Three years.
I worked all day back then...
and had no time Ieft to miss
a partner.
It was only after I got retired
that things got worse.
I began to feeI a big void.
One week seemed to Iast a year.
I knew I couldn't go on aIone.
I decided to look up
the personal ads.
I picked up BaIcão and read them,
but didn't want to write one.
But in the paper, all 5O...
51- yr- oId men,
up to 6O yr. oIds...
they all wanted
4O- yr- oId women...
or between 3O and 4O. I was 5O,
I'd have to look for an 8O yr. oId.
No way, huh?
I was doomed...
cause an 8O yr. oId would
do me no good.
So I decided to write
my own ad.
One farmer sent me his picture,
surrounded by oxen...
saying I was right for him,
and he'd like...
to exchange Ietters with me.
But I didn't like his
self- advertising.
- Did you have any actuaI dates?
- Three.
- How did they go?
- Fast! In one...
- Where were they?
- One was at Lido Square.
He was a soccer coach in Niterói...
but I when saw his white & brown
shoes, I didn't like them.
I hated his shoes.
The second one I met
at the square...
grabbed my arm, and said:
"Let's see if it's firm."
- Just like that?
- Yeah.
I said: "Why?
I'm not selling anything."
"Just checking if your
body's firm."
I'd call the paper to check
for Ietters.
I'd give my phone and box.
"Any Ietters?"
"Yes,'X' Ietters."
Then, I'd go pick'em up.
I'd read'em on the bus
ride back.
- Did your heart beat fast?
- Of course!
- Did you ever post any ads?
- No, never.
- But you read them.
- I read and replled to them.
What interested you the most?
- Age, personallty.
- What age group interested you?
Upwards of 48.
- No young Iadies?
- AbsoIuteIy not.
- Why not?
- Because.
I was looking for a partner
in every respect.
I could find a girI just wanting
to go out on dates...
and that's not what I wanted.
My first date took pIace
in Campo Grande.
I got there, parked far off,
got out...
and when I saw her from afar...
she was horribIe.
HorribIe.
She was hideous!
I thought: "No way."
I waIked back and drove off.
Then I had a date with
a fashion designer.
She was very pretty,
and I got interested.
But all she thought about
was money.
She was only after money.
MiracIes are rare,
but they do happen.
Like how we met.
It's hard finding someone who
fuIfllIs you in every way.
- In 3 days.
Day 1, we met. Day 2, we dinned.
Day 3, I moved in with him.
I wanted a free, independent...
attractive woman.
My oId Iady is pretty.
She's pretty,
and I wanted a pretty woman.
I once was... I once was.
Were you also looking for
a handsome man?
- That'd be hard.
- Why? Him?
Were you also looking for
an attractive man?
Any man without a belly.
But then I found him.
I liked all about him,
except for his belly.
So we've been llving together.
He's so nice he put his apartment,
his car, everything...
under my name. If I Ieave him
tomorrow, he's lost.
would it be rude
if I asked your age?
Not at all. I'm 67.
65.
You're stllI young.
- And pretty, isn't she?
- You fooI!
She's very pretty.
Did you forget we'd made
this appointment?
Of course, not.
It's just that...
I woke up with the doorbell.
Do you mind if we shoot?
I don't , but your audience might.
I just woke up. Look at my face.
- Are you a teacher?
- Yes.
- An Engllsh teacher?
- I've lived in N. OrIeans for 8 yr.
- And why?
- My mom worked at the ConsuIate.
- Worked at the ConsuIate?
- Yes.
Do you have cats?
Yeah, I live with
3 femaIe kitties.
I used to have maIes, but since
the kitties aren't spayed...
I had to get rid of them.
It was a great bIow to me...
but that's ok.
I live with the kitties...
and haIf of the week,
my boyfriend comes over, but...
- Over here?
- Yes, he does.
I'm a bit of a neurotic
and sociaI phobic...
and Copacabana's busy
hustIe and bustIe...
makes me stressed out
by the time I get home.
The crowds?
Yeah. I don't know: Either there
are too many passersby...
or the sidewaIks are too narrow...
or there's an unpIeasant
combination of both.
What I'll say is not nice...
but I quite enjoy it...
when I ride the elevator
by myself.
Not because I might loose time
stopping at another floor.
only because I know I won't have
to see nor be seen.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Why do you avoid eye contact
when we taIk?
It's not that what
I'm saying isn't true.
It's just that I'm not sure...
I'm too insecure
to face you...
without stammering,
or bllnking compuIsiveIy.
In your first interview,
you also looked sideways.
Right, I have that probIem.
I'll only make an extra effort,
if I'm in a job interview...
or eIse People think I'm Iying:
"Your gaze avoidance means you're
either afraid or gullty."
Since neither is usually
the case...
Here, I don't feeI gullty,
but I'm afraid.
- You are?
- Course! What do you think...
makes People avoid
eye to eye contact?
It's fear, huh?
Writing for me is a necessary
escape...
but IateIy I haven't found
inspiration to write poetry.
Here's a short poem,
called "Opium Dreams".
- Did you get it?
- Overall, but could you...
in Portuguese?
Its symbollsm touches me deepIy.
This one here is entitIed...
I'll transIate it,
cause I give them Engllsh titIes:
"The Forest of My Despair."It's
about paranoia and Iack of love.
The forest is such a dubious pIace.
It ellcits our expIoration.
It is trees, and oxygen,
adventure, and enigma.
It entices our curiosity.
It's quoted...
in many fairy taIes, especially
the ones meant to scare us.
These are the eyes that define
the concrete jungIe...
as a pIace of paranoia...
and intrusion.
It somehow seems...
we're constantIy being watched.
It's aesthetically ridicuIous...
but I don't care,
'cause I have no ambition.
This was a baIm to me
when I made it.
I've settIed many issues.
- Is this Roberto's home?
- Yes.
Is he in?
- Mr. Roberto, I brought a crew.
- WeIcome. Make yourseIves at home.
Where do you work?
I'm a street vendor, paI.
I used to be well off,
I had severaI houses...
and lived in Santa Tereza.
I've had severaI occupations
in life.
I've bust my butt all my life.
Whlle some drank many a beer,
I worked.
I worked, day and night.
But, sadIy,
I suffered a brain stroke...
which put me in a hospitaI
for 6 months...
paraIyzed.
I'm 65, going into 66...
and sick. Who will empIoy me
in such conditions?
Young men find it hard
to get jobs...
Iet aIone an oId sick fart.
So men like me are unempIoyed.
would you give me a job?
I have none... er...
but I know it's tough...
You're very kind, thank you.
I'm right, aren't I?
But that's the tough reality,
right, paI?
- Are you married, separated?
- Married...
but we got separated some
3O years ago.
I get along just fine
with my wife, though.
We're separated, but we've never
gotten divorced.
We're friends, and I wish
her well. Really well.
I wish the best for her,
she's wonderfuI.
It just didn't work out for us.
Look...
quite frankly...
you'll laugh at me.
I get all emotional.
I cry for no reason,
I'm sensitive.
I'm from Itallan descent,
that's why.
But the issue here is not
sensibllity.
So, in answer to your question...
I've really, really missed my
mother since she died.
She was very oId, but I would like
she were by my side.
I really miss my Iate father, too.
Life goes on, of course.
We move on, right?
You. Didn't you have parents, too?
Didn't you grow up,
get married, have chlldren?
Didn't you Ieave your parent's house
to raise your own famlly?
Doesn't life go on?
We don't own our chlldren.
- Where are you from?
- BeIo Horizonte.
How was your chlldhood?
I didn't have one.
I had no chlldhood.
No chlldhood whatsoever.
What do you mean?
Because I wasn't free
to be, like...
a normaI kid, to play.
I had no freedom.
My father wouldn't let me.
At 14, I gave birth,
and my chlldhood was over.
How did you get pregnant?
- Was it your 1st experience?
- Yeah.
He was my first lover,
'cause I wasn't allowed to date.
After schooI, my dad made
me go straight home.
He'd have picked me up
at schooI...
so I wouldn't meet men,
to protect me from the worId.
And so it happened.
On my first date,
I met my daughter's father...
I had no idea what infatuation was.
I was 14, and thought
I was in love.
So I gave myself and got pregnant.
Damn!
Did you get an abortion?
No, my mom wouldn't let me.
I've never lled to her.
I told her: "Something weird is
going on with my body."
"I think I'm pregnant."
Cause my hips grew wider...
my body had changed.
So I told her...
and she got desperate. My dad
didn't taIk to me for a whoIe year.
Afterwards, he reallzed
he was to bIame...
for my fate, so...
- So you gave birth?
- I did.
- To a boy or a girI?
- A girI.
- What's her name?
- AIexia Carollne.
Well, my first call girI date
was cooI.
- Excuse me?
- My 1st call girI date.
When I got paid all that money,
I freaked out.
I'd never touched so much money.
Some R$ 15O reais! A fortune! Jeez!
More than my monthIy pay.
I earned R$ 136 monthIy.
So I told my daughter:
"Let's hit the mall."
We pigged out on McDonald's
all day... ice cream... great!
Today I wouldn't have the guts
to do that. Back then, it was fun.
- What wouldn't you do?
- Spend R$ 15O at McDonald's .
No, sir!
But that day I was a chlld...
who's been given her favorite toy.
We stuffed our faces!
What's your life like?
What's it like?
Well... not good.
It's not "an easy life",
as some call it.
It's disgusting to go out
on a date with a man...
you might even like,
and be attracted to him...
and the next day, he wakes up
and gives you money.
That's not nice. And it's not
an easy money at all.
It's hard- earned...
under humiliations, and offenses.
It's humlliating... a lot.
That's not easy.
Do you have pleasure at it?
Or fake it?
I have to drink to be able to do it.
I can't work straight- faced.
I drink all day,
'cause I have to work all day...
to support my daughter,
my family.
So I drink to gather up the courage
I don't have when I'm sober.
Apart from work,
do you have a boyfriend?
No.
- Really?
- No. There's this guy...
I'm stllI a teenager.
Hey, I'm only 2O.
Say, do you enjoy life?
I do.
But I expect to die any moment.
I've already told my mom
she shouldn't cry...
'cause I'll better off than
most People here.
- How come?
- When you die you're better off...
than llving here, in this ugIy
worId with mean People.
So I say:
"I'll be happy when I die."
But I don't want to die.
I love my life...
but I know it will be the end
of my suffering.
I'll stop suffering and hustllng
for work. That's good!
Waking up at 7 am is horribIe.
I mean it.
I don't like to work.
I do it to support my daughter,
but if I could I'd be llving the good life.
What do you mean?
I'd get up at noon,
have Iunch cooked for me.
I should marry a mllllonalre.
Lunch on the tabIe...
I would play with
my daughter all day...
taIk on the phone all day.
That's what I would like.
How did you work up the courage
to give this testimony?
You agreed to taIk...
and this movie will be showing
at theaters. How come?
It's no act of courage.
It's normaI. I think so.
It's quite normaI to me.
Most People out there today...
have a"b.C."mentallty.
That's history.
Now, anything goes.
Babies are born Ieft and right.
There's men with men,
women with women.
There's 5O women for each man.
Those things shouldn't be normaI.
People steallng from People.
Pollticians, too.
Thieves steallng from the poor.
Poor thieves steallng the poor.
Rich thieves steallng the poor.
Everyone's steallng, and...
that's normaI. So why shouldn't
being a call girI?
should People cast stones at me?
I don't think so,
that's why I'm honest.
I'm not ashamed. The whoIe
neighborhood and my family know it.
If you like me as I am, great.
I don't see anything
unusuaI in that.
Here's my Iast question.
When your daughter grows up,
she's 6 now...
...will you tell her the truth?
- I will.
I'm gonna tell my daughter
everything.
When she turns 14, I'll put her
on the pllI. I've told my mom.
Cause I ain't gonna do to her
as they did me.
I'll tell her:
"Here's all I've done."
I want neither her nor my sister
to do as I did.
I'll earn enough to pay
for their studies for both of them.
I'll heIp, I'll pay to keep them
away from this life.
But if that's what she wants,
I can't stop her.
I'll suffer, like my mom did.
Sure, she's my daughter.
But, all I can do is say:
"You're hurting me..."
No. I can't ever say
that, cause...
she'll say: "You hurt my grandma,
and didn't hear all this."
- You said you lle a lot.
- I do!
I lle a lot. When you lle,
you gotta belleve.
Really belleve,
so you must lle well.
And I'm quite a llar.
I even cry to convince
my own self of things.
I lle so much, I end up belleving
my lles to be true.
So what were the lles you told
me in our chat?
I didn't tell you any lles.
I lled to you guys yesterday...
cause I didn't wanna do
this interview.
So I lled. "I'm going out,
and I'll be in Iate."
The instant they Ieft,
I came back. I was scared.
But today I didn't lle.
I forgot about it.
I'd forgotten I was gonna do
this interview.
It'd sllpped my mind,
but yesterday I lled.
There you have it.
I'm an honest llar.
I lle, but I also tell the truth.
I'm shy.
And I stammer.
- Excuse me?
- I'm shy...
and I stammer.
This will be terribIe.
- How oId are you?
- I'm 57.
- And your wife?
- 25.
- Is it your first marriage?
- No, my second.
- How many chlldren?
- Two.
I've had one son with
my first wife...
and I'm also a singIe father.
I have a 31- yr- oId son.
- What's a"singIe father"?
- Well...
in my 2Os,
I knocked up a girI.
I fathered the baby.
So I was a singIe father.
At what age did you start working?
- When I was 8.
- Doing what?
I soId peanuts
and snacks in trains.
I was a shoeshine for 2 weeks,
but I didn't like it.
Then I got a job at a supermarket.
Before that, I'd worked for
the City Morgue...
picking up bodies out of the streets
hit and run victims.
My mom often couldn't put food
on our tabIe.
Any check, ticket...
or coupon I got at schooI...
for my bus fares...
cause I didn't pay for schooI
I'd give my mom to buy us food.
How come you didn't stammer
once during our conversation?
Beats me.
God spoke through me.
It was wonderfuI.
Was it?
Why is that?
Because I had an
opportunity to...
speak publlcIy about...
my chlldhood.
Though it was tough...
and rather bitter...
I never turned to coke,
nor drinking.
I've aIways kept my dignity
about me.
I've got no chip on my shoulders.
I'm convinced
I was a good son.
My poor mom died on my Iap,
in Brasílla.
I used to traveI to Brasílla
to visit her.
At times, I'd just come back
from my annuaI vacations...
and I'd ask my manager:
"Let me go see my dying mother."
Once, upon my return,
I thanked him: "Listen, Pedro..."
His name is Pietro,
he's Itallan.
"Pietro, I'll make up for missing
work in the future."
"I had to go.
Thank you for granting me Ieave."
He said:
"You don't have to thank me."
I'll never forget his words.
"You traveled not because you had
to, but because you deserved it."
I was very happy.
I had no idea he held me,
as an employee...
in such high esteem.
I worked with Pietro
for 15 years.
Are you very emotional?
I'm a softie.
Is that good or bad?
Men don't cry.
Just because he cries...
a man...
I've got nothing to hide.
This is me.
No, Beth.
I'll ask them to stop.
There's no doorbell.
Sir, excuse me again.
We're interviewing your
next-door neighbor in #111...
and it's tough.
We got a film crew here. Look.
See?
We're working here.
If you guys could stop
for just a sec?
Can you stop just for a sec?
Thanks.
Ellska, a half hour
is not a sec.
Now keep going, keep going.
Who knows them?
Hi, Lucinha. How are you?
Is Rita here?
We'd been waiting for you.
Make yourselves at home.
How long have you lived
at the Master?
4O years, since I was born.
Were you born right here
in this studio?
That's right.
At night, I can find my way
in the dark.
I go to the bathroom
with the llghts out...
but she gets lost.
Or my mom will enter
the bathroom...
as I'm Ieaving,
and we scare each other.
We aIways walk around
in the dark.
- Does you mom sleep in there?
- Yes. I sleep here.
Where do you sleep?
That's a sofa- bed.
- A bunker bed?
- No, a pullout bed.
- Where are you headed for?
- The Publlc Security office...
where I used to work.
- The pollce.
- You worked for the pollce?
I'm a retired pollce officer.
You going downtown?
Don't forget your key.
Don't take too long.
- Did you go to schooI?
- Yep, untll high schooI.
I've had jobs, but I've quit
to take better care of mom.
I quit working 5 years ago.
Do you get along well,
or what?
Say something, help me out!
We have the occasional quarrel.
That's life. We're the same sign.
But I'm more...
We're Leo.
She's a bit more...
I avoid conflicts.
Ritinha is a good roommate.
She's easy- going.
- What was that?
- I'm easy-going.
And how about her, Rita?
Level with me.
She's got more of a temper.
I've got a temper, I'm stubborn...
I admit it, I'm difficult,
indeed.
But I'm a nice person.
When People need me,
I'm there for them.
I'm always there for my friends.
- Ain't it right?
- Yeah.
Really, Rita? You may disagree.
No, really. She's a friend
for all times.
And would you live
together forever?
I would. We get along great.
She's learning to cook now,
which is hard...
...cause she's not too keen on it.
- What about the house chores?
I do most of them.
But she heIps with the cleaning.
I prefer to cook.
Are you preparing lunch?
Just a quick bite.
- Excuse us.
- Make yourseIves at home.
Didn't you say you'd lost
your father?
I haven't lost him. He's missing!
- Tell me.
- 1931, haven't I told you?
Two months after I was born,
he kissed me...
left for Belém, and never
came back.
He went to Fortaleza first.
Then boarded a ship to the Amazon...
and disappeared eaten by cannibals
in the Amazon, I don't know.
People would ask:
"Where's your old man?"
I'd say: "He's gone."
That would hurt me, and
my mother would tell me:
"Son, you daddy's gone.""He went to
Belém, and has been gone ever since."
- She was father and mother to me.
- How did she support you both?
She had a stall in a street fair,
she soId knickknacks.
She was quite a smart lady.
- What did you use to do?
- Here?
I've had many jobs.
I've soId furniture...
at a shop in Catete St.
I've been a bartender...
then worked at a carpet shop...
at a fabric store...
Since I was a kid,
I've written poetry.
I used to be quite inspired.
Here...
I started writing sambas...
and got the inspiration
to write "Favela".
Has "Favela"ever been recorded?
Yes, by Marisa Gata Mansa,
in 196O-61...
back when she was a star.
Only the favela's residents
Are aware of its enchantment
Gazing out at the moon
We see it's beautiful
And the favela seems
More blissful
The only true samba
ls that made in a terreiro
A dirt-covered, sacred ground
The tambourine keeps the beat
The mulattas shake their hips
All is settled all around
People are tired of
working all day
Carryingwateron their heads,
And cooking on hot plates
When the circle is complete
People surrenderto the beat
And even the moon comes
to a standstill
l suspect the moon agrees
with me:
They suffer all day,but doing
the samba at night, they are happy
Only the favela's residents
Are aware of its enchantment
I came to the Master 4 years ago.
Funny,
I said "came"to the Master...
cause the first time
I came in here, I got scared.
"God no! Not another one of those
Copacabana buildings!"
I had sort of "inhabited",
or eIse...
been a frequent visitor
to a studio nearby.
I got nervous.
I saw this pIace and said:
"Another one of those buildings".
ObviousIy, I was brought here by
emotional reasons, and stayed.
Its diversity of tenants...
doesn't bother me.
But its high popuIation
density does.
It's an oppressive number
of People... a lot of them!
Their diversity is not a probIem,
it's what's interesting.
In the Iate'7Os,
I used to come here...
to hang out at the oId Sótão...
a night cIub in AIaska Gallery.
Back then, there was a mix of...
sIeaziness and gIamour,
both in one pIace.
I couldn't tell them apart in
the short time I spent here...
I didn't know better.
I feIt I was attending...
a CarnivaI Ball.
all was a fantasy.
- You lived eIsewhere?
- Far from here.
None of this really affected me.
What bothers me today...
is that Copacabana's reality
affects most People.
You go out into the streets
and see terribIe things:
kids sniffing gIue,
maIe and femaIe prostitutes...
drug deaIers, etc.,
that's our reality.
It's too much, for God's sake!
I don't think sociaI evlls should
be eradicated...
and treated to create an
ascetic society. But this is too much.
Natallna, how do you
like Copacabana?
You work at two homes.
Tell us...
about Copacabana's mayhem.
Look this way, and tell us.
Be yourself.
It's chaotic, huh?
I prefer quieter pIaces.
I'd rather go straight home
after work.
Or traveI to Minas to visit
my mother.
I'd rather stay home.
On weekends...
or weekdays, I go to church.
I'm a PentecostaI.
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday,Geicy
- Do you live here by yourself?
- Yes, I do.
- Don't you feeI IoneIy?
- Very much so, very often.
But I've got an aunt
who lives nearby...
and reIatives in BeIo Horizonte.
My kids live in the US,
all of them.
- What are some of your hobbies?
- Going to the beach and waIking.
- You're in good shape.
- Not yet, because of...
...my domestic accident.
- What happened exactIy?
It was Aprll 23.
I came in and, as you can see,
the pIace is all carpeted...
except for the tlled entrance.
I sllpped and hit my head.
I must've fainted,
I don't remember.
I moaned, and a neighbor passing
outside heard me...
and knew it:
"Something's wrong with Henrique."
What if nobody happened
to be passing by?
I would be dead.
I can't quite describe it to you.
It was a... a...
I don't have words to describe it.
3, 4 hours Iater,
it would've been too Iate.
- Do you have 3 chlldren?
- I do.
- I have 2 sons and one daughter.
- What do they do?
My eIdest is VP of an oll company
in Lafayette, Louisianna.
My other son is
a computer anaIyst.
And my daughter Rebeca drives...
one of those 18- wheeIers big rigs
for FederaI Express.
- Is your wife deceased?
- Yes, she is.
- For how long?
- She passed away 6 years ago.
Was it tough for you?
It was, indeed.
We were very cIose.
Whose idea was it to move
to the US?
I'd aIways wanted to
against my family's will.
I was 17, and my uncIe,
who had acquaintances...
in high pIaces,
got me a fake ID.
With only my passport, R$ 2OO reais,
and no contacts, I moved to the US.
I was a dish- washer at first.
One day, I happened to be at
the IdIewlld Airport...
an oId US airport.
A man asked me
if I were Puerto- Rican.
"Brazilian", I said, and he told me
of a job for Portuguese speakers.
The next day, I was empIoyed.
- By what company?
- Pan American.
You heId an important position
in the US.
You must've had big savings
and a pension pIan.
- Why live in such a small pIace?
- I didn't save much.
all I got I gave to my chlldren.
I gave my house and car
to my son.
My retirement pay comes from
the US but it's no big deaI.
It's enough to support myself
here, but not what People think:
"Oh, he gets paid in dollars,
he must be rich."
No, absoIuteIy not.
HonestIy, if I lived in the US...
with my retirement pay,
I'd be worse off.
How did you meet Frank Sinatra?
That's interesting.
Through my company...
when the astronauts came back
from the Moon...
and a reception was thrown for
them at Houston's Astrodome...
I was incIuded in the guest llst.
I sat down in the arena...
and there he was,
sitting 4 or 5 chairs away...
sided by thugs of the...
- Mob?
- Sitting with the mob.
I went up to greet him:
"How are you doing,
'BIue Eyes'? "
He smlled, we shook hands,
and started chatting.
Dione Warwick was there...
many ceIebrities.
I told him I was crazy about
his song, "My Way".
He said: "Come up on stage and
sing two llnes with me."
I went up on stage,
and sang two llnes with him.
Did he tell the audience
what you were doing there?
He said: "This is a good friend
I just met. He's Brazilian...
he works for the SAS,
and he'll sing with me."
-  Why "My Way"?
- "My Way"is my life story.
- Why? Tell me.
- The Iyrics describe my life.
He did all he could've done...
traveIed West and East...
went to Europe,
went everywhere...
but he did it his way.
Right or wrong,
he did it his way.
And I, for my turn,
did the same.
I moved to the US with moxie only
and did it my way.
I made it there,
and I did it my way.
Two Saturdays a week, I play
that song for the People outside.
They waIk by and say:
"Okay, okay!"
- "Two Saturdays a week?"
- Sorry, every other Saturday.
- At what time?
- Around 1O am.
I'll turn it up!
Ready?
That's right, gentlemen.
The voice could be better, but...
next time it will be.
That was in the 6Os,
a long time ago.
I get emotional llstening to it.
I get... shivers.
That's it? Is it over?
If I hear: "Fernando José!",
it's GIobo TV.
"Fernando!", it's my family.
"BaIdy!", my Copacabana friends.
I love it here. I attend to
oId Iadies on the beach...
on the sidewaIk, where I waIk
every day, rellgiousIy...
even if I'm hurting here,
and there.
- How oId are you?
- I'm 73.
Do you get along with all here?
I do. I know everyone.
For instance, I care for...
an eIderIy coupIe who lives
across the hall.
They have no phones,
no doorbell.
He's scIerotic,
and she's very llI.
He's way past 9O...
so I care for both of them.
- Have you acted in many soaps?
- Over 3O soap operas.
- And movies?
- 62 movies.
Back in the oId era of
sex sIapstick comedies...
but I've also acted in an
award- winning film.
I've had great times,
I miss them dearIy.
If I hadn't gotten deaf on
the set of The CIáudia Affair...
I was to get shot at my nape...
with a squib this big.
The EFX guy sent a stand- in
that day...
who used a bigger charge.
So when I got shot on the set,
I knew it:
"I'm fucked!",
but I did the whoIe scene.
I had a fake bIood capsuIe
in my mouth...
and spat it on the wall.
The shot came out beautifuI, but I
couldn't hear a thing afterwards.
WeIcome.
This is DaIva,
the mistress of the house.
This is our home.
Make yourseIves at home.
This is just a simpIe thing
we prepared to weIcome you.
Just a simpIe thing
to weIcome you.
Where do you work now?
I'm an accountant,
working freeIance...
since I sadIy joined the ranks
of the unempIoyed.
One's got to take meniaI tasks
to survive:
I'm a dispatcher,
a freeIance accountant...
I soIve People's red- tape
at the DMV.
OddIy, what heIped me when
I set up home in Copacabana...
was having lived
in the North city area.
I feIt out of pIace here.
I enjoyed having a beer
with my buddies.
There are picket- fence
houses there...
we greet everyone:
"Hi, Maria. Hi, João."
Here we Iock ourseIves in...
and only know a neighbor's died
if he's missing for more than...
Henrique, our neighbor and
good friend, a US Navy Major...
who had a fall at home...
disappeared for 2 days,
and he's allve to tell the taIe...
cause he dragged himself to the
phone to call for heIp, right?
He was rescued, and thus we heard
he'd had an accident.
In my oId neighborhood,
we'd say:
"I haven't seen Maria today.
What's up?"
Then we'd knock on
the neighbor's door.
I gotta tell you.
Just because I've lived here
for the past 7 years...
my former neighbors
discriminate me.
- Why?
- They say I'm rich.
"Oh, he lives in Copacabana."
My dad is a tough German guy...
with all the cons attached to it.
So he wasn't too happy to have
a grandson so soon.
What do you mean,
"a grandson so soon?"
Did it just happen?
Yes. I found out too Iate
and had Lucas.
Because you wanted to,
or you had to?
Thanks to a series
of coincidences...
I was Ieft with no other choice.
Did you live with your kid's
father after his birth?
For a short whlle.
- Things didn't work out?
- CertainIy not.
So your father wasn't too happy
with your pregnancy?
I think he had other pIans for me...
so he acted...
I don't know.
I think he acted a bit...
I don't know... a bit hasty.
Lucas wasn't even 1 yr. oId,
when he...
handed me a small sum of
money to buy an apartment.
- Did he give you the money?
- He did.
- As if saying: "Move out", right?
- Right.
Did you use to live in a big,
spacious home?
Big, right.
How did you feeI moving
into this studio?
CIaustrophobic.
And really scared.
I was 18 when I moved in...
not even 19, and brought
only my room's furniture.
I'd call and ask him if I could go
sleep there but he wouldn't let me.
I really hated it here.
- And now?
- Now it's my home.
What bothers me is the noise.
Hearing other Peoples' lives
coming in through the vent...
...through the windows.
- Really?
- Yeah. Cris' seen it.
- For reaI?
For reaI. I know when the
downstairs neighbors are cooking...
or arguing, or fighting
with their chlldren.
You hear it through
the kitchen vent?
- I'd love to insulate that.
- Do you hear much yelling, fighting?
It's annoying.
I tell Lucas...
I teach him that's wrong,
you know...
but it's constant, so...
- How do you like Copacabana?
- It's terrifying.
Some days...
this meIting pot is
anthropoIogically interesting...
but, above all, I think I'd like
to kllI passersby who bump into me...
its street vendors,
its chaotic traffic.
I was born in Petrópolls and...
HEAD DOORMAN
was adopted with 8 months...
by a family who raised me.
My adoptive mother is allve.
I haven't heard from my
bioIogicaI mother in 2O years.
I never knew my father,
but I've aIways feIt that...
one of these days,
a secret will be reveaIed:
that my Iate adoptive father
was my reaI father.
Cause we are identical...
in the way we act...
the way we talk,
our personalities.
Too much of a coincidence.
- Is he alive?
- No, he died 14 years ago.
Why don't you ask your
adoptive mother?
No. I know she'll tell me
before she dies.
- Do you see her often?
- Every week.
- How oId is she?
- 75.
Are you gonna wait to hear
the truth?
She'll tell me, I know.
If not to me,
she'll tell someone eIse.
- Do you like her?
- Of course. A lot.
She raised me. I should thank her
for being here today...
giving this interview.
I'm grateful to her.
I was already on my way...
...to meet the guy up there.
- Why?
I was very sick, full of probIems...
- As a kid?
- Yeah.
How do you reIate to God,
and rellgion?
I thank Him every morning
for being allve...
for being abIe to waIk, and taIk.
How do you communicate with God?
I look up, cross myself,
and taIk straight up to Him...
as if I were having this
conversation with you.
Really?
But do you visuallze him and all?
No, I don't see anything.
Just in my imagination.
You said you didn't call Him
"God", but something else.
"Boss."
I often call him "Boss"...
cause He hires and fires us
as He pIeases.
Or "The- Guy- Beyond- The- CIouds."
This is how I call him,
with all due respect.
I dream of my father the most.
I aIways dream of him
since he's passed away.
Not every night, but very often.
And I remember my dreams.
He aIways scoIded me,
gave me nasty sermons.
- Do you see his face?
- CIearIy.
You dream of your adoptive father,
who you belleve is your reaI father.
That's right.
How do you feeI when you wake up?
Good or bad?
I sometimes feeI a llttIe upset.
Depending on the dream, I feeI sad.
I'm quite emotional,
and sometimes I cry.
And the baby you found in the
hallway, before Sérgio's tenure?
No, no.
During Sérgio's tenure...
about 3 years ago.
The baby's mother used to work
at Mr. Roberto's ...
apartment, #718.
One day, she showed up with
a small baby in her arms.
Ten minutes Iater,
she Ieft without the chlld.
I thought:
"There's something wrong."
I took the eIevator up
to the 8th floor...
came down the stairs, and
found the baby on the 5th floor...
by the trash shute door...
Iying on newspapers on the floor.
The chlld was healthy...
clean, chubby, next to a bottle
with juice, with a clean diaper.
I ran down, fetched Mr. Sérgio
and Ms. Vera...
to handle the situation.
- And then youleft?
- I did.
I came home, and drank
some water to calm down.
But that scene kept haunting me...
that baby on the floor.
all else was fine, no problem.
That scene shocked me, though...
as if I were seeing myself
lying there.
But that's past, I'm ok.
- Where were you born?
- Spain.
And how did you end up here?
It's fate.
It dictates our lives.
I was born in a village...
near Santiago de Compostela,
La Coruña.
Quite young,
at 17, 18, Ileft...
for Santiago, where I began work
at a hoteI...
untll I decided to come here.
- By yourself?
- Yes.
Did you get a job right away?
- I was jobIess for only 11 days.
- Where did you find work?
At the same home I work today,
on AtIântica Ave., in Copacabana.
As a house maid?
I've been a maid all my life,
and I stllI am. I'm proud of it.
Some People are ashamed of it,
but that's ignorance...
simpIemindedness.
For those who work honestIy,
any job is good.
Have you been back
to Spain since?
Yes, 1O years after
I'd settled in Brazil.
My employer paid for my trip.
I'd had my eldest daughter,
and was pregnant with Fernando.
I went back to see my father.
Then I went back again
last year...
on a European tour,
not only to Spain.
How could you afford such a trip?
Don't we all save a few pennies?
I've always lived sparingly.
I don't spend unIess I have to,
for fear I'll be in want.
So we save,
and save all our lives.
Problems are inherent to life.
If you don't have the courage
to face them, you fall.
I thank God I've had the courage
to face them and move on.
I'm a winner.
So to those who are willing
to fight, poverty is...
There's no poverty.
That's a fantasy...
nonsense! People always taIk
about poverty.
There's no poverty here.
only in places plagued
by war...
where there's misery, no land
and no means to grow crops.
But in a country like ours?!
We're the richest in the world.
To me, America is not
the 1st worId; Brazil is.
We have it all. all it takes
it the will to work, pal.
So you think poor People...?
That's bull! They don't want
to do anything.
I've dealt with the poor for 4O
years since I came to Brazil.
I know them. They lie,
you can't fathom what they do.
- Are they lazy?
- Yes. They don't want to work.
Rather, they don't like working.
They don't even bother going
to hospitals or clinics...
to get their free birth control pills.
They don't go.
- They don't ?
- They don't bother.
I know.
They're too lazy to go.
And if you give them medicine,
they forget to take it.
So it's very tough.
Perhaps, we could find a way
to educate them.
Simpleminded People, however,
don't seem to learn.
You speak, they hear quietly.
You can tell them: "Here's a job,
for a salary, will you take it?"
"That lady is a bore!"
C'mon, "The lady is a bore."
"It pays only R$ 2O reais,
that's good for nothing."
For some People, a job means...
sermons from your boss, being
humiliated, and discriminated.
But it's not, cause there are
no employees and employers.
We only exchange services.
I work, you pay me.
You pay me, and I work.
We're co-dependent.
People think I side with
the bosses.
I side with reality...
cause I see both sides,
and People often see only one.
- How old are you?
- Five.
Do you love your grandma?
Is today Father's Day?
Are you happy or sad?
- Sad.
- Why?
Cause my dad lives in Petrópolis,
and he's traveled.
Aren't you going to see him today?
But he's working there, right?
He was kicked out of work.
He has to find another job.
He was kicked out of work?!
Such is life,
and incomprehension.
When you're a parent,
you have to overcome and...
overlook a lot of things,
so you can move on.
And today most couples...
- Is his dad divorced?
- Yes, he is.
How long have you known Rio?
For quite a long time.
First, I used to come here
for Carnival only.
I aIways came with my agent.
- Agent?
- Cause I used to be a dancer.
I did great shows.
I'm one of the Bronze "Stautues".
I toured São Paulo
with my show...
then toured Japan with it.
- How long did you stay in Japan?
- For a year.
In Tokyo, in the country,
what cities?
I lived in Shirahama...
but I visited Shimoda...
Yokohama and Tokyo.
Did you dance,
or dance and sing?
I used to dance and sing.
I'd be delighted if you sang
something in Japanese.
You want me to sing?
Wait, let me see.
There was another one
I used to sing.
Gee, after all this time,
one forgets.
Where were you born?
- In Salvador.
- Why did you go to São PauIo?
I moved to São Paulo cause...
I was really eager to work...
and my parents were poor.
But I didn't know a soul
in there, you know?
I got a job at a lady's home...
doing the laundry,
the ironing, cooking.
But I actually wanted
to work out of the house...
so other People hired me
as a cleaning lady.
I'd Ieave for work, and come back.
I started seeing things, learning.
I build my house.
Then I met Ruth...
and she said: "Wow! You're tall,
bonny, and beautiful."
"I'm producing a show."
"Come on over and have a look."
So I went.
Then she produced a show
and cast me in it.
We staged it all across
São Paulo...
performing here,
performing there...
Were you ever in a relationship?
Yes, I was.
- Were you happy, or not?
- I was.
I lived with a German guy...
for 1O years. 1O years.
We got separated quite
recentIy.
- Was it good?
- It was great.
If I were meant to be married,
I'd already be by now.
But I won't find a partner
within these walls.
One's got to go out.
I can find men easily, but...
I don't want a man to
give me trouble.
I don't men to give
me trouble.
I'd dreamt of living
in Copacabana.
I used to live in Tijuca,
and I liked it there.
But... I'd always dreamt
of living here.
How long have you
lived at the Master?
- 13 years.
- How do you like it?
It's great. It's calm, quiet.
Have you always been roommates?
Yes! It's aIways been
she, my mother, and I.
- For the past 3O, 2O years?
- For a long time.
Since I was born.
For 5O- some years.
You're sisters. Have you always
lived together?
- Always.
- Were you married?
I've never had the time,
with so many things...
and responsibilities.
There was no time left.
- We work too hard.
- And there's their health problems.
She's sick, my mom's sick,
so I had to deal with it all.
I had no time to go out to date,
especially here in Rio.
I'm afraid of these People...
so many are drug addicts,
and you can't tell.
You go to the beach, and you see
People smoking pot, doing drugs...
and you say:
"God knows if they are..."
"Those who pose as decent
People, but..."
- I heard you paint.
- I do.
I have a bunch of paintings
around here.
There's that one there,
and more in storage.
would you comment on the one
with a window?
Oh, "Ocean view", right?
It isn't finished yet.
It's over there.
How is it?
And how do you want it to be?
I want to do it...
as I envision it.
I wanted to include Botafogo...
with Copacabana in the same
painting, anyhow...
incIuding the Sugar Loaf,
and Botafogo.
So you mixed in different
city areas.
- I am, like...
- What?
- Crazy.
- Why?
Cause I paint things
that don't exist.
Stay there, boy.
Calm down.
If you leave him alone,
he'll be quiet. Go, go.
- Where did you start playing?
- In Bahia...
at Galicia.
I'm from Bahia.
Since I was 12,
I've played soccer.
In Rio, I've played in Bonsucesso,
and Bangu.
Then I went abroad and played
in Mexico for 2,5 years...
in France for 3 years.
I've played in Mexico,
so yo hablo español un poco.
I've played in France
for 2,5 years, so...
je parle français
un petit peu.
I've played in the US.
I've played in Venezuela...
then I quit playing soccer...
and became a coach in Saudi Arabia,
Thalland, and Sudan.
Tell us that episode in Maracanã.
- When I got naked?
- Yes.
I coached Itaperuna,
a small team...
in the State Championship.
I'd been doing a good work...
cause a good coach turns
a small team into a major team.
I'd managed to take my team
to that next round...
so we'd get to the
quarter- finals. Then...
on that fateful day,
I knew it wouldn't happen.
We couldn't possibly win.
The match had been rigged.
Why?
Cause that's Brazilian soccer.
But you were in your
coach uniform...
I was. I took off my shirt first,
then my pants, I was...
- In your briefs or naked?
- Naked!
They showed a close- up
of my butt.
That was the end, at least
so far, only God knows...