Translate and processed by REHAN55
You think you can manage going shopping for dinner?
Or should I do it?
No, it's okay. I can do that.
Ben is bringing someone?
Nuh-uh
Again?
This time he was caught.
The girl saw with B girl in your favorite Italian restaurant.
(Sarcastic) Nice movement.
Go ahead.
The girl turned, began to make a scene ...
... and poured a glass of wine over his head.
Girl B drank their wine and left with him.
Interestingly, things like this happen only with boys.
And not for women?
Nope.
Bye. Have a nice day.
Ah, it's good to get a hold on you.
Good morning, Dr. Kühne.
Good day.
I still have not received a response from you.
You are my preferred candidate
and I have not heard from you in a long time.
I'm really sorry. I ...
I have not had time to think about it.
Come on. Pull yourself together.
It's a great opportunity.
But I have to tell you, I?
I really appreciate your offer.
Good morning, Dr. Kühne.
11 hours in my office. Do not forget.
Sure.
(Medical alderman?)
Sounds good, does not it?
We never had a woman in that position.
Oh, and a new colleague is coming today.
Mobile Task Force.
Any anormalies?
Not that I know of.
But you're always good for a surprise.
Wait a second.
Good morning, Linda.
I am not sure if this will be good.
I can not classify its rail chaos.
Life is not just about cleanliness.
That is why chaos is so attractive.
Maybe for you.
So? What we have today?
There are some employees who had time to think about their complaints.
M-hm. Especially one.
I put official Langmüller second.
Even if he was here first thing in the morning.
You're so good to me.
Hello
Sit.
Ah, yes. Detective Franziska Hansen.
You're from Hamburg.
Is this your first job in a task force for mobile?
Yes.
Good.
At first glance, I do not see anything unusual in your file, bu -
oh, wait a minute.
A whiplash injury after a car accident.
That was how long ago?
Sept. 200 -
17 months and 2 weeks to be exact.
I understand.
Was there any sequels?
So you have no problem with him anymore?
No.
Good.
But I still have to examine it.
Please sit up there on that bed and take off your shirt.
This happened on a mission?
No, it's from the accident.
After effect.
You can dress.
Are you doing some kind of sport?
All we have to do.
That's not enough.
The back muscles are not very evolved.
Swimming is good for that.
Good.
Ms. Weber will have a blood sample and she will be doing an EKG.
It will take some time until we get the results.
If we're not getting back at you, then it's okay.
Okay.
I wish you a nice stay in Munich, Ms. Hansen.
Thank you.
Good morning Doctor.
Mr. Langmüller.
You have to check my eyes again.
With more than -8 can forget the mobile task force.
The glasses that you pre-set -
The results are unmistakable.
No, I think there is an error.
I'll prove it to you.
Look, one plate of the car down there.
The silver BMW.
That's at least 90 to 100 meters, maybe more.
M - N - S - 1753
And from this moment. What do you think?
Mr. Langmüller
This is your car down there.
Not bad.
And on photo 13?
Maybe I do not like that number.
That's what I call perfect timing.
Max Hansen this is Siska
Detective department drugs in Hamburg.
Detective Max Zollner, his new partner.
I'm sure you already knew his wife this morning.
She will help with the case Seligmann.
Excuse me?
Hansen is capable of the Serbo-Croatian language
and has a broad knowledge of Eastern Europe.
What is definitely an advantage for us.
For good teamwork.
Yeah, sure, why not.
Good.
Zollner?
Ella.
No, I can not.
He just left?
Okay, listen. I need to go in one operation.
And maybe I can stop later.
When I know how long it will take.
Ok, so far.
What?
The task force is mobile going bust two drug dealers armed.
And?
Within the next 15 minutes.
So here we go!
Linda? Please reschedule all my appointments for tomorrow.
I need to help my aunt in her practice.
His receptionist quit.
Oh, and please, find out which department he worked in accident Ms. Hansen.
No, it's official now.
Yes, thank you.
Very brave, little man.
Done. But you need to take your meds.
Okay.
Bye.
Ella, listen.
Something like today is not working.
I can help once in a while
but if you can not do it on your own
you have to hire another doctor
or reduce patients or ... I do not know.
I can not do well.
Why not?
First, I do not want anyone else here
and second I do not want anyone but you.
You should not smoke.
Taking practice and I'll quit.
Ella!
You're not happy with your work.
Listen, I talked to my bank
and we're talking a six-figure loan
to suit practice with modern technology.
Ah, all this crap technique can not replace a good doctor.
And you're a natural.
Numbers like that scares me, you know?
This is the last bottle.
I would not have guessed.
Hm?
You do not hold it against me.
What?
Siska Hansen.
I really do not know why someone just plonked in front of me without telling me.
I do not have "plonked" someone in front of you, Max
I just ordered the best and most qualified agents to the case.
Hey, you're the boss.
You've seen it, too, right?
What?
Hansen.
What do you think?
Interesting woman.
Interesting?
What do you mean?
In what way?
Well, she has this odd mix.
Cool and vulnerable.
I do not know.
Well, I think you read way too much into it.
Occupational disease.
To me it does not seem very professional.
My God, Max!
You just asked about a first impression. What's wrong with you?
I just do not want to spend the night analyzing Franziska Hansen.
In any case, it has excellent references.
The main point is that it does not spoil my case.
So let's change the topic, ok?
He definitely enjoyed dinner.
Not surprising. You cooked after its revenue.
True.
You really thought Kuhne on offer?
I do not want to force things.
Come on.
Do not be angry with Ben.
I mean it also has its advantages to be friends with your boss.
Yeah.
As you can see.
Tell me ...
How long has it been since we had sex?
Well, her birthday is coming.
Well, congratulations.
Ah-ha.
It's about time that I came back.
I'm not saying anything.
I do not want to rip off the woman of my dreams.
Actually, why not?
Let's grow old and fat together, ok.
Oh, that sounds terrible.
Let's go somewhere.
Something different.
I guess it's not a good idea to take a vacation now.
Then Hansen is taking on the case Seligmann
Seligmann and is my case.
Yup.
I'm not like you.
I want to succeed in my work.
What does this mean?
For two weeks Kühne has offered him his replacement.
So what?
Do you accept?
You always think things will resolve themselves.
I'll take a shower.
A second more and my lungs would burst already.
You do not have to stay down for so long.
But it felt good.
You're already set in?
I found an apartment.
If you can call it that.
You are a very good diver.
I like the depth.
Have you ever been diving in the ocean?
No. Too deep.
Very dark.
Does that scare you?
Maybe it's something we should talk.
You do not want to talk.
We think Seligmann is the central figure.
He is a former police officer.
He is familiar with our methods, touched coverage of an agent a year ago
and shot in cold blood.
From this secret agent, we know that Seligmann
ran a ton of cocaine to Germany.
What we do not know is how he does it.
What we know is that he has excellent contacts in the Balkans.
Any questions?
Seligmann is to be observed 24/7, now six weeks.
That's how he is saying that we have much to do. Here.
You are the first policeman I meet who do not drive.
You do not want to drive or you can not drive?
I do not want.
I do not understand.
I mean, there must be a reason.
I do not get anything out.
You do not gain anything by it?
Yeah. I do not get anything out.
What? No skid marks?
Ok, but what has Hansen explanation?
I understand.
Can you tell me who treated Hansen?
Yes, the hospital.
I also got to know who was in charge of their medical care in police.
Someone died?
It's about time.
(Bavarian accent) It's really about time, Max! It's getting cold.
What?
It's cold. You're late. I want to go home.
He is doing drugs, too?
Seligmann is a control freak.
He is not on drugs.
But?
Prostitutes.
He likes to pay for it.
It seems important to you.
Can you get me some water?
What is holding you back?
It's a big step forward.
Yes, I know.
Is that the problem?
What do you mean?
You talked to Max about it.
Not true.
You know you make a quick career than him.
Do not underestimate the vanity of the male brain.
It's not about that, believe me.
I just want to be a doctor. And a good, you know?
Sure.
Tell me ...
They are good together?
Very good.
Jealous?
Where is my car?
Go!
Put your weapon!
What the fuck was that, Hansen?
You partner would be dead now!
It's kind of absurd to persuade someone to a promotion.
You will not find the answer in the tea leaves.
I do not know why you are hesitating. Perhaps for private reasons.
But I know that acceptance by staff,
his experience and his extraordinary sense
shows that you are perfect for the job.
That's why I want you.
For everything you're saying I feel honored
and that is what makes it also difficult for me to decide.
Look, Dr. Kühne
I see my purpose in occupational less administrative stuff
I need direct contact with patients.
The situation is so.
I have to say a name or I have to advertise the position.
I need your answer until next week.
Come, I'll help you.
Max Max, please!
I have so many things on my mind.
I love you.
Only three more weeks until my birthday.
What time is it?
You have not found an apartment yet?
I have, but I got stuck in custom reports.
In custom reports?
Seligmann means in Serbo-Croatian xxx
And this name appears with other animal transport.
Transport of animals that are shipped in Trieste on Croatia.
They are legally imported.
And?
Maybe they smuggle stuff like this.
Forget it.
Transportation like this are handled very good.
It is impossible to hide this much unnoticed cocaine in a truck.
I was not thinking about the trucks.
What do you mean?
Animals.
Do you think they feed the cows with this material?
Unlikely.
Enlighten me.
Cows are ruminants.
True. They regurgitate and chew packets in two.
But what -
Pigs.
The more I think about it, it's brilliant, you know?
Coincidence.
Combinatorics.
Intuition.
Ok, I admit. I'm a genius.
Good. In the mood for a drink?
Destroy some cells genius?
It is not new. I could not find anything online, if pigs are suitable as courirs drugs.
Ok
Digestion times and stuff.
I have to ask a national title in the library.
And how long would it take?
At least 8-9 days.
We could make him an express mail and you would get it on Monday.
No, that is too long.
I need the books this week.
Faster is not possible.
Hi
Where do you come from?
From the outside.
Ah, yes.
I am looking for information on veterinary medicine.
Second floor.
You wanna come with me? I'll show you.
They told me that Munich is a city, but this small?
But, so you will not lose sight of anyone.
Uhm, I can give you a ride somewhere?
I got my bike.
Well, good luck then.
Oh, excuse me.
Hello?
Hello? Who's there?
My god, Ella. Please calm down, can not in -
Okay, stay there. I'm going.
Unbelievable, my aunt had a car accident.
Is she hurt?
No, I do not think so, but ...
She is so out of it these days.
I think she needs my help.
You want me to go?
Can you remember everything?
Could you please leave the car?
I'm talking to the patient.
Can somone please get Mrs. confusing to leave the car?
Now, not insolent.
The woman is a doctor.
And who are you?
I am also a doctor.
You see, you're not needed here.
Should I give you a ride home?
No thanks.
Glad you're laughing again.
You are the driver of the car?
Yes.
Driver's license and registration, and please drive your car to the side of the road.
With or without registration?
So you're driving without a license for years?
The car was the pride of Peter and I did not have the heart to sell it after he died.
You can always request a driver's license.
And as fit as you are, you can drive for over 10 years.
Grande.
You're just playing with me.
So now let me out.
I just want a whiskey and bathtub.
We must take him upstairs?
No, it's okay.
The car suits you both.
You do not speak Serbo-Croatian, is not it?
Do you live alone.
Not true.
Fish were my husband.
When you lose the person you love most
is probably the worst that can happen.
How do you know?
I know.
Uh-uh.
You know.
What do you know?
At first I thought it could not get through it.
But you keep on living.
Whether you want to or not.
The nights are difficult.
You keep waking up and
you expect
it was just a dream.
You think, My God
do not let him be dead.
But you know it's not a dream.
I uhm
I do not know what I would do.
I tell you what you would do.
Work.
Work. Work.
Without breaking. No thought. Just working.
Then you forget.
Are you sure that is the right way?
Yes.
I tried.
Where have you been?
I've wondered where you were when you came home late?
I'm on duty.
Well, I was too.
You do not want to tell me what is happening?
Ella had an accident.
What?
Ella had a car accident.
I had to care for her half of the night.
What happened?
Is she hurt?
No, no one was injured.
What's with the inquisition?
I'm dead tired.
I have to sleep now.
Why do I have the feeling you're not telling the truth?
It's nothing. Believe me.
Good day.
What are they doing with the car of Ella?
Katrin asked me to bring him back to her.
How do you know which car is Ella?
I met Katrin yesterday and took Ella home.
Linda, you could find a doctor that hospital in Hamburg?
That the teacher ...
Bäumer.
Yes.
I found him, but he has not called back yet.
Could you please call him again. I really need to talk to him.
Now?
Yes, now.
Hello, Katrin.
Hey.
Ms. Hansen results are already here?
I put them on his desk.
Oh, yeah, right.
Well then, follow me.
Franziska.
I. ..
Oh
Franziska.
Siska. I'm sorry.
But out there ...
Linda hears coughing fleas.
Sure.
Doctor.
Yes, exactly.
Siska, listen.
What happened last night ...
I think it should ...
Yes?
Well ...
I think it's better when we forget it.
Jeez, Siska. We are not disposed of in this manner both.
For most people as something that happens during puberty.
And for us a little later.
I do not need psychological explanations.
I'm not your patient.
You are also my patient.
And what else?
Ah, yes.
Something you better forget.
Shit!
Pigs?
Exactly.
Pigs as drug courir, not bad.
And it fits much of the stomach of a child.
And you save the ticket.
Is everything okay with you two?
Sure.
Seligmann is taking charge next night somewhere on the border near Salzburg.
Salzburg?
There are actually police in charge of Austria.
Come, forget Austria!
Already did.
Siska? Hello? It Katrin.
What are you doing?
I gotta go.
But we'll have dinner together right?
You can not. I'll get picked up anytime.
What's wrong? Why are you so grumpy?
I have a reason?
I do not know.
His story about the accident Ella was very thin.
Why do not you tell me Siska was with you?
Because I. ..
Gee, Max, I do not think it was important.
I just forgot about it. It was not important. It was Ella.
She would have been the perfect alibi. My partner. What a coincidence.
But you should have planned better.
Are you crazy?
Where you been all night really fucking after the accident?
Max I. ..
Shit.
Hey, come on in. I'm almost done. Katrin is cooking.
Mhm, smells good.
If you want you can join us for dinner.
No, you do not want.
I'd love to.
Great.
Delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
I thought I blew it.
I can not imagine you ruin anything.
To me you look so ...
perfect.
I'm sure you have everything under control.
Job. Domestic.
Marriage.
You really appreciate it?
I think we should go.
Goodbye.
Doctor.
And thank you for that wonderful dinner.
Bye.
I guess I do not have to wait for you.
No.
What is that over there? Is that a house?
Forget it. It is inhabited. The lights are on.
Could you please not smoke in here?
Thank you.
Somehow Oyu strike me as someone who is just passing through.
I'm just passing through.
You really live alone?
You want to force a conversation about me?
Blimey, what's happening with you?
We work together. We are partners. It's completely normal I ask you all this.
I wonder what you're doing. From where you are.
Why?
I'm not sure if this is a good idea.
It's the only reasonable thing to do.
It's an hour from the border and the fifth single vacancy there.
This can not be.
It's total crap that we are doing here.
Just think. What is the probability to choose between hundreds of farms -
(Translates) They are dead. Let them inside.
What?
Shit! Why are not they coming out?
Now let's not get out and we will lose Seligmann.
Truck transport grayish yellow animal. Number plate ...
Pigs poor.
I could smoke one too, now.
You will get burned.
Thank you for taking some time to myself.
This is very good.
My pleasure Dr. Zollner.
I'm always happy to help a colleague.
Especially when I feel - as in the case of Mrs. Hansen - I've forgotten something.
I do not think you have to blame yourself for anything.
You know she is a woman who possibly saw her husband die.
And something like this can evoke -
posttraumatic disorders, yeah, I know.
That's right.
But what I'm most interested in is -
Yes, yes I know.
The time later.
The most important thing is to regain emotional stability.
In case of a chronic disease that can lead to a hostile and suspicious attitude against society.
The result is a retreat and social alienation.
It occurs excessiv reactions of shock, panic attacks.
In the case of Ms. Hansen I have recommended a ban of 6 weeks of work and therapy.
And?
Hansen cut the brief therapy.
I understand.
You neurologically examined Hansen once again?
No.
She has already been transferred.
Maybe that was the mistake.
In the accident report, said there were no skid marks, you know?
I mean, I wonder ... she lost consciousness? She just let it happen? Or ...
She did it on purpose.
Gee, Max! We have nothing!
We just could not get out of there.
Which means you could not get out of there?
What did you do there?
Playing Hide and Seek in the barn?
Hey, honey.
You ate it.
I mean why not?
She is a woman erotic.
I do not know what I would do if I spend one night with her ... watching.
Do not do it. Do. It.
A broken soul, hm?
My ass!
After catastroph in your life that you want to spoil everyone else.
But not on my watch! I swear to God!
Shit!
You sleep with me. With Max What's next? A trio?
Is this what you want?
You both use me.
To distract their problems.
Oh yeah? And you use us to get messed up on his life.
At that time
when we sat in the car
Martin and I
and he told me that he is sleeping with someone else
he wants to live with her
I hated him.
It's my fault that he died.
Back then, I swore to myself I would not fall in love again.
Up to now.
You touched something in me that I thought had died with him.
But damn! By Max?
I wanted to hurt him.
Ella?
Why dresses give us a sense of being someone else?
Good day.
In this dress, for example, I feel Russian.
You look worn. Is there something wrong?
Why do you think?
Not true?
Yes, it is.
I'm totally confused.
Why?
Do you remember this woman?
The one on my car?
Siska, yes.
You know ...
I'm making your hiring exam and came across something.
What are you holding?
Yes.
Why are they doing this?
Because I'm not sure about that.
Siska had a car accident where her husband died.
I can not shake the feeling that she wanted to kill herself.
Maybe her and him.
Maybe it was just an accident. I just do not know.
But you have to do your job.
Yes, but what if I'm wrong?
She could lose her job.
But otherwise you will lose your.
You fell for her. That's the point.
I never felt attracted to women.
I do not mean like that.
Sometimes people come into our lives that we can not explain.
That help us on our way, however.
Who is this?
You do not know her.
I'm not gay.
Neither do I.
Here. Dieter and me.
Married for 10 years and suddenly the spark was gone.
But it was a mistake to stay together.
And then there was her.
Not that he had a mistress, but I did.
But why would a woman?
Maybe hopefully be understood by a woman without explaining ourselves.
Ella!
This is just mean.
No, no, no, no ...
You should not get rid of some inconvenient truth as a line.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Just a headache.
That does not sound right.
I want to examine next week.
No, it's okay.
Come to the table.
For the lamp.
The registration documents of your car?
Just take it.
The car is yours.
Ella!
I can not accept that.
Let the breeze of the wind through your hair.
Actually, I'm on guard.
So what?
When something happens we'll be back soon.
You know, when I was four ...
I came here with my parents too.
And there we always had a break.
Then what?
Then we went inside.
Here.
He knelt.
And he prayed.
Do you believe in God?
No more.
Katrin?
Max, I need the weekend to myself.
Hello?
Hellooo?
Who's there?
Max?
Get out of there!
Can I help you?
It's ok honey.
What is happening to you?
Katrin is gone.
She never did this before.
Then you marry for love?
Yes, we really did.
But there was a party or a honeymoon.
We were kinda broke at the time.
Max was not promoted.
We always wanted to make up for it.
But?
But ...
I do not want to talk about Max now.
I just lost sight now.
I mean you think I'm capable of something like this is bad enough
But we're talking about his wife.
Benno, there is something happening.
Shit! I do not want to lose her.
If you want advice from me as your friend ...
So do not try to change it.
Give her the feeling that you love her as she is.
I have to find it first.
Concerning find. We have a clue where Seligmann.
Some slaughterhouse outside Munich.
I'll give you the details when I have them.
I fell in love.
With us.
Yes?
Where is this?
Ok, I know.
I can not get a hold on her too.
No, no, I'll do it.
I love you.
It's like a tug.
I really do not understand all this.
I try to understand that everything is a disease that destroys all the beauty.
Here, so you will not forget me.
I will not forget you.
I. .. I have to tell you something.
You can not work in the police.
I need my job.
The police are all I have.
I think 5 is more appropriate.
Times are tough.
The controls are increasingly stringent, what can I do?
So what now?
If you're trying to pull something I'm personally reduce your stomach.
Hey! You got me?
You'll make tonight your work as always.
And I hope that their action skills are as sharp as his criminal energy.
I knew it.
I knew that if someone is caught I would.
I could feel that this whole thing was about to explode.
After the latter I wanted to stop.
You know what? Whoever sits here wanted to stop now.
I can not do that.
You can remarkably reduce his sentence.
If you work with us.
I can not handle the pressure.
Then, a drink for sedation. You're a doctor.
Medical huh?
What do you think?
With a villa in Grünwald and a Porsche in the garage.
Exactly.
It's a shitty job with a payment of shit.
Hey! Calm down ok?
Not that tone.
I have to go back to Munich immediately.
It will never be like that again.
I do not think so.
Where have you been?
Seligmann has been in during 5 minutes.
It can not be long until he returns to the material.
Shit!
Is everything okay?
No.
Have you talked with Katrin?
I do not know where she is.
I'm sure she's home again.
Probably not.
And just from that moment you appeared here.
You do not make it just a little easier?
Easy?
I wonder what my wife is doing.
You want to know what his wife is doing, but I'll tell you one thing.
The last thing you need is a Katrin guy.
And what does she need?
Devotion.
Are you crazy? What is the point of that?
First you sleep with me and then tell me how you wanna take my wedding?
Listen, if it should be a little fucked up game, forget it!
I love Katrin.
Me too.
Go! Go!
Go, get a car.
Come on!
I'm counting to 10 and all must have disappeared.
If someone does something stupid I'll shoot this guy.
C'mon, c'mon!
Put your weapon!
Maaaaaaaaaaaaaax!
Wait a second.
I thought I would never return.
Caution.
Please, let's grow old together and fat.
How is he?
You must have covered.
But you did not.
Why?
You could not do it, right?
Damn, Siska!
You acutally know what you did?
He could die.
When I lose it, then ...
I would never forgive myself.
He will not die.
I should not have allowed you to report on duty.
You are sick.
In dangerous situations, you always fail.
You do not belong to the police.
I do not know where you belong.
I thought I belonged to you.
I love Max
I can not help myself.
You helped me.
Max is more worse.
What?
They could stop the bleeding.
My dear son.
I am writing to you because I do not know how long I'll be able to.
The head is round so that thoughts can change direction.
With a tumor on the road was no longer possible.
As a doctor I know what is ahead of me.
And I'm afraid.
Unfortunately I can not be here when you give this practice a facelift dusty.
But I know he will be a human.
I love you like the daughter I always wanted.
Whatever you do, the decision is yours.
And with that right.
Speaking of which ...
Today is my birthday.
Forget it.
I have a headache.
Caption by OoPalookavilleoO
participate in a synchronization dunyamorton
Translate and processed BY REHAN55