Whistle with me
Baby, come, be my lady
Why do you make me crazy, O beautiful
I love you everyday
I would take you holding your hand
What would the whole world think
I don't have to come in your hands
I am afraid that you'll make some excuse
and leave me and go
Don't talk about leaving
I am planning to get married to you
Come close, match your lips with mine
and with me, whistle
Why are you troubled O baby
I am your life, O baby
Today's is your chance, you should hold it tight
else you'll be in loss baby
Come to my class
learn the ABCD of love
Take hundred out of hundred
and match lips and whistle
So, whistle, now whistle
Everybody in the party now whistle
now whistle, now whistle
Whistle with me
Come dance, dance with me
You keep my heart, O beautiful
And beware of guys
who are behind you now
No, I won't come in anyone's hands
I just have to be yours
Whatever I do, I won't get anyone
mad for me like you are
The wish to do something
to move a bit ahead
Come close, match your lips and
with me, just whistle