♪ Mere Naal Tu Whistle Baja ♪
Whistle with me
♪ Hey Baby Ni Tu Ban Meri Lady ♪
Hey baby, become my girlfriend
♪ Kyun Tu Kare Mujhe Crazy Soniye ♪
Why are You making me go crazy, O girl?
♪ Love Kara Tenu Daily ♪
I’ll love You daily
♪ Le Jaava Tera Hath Fad Ke ♪
I’ll grab Your hand and take You away
♪ Ki Sochega Saara Zamaana ♪
What will the whole world think?
♪ Haath Tere Main Ni Aana ♪
I won’t come in Your hands
♪ Dar Lagta Hai Mujhe Kar Ke Bahaana ♪
I’m feeling scared after making excuses
♪ Tune Maine Nu Chhad Jaana ♪
You’ll surely leave me and go away
♪ Ho Gal Na Kar Tu Chhadne Di ♪
Don’t even talk about me leaving You
♪ Plan Hai Ghodi Chadhne Di ♪
My plan is to marry You
♪ Paas Mein Aa Zara Hoth Mila Aur ♪
Come near me, touch Your lips with mine and
♪ Mere Naal Tu Whistle Baja... ♪
Whistle with me
♪ Paas Mein Aa Zara Hoth Mila Aur ♪
Come near me, touch Your lips with mine and
♪ Mere Naal Tu Whistle Baja... ♪
Whistle with me
♪ Hey, Tu Kyun Pareshaan Hai Baby ♪
Why are You worried baby?
♪ Hum Aap Ki Jaan Hain Baby ♪
I’m Your life baby
♪ Aaj Hai Mauka Pakad Le Kas Ke ♪
Today You’ve got the opportunity to hold me tightly
♪ Ni To Tera Nuskaan Hai Baby… ♪
If You miss this chance, then it’s Your loss baby
♪ Arey Meri Class Mein Aaja ♪
Come in my classroom
♪ Seekh Le Pyaar Ki A B C D ♪
Learn the A B C D of love
♪ Sau Mein Se Sau Le Le ♪
Take 100 out of 100
♪ Bas Honth Mila Ke Baja De Seeti ♪
Just touch Your lips with mine and whistle
♪ Now Whistle, Now Whistle ♪
Everybody In The Party Now Whistle
♪ Mere Naal Tu Whistle Baja… ♪
Whistle with me
♪ Ho Nach Le Mere Naal Tu Nach Le ♪
Dance with me
♪ Dil Mera Tu Hi Rakh Le Soniye ♪
Keep my heart with You, O girl
♪ Rehna Mundeyan To Bachke ♪
Beware of the guys
♪ Jede Tere Piche Padge Ne ♪
That are after You
♪ Na Na Maine Hath Ni Aana ♪
No, I won’t come into their hands
♪ Maine Bas Tera Ban Jaana ♪
I just want to become Yours
♪ Nai Milna Mujhe Google Karke ♪
Even after searching on Google
♪ Tere Warga Deewana ♪
I won’t find a guy as crazy as You
♪ O Aarzoo Kuch Karne Ki ♪
I have a desire to do something
♪ Thodi Aage Badhne Ki ♪
And to move forward
♪ Paas Mein Aa Zara Hoth Mila Aur ♪
Come near me, touch Your lips with mine and
♪ Mere Naal Tu Whistle Baja... ♪
Whistle with me