According to some medical research,
only 10% of the normal human brain is active.
The other 90%
is dormant or repressed.
Even for a genius like Einstein,
his brain
was only 3-5% more active than others.
So you can imagine
if our brain is 100% active,
how smart and powerful we will be!.
But the world is full of extraordinary things.
Someone might have already
developed this potential
and become a superhero!.
So if you see
someone doing something incredible,
don't be scared. It's not witchcraft!.
It's only
a science-defying experience,
a witness to a magical power
that we all yearn for!.
Magic To Win
Macy Cheng.
Macy Cheng!.
Superman returns!.
Good morning, Prof Kang.
In that film,
by flying around Earth in super speed,
Superman spins Earth backwards
and reverses time.
If we are to formulate this concept,
then Time is equivalent to Earth.
Macy, you just returned to reality.
What's the mass of Time?.
Well, it depends on...
how heavy your watch is.
That's what you think.
The correct answer is...
5.975x...
Hey!. The game is about to start!.
But he still has the volleyball.
Let him keep it as a souvenir.
10 to the power 21 ton!.
That's the mass of Earth.
That's also the mass of Time.
If men are so powerful,
can they reverse time?.
According to the law of conservation,
energy can be transferred or absorbed.
So in theory, the answer is yes.
But in reality...
Catch it!.
Men simply cannot withstand such power.
How can they reverse time?.
Stop daydreaming.
Don't waste time!. Macy!.
In order not to waste time, we better go now!.
Hey!. What are you doing?.
off to a game?. Yes!.
Bye-bye!.
Good luck!.
Look,
our opponents seem formidable!.
We better watch out!.
How you look is more important than you hit!.
Formidable or not, we'll wait and see!.
Look how fit our team is!.
And look at them...
What's our strategy today?.
We'll take the offensive
and spike the ball at them.
Great?.
Great!. They'll die.
What's so funny?.
Never mind. Coach Liu will deal with him!.
By the way, what's taking Coach Liu so long?.
oh yes!.
Good morning!. Sorry!.
In a hurry, Coach Liu?.
We have a game.
Come root for us if you're free!.
How fast the elevator goes
is not related to how fast
you press the button.
Is that so?.
Pressing it too fast
might short-circuit...
...the board.
If you carry on, you may damage the elevator.
What's going on?.
We're stuck in the elevator!.
Help!.
You should have come earlier
to root for your team.
If they lose any more points, they're doomed.
Really?. Let's just take this
as a handicapped game.
Winning...no,
friendship is...more important.
Macy...are you all right?.
You're giving us so much face!.
You used your face to hit the ball!.
So thick-skinned!.
Thick-skinned?.
What's going on?.
Where is Coach?.
We have no idea.
90% of elevator accidents are man-made.
only 10% are due to mechanical malfunctions.
This one belongs to the former,
so we're safe.
Come here and kneel down.
Why should I kneel down?.
just do it.
Hey...
That's dangerous.
It won't be.
You won't be in danger, but I will!.
We're both in danger!. But I'm in a hurry!.
I'm already late!.
just hit the ball back. How hard can it be?.
Macy!. Macy...
Macy, don't hit the ball with your face again!.
Are you playing or killing?.
What's wrong with you?.
Time out!.
Hey!. Why time out?.
just lose the game, so I can do my groceries!.
None of your business!.
Where have you been?.
Go straighten them out!.
Come over!.
Well done!. Well done!.
Is that the first time you played volleyball?.
The front line roofs the ball;
the back row follows up.
No.6 outflanks at the baseline.
These are basic positions. Have you forgotten?.
use your brain when you're in the court!.
We've done our best.
They are really strong.
Can you speak up?.
Strengthen your defense.
Don't lose one more point.
oK?.
If we've tried our best
and they're too strong,
it's fine even if we lose.
Spike the ball at their faces. Got it?.
Spike at them, oK?.
Spike till they cry, all right?.
I think we still have a chance.
We can still beat them.
oK, buddies?.
victory!.
victory...
Don't be robots!. Howl when you hit back!.
Coach Liu!. Come to my office after this!.
You!.
Principal Gao is leaving!.
It's only 21 to 0.
oh no, should be 22 to 0!.
How to do?.
Good morning, Principal Gao!.
Morning?.
Are you oK?.
Do you know how I'm feeling right now?.
I don't think you understand.
Someone I trust has betrayed me.
She's cheated my feelings.
She lied to me that
our team would win this game.
But we're 0...
...to 25 already!.
I'm going to replace the whole team!.
Principal Gao.
They only lack experience.
Give them a chance!.
only well prepared people...
...deserve opportunities.
our university
has risen from top 100 to top 10.
To go higher...
we need to excel...
...in sports as well.
You understand?.
I need...
...results!.
Kang!.
Why didn't you knock?.
Because you didn't close the door?.
oK then. What can I help you?.
I'm warning you,
don't mess with me anymore!.
Mess with you?.
Are you in trouble?.
Tell me. I might be able to help you.
our team lost,
but you were gloating.
I saw that.
I think you're a very mean person.
Gloat?.
Why would I gloat?.
You're mistaken.
How will you explain
the elevator accident then?.
Explain?
I think you rigged the elevator...
...to make me late.
You wanna be the vice principal?.
Let's race fairly.
You wanna use tricks?. Fine by me too!.
But if you involve my team,
I won't let you off!.
just let me off!.
It was an accident!.
This is an accident too!.
You're Gu Xinyue, the author of this book?.
Yes, you want me to autograph for you?.
You see the future.
You should know what I want.
I'm an author, not a clairvoyant!.
You're too obsessed with my novels.
I know you're a Wood magician.
What?.
Don't pretend!.
You turn what you foresee into sci-fi novels.
You knew I would come.
Then why are you still asking?.
Let me ask you something I don't know then.
After amassing the magic of all 5 elements,
is it true that you can return to the past?.
If I haven't written it,
that means I don't know.
Wait for my next book.
How can you not know?.
I don't wanna know!.
Since you don't know,
then do as you've written.
Lend me your Wood magic!.
What for?.
What a humiliating defeat!.
our opponents were too strong today.
0 to 25 is too embarrassing!.
There're 6 of us.
We lost on average 4 points each.
I must have lost the extra point.
We should always look on the bright side!.
Winning 1 point next time is an improvement!.
So great!.
Food is more important than volleyball!.
Let's eat!.
Macy!. open the door!.
open the door!. Hurry up!.
Coach...
Eggs?.
Haven't you had enough today?.
We're trying to
get it out of our system.
Yes, we're trying to feel oK about ourselves.
Shut up!.
Aren't you shameless?.
Assemble at the volleyball court in 3 minutes!.
Accuracy is essential to playing volleyball.
As long as you can hit the ball accurately,
you can control the rhythm of the game.
There are lots of numbers in the court.
Go to the baseline
and hit them down in order.
Hurry up!.
Hit harder!
Hit accurately!
Carry on!.
Coach, we can't hit them!.
Can we move up a bit?.
Stop negotiating with me.
You wanna come up here and be the coach?.
You gave up before you even started?.
I wanna tell you,
volleyball is a sport, an athletic event.
You need to transcend your dream
in this event.
If you lose your fighting spirit,
you're lost already...
...before the game starts.
Because you're rubbish!.
Rubbish!. Rubbish!.
Your lives are over!.
Absolutely over!.
Enough!.
Coach, I'm thirsty.
Are you?. I'll get you a drink.
Shit!.
Macy?.
Macy.
Are you oK?.
Want me to take you to the clinic?.
No, thanks. I'm fine.
just leave me alone.
You're still oK after the collision?.
No need to go to the clinic?.
But I do.
The 5 elements
counteract one another!.
Water breeds wood, wood fire, fire earth...
You must be an Earth magician.
I'm here for Prof Kang.
You shouldn't be here.
Why do you want others' magic?.
Since you're here,
Iend me your magic.
Be cooperative.
Sorry!.
hurry...hurry...hurry...
Macy sleeps like a log!.
Macy wake up!. Get up!.
What's all this noise?.
We must be late...hurry...
They keep calling!.
We must be late...
Where are you going?.
off to the game!.
Why are you so hot?. You got a fever?.
I don't think so!. Then get changed!.
You talked back to the coach last time.
If we're late, we're dead meat!.
up!.
How comes my magic is gone?.
Hold on!.
Why?.
Great!.
Macy, are you all right?.
Tell me, can I still trust them?.
I believe in them!.
You're very hot!. Are you ill?.
I'm fine.
I'm filled with energy!.
The game has started. Stop chatting!.
All right!. Keep it up!. Hold up!.
We have a chance!. Focus and spike!.
We've got the point...
We've got the point!. Keep it up.
Hey!. Watch out!.
Good shot!. Go for it point by point!.
Good shot!.
That's bad!.
Leave the ball!. It's going out of bounds!.
Don't go out of bounds!.
A spin with her pinkie?.
We won!. Coach!.
We've regained all our honors!.
Well done!.
Thank you, Coach!.
Macy, why were you so good today?.
I don't know...
Seems like if I focused,
I could will things.
That's incredible!.
That's incredible!. Can you do it now?.
Yeah!. No idea.
Try to take a pack of juice out!.
Go!. Go!.
This one!. This one!.
Wow!. It's real!.
Who wants it?.
Me!. Me!. Me!.
Me!. Here!.
Here!.
Me!. Me!. Me!.
Shit!. All wet!.
What a hassle!.
No hassle!. We'll be rich!.
What do you mean we'll be rich?.
We can use magic to earn money!.
Good idea!.
How do we earn money?.
Set up a club to help people win games!.
Good!. I think I can handle that!.
Let's think of a name first!.
Something simple.
Let's call it victory Club"!.
Good!.
victory!.
How about that?.
That's great!. You deserve an award!.
Press there and see what happens!.
Hurry up!.
You have to press here to enter first
Then hit whatever they want you to hit.
Then we get our money here!.
We'll be rich!.
of course!.
We have business!.
So quick?.
A bowling game.
oK?.
What do you think?. of course!.
Really!. Count on you!.
No need to look.
The trophy is yours for sure!.
Really?.
Imagine there's a kind of magic
that allows you to live
without making a living,
achieve excellent results without studying,
and do the impossible in just one click.
Effortlessly you can do everything.
Stay at home all day long and do nothing
Apparently that will be a perfect.
Your life will become easy,
admirable and outstanding.
Get rid of the unwanted,
Ieave the uninterested undone.
But as the days slip away
you will realize what you need is very simple
A bicker with your lover
or an attempt to spend
all the savings at one sweep.
So-called "magic"...
wipes out the joys of life.
Happiness and youthfulness...
are short-lived.
Doesn't matter anyway.
Let's make a time of it!.
You'd be fascinated by this magic for sure.
Become slim and pretty no matter
how much you eat
cast a spell to date
whoever you have a crush on
and have unlimited amounts of money to spend.
Such magic should
be called "reap without sowing"
making your entire life easy and comfortable
yet indolent and ignorant
You get the results, but not the happiness.
Happiness and youthfulness...
are short-lived.
Doesn't matter anyway.
Let's make a time of it!.
Let's see if they're pretty!.
What is it?.
We received lots of "victory" requests.
It's record breaking!.
Quiet!.
Listen to my financial report first!.
our business has been booming.
our account has reached 5 figures!.
We should donate everything to charities!.
Sure!. After deducting all operational costs.
Transportation fee,
Accommodation fee, Diet costs
Conversation fee,
Entertainment expenses, Shopping fee...
Agreed!.
Thanks, Macy!.
Energy transfer.
What will you eat today?.
What should I eat?.
urgent matter to discuss in volleyball court.
Prof Kang?.
Why does Prof Kang wanna see you?.
Beats me!.
Hurry up!.
Bye!. Bye!.
Can you see me?.
Can anyone see me?.
Please answer me!.
Wait...show you something!.
Look!. ok, wait.
Here!.
Is it fun?.
I want to try. Is it oK?.
Prof Kang!.
Why did you bump against me, Prof Kang?.
I wanna get my magic back.
What magic?.
What are you talking about?.
Don't play dumb!.
After you bumped into me last time,
my magic was transferred to you.
It's fair that I get my magic...
back the same way!.
You mean this kind of magic?.
Give me back my magic!.
Can you prove it's yours?.
That means you can't!.
The magic is inside me.
It's mine!.
Bye!.
Help me up!.
I can't get up on my own.
You're in my way!. Scram if you're not buying!.
You can see me?.
of course, I can!. Think I'm blind?.
You must help me!.
Calm down!.
You want money?.
Nobody can see me but you!.
Please help me.
You're cute
but your pick-up line is lame,
though it's still quite original!.
Are you practicing your monologues?.
Good that you're here.
He needs help. Can you help him?.
You're good acting with the air!.
The air?. I meant him!.
You're good!. Keep up with it!.
Nobody can see me
but you.
Please help me!.
They can't see you?.
Don't come near!.
Are you a magician?.
I didn't mean it!.
I can see nothing. Scram!.
Hey, I'm a man!.
What happened?. You look like shit!.
I saw nothing but crazy people today!.
People I shouldn't have seen!.
What an unlucky day!.
Who's in charge of victory Club?.
You've got the wrong address.
I brought presents. one for everyone!.
Wow!. Padpad!.
Please come in!.
Want something to drink, cutie?.
Anything is fine!.
Good!.
Hello!. Hello!.
Who let you in?.
They did.
Why do you keep bothering me?.
I want your help.
I want your help too!.
Cut your attitude. He's a vlP!.
Come over
Welcome our vlP!. Come over and sit down
Actually, what can we help you?.
very simple.
I wanna win decathlon
this year.
Decathlon!.
What am ambitious goal!.
In fact...
I really need your help!.
I won't help you!. just leave me alone!.
In fact,
both my parents are athletes.
I just wanna win the event
on their behalf!.
This is to show you how sincere I am.
We'll help!.
We'll definitely help you!.
What's with you, Macy?.
He's a vlP!.
Look at the figures!.
Definitely first priority!.
I wasn't talking to him!.
Fatso, don't worry. I'll definitely help you!.
You!. Scram!.
Don't mind her!.
She got the worst temper!.
Yes, don't mind her.
We'll help you. You'll win for sure!.
Thank you... just go home and rest.
Go!. Go!.
You shouldn't use your magic for profit!.
None of your business!.
We're both magicians!.
Why not help me?.
If you're a magician, why you need my help?.
I really don't know why I lost my magic!.
Don't push me!.
I won't give up. You will see me again!.
You didn't tell me
how I could win the race.
just relax and charge ahead.
That's it?.
That's it!.
I'll take care of the rest.
Go!.
on your mark!.
Get set!.
Congratulations!.
Yes!. Yes!.
Mom and Dad!. I did it!. Yeah!.
Pegasus athlete throws
the javelin out of the arena.
Breaks world record!.
Great!.
Long jump heat.
Pegasus just breaks the world record again!.
Long jump finals
What are you doing?.
What's wrong with you?.
It's decathlon. I've just lost one event!.
If you don't help me,
I won't let you help him.
Winning 9 events is good enough.
Stop messing around!. Scram!.
Don't mess up again!.
I have to win high jump later!.
If you don't help me, he will lose for sure!.
What's wrong?. I got through!.
Disqualified!.
You... What's going on?.
I lost again!.
You should have told me you couldn't do it!.
If I lose again, I won't pay you.
Don't worry!. There are 8 more events!.
Are you leaving or not?.
Will you help me?.
You wanna play?. I'll fight you!.
What...again?.
In front as well?.
Hey...what's wrong?.
Shit!.
Fatso is badmouthing victory Club!.
our failure today...
has jeopardized our name.
That's oK!. Macy has tried her best already!.
Next time, I will win for sure!.
Why don't you take a rest?.
You're exhausted.
How about this.
You brainstorm how to get more business.
I'll make supper.
Will call you when it's ready.
So generous of you!. Hurry up!.
Let's go!.
How can we cheer Fatso up?.
Give his presents back.
But I love my padpad!.
We can give you to him!.
Me?.
I should send you there to pamper him!.
It'd be better you go!.
Macy Cheng...
I'm back!.
You again!.
Haven't you done enough damage?.
Macy, are you all right?.
I'm fine!.
I don't wanna harm you. I need your help!.
oK!. I'll help you!.
Really?.
Yes!.
I'll help you crush your bones!.
Macy!.
Go!. Hurry!.
Hurry!. Go!.
Go!. Hurry up!.
Go!.
What's the matter, Macy?.
Blowing off steam?.
Are you all right, Macy?.
Her scream was so scary!.
It's oK!.
Don't be scared by everything!.
Let's go in and see.
Is it a good idea?.
We're just going back to our room.
Macy!.
What happened, Macy?.
I'm oK!.
Please clear the room. I need to step out!.
We better come back later!.
Yes!. We better go now.
Help!. Prof Kang...
What's happened to me?.
Please help me!.
I bumped into you; you refused to help me up.
Now you dare to see me with a covered face!.
Are you too ashamed of yourself?.
That's your payback for abusing magic!.
Help me first!.
I don't wanna looK like this.
I can help you with a condition.
As long as I can be normal again,
I'll do whatever you say.
You'll obey my orders and report to me.
And you'll come whenever I summon you.
Anytime!.
I'll do anything to become normal again!.
oK, deal!.
Come.
Follow me!.
Exhale...
Inhale...
Magic is controlled by will power.
That's why it drains your energy.
Lack of control or abuse...
will harm your body!.
Let's practice how to control it.
Relax!.
Now look at the mirror.
oK.
Magic is fantastic,
but it's also dangerous.
I advise you not to use magic again.
Prof Kang, don't you want your magic back?.
If I'm destined to lose my magic to you,
what else can I say?.
I hope you can help others with magic.
You know, helping others is helping yourself.
Even an ordinary person likes to help others,
Iet alone someone...
with superpower like you. oK, oK!.
Stop pestering me!. I'll help others!.
What?. You think I'm a pest?.
So you're playing me?.
Such an ingrate!.
You're so tenacious.
You even followed me here?.
Sorry.
I just wanna make sure you're better.
Since you're oK,
I won't bother you anymore.
Bye!.
Hey, where are you going?.
I don't know.
oK, I'll help you.
Please don't bother again tomorrow.
Come!. Let's go!.
What's your name?.
I don't remember.
Then why did you come to this university?.
I really don't remember.
I can't help you if you remember nothing.
I remember there's something important.
That's why I'm here!.
You're so contradictory.
It's hard to help you.
I really can't remember.
Why don't you read my mind?.
Read your mind?.
Yes. Aren't you a magician?.
Yes, I am.
Hey, what are you doing?.
Reading your mind.
You're so lousy!.
You don't read minds there!. It's here!.
So you think you're so smart?.
Haven't you forgotten everything?.
I see visuals.
You were in the library before?.
Sounds familiar.
But why was I there?.
I see some electric towers.
There're plants and flowers.
Are you a florist?.
Flowers?.
What else do you see?.
Write them down
and take me there!.
What?. Are you serious?.
Hurry up!.
So hot!. It's oK to forget things.
I do that all the time.
Hey!. Looks like it's ahead of us!.
Does it ring a bell over there?.
I saw this plate when I was reading your mind!.
Are these flowers?. So weird?.
Don't touch.
This flower is very fragile.
I never saw these flowers before!.
Is it a rare species?.
Is this your home?.
It's quite pretty!.
So your name is Ling Feng!.
An ecologist!.
oh, the computer is still on.
Do you remember your password?.
Are you an ecologist...
or an astronomer?.
That's our school's logo!.
What's the one beside it?.
I have no recollection.
Don't be sad. Let's take a picture first.
What's the matter with you?.
I decompose when in contact with electricity.
So you're afraid of electricity.
Did it hurt?.
It hurts every time I decompose.
Be careful!.
Look!. I couldn't take your picture!.
Hey, it's someone calling me!.
Go answer it far away from here!.
So you want me to go?.
oK!.
I'll go!.
Now that I've brought you here, we're quits.
Let's not meet again!.
Where are you?. It's so late!.
Go back in!. Leave it to me here!.
Don't just mind the flowers.
Mind yourself too!.
If there're no more plants on Earth,
men won't have enough oxygen to survive.
Do you want this world to be over?.
If you don't recover
and always need my help,
then I'll be over instead!.
30 years from now, this world...
will require twice
the resources of Earth to survive!.
Enough!.
I'm so tired!. I need to sleep!.
Shit!. I'm late!.
These are books about magic.
Study them first.
I'll explain to you later.
How can I read so many of them?.
So you think it's easy to be a magician?.
Any questions?. Feel free to ask me now.
How many magicians...
...are there in the world?.
So-called magic, voodoo, or superpower
actually refers to an inexplicable power.
It's inherently the same.
I've no idea how many magicians...
there are,
but I'm sure you're not the only one!.
Who can...
...have superpower?.
Every common person
can have superpower.
Take you for instance,
It takes a big illness or an accident
that causes physical or emotional trauma
to stimulate your brain cells to expand
and absorb tremendous energy.
It's still unknown...
...how the power is absorbed.
If one's magic is lost,
how can one get it back?.
I wanna know that too.
Do you know what this symbol means?.
It's only a magical stratagem.
Taoists use spells,
witches use brooms,
Harry Porter uses his magic wand,
and some people use magical stratagems.
They're just tools,
same as using your hands.
How did you get this picture?.
I took it in Ling Feng's studio.
Ling Feng?. A man?.
How did you meet him?. And where?.
Does he have bad habits?.
Easy!.
That's a picture we took together.
Are you kidding?. Together?.
It's just you.
It's true!.
He said he's a magician who lost his magic.
He wants my help
but don't know what.
He said I saw him because I'm a magician.
It's true!. I'm not pulling you leg!.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?.
It takes...
...a lot of energy to decompose the body.
If someone can do it,
he must be incredible.
Ling Feng!. You've come!.
I'm Gu Xinyue,
a Wood magician.
I knew you would lose your memory.
Have you read my novel?.
I put all my predictions there!.
I know you won't believe me.
just start with the first 25 pages.
You're Ling Feng, an Earth magician.
You believe me now?.
Freaking out?.
Listen up.
There's one Fire magician.
When he amasses all 5 elements,
he'll have the energy to go back to the past.
I don't know why he want to do.
If he changes the past,
the present is warped.
All hell will break loose.
I gave you a magic stone before.
It's because you were wearing that stone
which manifested its power
when you met the Fire magician
that your life could be spared.
That's why you can still come here today.
Watch the visuals.
Remember.
Your goal...
...is to look for Prof Kang
and that blond magician Charlie!.
only when you guys...
pull your power together
can this disaster be averted!.
Life is important to everyone.
In a magician's world,
his hands are more important than his life!.
But your hands are as important...
...to me!.
Let's go!. Showtime!.
Who are you?.
I'm here to help you finish your magic show.
What do you want?.
Take it easy.
I know you're a Metal magician.
A magic show without the use of magic.
Lend me your magic.
We help each other.
Fair enough!.
Don't disappoint my audience!.
It will be absolutely spectacular!.
Let's start!.
What's next?.
just watch!.
And then?.
Pull out your knife!.
If the audience knows the secret of the magic,
They'll be even happier!.
The show is about to end!.
Buddy, who are you?.
Hello, Prof Kang.
I'm a Fire magician.
Lend me your magic.
What happened?.
What happened to your magic?.
What magic?.
Know how long I've waited for today?.
You're telling me you don't have magic?.
I really don't.
What happened to your magic?.
I don't know.
I found it!.
Run!.
So you got his magic!.
Prof Kang!. Prof Kang!.
Wake up!.
Wake up!. Prof Kang!.
Macy!.
Coach Liu?.
Are you all right?.
Watch out!.
The guy who hurt me may come back!.
Prof Kang!. Don't worry. I'm here to help.
Aren't you a magician?.
Why can't you see me?.
There's nobody.
You're too tired!.
Take care, Prof Kang.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Prof Kang!. Look at the blackboard!.
Don't be scared!. He's a friend.
He's just transparent.
You see him?.
I can't, but I know.
You're Ling Feng.
Macy mentioned you.
A magician kidnapped her. Let's rescue her.
I'm going too.
Don't!. It's very dangerous!.
Macy is my student too!.
Then put down your stuff first!.
What a big bottle of wine!.
Wine...
a big bottle of wine...
I've found Macy!. over there!.
Let's go rescue her right away.
There's an electric net.
What should we do?.
Don't let him amass all 5 elements!.
Stop him!. Hurry!.
1, 2, 3!.
My magic is back!.
He's absorbed all the energy.
Don't let him drop the coin in!.
or else the time portal will open!.
Stop fighting!.
You're fire!. I'm water!. You can't beat me!.
Stop,
or you'll die!.
Why do you have to go back to the past?.
Shit!.
We failed to stop him after all!.
We're dead!.
You'll only see...
...the images of the past.
Men cannot change the past.
Even with magic,
we can't do that.
I can give up my magic...
for my family.
The horse is out of service.
Come back!.
Keep the coin. Let's play next time.
Mommy!.
Where's mom?.
Hubby!.
Mommy!.
The past...
...is just memories.
We got no choice.
We pay our parents...
back by living happily.
our life is here and now.
Happy or not, we definitely have a choice.
I hope you won't make the wrong choice.
Take back Ling Feng's magic stone!.
or he'll be helpless.
Hey!. Come help me!. Hurry up!.
Are you serious?.
Get me out right away!.
How do I get you out?.
just give me a piece of cloth!.
What's the use of a piece of cloth?.
To help me get out!.
I know!. It's magic!.
It's very dangerous!. Leave now!.
Shit!. Too late!.
Get something to stop up!.
Help me!.
Ling Feng!. Wake up!.
Wake up!. Wake up!.
You're awake!.
Are you ok?.
I'm fine.
He's angry!.
Come on!. Pegasus!. Come on!.
Fighting!.
Fighting!. Fighting!. Fighting!.
Yes!.
Who's using magic?.
In his book, Gu predicts that.
the ball will be out of bounds.
I'm just helping them.
Prediction?.
Any of you believe that?.
They play quite well!.
They should win!.
No need to guess!.
just put the ball in the court and that's it!.
They're playing well with their own skills.
You guys don't need to interfere.
Even if they lose this point,
they'll strive to win it back.
It's oK!.
Yeah!. victory!.
We won!.
We're doomed this time!.
Coach!.
Coach...
Well done!.
You really have
the Midas touch!.
I'd like to hire you...
as our university's coach.
She's no longer a coach.
She's our vice principal.
vice principal!.
Welcome back!.
Thanks for your trust, Principal.
But I don't want to be the vice principal.
What do you want then?.
I only want to be their coach.
Coach!.
Then I'll be the vice principal!. oK?.
I approve!.
We approve too!.
Everyone approves, and so do I!.
You need my help again?.
No!.
But I never expected
you could play so well without magic!.
of course!.
Pass me your cell.
My cell?. What for?.
just give it to me!.
Take a picture.
A picture?.
A picture together?.
Good!.
1, 2, 3.
You're quite photogenic!.
ok?. I want a picture too!.
A picture together. Good!.
Come!.
YEAH!.