NARRATOR: Missing in action.
Anakin Skywalker's heroic droid navigator,
R2-D2, was lost in battle.
When a desperate search
fails to locate Artoo,
Anakin is forced to take on
a new navigator, R3-S6.
Now, the Jedi embark
on a dangerous new mission
to find a secret enemy listening post.
Meanwhile, R2-D2 has fallen
into the hands of a vile droid smuggler
and is on his way to General Grievous,
who will surely plunder the
Republic secrets hidden within him.
I am entering your orbit now, General.
I will be at your station shortly.
And, General...
What is it, Gha Nachkt?
I prefer to get my reward in cash.
(GROANS)
(CHUCKLING)
We've searched their supply grid, sir.
There is nothing to indicate
the presence of an enemy outpost.
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Huh?
Master, I'm receiving
a strange transmission.
I can't seem to make it out, though.
(STATIC WARBLING)
Boost the volume, Goldie.
(LOUD WARBLING)
No, you're losing it.
(WARBLING)
-That's Artoo.
-Uh, that doesn't sound like Artoo.
It's him. I could never forget that voice.
-Trace it, Rex.
-Sir.
What is going on here?
(BEEPING)
(STATIC WARBLING)
You sneaky little scrap pile.
(ZAPPING)
(SQUEALS)
You'd better be worth all this trouble.
(R2-D2 BEEPS MOURNFULLY)
(CHUCKLING)
Master, our orders were to find
the Separatist listening post.
Perhaps Artoo is at the listening post.
Did you consider that?
We have a lock on the droid's location, sir.
-Prepare to jump to those coordinates.
-Yes, sir.
(TWILIGHT POWERING UP)
Hold on, Artoo, old buddy. We're coming.
GRIEVOUS: What is it, Gha Nachkt?
I've arrived. Could you lower your shields?
(GRUNTING)
(ZAPPING)
Keep moving, grease spot.
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(STARTLED BEEP)
(GRUNTS)
This is the droid
those Jedi came looking for, General.
What secrets do you carry,
my little friend?
(BEEPS DEFIANTLY)
So defiant.
No need for fear, we're all droids here.
(LAUGHS)
Rip this little rat apart
and find out everything he knows.
(GROANS)
Right away, General.
(R2-D2 BEEPS IN PANIC)
Sir, the last transmission came
from that moon's upper atmosphere,
directly ahead.
That's a Separatist battlesphere.
I'm picking up a lot of encrypted chatter.
Contact Obi-Wan.
Stubby, scramble secret code set 1-4-7-7.
I don't want that station to pick this up.
-Anakin.
-Master, I believe we've found
your Separatist listening post.
Excellent work. Back off and wait.
I'll send two mainline cruisers
to help you destroy it.
But Artoo...
We believe my droid, Artoo, is onboard.
He's the one that led us here.
Hmm.
This complicates things.
You must sneak aboard that station
and destroy it
before they crack Artoo's memory banks.
I know you're fond of that droid,
but he's fallen into enemy hands.
I could rescue Artoo.
No, this is not a rescue mission.
Keep jamming their scanners.
If they spot us, we're dead.
We're bringing the droid?
We'll need Goldie to open secured hatches
and access the station's computer for us.
Oh, and, Rex, you get to carry him.
(BEEPING CHEERFULLY)
(DISDAINFULLY) That's just great.
Follow me, boys!
Take this upstairs
and be sure not to drop it.
Whoa! Ow!
Those 631 's are not
the brightest lights on the ship.
Next time,
you're lugging this astromech around.
(CHUCKLING)
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(SCRAPING)
All this moisture
is corroding my servo-motors.
Go up to level 8. Get your head adjusted.
-It feels great.
-That'll feel...
(EXCLAIMS)
What the...
All right, Stubby, get to work.
REX: We are here.
The reactors are 30 levels below us, there.
Ahsoka, you take the squad
and blow up those reactors.
Gravity will do the rest.
We'll meet in the landing bay.
-Where are you going?
-I'm just gonna have a little look around.
I hope you find Artoo in one piece.
(BLEEPING)
This is... This is... General Grievous!
What is it?
It appears this droid's mission memory
has never been erased.
It contains every Republic formation
and strategy they have.
Good work.
You certainly earned your fee this time.
More than my fee.
This droid is worth more, I get paid more.
Now I suggest...
(GROANS)
(GRIEVOUS LAUGHING)
There's your bonus.
Report, Agent R3.
(BEEPING)
The Jedi are here?
Delay them until I arrive.
(BEEPING)
Goldie, where are you?
Sound the alarm.
What are you doing back here? Come on!
Now we will transfer
all your secrets to me.
(WHIRRING)
Don't worry.
I won't let anything happen to you.
(WHIRRING)
Republic troops have infiltrated the base.
Keep this droid secured.
(BEEPING IN RESPONSE)
I will deal with the Jedi myself.
(BEEPS WEAKLY)
We found the reactor room, sir.
The alarm triggered another security door.
Ray shielded.
-This could take a while to bypass.
-Good luck with that.
Go ahead, Goldie, make me proud.
Hope this will be good.
(BEEPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Those droids are getting close, sir.
You think R3 is gonna open up
that door any time soon?
He's working on it. Patience, Captain.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
-DENAL: I can always hot-wire it, sir.
-Hurry up, Goldie.
I think we've run out of time.
Blast them!
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
Rex, droid-poppers, now!
REX: Droid-poppers!
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
(SIZZLING)
Take the captured R2 unit to my ship.
They sent a child to destroy my station?
The Republic must be running out of Jedi.
You must be General Grievous.
(LAUGHING)
(COUGHING)
He's just another tinny, boys.
Let's scrap him like the rest.
(LIGHTSABERS WHOOSHING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Sorry to interrupt your playtime, Grumpy,
but wouldn't you prefer a challenge?
That wouldn't be you.
(GRUNTS)
(R3 BEEPS)
All units stay on high alert.
Watch out for a second Jedi
loose in the station.
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
Artoo!
Hang on, Artoo!
(R2-D2 BEEPS)
Where is the fight
you promised me, youngling?
(COMLINK BEEPS)
Ahsoka, it's me, Rex.
There are only two of us left.
-Should we abort the mission?
-No. Complete the mission.
Set the charges
and rendezvous at the landing bay.
-REX: But, sir...
-That's an order, Rex.
I'll keep the General busy. Ahsoka out.
She's distracting Grievous.
Come on, we've still got a job to do.
Come here, child. I'm looking for you.
So far, you have failed to impress me.
Goldie! Over here!
(BEEPING)
Goldie, no!
(GASPS)
REX: Ahsoka, we're in the reactor room.
Your friends won't help you.
You're stuck with me.
(BEEPING)
You have something that belongs to me.
(BEEPS)
Thanks, Artoo.
(BEEPS WEARILY)
It's great to see you, too, buddy.
You don't look so good. You okay?
(BEEPS IN AFFIRMATION)
(COMLINK BEEPING)
Rex. Rex, can you hear me?
R3. R3, is that you?
I've got Artoo.
I'll meet you back at the landing bay.
(BEEPS INQUISITIVELY)
R3?
Yeah, I had to get a replacement droid.
Look, sorry, Artoo.
(BEEPS ENVIOUSLY)
It was Obi-Wan's idea.
Look, we'll talk about this later.
Twilight, this is Skywalker.
Rendezvous at the south landing bay
immediately for evacuation.
Acknowledged, General. I'm on my way.
R3, what have you to report?
(BEEPING)
That stubby little backstabber.
So, Skywalker has come for his R2 unit.
(LAUGHING)
Go and make certain they do not escape.
Great, there's the Twilight.
Now, where's everyone else?
Sir.
(R3-S6 BEEPING)
ANAKIN: Hey, Stubby, where's Ahsoka?
REX: General Skywalker!
Explosives are in place, sir.
Objective completed.
-Where is Ahsoka?
-She engaged General Grievous.
Alone?
She distracted him
while we completed the mission.
It was on her orders, sir.
The droid was with her.
-We've gotta find her.
-I can take you to her, sir.
What is the matter with you?
Are you trying to get us killed?
(BEEPS)
REX: I've got a bad feeling about this, sir.
That double-crossing droid is a spy.
(BEEPS)
(GRIEVOUS GROWLS)
(AHSOKA GRUNTING)
Another lightsaber
to add to my collection.
My spy droid, R3,
has trapped your precious master.
When I've finished with you, he's next.
You're wrong. He's gone by now,
and he's gonna blow up
your precious spy station.
Not this time.
(FIRING)
-Captain, trigger the explosives!
-But, sir, we're still in the station.
-You just let me worry about the details.
-Sir, yes, sir.
(BEEPS)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(ROARS)
Artoo, I need you
to get the hangar door open.
See if there are any controls
in the outer platform.
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(POWERING DOWN)
So, what did I miss?
Oh, the usual.
It was foolish of you
to take on Grievous by yourself.
Well, I was leading the mission, and
it seemed like a good idea at the time.
Did he tell you your stubby
little gold droid pal works for him?
He might have mentioned it.
I guess we were all fooled.
General Skywalker,
there are fuel cells over here!
Get ready, Rex.
-Artoo did it.
-Of course he did it.
Now, let's get out of here.
(WHIRRING)
Artoo, where are you?
(EXPLOSIONS)
(BEEPING)
(SQUEAKS)
REX: General Skywalker's gotten
into his fighter. Where's he going?
He's going after Artoo.
I'll be right back. Don't wait for me.
(BEEPING)
(R3-S6 BEEPS)
(R3-S6 SCREAMS)
ANAKIN: Come on, Artoo.
(R2-D2 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
So let me get this straight, Anakin.
You risked the mission, all your men,
even your Padawan, to save a droid?
(R2-D2 BEEPS IN AFFIRMATION)
Artoo found the listening post,
and he saved our lives.
We couldn't just leave him there, Obi-Wan.
(SIGHS) Anakin, one day...
I'm glad we got Artoo back, Master,
but Obi-Wan does have a point.
Ahsoka, I knew
you would complete the mission.
Besides, Artoo is more than a droid.
He's a friend.
(R2-D2 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
English - SDH