ANNOUNCER: A galaxy divided by war.
Peaceful worlds must choose sides
or face the threat of invasion.
Republic and Separatist armies vie
for the allegiance of neutral planets.
Desperate to build a Republic supply base
in the system of Toydaria,
Jedi Master Yoda travels to secret
negotiations on a remote neutral moon.
GUARD: We are getting no signal
from the Republic, Your Highness.
KATUUNKO: I don't see anything.
It is not like the Jedi to be late.
VENTRESS: Greetings, King Katuunko.
-Who are you?
-I am only a messenger, Majesty.
My master wishes to speak with you.
Katuunko, great king of Toydaria,
forgive my intrusion.
Count Dooku.
I am aware Master Yoda hopes
you will allow the Jedi
to build a Republic base in your system
in exchange for protection, correct?
Your spies serve you well, Count.
I ask, how can the Jedi protect you
if they cannot protect themselves?
Toydarian Royal Delegation,
this is the Republic Envoy. Please respond.
General, the Toydarians' beacon
is active on the moon,
but all our transmissions
are being jammed.
Hmm.
(ALARM BEEPING)
DROID CAPTAIN:
We caught them by surprise, all right.
CLONE: We're losing our shields!
Too late it is. Sprung is the trap.
-I must get you to safety, General.
-Retreat you must.
On the moon below is my mission.
There I must go.
I suppose you and your droid armies
can do better?
Without a doubt.
I sense you are one
who respects strength, Your Highness.
Our droid armies outnumber
the Republic clones 100 to one.
Perhaps,
but I have heard that a single Jedi
equals 100 battle droids.
Quickly, now.
Reach the planet's surface we must.
In an escape pod, sir?
The enemy will fire at anything we launch.
Then launch all of them you will. Hmm?
Master Yoda's powers
have been greatly exaggerated.
That remains to be seen, Count.
Indeed. When you decide to join us,
my apprentice will contact me.
Hang on. Almost...
-What a terrible shot.
-Oh, well, it's my programming.
That was a close one!
General, I think we're out of range.
I agree, but entering another trap we are.
-Are you sure?
-A disturbance in the Force there is.
My lord, Master Yoda's warship
has fled the system.
What further evidence do you require
of the Jedi's weakness?
(DEVICE BEEPING)
This is King Katuunko. Speak.
Master Yoda would like
to talk with you, sir.
A pleasure it is to hear your voice,
Your Highness.
Master Yoda of the Jedi Council this is.
Master Jedi, I thought perhaps
Count Dooku had frightened you off.
Delayed have I been,
but not too far away am I now.
Unaware I was
Count Dooku was invited to our meeting.
The Count invited himself.
He assures me that, in this time of war,
his droids can offer my world
greater security than your Jedi.
Hmm. A matter of debate that is.
Your Majesty might prefer
more than words.
What do you have in mind?
lf Yoda is indeed
the Jedi warrior you believe he is,
let him prove it.
Allow me to send my best troops
to capture him.
lf he escapes, join the Republic.
But should my droids defeat Yoda,
consider an alliance with the Separatists.
I did not request Yoda's presence here
to test him in battle.
Accept the challenge I do, Your Highness.
Arrive by nightfall I will.
Master Yoda must be given a fair fight.
My dear King Katuunko,
I would have it no other way.
Beautiful this moon is, hmm?
Amazing the universe is.
There's gotta be a full battalion in there.
Probably packing armor, too.
(GUN CHARGING)
We'll have something for them.
l am deploying my forces, Master.
Yoda has made a grave mistake
straying this far from Coruscant.
l will see the Jedi gets his "fair fight."
Carry only what you need.
Too much weight, slow you down it will.
Destroy Ventress your weapons will not.
Come, come, Lieutenant. Hurry we must.
Sir, the rendezvous point is that way.
As is our enemy.
To reach our goal,
a straight path we will not follow.
Let's move it, boys!
Find Master Yoda.
Uh... What does he look like?
He'll be the small, shriveled green one
with the lightsaber!
Small, huh? Don't worry, Supreme Leader,
we'll take care of him.
I think I see them.
They're hiding deep in the trees.
Fire on Sector 11!
At ease be, my friends.
Within range we are not.
Uh... Hold it. Hold it.
I said hold it! Wait!
That's far enough! I mean it!
Stop! I said stop!
-We're too big to fit in there.
-No, we're not. Watch this.
-You were right.
-Next time, listen to orders!
Those tanks are too big to follow.
See? See? Size is not everything, hmm?
Smaller in number are we,
but larger in mind.
(LAUGHING)
CLONE 1: Do you have any idea
what the General is talking about?
CLONE 2: How should I know?
There's no figuring a Jedi Master.
DROID COMMANDER: Infantry, advance!
Go get them, boys!
Sir, there are two patrols
coming in on foot.
Now is the time
to face the enemy, Lieutenant.
Ambush them we will.
CLONE 1: We'll flank them from the south.
CLONE 2: Right. Let's move!
(LASER FIRES)
What was that?
Blast him!
Look! A little green life form!
You buckethead! That's the Jedi!
He is a little one! Blast him!
Split up by squad and spread out!
DROID 1: Roger, roger.
DROID 2: Roger, roger.
Okay, clankers, suck laser!
CLONE 1: Where's the General?
CLONE 2: I don't know. We got separated.
Clankers!
CLONE: Fall back!
There are too many of them!
He's around here somewhere.
Hey! Get off of me!
(YODA LAUGHING)
Don't move.
The Jedi destroyed our advance troops.
Ha! Master Yoda
is living up to my expectations.
Commander,
have you pinpointed the Jedi's location?
Affirmative.
The clones gave away their position.
Our heavy troops are moving
to engage them now.
(EXPLOSIONS)
CLONE 1: I hope the General reaches
the rendezvous point.
CLONE 2: We're sure buying him time.
(CLONE GROANS)
-Lieutenant, can you walk?
-I think I'm okay.
DROID: Die, Republic dogs.
What are we gonna do, sir?
Hmm.
-What's the General doing?
-Keep blasting!
DROID: Hey, what's going on?
Get out of the way! All of you!
I'm having a serious malfunction.
Don't shoot!
I’m on your side!
You found us just in time, sir.
Left behind no one will be.
(RATTLING)
Rollies, inbound!
Retreat! Cover you I will.
Republic troops are injured.
The Jedi is in full retreat, Supreme Leader.
Good. Pursue them without delay.
The contest is not over yet.
Master Yoda! I hear you're having trouble
with the Droid Army.
Trouble? I know nothing of this trouble.
Look forward to our meeting soon I do.
The Jedi won't elude me for long.
Are you sure we should go in there,
General? There's no way out.
Now rest we must.
CLONE 1: We're low on ammo, sir.
Only two grenades,
and one rocket for the launcher.
CLONE 2: Against a battalion?
Forget it. We've lost.
So certain of defeat are you?
With respect, General,
maybe you should go on.
Let us slow them down.
All around us
is that which we need to prevail. Yes.
Come. Sit. Your helmets, remove them.
Your faces I wish to see.
There's not much to look at here, sir.
We all share the same face.
Deceive you eyes can.
In the Force,
very different each one of you are.
Rys, always focused on the enemy are you.
For inspiration,
look to yourself and those beside you.
Jjeck, concerned about weapons you are.
Weapons do not win battles.
Your mind, powerful it is.
Outthink the droids you can.
Thire, rush not into fights. Long is the war.
Only by surviving it will you prevail. Yes.
Clones you may be,
but the Force resides in all life forms.
Use it you can to quiet your mind.
(RUMBLING)
Tanks. Is that the best
they can throw at us?
Yeah, but I've only got one shot left.
Greet them I will.
General, you don't plan to take
that whole column by yourself?
(LAUGHS)
Have you three I do.
Outnumbered are they.
Know the time to help me you will.
It's the Jedi! Block his escape!
Prepare to fire!
Supreme Leader, we've found the Jedi.
-Excellent. Where is he?
-He's just sitting here in front of our tanks.
Shoot him! Shoot him now!
Quickly! Ready, aim, fire!
Fire!
DROID COMMANDER:
He's going under the tank!
Oh, no!
Run for it!
But I just got promoted!
CLONE: It doesn't look like
the General needs help to me.
(BEEPING)
We've got him in our sights!
(DROID SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
That's a lot of smoke for a surrender.
Report. What's going on over there?
224, come in!
Where is 224?
Destroyed, Supreme Leader.
The Jedi has overrun our position and...
(SCREAMS)
l think perhaps all those stories
about the Jedi are true.
The fight isn't over yet, Majesty.
(BEEPS)
CLONE: The General's cutting them up.
(ALL LAUGHING)
We got trouble.
The clankers sent reinforcements.
The General's too busy with that tank.
He won't see them coming.
I think I know how to deal with them.
-Yeah!
-Great shot, sir!
-That's giving it to the clankers!
YODA: Hmm.
Learned something today,
have you, Lieutenant, hmm?
l think we all did, General.
Come, behind schedule are we.
Not polite to be late.
You were right, Count Dooku.
One Jedi is not worth 100 battle droids.
More like 1,000!
I’m sorry,
but I will be joining the Republic.
I urge you to reconsider, wise king.
I promise you won't regret it.
Your agent also promised me
Yoda would get a fair fight.
I will not deal with those
who break their words.
So be it.
Perhaps our negotiations
will more fruitful with your successor.
Ventress! Kill him!
(VENTRESS GRUNTING)
Jedi Master Yoda.
I am very pleased to meet you at last.
Share the feeling I do, King Katuunko.
Failed you Ventress has, Count.
I don't fear you, Jedi.
Strong you are with the dark side,
young one,
but not that strong.
Still much to learn you have.
Surrender you should.
(EXPLOSION)
Hmm.
In the end, cowards are those
who follow the dark side.
It’s a pity I wasn't there in person,
my old master.
A pity indeed, my fallen apprentice.
Perhaps now begin negotiations we can.
That is not necessary, my friend.
You have my faith.
Toydaria would be honored
to host a Republic base.
My people are at your service.
Your Majesty, fail you we will not.
(RUMBLING)