Invasion!
The planet Cato Neimoidia
is under Separatist attack.
Anakin Skywalker
and his Padawan, Ashoka Tano,
rush to the rescue as they lead
a squadron of starfighters
to the planet below.
Ahsoka, punch a hole
for the gunships to get through.
I know the drill, Master.
Look out, incoming missiles.
No problem.
Uh...
slight problem.
Ahsoka, I've got buzz droids.
How bad did you get hit?
I'm all clear.
What?
You always have it easy, Snips.
Good job, R2.
Someday these droids will learn
they keep messing
with the wrong Jedi.
Looks like you're clear.
Just keep watching
and learning, Padawan.
Uh-oh.
You're trailing smoke.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing serious.
Just a small malfunction.
Ugh!
Master?
Master, come in.
R2, what's going on over there?
Unconscious?
Fly back to the cruiser.
What do you mean there's something wrong
with the engines?
Tip your wing.
I'll see how bad it is.
Oh, that's not good.
Let's just say now would be
a good time to land.
R2, can you land the ship
on that cliff ledge?
I don't care if the landing zone
is too short.
Get that ship on the ground.
R7, take over the ship.
I'm going after Anakin.
Somebody has to save his skin.
R2!
Ugh, very funny, R2.
Are you okay, Master?
Yeah, what'd I miss?
Oh, not much.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't I flying?
Where's my fighter?
How did I get here?
Fighter crashed.
I saved the day.
You're welcome.
Huh, all right.
Captain Rex,
Ahsoka and I need a little help.
Right away, sir.
Master Yoda.
Return to the Jedi Temple
quickly, you should,
you and your Padawan.
We're kind of busy, Master Yoda.
The reason we need you,
important it is, Skywalker.
Bombed the Temple hangar, someone has.
Your assistance to find
the terrorist, we need.
Who could successfully bomb
the Jedi Temple?
We'll be right there, Master.
How could the Separatists
infiltrate the Temple?
Worse than that it is.
What could be worse, Master Yoda?
Everything is on the table.
We have to look at the possibility
that it could've been anyone
in the Temple, even a Jedi.
If a Jedi this is,
gone to the dark side they have.
I...
I can't believe a Jedi
would attack a place this sacred.
We'd like for you two to lead
the investigation.
We can't trust anyone
who was here, even a Jedi.
You and Ahsoka will provide
an impartial point of view
free of assumptions.
We'll do everything we can.
Careful you must be, Skywalker.
If willing to destroy the Temple
the attacker is,
to great lengths they will go
to keep from being caught.
Then I guess we'll have to go
to even greater lengths
to catch him.
I can still hear the screams.
Do you believe what they said, Master,
that a Jedi could do this?
Not every Jedi agrees
with this war, Ahsoka.
There are many
political idealists among us.
But a traitor?
I'm afraid one can eventually
become the other.
Remember Count Dooku and General Krell.
That's how they started, too.
Only analysis and investigation
will prove what is true or not.
Who are you?
I am Russo-ISC,
Crime Scene Analyzer for the Jedi.
I will be working with you
and your Padawan on this case.
I was assigned by Master Windu.
Okay, Russo,
you and Ahsoka should
begin the interviews.
I would rather interview
the witnesses alone.
Why?
Many of the wounded have heard rumors
a Jedi was behind this explosion.
There will be ill will toward you.
I think you're overexaggerating, Russo.
There were Jedi killed in that blast
along with maintenance crew and clones.
Take Ahsoka with you.
Let me know if you find anything.
I will, Master.
Did you notice anything unusual
about the hangar?
Not really.
Although, I left the
hangar five minutes before
the bomb exploded.
Did everything seem okay before that?
Everything seemed normal.
Is it true a Jedi might be
responsible for the attack?
We're not certain of anything
at this point.
This distrust is troubling.
Some of these people have worked
in the Temple for years.
Fear makes even the most
trusting individual irrational.
I think I know who did it,
who blew up the hangar.
Who?
I believe it was Jackar Bowmani.
Jackar Bowmani.
Who is Jackar?
One of the maintenance crew
in the hangar.
Why do you think it was him?
I passed him as I was going
on my shift change.
He...
he had been working all morning
in the section the blast came from.
It was the last place I saw him.
Is this him?
Yes.
I need to know, have you
seen him since the explosion?
No.
Truthfully, I didn't see much
of anything after the explosion.
Thank you.
Looks like we need to find
Jackar Bowmani, Russo.
Did you find anything?
No, but the rumor about it
being a Jedi is growing, Ahsoka.
I can feel the anger and confusion
throughout the Jedi Temple.
Russo and I have a lead.
We are looking for one of the
Temple workers, Jackar Bowmani.
One of the witnesses saw him in the area
where the bomb exploded
right before it happened,
and we have not been able
to find him anywhere.
Come on.
Nobody just disappears.
Unless it was well planned out.
Well, it had to be well
planned out to get past Jedi.
I'll talk to security.
No more clones.
Stop the violence.
End the war.
They're all family and friends?
Yes, looking for answers.
So am I, Cin.
This is the guy who might be
behind all of this.
If you see him, alert me immediately.
That is Jackar.
You know this man?
He is my husband.
I've been trying to reach him
since I heard of an explosion.
Where is he?
I need you to come with me.
You have no idea where Jackar is?
No.
You are a Jedi, and you cannot find him?
I understand your frustration.
Don't.
Just find Jackar.
Letta, do you think Jackar
could do something like this,
blow up the Temple?
Do you have any idea
what someone has to go through
to work in the Jedi Temple, hm?
Jackar dedicated his life
to serving the Jedi.
It had been his dream.
Not just anyone can walk into
your precious Temple.
He passed all the entry tests
that were needed.
Okay, I had to ask.
Unfortunately, everyone's a suspect.
Jackar would never do anything
like this.
Please, find him.
Hmm...
based on the trajectory of the debris,
it seems the blast came from there.
Why is there no bomb residue?
So you think whoever did this
triggered a ship to explode?
We think so.
Russo's trying to use the
shrapnel to determine that now.
The witness says he saw Jackar
in the area.
Maybe Jackar planned to do this
and just kept quiet.
Or...
It actually was a Jedi.
I found something, an anomaly,
something that should not be here.
These pieces came from the blast origin.
They are covered with microscopic droids
of a highly volatile nature.
Nano-droids.
Yes, nano-droids.
Great.
Now we're chasing nano-droids.
Russo, go through security footage.
Try to see if Jackar went
to other parts of the Temple.
Ahsoka, let's go find out
how Jackar got his hands
on these nano-droids.
Bowmani's file, Master Jedi.
He's a munitions expert.
Jackar was the foreman over
all of the gunships,
bombs, and weapons.
His specialty was nano-weaponry.
We've got to find this guy.
Isn't that going a little
too fast for you
to make sense out of it?
It is simple data.
At this pace, I am able to view
hundreds of hours of footage.
Have you found Jackar?
No.
I'll gather some Jedi
and search the Temple.
If he's still here, he might be
planning another attack.
Instead of Jedi,
I have droids
that can do the job much faster.
So you've found nothing so far?
We have a clue we're following.
But we still don't have answers.
It is imperative
that the truth be found soon.
There are whispers
the Senate will have a meeting
to decide whether the military police
will need to become involved
in the investigation.
They can't do that.
Clones died in that explosion,
maintenance clones working
on the gunships
as well as civilians.
The Senate tends to take notice
of these things
no matter where they happen.
Master Skywalker, we have found Jackar.
Lock down all exits so he can't escape.
Where is he?
Well, part of him is here.
I don't think now
is a good time to joke.
This is all that remains of Jackar.
His hand?
The rest of him exploded.
Because he was so close to the bomb?
Because he was the bomb.
What's this?
The connection we were looking for
to the explosion in the hangar.
The nano-droids.
How did they get in his bloodstream?
Oh, this just keeps getting
better and better.
We're going to have to search
Jackar's home for evidence.
This is not the nicest place.
I would've thought working
for the Jedi paid better.
Letta?
Are you here?
You search for the droids,
but be careful,
and remember, he was a munitions expert.
I'd rather not set off
another explosion today.
I'll see if he left a note.
Letta?
Master.
The sensors are picking up
traces from the disposal.
The nano-droids
were in the food.
Well, I guess the question now is,
did he eat them willingly,
or did someone feed them to him?
Wh-what are you doing here?
We've learned Jackar
was involved in the bombing.
That can't be true.
See if she has any nano-droids
on her, Ahsoka.
Nanodroids?
She's clean.
What do you mean,
"nano-droids"?
We believe someone set Jackar
up and made him the bomb.
I...
I don't understand.
Letta, I want to bring you in
for more questioning.
Maybe you can help us make sense
out of all of this.
I'll answer any question I can.
Letta, stop.
Letta!
Letta.
Take the high road.
Right, Master.
Letta, stop!
Let me go.
Running means you know more
than you're telling us.
Jackar is dead,
and now you're trying to blame
his murder on me.
Nobody ever said he was dead.
But running proves you had
something to do with the bomb.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
People blamed Jedi because of you.
People were killed because of you!
You can't prove anything.
Did you feed the nano-droids
to Jackar?
You will answer me.
Now!
I did feed the nano-droids
to Jackar.
You set up your own husband to die?
You're dealing with things
you don't understand.
Oh, where you're going,
you'll have plenty of time
to explain everything.
We're holding Letta
in the cell below the temple
to await further questioning.
I am pleased to report
there were no other nano-droids
found in the sweep of the Temple.
I am also pleased to report,
based on the security footage,
Jackar Bowmani acted alone,
which means no Jedi was involved.
Thanks, Russo.
Good job.
Did this woman say what her
reasons were for attacking us?
Not yet, but we're working on that.
I think we can guess
her motives easily enough.
Public opinion is
swaying against the Jedi.
That is becoming clear.
This war is becoming less
and less popular
every day it persists.
Master, I'm relieved
we solved this case, but...
What if it had been a Jedi?
Yes.
I don't know how I would have felt
if a Jedi was really behind this.
There are going to be Jedi
who disappoint us, Ahsoka.
But as long as we know
there are good Jedi
who fight for what's right,
it makes it all worthwhile.