ANNOUNCER: The Republic fleet is on
the defensive and pushed to the brink.
As war rages in the much-contested
Outer Rim territories,
chaos and fear mount as
the Separatist army wages an epic battle
against heavily outnumbered
Republic ships.
In the far reaches of the Quell system,
Anakin Skywalker
and his Padawan, Ahsoka,
race across the galaxy
to aid Jedi Knight Aayla Secura
who is in the midst of a fight for her life
as the sinister droid army closes in.
Our shields are gone!
Hurry, Skywalker, we're depending on you.
Prepare the gunships.
We have them now.
Send in the super droids.
Commander, get out there
and stop those droids.
I'm on it!
This way.
We're ready, Admiral.
General, Skywalker's here.
And none too soon.
We're entering the atmosphere.
Rocket droids! Incoming!
Those droids are boarding Aayla's ship!
Take care of that clanker.
I'll be onboard Aayla's cruiser.
Master, are you sure
that's the wisest thing...
(ALARM BEEPING)
-Hey, kid.
-I know! I know! I'm hanging on!
This is taking too long.
Destroy that cruiser.
But, sir,
there are still hundreds of droids onboard.
-I don't care.
-Roger, roger.
Nice entrance, Skywalker.
How do you plan to get us
out of this mess?
Well, I have a ship docking
in the lower hangar as we speak.
-Activate docking port.
-On it.
Hold it.
Ha-ha!
We made it.
Gangway locked in, sir!
It's too late!
AHSOKA: Master!
Don't move the ship.
Are you guys all right down there?
Ahsoka, we have to leave now!
Hurry, get him on the ship.
I'm gonna turn on the deflector shields!
Gangway release.
You'll never be able to dock
with our ship in the middle of this battle.
We have no choice, Admiral.
General Skywalker's condition
may be critical.
We must get him onboard the Resolute.
-Are all Jedi so reckless?
-Just the good ones.
The hyperdrive's been activated!
-Shut it down!
-I can't!
General Secura, what's going on?
We're going into hyperspace.
Detach! Detach!
-They'll take us with them.
-Evasive maneuvers!
Plot every course
along their last known trajectory!
We need to finish this battle
and find them!
I need you with Commander Bly
up on the bridge right now.
AHSOKA: I should stay.
Commander Bly doesn't need my help.
Anakin does.
You can help Anakin
by getting this ship to safety.
General Secura, we have a problem.
What is it, Commander?
In our haste to escape, the navicomputer's
coordinates were inputted incorrectly.
And, well, we're headed right for a star.
It's no use. The navigation computer's
completely fried!
Shut down all power circuits
to reset the coordinates.
That will cut off Anakin's life support!
I don't like it any more than you do,
but it's a risk we're going to have to take.
We're switching off primary power units.
BLY: We're cutting it awfully close.
AAYLA: Ready to shut off auxiliary power.
On three. One, two, three!
We're out of hyperspace,
resume all power!
(GROANS)
Switch the power back on!
What are you waiting for?
Hurry, hurry!
Well, we're not gonna crash into the star,
but we're definitely gonna hit that planet.
(GROANING)
Everyone, out!
Well, we made it,
and Master Skywalker is still alive.
I'm just glad
he wasn't awake to see that landing.
He would have been proud.
I've certainly perfected
the art of demolishing ships
and almost getting my master killed.
Anakin doesn't have much time.
We have to find help tonight.
Okay, you and Bly go south.
Rex and I will stay here with Anakin.
No, Ahsoka.
In order to get help quickly,
we must work together.
I can't leave him.
Master, I know if I was hurt,
he'd never leave me behind.
I know this is hard, Ahsoka.
But Anakin has to stay behind,
and we have to go now.
There is nothing more we can do for him.
We must do all we can
to get off of this planet.
As a Jedi, it is your duty
to do what is best for the group.
General Secura, look.
We're not the only ones
here on this planet.
There has to be
some kind of something here.
(DISTANT SCREECHING)
If you don't mind me asking,
General Secura,
where exactly are we going?
To go find the people
who live on this planet.
Where are we going to find them?
We have no idea where they are.
It seems to me that the people
we're looking for live near giant trees.
Very perceptive, Padawan.
Be strong, Master. Just a little bit longer.
Rex will watch over you.
It is time to go.
Don't worry, kid. I'll take good care of him.
Captain Rex, keep your locator on.
We should be back by daybreak
with whoever or whatever
lives on this planet.
Got it, General Secura.
Hey, kid. Good luck.
Come on, guys, let's move out.
I can still sense your worry for Anakin,
your attachment to him.
It's just... I get so confused sometimes.
It's forbidden for Jedi
to form attachments,
yet we are supposed to be compassionate.
It is nothing to be ashamed of, Ahsoka.
I went through the same process
when I was your age with my own master.
Really? You?
He was like a father to me.
I realized that for the greater good,
I had to let him go.
Don't lose a thousand lives
just to save one.
Maybe, but that doesn't mean
that I can't try to save his life.
(SOFT SNARLING)
I don't see any signs of life.
(GASPS)
Watch out!
No wonder it's deserted! It's a death trap!
You'd have to be crazy
to want to dodge those on a daily basis.
It looks like someone
or something intelligent enough
to figure out a use for the pods
has dragged them away!
All we have to do is follow the trail!
Let's go!
(SNARLING)
General! Are you all right?
Be...
Behind you.
What the...
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(CAWING)
Watch your left! Left!
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
Cameron's dead. So are Lucky and Flesh.
We have to keep moving.
Pod central. We made it.
Hello?
What have you come here for?
We are peacekeepers.
We are Jedi from the Galactic Republic.
Our ship crashed a few miles away,
and one of us is very badly injured.
We need your help.
Violence breeds violence.
Jedi are no peacekeepers.
We're fighting for freedom.
And freedom and peace
require fear and death?
We colonized this system
to find solace from your wretched war.
We came here to find peace.
You must leave.
You will only destroy what small amount
of peace is left in the galaxy.
You will only bring the destruction of us.
Regardless of the Clone Wars
and our part in them,
we still need your help.
I'm afraid I must do
what's best for my people.
We cannot help you.
Please, can you at least
give us some medical supplies?
My friend is dying.
I cannot ignore a plea for help.
I will send my son, Wag Too,
to help your friend. He is a healer.
But only one Jedi may go with him.
The other must stay as insurance.
We wouldn't want a surprise attack
on our village
or the kidnapping of our only healer.
Bly and I will stay.
Padawan, go and help your master.
No! The clone and his blaster cannot stay.
He will go with the youngling.
I can handle it. I don't need help.
-Ahsoka!
-Don't worry.
Be mindful of your surroundings, Padawan,
those creatures are still out there.
Got it. We won't be long.
-Here, it will restore your energy.
-Thank you.
I'm sure you are aware that
the Jedi did not initiate the Clone Wars.
Our only intention is to end it
and restore peace to our galaxy.
What difference does it make who started
the war and who only wants to end it?
No side is free of fault.
It takes two to fight.
-But isn't liberty worth fighting for?
-But is it worth killing for?
Fighting for something
doesn't necessarily mean
you have to destroy everything
in your path.
Only when you lay your arms down
and pursue a course of non-violence
can you make this claim to me
that the Jedi are peacekeepers.
(GROANS)
General, you need to maintain your rest.
I can't rest!
Rex, they're coming. I can hear them.
We must fight.
(SCREECHING)
No, don't!
Fine.
Good work, little guy.
(GROANING)
Master!
Good to see you, Snips.
This is Wag Too, he's a healer.
He can make you well again.
Don't you worry. I can fix you right up.
Um...
Snips?
The oil from the pods
will aid in the healing process.
Don't worry, you'll be well in no time.
-You were right all along, Master Secura.
-About what?
AHSOKA: If I had stayed with Anakin,
we probably wouldn't have found
this village in time to save him.
At least this whole ordeal is over now.
We still have to find a way off this planet.
Well, I'm sure Admiral Yularen
and the Republic fleet are looking for us.
It shouldn't take them too long
to get here.
English - SDH