Villainy swells!
With an army of the galaxy's
most vicious criminals,
Darth Maul and Savage Opress
conspire with Pre Vizsla
and the Death Watch
to topple Duchess Satine,
ruler of Mandalore.
While the conspirators prepare to attack
the Mandalorian capital of Sundari
from a base on Zanbar,
the fate of 2,000 other neutral
systems is under threat
as Darth Maul moves closer
to establishing
a vast criminal empire.
Where are my targets?
We've identified them
at these locations.
However, as I've said before,
if we try to take Mandalore by force,
our people will turn against us.
I will use
my army of crime lords
to attack different targets
across Sundari
and sow chaos to undermine
the Duchess' rule.
Our gangsters will make her look
too weak to maintain control.
Then you and your Death Watch
will capture and arrest us,
bringing order where Satine's
weak government could not.
We'll be saviors.
Exactly.
A good plan.
Indeed.
I'll prepare the troops.
It's a risk to trust those monsters.
How do we know they'll keep
their end of the bargain?
We need those Sith and their thugs
to cause some pain and show
the Mandalorian people
how weak Satine really is.
After this is done,
no one will doubt why we're in power.
Most will welcome us.
Then what?
Then we execute Maul and those thugs.
Those criminals will scatter,
and Mandalore will be ours.
I believe Vizsla will betray us.
We have no other choice.
We cannot rule openly
without drawing the attention
of the Jedi.
We need Vizsla as the face of our rule
for now.
The promise of wealth
will find us a new face on Mandalore.
You have learned well, my apprentice.
Greed never fails to motivate.
What's the matter?
I am scanning life forms.
I believe this spice shipment
is infested.
Step back.
Ah!
Gangsters!
We're under attack.
Surrender.
My Master is taking over these docks.
You are now under the control
of the Pyke Syndicate.
Duchess, the shipping docks
are under attack.
By whom?
The Death Watch?
No, it appears to be a crime syndicate.
Our guards are helpless
against their numbers,
and the people are demanding
we do something to stop them.
Welcome to Mandalore.
Stand down.
You are now all slaves
of the Black Sun Clan.
Fall back!
It's the gangsters.
Lock the vaults.
Open the bank.
We're here for a withdrawal.
Guards, now.
The Black Sun is attacking the vaults.
Send reinforcements.
Take him.
I need you all to remain calm.
These attackers are just thugs
brought on by the lowest element.
The Duchess Satine has led us to ruin.
Death Watch.
Guards, stay back.
Vizsla, you must be the one
responsible for these attacks.
No, I'm not responsible.
But I can offer a solution.
People of Mandalore...
I am Pre Vizsla of clan Vizsla.
Death Watch is here to save you
from these intergalactic gangsters
that threaten our great city.
This is a war,
and we will win.
Join me and let us defend
Mandalore against the criminals.
We need action, not pacifism.
Do not listen to him!
His war will cause the end
of Mandalore as we know it.
We are under attack.
There is no time for discussion.
The name Mandalore should send fear
into the hearts of these gangsters.
It's war!
Vizsla! Vizsla!
War!
The people are beginning to follow you.
It is time for Death Watch
to take action.
Make sure you put on a good show.
As you wish, Lord Maul.
What should we do?
There's nothing we can do.
The Duchess' forces are being overrun
across the entire planet.
Listen.
It sounds like there is fighting
going on out there.
Ah!
What's going on?
We're Death Watch,
and we're here to rescue you.
You have my thanks, soldier.
No, thank Pre Vizsla.
You're safe now.
It's the Death Watch.
The Death Watch are our saviors.
- They saved us.
- They freed us.
Our saviors.
The Death Watch saved us.
Stop them!
They've robbed the main vault.
Keep up, you weaklings.
Ugh.
This monster will not trouble
the people of Mandalore any longer.
Take him away, Captain.
Vizsla!
Vizsla! Vizsla!
Duchess, Pre Vizsla and his
men have entered the palace.
Should we stop them?
How can we?
The people are on their side now.
Vizsla! Vizsla! Vizsla!
No!
There will be no bloodshed.
But, Duchess...
- I will not be provoked
to violence by these terrorists.
Listen, Duchess.
Do you hear the people?
They cry out for change.
Your weak-minded rule
of Mandalore is at an end.
The resurrection of our warrior past
is about to begin.
Duchess Satine
and the New Mandalorian leaders
have fled in cowardice
while the Death Watch brought
these criminals to justice.
Your new Prime Minister, Pre Vizsla,
leader of Death Watch,
exiled governor of Concordia,
true son of Mandalore,
presents you with the lords
of the most feared crime
families in the galaxy.
Vizsla!
Vizsla! Vizsla!
Vizsla! Vizsla! Vizsla!
Vizsla!
You cannot hold me here.
I am the Duchess of Mandalore.
Your actions will bring
our civilization to ruin.
Is that you, Satine?
Almec?
Here for a visit,
or has peace betrayed you too, Duchess?
Peace exists only in the minds
of the faithful.
And faith has been
the greatest disappointment.
Only when it is broken.
What you did for the people
as Prime Minister
betrayed their trust.
And you betrayed mine.
Destitution leaves little room
for faith.
My actions allowed the people
hope in your leadership.
The supplies I bought on the
black market kept you in power.
Another error of judgment.
The people made willing
sacrifices for their freedom.
Corruption is not the answer.
Then enjoy your freedom, Duchess.
You'll have plenty of time
to tell me all about it.
The transition of power
will be seamless.
We now have the support of the people
and Satine to bait Kenobi.
With his demise,
our deal will be complete.
Your oversight requires correction.
We now have a base, an army,
and the means to expand
to other neutral systems.
It wasn't an oversight.
It was intentional.
I don't have an interest
in the other systems.
Your vision no longer matters.
Oh, don't fret.
I'll still honor our deal.
Kenobi will be dealt with.
But now you'll do as I say.
The violence is over!
The last of the parasites
infecting Mandalore
has been caught.
The Duchess has abandoned her duty
to protect Mandalore.
Her political dream
only encourages aggression
against our planet.
We have learned from this beast
the consequences of pacifist principles.
It's now time to restore
the traditions of Mandalore.
No one will ever threaten us again!
Vizsla! Vizsla!
Vizsla! Vizsla! Vizsla!
Vizsla has captured
the support of his people,
just as we planned.
However, he is not
their anointed leader yet.
There is still time for us
to put in place a leader
under our control.
Then let us escape,
and we shall find one.
Patience.
We must move cautiously.
By placing us in prison,
Vizsla has unwittingly put us in reach
of several candidates for his successor.
Who do you mean, brother?
Vizsla has imprisoned the Duchess here.
Other political advisors of hers
will be within these walls
who will suit our purposes well.
Hey, quiet, you two.
Apprentice,
I wish a tour of this facility.
Ah!
Zap!
Crash!
You are the now the former
Duchess Satine,
are you not?
What do you want, you monster?
Mm, nothing yet,
but I will have a use for you in time.
Where are the other leaders
of your people?
You should know already.
They've either sided with Vizsla
or have been killed.
There's no one left now but Almec and I,
but he's as corrupt and vile as you.
Really?
Hmm.
Thank you for being so cooperative.
Almec?
Yes?
I can deliver you from this prison.
What was your position
in this government?
I am the former Prime Minister.
Satine imprisoned me on charges
of corruption and conspiracy
for using the black market.
He's a murderer.
He caused the death of children.
Quiet.
What do you want from me?
Mandalore is in need
of a Prime Minister.
I thought you were in league
with Pre Vizsla.
We were.
Clearly you are powerful,
but how can two of you overthrow
Vizsla and his supporters?
Vizsla is a soldier,
and like every soldier,
he is bound by honor.
I will challenge him to single combat
in front of his men.
He will not deny me.
Hmm.
If you defeat him,
according to the ancient laws
of Mandalore,
his soldiers will be honor-bound
to follow you.
Precisely.
Sir, they're attacking.
I challenge you,
one warrior to another.
And only the strongest
shall rule Mandalore.
So be it.
Give him his weapon.
For Mandalore!
Ah!
Crack!
Oh.
Like you said,
only the strongest
shall rule.
I claim this sword
and my rightful place as leader
of Death Watch.
Never.
No outsider will ever rule Mandalore.
Hmm.
If you'll not join me,
you will all die.
You're all traitors.
Unfortunately for you,
history will not see it that way.
Execute them!
Silence, please, silence.
Hear me now.
Duchess Satine,
the so-called pacifist,
who could not protect you
when your lives were at stake,
has murdered Pre Vizsla,
the true hero of Mandalore.
Satine is now under arrest,
and it was Pre Vizsla's last command
that I be reinstated as Prime Minister.
I know my past is checkered,
but I promise you,
I take full responsibility
for my people.
And my heart now bleeds for your pain.
However, from this point on,
Mandalore will be strong,
and we will be known as the warriors
we were always meant to be.
You have done well, Prime Minister.
I shall waste no time
in building my administration.
Choose wisely.
I will hold you personally
responsible for their failures.
Yes, Master.
Is there anything more you require?
Go.
Rule my people.