ANNOUNCER: Clone forces rally.
As the war escalates in the Outer Rim,
the Jedi Knights are spread thinly
across the galaxy.
Many new clones are rushed into service
to support their Jedi generals.
Unfortunately, because
of the relentless demands of battle,
many young clones must join the struggle
before their intensive training
has been completed.
These clones, manning a vital network
of tracking stations,
are all that stand
between the Republic and invasion.
This is the deck officer checking in.
Nothing going on, as usual.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
You're listening to the
Grand Army of the Republic broadcast,
the voice of the Outer Rim.
This next one goes out to the mud jumpers
of the 224th slugging it out on Mimban.
Keep your heads down
and your seals tight, boys.
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING) Yes!
(SCOFFS) Who's next? Fives?
Shouldn't you be watching
your scope, Hevy?
Yeah! Let's take a look.
Hmm. What do you know? All clear.
Just like the last hundred times
I looked at it.
Personally,
I like that it's so quiet out here.
I can catch up on the reg manuals.
Echo! What is wrong with you?
We should be out on the front lines,
blasting droids.
Ah, leave him alone.
They kept him in his growth jar too long.
HEVY: (CHUCKLING) Yeah.
You may not realize it yet, Fives,
but you landed on the most boring post
in the Outer Rim.
And one of the most important.
(ALARM SOUNDING)
Attention! Sergeant on deck!
At ease. Even though you're all new here,
I shouldn't have to remind you that
this quadrant is key to the Outer Rim.
If the droids get past this station,
they can surprise-attack the facilities
where we were born,
on our home world of Kamino.
There are some officers on the way,
so I want everything squared away
for inspection. Understood?
ALL: Sir! Yes, sir!
Still here, Anakin?
When was the last time you slept?
I'll sleep after we find General Grievous.
Clone Intelligence spotted him
in the Balmorra system,
but that was weeks ago.
Since then, he vanished.
Well, unlike you, maybe he's getting
some much-needed rest.
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
YULAREN: Excuse me, General.
Incoming transmission
from Commander Cody.
CODY: General Kenobi, General Skywalker.
Cody. How goes the inspections?
The tracking station at Pastel
is fully operational.
Captain Rex and I are proceeding
to the outpost in the Rishi system.
Good. Report back once you've arrived.
Copy that. Cody out.
Good man, that Cody. Don't worry, Anakin.
If General Grievous comes anywhere
near this quadrant, we'll know about it.
(ALARM BEEPING)
-Sir! Incoming meteor shower!
-Raise the shield.
(POWERING UP)
-You wanted excitement, Hevy.
-Right.
(EXCLAIMS MOCKINGLY)
Meteor shower.
What the...
(SHOUTS)
-Get these doors open.
-Roger, roger.
CT-327, report in. Sentry! Do you copy?
-Interference from the meteors?
-I don't see him down there, Sarge.
You two, go find him.
Droids!
(GUNS FIRING)
Sound the alarm!
(BEEPING)
They've disabled the beacon.
Get a message to the fleet!
We have to warn...
(GROANS)
Sarge!
That should slow those buckets down.
-This way! Hurry!
-No! We can...
(BUZZING)
There's too many!
-Four clones escaped, Captain.
-They don't matter.
Hard-wire the all-clear signal
and contact General Grievous.
The outpost is secure, General.
We shut down the alarm
and turned on the all-clear signal.
Excellent. Keep that signal alive.
I don't want the Republic
to find out we're coming.
General?
Our spy on Kamino is making contact.
All the preparations for your invasion
are in order.
Good! Our fleet is
approaching the system.
We are almost at the rendezvous point.
Very good, my lord.
I will await your arrival.
The destruction of Kamino will stop
their production of clones for good.
Rishi Outpost, this is Commander Cody.
Do you copy?
Rishi Outpost, please respond.
(TUNING VOCABULATOR) Open...
(IMITATING CLONES)
Open comlink channel.
Rishi Outpost, come in!
DROID: Sorry, Commander.
We're experiencing technical difficulties.
-This is the inspection team.
-Inspection? Negative, negative.
We do not require an inspection.
Everything is fine here. Thank you.
We'll be the judge of that.
Prepare for our arrival.
Roger, roger.
Something's not right here.
Well, good luck.
I'm putting you in charge of this one.
(METAL CLANGING)
FIVES: What do we do without the Sarge?
ECHO: The reg manual says the next...
HEVY: Wait. Wait!
(WHOOSHING)
Did you hear that?
FIVES: Yeah, what is that?
HEVY: It doesn't sound like droids.
(RUMBLING)
-Don't forget about those giant eels.
-CUTUP: I've never seen one...
(CUTUP SCREAMING)
HEVY: Cutup!
(SCREAMING)
-What the hell was that?
-That was an eel.
That's why we have the regulation
not to go outside.
HEVY: Let's move before it comes back.
ECHO: (SIGHS) Poor Cutup.
FIVES: Look! It's Commander Cody!
It's the inspection team!
CODY: This is not good.
I don't see the deck officer anywhere.
REX: These boys are sloppy.
There should always be an officer on duty.
HEVY: We have to warn them.
Get on the comlink.
CODY: I have a bad feeling about this.
DROID: Welcome to Rishi, Commander.
As you can see,
the outpost is operating at peak efficiency.
Thank you for visiting,
and have a safe trip back.
CODY: We need to inspect the base
just the same.
Uh, there is no need.
Everything is fine and fully operational.
(TUNING COMLINK)
ECHO: It's no good. Their comlinks
are on a different scramble set.
HEVY: I'll signal them with this flare.
-Take us to the sergeant in command.
-Roger, roger.
CODY: A droid attack flare!
(CODY GROANS)
Rex! What the heck are you doing?
REX: Relax.
Just as I thought. Looks like
one of those new commando droids.
REX: That flare must have come
from the survivors.
Ambush!
CODY: Those clankers have tough armor!
We're cut off!
(BEEPING)
Off the platform!
CODY: Copy that.
No sign of them.
They must have been pulverized.
(DROID LAUGHING)
Resume defensive posts.
CODY: Well, that sure
complicates things, Commander.
REX: No worse than that time on Tibrin.
CODY: We had Jedi with us on Tibrin.
They helped.
REX: Hands above your heads!
Take your sun bonnets off!
-ECHO: Sir?
-Take them off! Now!
(EXPLOSION)
(ROARING)
HEVY: Nice shot!
The name's Rex.
But you'll call me "Captain" or "sir".
ALL: Sir, yes, sir!
I'm Commander Cody, your new boss.
My designation is
Trooper 27-dash-5555, sir.
We call him Fives. I'm Hevy. This is Echo.
-Where's your sergeant?
-Dead, sir.
We're all that's left.
Looks like we got ourselves
a batch of shinies, Commander.
-"Shinies," sir?
-That's right.
Your armor.
It's shiny and new, just like you.
Sir, me and my batchers
are trained and ready.
We'll take back our post, shiny or not.
There's hope for you yet, rookie.
Commander Cody, do you copy?
Captain Rex, please respond.
They should have checked in
from the Rishi station hours ago.
It appears your captain follows orders
as well as you do.
Hmm. Perhaps Cody is boring Rex
with standard procedures and protocol.
We need to work
on our own boring procedures
and figure out a strategy to find Grievous.
Right. Admiral, let me know
if you hear from Rex.
REX: Look sharp, rookies.
As long as those tweezers
occupy this post,
our home planet of Kamino is at risk.
ECHO: But there's so many of them.
REX: Doesn't matter, kid.
We have to retake this base,
so we will retake this base!
(GUNS CLICKING)
CODY: How do you propose we get through
those blast doors, Rex, old boy?
REX: I have a few ideas.
(BEEPING)
What is that?
Unit 2-6, is that you?
REX: Roger, roger.
You sound strange. Is something wrong
with your vocabulator?
Roger, roger.
Take off your helmet.
Let me see your faceplate.
(FIRMLY) Roger, roger.
This is never gonna work.
-Clones!
-Roger, roger.
REX: Right. Let's move.
-HEVY: Permission to take point, sir?
-I'm always first, kid.
(SHOUTS)
-ECHO: Fives!
-He's okay. Focus on the battle.
(FIRING CONTINUES)
-I got one!
-Sorry, Echo, I junked that one.
Like hell you did!
Not so tough now, are you, sparky?
Get to the window.
It looks like we have more visitors.
It looks like a Separatist fleet!
That's why they commandeered
the outpost.
They're mounting a full-scale invasion!
We have to warn command.
The Republic base
is still transmitting the all-clear signal,
but for some reason
our commando droids are not responding.
We can leave nothing to chance.
That base cannot be allowed
to alert the Jedi that we're coming.
Send down reinforcements to investigate!
Those clankers sabotaged our transmitter,
and they hard-wired the all-clear signal.
-It'll take time to repair...
-We don't have time. Look.
(RUMBLING)
Well, buddy, you always said
you wanted to be in the front lines.
We can't protect the outpost long
against that army of clankers.
Then we'll destroy the outpost instead.
But, sir, our mission
is to defend this facility at all costs.
We have to warn the Republic
about the invasion.
They'll take notice
when the all-clear signal stops.
That's right.
When they stop receiving our beacon,
they'll get the message
something's wrong.
I need every thermal detonator
in the inventory.
It'll take more than a few detonators
to destroy this outpost.
We can use the L.T.
This moon freezes for over half the year.
We use liquid Tibanna as fuel
to heat the base.
Liquid Tibanna. Highly explosive.
Good. Bring the tanks here
and prime the detonators.
All right, listen up.
There's only one target of interest
in this sector: Kamino.
It's the closest thing
we clones have to a home.
Today we fight for more than the Republic.
Today, we fight for all our brothers
back home. Understood?
ALL: Sir, yes, sir!
REX: I think we can even the odds
a bit, Commander,
especially since they don't know
we're here.
CODY: This one here is mine.
REX: (SCOFFS)
A big gun doesn't make a big man.
Reinforcements reporting. Open up.
You didn't say "please".
DROID: Clones! Get them!
We could use a Jedi about now.
Captain Rex, come in!
Commander Cody, are you there?
(STATIC BUZZING)
General, there's still no response.
How about the all-clear signal?
-Is the base still transmitting?
-Yes, sir.
If something were wrong,
Cody would contact us.
GRIEVOUS: What is the status of the base?
We've run into some difficulties.
There seem to be a few clones left, sir.
Then wipe them out!
We can't let a few puny clones stop us.
CODY: Fall back to the op center! Move!
-Rex? Time's wasting!
-REX: Almost ready.
The handset isn't linking up
with the detonator.
-Hevy?
-HEVY: Yes, sir.
REX: This detonator isn't working.
HEVY: I'll take care of it. It'll be fixed
in no time. You guys get out of here.
Just make it fast.
Those droids are getting close.
There, that should fix it.
(DROIDS MARCHING)
This isn't good.
There's got to be another way.
The base is ours again, sir.
The clones are fleeing.
The cowards. Secure the area.
Hevy, hit the...
-Where's Hevy?
-HEVY: I'm on it, sir.
Hevy, get out of there!
The remote isn't working.
I'll have to detonate it manually.
Hey! Hold on, there! Blast him!
Hevy! We've got to get up there,
back to the maintenance pipe. Let's move!
It's no use! I know what I have to do.
I don't like your tone, rookie.
REX: Soldier, come in! Are you there?
Soldier, come in! Respond! Talk to us!
(CLICKING)
ECHO: Hevy, come in! Come in, Hevy!
Hevy, come in!
Do we take prisoners?
I don't.
ECHO: Hevy always did hate that place.
The all-clear signal has been disabled?
The Rishi base has stopped transmitting!
Grievous!
Sound the invasion alarm.
Let's get the fleet underway.
(GROANS)
I didn't tell them to blow up the station!
But isn't it good
that the base is destroyed?
Idiot!
The Republic fleet!
We're outgunned. Get us out of here.
FIVES: We've got those tinnies on the run.
ECHO: Thanks to Hevy.
Gunships!
We're getting off this crater, boys!
(DRONING)
On behalf of the Republic,
we thank you for your valiant service,
and we honor your comrade's sacrifice.
Your new unit is lucky to have you.
I'd be proud to fight beside you,
anytime, anywhere.
Congratulations.
You're not shinies anymore.
With all due respect, sir,
we failed our mission.
We don't deserve this honor.
No. If it weren't for you,
the Republic wouldn't have learned
of the Separatist invasion
until it was too late.
You showed me something today.
You're exactly the kind of men I need
in the 501st.
-Sir! Yes, sir!