Secret transmission intercepted!
The Jedi Council has intercepted
an encoded transmission
of General Grievous.
However, Republic Intelligence officers
have failed to crack
the new encryption code
being used by the droids.
Fears escalate that the Separatists
are about to mount a major offensive.
Having located the source
of the transmission
deep in Separatist space,
the Jedi plan a counterstrike
to capture an enemy decoding chip
which will allow them
to understand the transmission
and thwart the Separatist plot.
Time is not on our side,
so I'll make this short.
You droids have been chosen
for a very important mission.
There's an encryption module
on board this Separatist dreadnought.
This device is scrambling
all Separatist communication
in the region.
We believe you five
can get behind enemy lines,
infiltrate the vault
without drawing attention to yourselves,
and steal that encryption module.
WAC-47, reporting for duty!
Sorry I am late.
I thought the message said to meet
in the "Jedi storeroom",
whatever that is.
Heh.
So did I miss anything?
Fall in line, soldier.
So I hear we're
gonna be taking out Separatists.
I will be honest.
Some of you may not make it back.
What...
why is he looking at me?
Uh, were you just looking at me?
I... I was just kidding.
But I have faith in your abilities.
You are not ordinary droids.
You've worked with the Jedi before.
You are our secret weapons.
Now, let me turn you over
to your mission leader.
The colonel is one of our top minds
at Strategic Command.
He's been with the Republic
since the Battle of Geonosis,
Colonel Meebur Gascon.
Thank you, Master Windu.
I'll take it from here.
May the Force be with you.
Attention!
Now, I'm only gonna say this once,
so turn up your audio inputs.
Once we're inside the cruiser,
we make our way to "C" deck.
That's where their
communication center is housed.
We bypass security here and here,
divert the super battle droids here.
Then we break the vault code,
beat the swarm mines,
steal the encryption module,
and return home in time
for my promotion ceremony
to brigadier general.
Are we clear?
Uh... uh...
Good, that's what I like:
no questions.
Oh.
D-Squad, fall in line!
The line starts behind me, mech.
Clang!
Over here, you mechs, front and center.
This is Dr. Gubacher.
- He is...
- Uh, uh, Corporal?
Colonel.
Right.
Well, I just want
to set the record straight.
I am not a mech.
You called us all mechs back there,
but as you can see, I am a WAC.
Granted, my master's not a Jedi,
but I am a different class of droid...
better engineering.
As I was saying,
before I was rudely interrupted,
Dr. Gubacher
is going to equip each of you
with a tactical upgrade
specially designed for this mission.
All right, enough with the chatter.
Let's get this show on the road.
Cyclops,
you're not needed here.
Go prepare our shuttle for launch.
R2-D2,
these advanced rocket boosters
should give you better aerial mobility
and for longer periods of time.
Ah, but be advised:
the navigation controls
are finely tuned.
QT-KT,
this coil
is a remote-controlled magnet.
It can attract any metal object
in a seven-meter radius.
But when dealing with mines,
you'll want to take care.
The magnetic force
is extremely powerful.
U9-C4,
this laser-cutter
will slice through most
materials you encounter.
But make sure
you're in a locked position.
The recoil packs quite a wallop.
No, no, no, no, no.
M5-BZ, we are not
putting anything inside you.
We're taking something out:
your memory banks.
I'll be making the extraction myself
in the salvage room.
I am sorry,
but we need to make room
for the colonel's command center.
No need to baby him.
He's just a droid.
Fortunately,
he won't remember any of this.
What do you want, BZ?
It's me, you moron.
What are you doing in there, Corporal?
And how many times
do I have to tell you?
It's colonel.
Nice setup.
I want to know
why I did not get an upgrade.
Because you are just a pilot!
Now do your job
and pilot this ship!
Just a pilot...
we will see about that.
All right, Cyclops, listen up.
I want you to alert me
when we near the dreadnought.
I have a plan on how
to attract their attention.
Relax.
I already took care of it.
What do you mean?
What did you do?
I put us on a collision course
with the dreadnought.
See, Corporal?
I am not just a pilot.
You idiot!
We're caught in a tractor beam.
Hold it right there.
Out of the way, tin cans.
Let's check the cockpit.
No sign of life, just these droids.
Continue your search
while I take these droids
in for interrogation.
Everyone just stay calm.
Oh, my gosh!
You are Republic droids!
That is right, and I am their leader.
Yeah, I got him.
Well, thanks for the assist, QT.
All right, listen up.
The next phase of my plan
is to reach "C" deck.
We'll take this path here.
Since the mechs
won't draw much attention,
we'll go in a convoy.
Cyclops, you lead the way.
If anyone asks,
you're taking the droids
on a repair job.
Got it?
Yes, sir, uh...
Captain.
It's colonel!
I swear, Cyclops.
You are gonna drive me crazy.
Now, I want flat top
to locate the comm-vault
power supply
then use his laser to cut the main line
and cause a temporary loss in power.
You can do it, C4!
Oh, do not forget
to lock down your...
Sir, there was a temporary
power loss on "C" deck.
Has
the power been reestablished?
Yes.
It was only a temporary fluctuation.
Hmm, curious.
All right, listen up.
Cutting the power
put the comm-vault
security system
in manual override.
But someone still has to distract
some super battle droids.
Oh, please, please, please.
Let me do it, come on, come on,
come on, come on, let me do it, please.
Come on, come on.
All right.
You will not regret this, corporal.
I am not a...
Halt.
I have been ordered by General Grievous
to test comm-vault security.
And I need your help.
Now, follow me.
Now, I will go inside
the comm-vault
and send out a power surge.
I need you two to stay here.
It will not be safe for you
while I am working.
Are we clear?
Yes, but...
- Good.
That is what I like:
no questions.
Huh?
Thank you, thank you,
thank you very much.
Shh.
Quiet.
We need to keep moving.
BZ, open the comm-vault
security door.
Uh, make sure it
is not booby-trapped.
You blockhead!
Now we're going to lose manual override.
You... you terminated BZ.
It's not my fault
he fried his circuitry.
I didn't tell that nitwit
to attack the access panel.
So what do we do now, Corporal?
Look, we can still salvage this mission.
If one of you could just...
you need to reaccess that panel,
and we have to open
that comm-vault door fast
and grab the encryption module
before we're caught red-handed.
No, I will not do it myself.
I'm an officer.
I've got no experience
in this type of crisis maneuver.
You fought in the Battle of Geonosis.
That did not prepare you for a crisis?
Well, technically,
I didn't fight in that battle.
I'm a military analyst
by trade and...
You are a map reader?
I am an accomplished
battlefield strategist.
I analyze the enemy terrain
and plot a course to victory.
In other words, you read maps.
You're off base here, Cyclops!
I was chosen for my fearsome cunning,
although my size
may have played a small factor.
But do not think for a moment
that Colonel Meebur Gascon
is going to relinquish command
of this mission.
I have waited a lifetime
for this opportunity,
and some ragtag collection of droids
is not going to deny me my destiny.
So one way or another,
I will open
that comm-vault door.
Oh, there, just like I planned it.
Now, we're
going to infiltrate this vault,
neutralize the swarm mines,
and then secure the encryption module.
Any questions?
Have you ever been in a battle before?
No, I have not.
But if you'd care to see
what I'm made of,
we can go to war right now, you and me,
and probably get ourselves
captured by a Separatist.
Or we can execute my plan
and come out of this mission
looking like heroes.
The choice is yours, Cyclops.
First of all, my name is WAC.
Second of all,
we will execute your plan.
But you have to stop calling us
stupid names, Shorty.
Very well, WAC.
I'll play nice,
but only until one of you
screws up again.
Sir, there has been another
disturbance on "C" deck.
I will investigate
this situation personally.
All right, Pinky...
I mean, QT.
This is your chance to shine.
Use your magnet
to attract those swarm mines.
There it is, the encryption module.
It's all up to you now, R2.
Not so fast.
Arms up.
Gravity.
Pop!
Right, turn it off, quick!
Thud!
Ah!
I will help you, Corporal.
Oh, I'm gonna be sick.
Corporal, are you okay?
Look out!
I will turn the gravity back on.
Hurry, WAC, hurry!
Pop!
I'll take that.
Ha-ha, good work, R2.
Intruder alert.
Let's move it out,
D-Squad.
What are you doing?
We're going to get caught!
R2 says
we cannot leave BZ behind.
R2's right.
We can repair him on the shuttle.
There's trouble on "C" deck.
Report there immediately.
Get out of the way,
you stupid astromechs.
Funny thing about droids
last thing they'd expect to betray them:
another droid.
D-Squad, let's go home.
Ah, my first mission...
a rousing success
and a brilliant plan
if I do say so myself.
I agree, R2.
The team's execution was not too shabby.
Who knows, you droids
might just make decent soldiers
after all.
Oh, and you, too, WAC.
Yes, sir, Colonel.