ANNOUNCER: Battle droids on Naboo!
As the Separatist rebellion
rages through the galaxy,
even peaceful planets are threatened.
Following the discovery
of Separatist droids
wandering the grassy wasteland,
Naboo is once again on high alert.
Fearing their home
is facing another invasion,
Senator Amidala and Representative Binks
race to Naboo to assess the situation.
Meanwhile, near the Gungan swamplands,
an even graver threat
is about to be discovered.
We came as soon as we could, my lady.
Have you found any more droids?
Only the three.
But you can be sure they aren't tourists.
I need you to convince the Senate,
or the Jedi Council,
or whoever is in charge
of this terrible war,
that we are threatened.
They'll need more proof.
Finding a couple of battle droids
will not be enough.
(COMLINK BEEPS)
MALE VOICE: Captain Typho,
the battle droid is ready for analysis.
PADMÉ: Have you been able
to retrieve any information?
Unfortunately, the Naboo security who
discovered them preferred to shoot first
and retrieve data later.
(SNIFFING)
PADMÉ: (SIGHS) If they were
found in the grasslands,
where'd they pick up all this mud?
TYPHO: Add that to
our very long list of questions.
Oh, yummy, yummy!
(WHIRRING)
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
With your permission, Senator Padmé,
I would like to shut down
before I get sensory overload.
-Permission denied.
-Denied?
Threepio, you may be able to get
some information out of him.
Cannot see. Where am I?
Oh, yummy, yummy!
You are in very good hands
onboard a Separatist ship.
Count Dooku himself intends
to reward you for your bravery.
-Bravery?
-For your assignment on Naboo.
Do try to activate
what's left of your memory.
We all want to hear
your tale of medical heroics.
(STUTTERING) Virus.
Yes, the virus. You do remember.
Please continue.
(EXCLAIMING)
A small amount leaked out.
Must contain. Naboo cannot know.
(EXCLAIMING)
(CLATTERING)
(EXCLAIMS QUESTIONINGLY)
Lab must remain secret.
A secret lab on Naboo? Where?
You must tell...
It is a secret. This is no Separatist ship.
Unless you want to become
a box of spare parts,
you'll tell us where that lab is.
(JAR JAR EXCLAIMS)
-The lab is secret.
-Look out!
DROID: Uh-oh.
(CLATTERING)
We'll never get any information
out of him now.
Meesa sorry. It was a accident.
(CLEARS THROAT) Is this what you're after?
Meesa loving!
Thesa very, very good tongue-grabbing!
Yousa finding only in one placen.
-Where?
-In the mud under the Perlote tree.
Like the mud on this droid.
The Eastern Swamps!
I think Jar Jar just found out
the location of that lab.
They're planning an attack on Naboo.
It's the only explanation.
Delicate the situation is.
Two Jedi we will send.
May I recommend
General Kenobi and General Skywalker?
Relations with the Gungans
are a little tense right now,
but they trust General Kenobi
like one of their own.
Send them we will.
I want as much information as possible
before the Jedi arrive.
See if you and Threepio can download
any of the other battle droid's memory.
-I'm going to find that lab.
-Are you sure that's wise?
PADMÉ: Come on, Jar Jar.
(SQUEALING)
(GRUNTING)
Back! Back! That water gone poodoo!
This is muy bad.
(JAR JAR GRUNTING)
Ah! This is bombad.
Whatsa happened to them?
It's the plague.
We're definitely getting close.
(PADMÉ GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
-Whosa are you?
-What you doing?
Why yousa here?
(MUMBLING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Whatsa yousa thinking?
Don't move! I don't want to hurt you.
Jar Jar, put your helmet back on.
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
Yousa okeey-day.
Is not in the air, is in the water.
-Who are you?
-Meesa Peppi Bow.
We think the virus that made your
animals sick came from the Perlote trees.
Yousa follow this river,
yousa finda yousa Perlote.
Meesa take you.
No, Peppi, you stay here.
You'll be going home soon, I promise.
I'll send some soldiers to pick you up
and take you back to Theed.
Keep your eyes open.
Look for anything out of the ordinary.
(MECHANICAL BUZZING)
VINDI: I suppose one can never have
too many lab rats.
-Please, escort our guests inside.
-Roger, roger.
(EXCLAIMS)
A hatch!
Captain Typho, I think we're standing
right on top of the lab.
I need a geo-scan of coordinates SP127.
(BEEPING)
(SIGHS)
No way we're gonna open this.
-We'll just have to...
-Freeze! Hold it right there.
-Yousa let us go!
-Who are you? Why are you holding us?
Wonderful specimens.
What's a life form like you
doing in a swamp like this?
-I was about to ask you the same thing.
-Thanks to the support
of my compassionate friends
in the Separatist Alliance,
I am creating life!
-Howsa yousa creating life?
-I'm so pleased you enquired.
A demonstration is in order.
Allow me to present
the return of the infamous
Blue Shadow Virus.
The Blue Shadow Virus?
I thought that deadly disease was extinct.
Yes, it was wiped from the galaxy
generations ago,
but I have given it life once again.
(EXCLAIMS) Yousa no creating life,
yousa taking life!
Yousa poisoned the Gungan water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes!
Unfortunately, the Blue Shadow Virus
in its natural form
thrives only in water.
Until I improved upon that weakness.
(LAUGHING) Yeah, yeah, yes.
Your eyes do not deceive you.
I have perfected an airborne strain
of the Blue Shadow Virus.
This is the last of the bombs, Doctor.
I'm well aware it is the last!
You think I'd lose count?
The virus in its gaseous forms,
combined with these bombs,
will release the Blue Shadow Virus
back into the galaxy
more potent than ever before.
Are you insane? It's a deadly disease!
No life forms are immune to it.
That's why it was eradicated.
You mean murdered!
-Take this away.
-Okay.
Meanwhile, as we speak,
thousands and thousands
of so-called superior life forms
are spreading their disease of war
throughout the galaxy.
Perhaps they are the ones
who should be eradicated.
General Kenobi, Anakin. We're so glad...
-Where's Senator Amidala?
-She went to look for the lab.
And you let her go?
Senator Padmé can be very hard to stop
once she has made up her mind.
Good point. I know what you mean.
This is Peppi Bow.
She was the last person to see them.
Padmé sent her here to safety.
Theysa looking for the sick-maker.
-"They"?
-Representative Binks was with her.
(BEEPS)
-Go with the Gungan, see if you can them.
-You've got it, Master.
Why didn't you send someone
to look for them?
Considering the latest developments,
we thought it was best to wait for you.
What latest developments?
We did a robolobotomy
on the battle droids
and came up with this piece of memory.
Who is that?
Dr. Nuvo Vindi,
the senior medic for the Perma families.
He disappeared 10 years ago.
Good news,
my soulless automaton friends!
We now have enough
of the Blue Shadow Virus
to start filling the bombs.
He said "bombs".
(R2-D2 BEEPS)
We will only need to send one bomb
to each key star system.
Work quickly.
I want them ready to deliver by...
If those bombs get delivered,
we'll be facing a galaxy-wide plague.
The war will be the least of our worries.
There is some good news.
Senator Amidala found the lab.
She sent us the coordinates
before she disappeared.
We've managed to get
a geo-scan of the area.
-It's enormous.
-It looks like there are three entry points.
Here, here and here.
This appears to be the main lab.
And the bombs?
There seems to be an above-average
amount of radiation in this area.
It's likely where they're being assembled.
If Padmé has alerted them
to our presence in any way...
If Padmé is in there,
and then we go in guns a-blazing,
-she may get killed.
-It is a risk we have to take.
Dr. Vindi and those bombs
must not leave the lab.
And if they, or we, detonate one
during the attack...
Better to have one planet infected
than the entire galaxy.
-This the ship belonging to them.
-So, where are they?
Their tracks end here.
(MECHANICAL BUZZING)
(SOFTLY) Peppi! It's a scope.
Don't let them see you.
(EXCLAIMS)
-Where are they?
-Patience. They'll be here in a moment.
You seem a bit on edge.
There's a good chance we're
about to destroy all life on this planet,
including ours and the Senator's,
so yes, I'm a bit on edge! Why aren't you?
I'm better at hiding it.
(COMLINK BEEPS)
AHSOKA: Master, are you there?
-Did you find her?
-Negative.
I'm pretty sure she's inside the lab.
The whole area is wired
with pressure sensors.
There's no way to get in
without being detected.
-But I'm more than happy to...
-Do not attempt to get inside.
I need you to detonate a bunker bomb
at the south end of the facility.
It should cause a nice distraction
and seal off the bomb area,
while we come in through the hatches.
You can count on me.
Rex and his men will be
right behind you, Snips.
They'll have your back.
Come on, we'd better hurry.
Padmé may be lost, Anakin.
Don't risk the mission trying to rescue her.
I'll take care of the bombs,
you focus on the doctor.
I know what's at stake here.
(GRUNTING)
(WHIRRING)
Now!
(ALARM BLARING)
We have a breach!
All droids to hatch number one!
Friends of yours, I assume.
They arrived quicker
than I would have thought.
Meesa come, too!
No! Stay here
and make sure no one escapes.
(EXCLAIMS PETULANTLY)
Okeey-day.
(LIGHTSABERS WHOOSHING)
(LIGHTSABER ACTIVATING)
Ah! It's quiet in here.
Looks like Ahsoka's distraction is working.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
Forward! Come on!
(WEAPONS FIRING)
Fall back!
(GROANS)
(EXCLAIMS QUESTIONINGLY)
(EXCLAIMS IN ALARM)
-Padmé!
-Take another step and your friends die.
(SCREAMS)
Drop your weapons!
Wait!
(SCREAMING)
Do as he says.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
I can't hold them!
(CLATTERING)
-Need some help?
-(SIGHS) So good to see you Master Kenobi.
I realize I won't be able to hold you
for long, Jedi.
That is why I'm going to give you a choice.
Fine with me,
as long as one of the options is killing you.
How about capture me
or save your friends?
(SCREAMS)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS)
Are you okay?
Ani, how about
the next time you rescue me
-before you kill all the battle droids?
-A little thank-you would go a long way.
Things are going well.
The lab is secure, and hopefully
Anakin has reached Padmé by now.
-I'll get the bombs.
-I'll keep the droids occupied!
Grab your blasters.
We need to find that doctor.
CLONE: Well, looks like the bomb room.
OBI-WAN: Yes. And luckily,
they appear inactive.
(ALARM BLARING)
(BEEPING)
I spoke too soon.
Get these deactivated now!
(COMLINK BEEPS)
Anakin, I'm guessing
you didn't capture the doctor.
I'm working on it. Do you have the bombs?
I'm working on it.
Dr. Vindi has remotely activated
the bombs. They're counting down.
-That's great.
-And on top of that,
one of them seems to be missing.
ANAKIN: It's down here somewhere.
Ahsoka, we've got another situation.
Send all the clones to search the facility.
-We've got a...
-Master?
We've got a missing bomb and a
trigger-happy mad doctor on the loose.
Missing bomb?
I saw Dr. Vindi give a little droid a bomb.
You guys split up. Find that droid.
You heard him. Let's move!
(PANTING)
-What?
-Jedi!
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
-Leaving so soon, Doctor?
-You are running out of time.
Catch!
Obi-Wan! Dr. Vindi's escaping!
He's at the landing platform!
All right. I'm on my way!
(BEEPING)
(SNIFFING)
Ooh! Something smells good in here.
Hey, there, little guy.
How about you hand that over to me?
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMS)
-He's getting away!
-No!
(WHIMPERING)
(BEEPING)
Ahsoka, I found the last bomb.
Stay there. I'll get the bomb squad.
(GRATING)
Almost got it.
Don't shoot! If he drops one of those vials,
we're finished.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS) No! Nossa!
You're under arrest, Dr. Vindi.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
(BEEPING)
Yes! The bomb's going off
and we're all going to die!
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Die!
-Oops! What happened?
-REX: Deactivated.
And plenty of time to spare.
(JAR JAR MUMBLES)
-Ahsoka, are you there?
-I'm here, Master.
The bomb has been deactivated.
-Did you find Vindi?
-Deactivated as well.
-Have you seen Padmé?
-She's right next to me.
I'm okay, too. Thanks for asking.
English - SDH