As the Clone War scorches
its destructive path across the galaxy,
it is the Jedi who bring order to the chaos.
Though as the war progresses,
the number of Jedi have declined,
and new younglings are harder to find.
When a youngling is located,
they are brought to the Jedi Temple
and learn quickly
that their true family is now the Jedi Order.
The trials are hard, tests must be passed,
but none is as important as The Gathering.
It is then that a Jedi's path will truly begin.
Hurry, younglings.
You have proved to be
the top of your class,
and so now is the time of The Gathering.
For a Jedi,
there is no greater challenge or honor.
What is The Gathering, Padawan Tano?
Petro,
Ganodi,
Byph,
Katooni,
Zatt,
and Gungi,
the time has come
for you to build your own lightsabers.
- I knew it!
- That's so wizard!
- Whoa!
- I knew it!
Be warned, this is no simple task,
and many perils lie ahead of you.
Where we are going,
there is no place more sacred to the Jedi.
Not the most hospitable place.
I think that's the point.
It's a dead end.
Younglings, outstretch your hands
and focus the Force.
Together, and only together, can we enter.
Now hurry. The sun has already risen,
and we must begin.
Master Yoda.
The Force made physical, a Jedi is.
Comes great responsibility with that. Yes?
Protect others, how does a Jedi? Hmm?
Build your own lightsaber, you shall.
But first, harvest your crystal,
each one of you must.
- See, I told you!
- No, I told you.
Yoda! Wow.
No, I told you.
The heart of the lightsaber, the crystal is.
Focuses the Force from the Jedi, it does.
If Jedi you are to become,
enter the Crystal Cave, you must.
Trust yourself,
trust each other,
and succeed, you will.
Once you have found your crystal,
do not remain inside.
As daylight ends, the door will freeze
over again, and you will be trapped.
For how long?
For one rotation. There will be nothing
anyone can do for you.
How will we know which crystal to pick?
Only you can know which one is yours.
Now hurry.
How do they expect us to find our crystals
when the whole place is made up of ice?
I don't see the big deal though.
I could easily last a night in here.
From my calculations,
taking into account
the planetary movements in this system,
um, the sun only rises
on Ilum every 19 days.
That's a very long night.
Well, I don't know about you lot,
but enough with the chatter.
I'm going to be the first
to get my crystal and get out of here.
Petro, wait.
Maybe we should stay together.
No, thank you. You're on your own.
Come on, we need to keep moving.
You're right. He is selfish.
Uh, which way now?
We don't have much time,
and we have no idea
where the crystals are.
We need to break into groups.
What? No!
Are we Jedi or cowards?
On the count of three,
close your eyes and point to a door,
and that's the direction each of us will go.
One, two, three.
Uh, sorry, Byph.
Looks like you're on your own.
Byph, your instincts
told you to go that way.
You have to follow your instincts.
You shouldn't be afraid of monsters, Byph!
You're a Jedi.
That must be a crystal.
I don't think this is the right way.
We better go back.
Wait. Up there, look!
Something's flashing.
- I can't see anything.
- Why can't you see it?
Maybe because it's your crystal.
They said only we would know.
You'll have to climb.
But up there?
It's just so high.
I can't do that.
I believe in you.
What if I get up there, and there's nothing?
Well, that's a risk you'll have to take.
Hey, you're lucky.
I haven't even seen
anything resembling my crystal yet.
Good luck.
A whistling? I can't hear anything.
You think it's your crystal?
Gungi, no. You'll never make it.
You'll freeze to death if you fall in.
You need to be patient.
See how the sun is setting
and moving away from the lake?
Just like the door we came through,
it's freezing over again.
Once the water freezes over,
you will have very little time
to get your crystal and get out.
Now, excuse me. I have a crystal to find,
and I'm running out of time.
Good luck, Gungi.
This whole thing is ridiculous.
I don't even think there are any crystals.
You hear me?
You just have us walking in circles
until we freeze to death.
I'm never going to find a crystal. Never!
Ah!
Now what?
Looks like I'm the first back
with my crystal. Hmm.
That wasn't so hard.
And the others?
Who knows? I didn't want to gloat
since I found mine so quickly.
Show us.
A crystal, you have found.
Water, you have brought.
But that's impossible.
It was my crystal, I was sure of it.
Hmm.
So certain, were you.
Go back, and closer you must look.
But the door is already half-closed.
Then you better hurry.
Oh!
You can do this, Katooni. You can do it.
That's impossible.
It's saying there's crystals everywhere,
but I can't see anything!
Where? Which way?
Ugh!
You're useless.
Stupid, useless, dumb thing,
can't even find a simple small crystal!
Ugh!
There's so many.
How am I supposed to know
which one is mine?
It's hopeless.
Hopeless.
Well, that's going to take too long.
I'm not afraid.
I can do this.
I'm a Jedi.
I'm one with the Force,
and the Force will guide me.
I'm running out of time. Where is it?
Come on, Zatt.
You're going to have to trust yourself
instead of relying on technology.
You can do it.
I can feel it.
It's close.
I can sense it.
That must be it.
Oh, great!
Ah!
Oh, no. It's a dead end.
Is anyone there?
Can you hear me?
Great! I have my crystal,
but I'll never get out of this place!
Well done, Gungi, but two still remain.
I'm running in circles!
Petro! Petro!
- Katooni?
- Petro, I'm trapped.
Can you help me get out?
I...
I can't. I still haven't found my crystal.
Petro, you can't leave me!
- I have to go.
- Petro, no!
Petro! Petro!
- Will they make it, Master?
- We should help them.
Left the cave, you have.
Help them, you will not.
Come on!
- Katooni. Katooni!
- Petro?
- Petro!
- There's no time.
Put your hand on the ice.
Together, we can break it.
I knew you'd come back.
Come on. The doors are closing.
Petro?
Go ahead. I think I see something.
But it's too late.
Trust me. Go!
I have my crystal, but Petro is still inside.
Give up on your friend, do not.
Petro! You made it!
How did he break the ice?
Only water made solid was the door.
Easy to break, if you have the will.
You said we would be trapped.
Not by the cave, you were,
but by your mind.
Lessons you have learned.
Find courage, you did.
Hope,
patience,
trust,
confidence,
and selflessness. Yes?
Take your crystals back to the Temple
and keep them safe, young Jedi.
- So exciting!
- Yes!
All right!