Evil alliance.
Darth Maul and Savage Opress
escape Obi-Wan Kenobi's assault
once again.
With their plan to build
a crime organization in peril,
the brothers' fate
is about to be changed forever
as they drift, barely alive,
through unknown space.
What are you?
Should we rub 'em out?
No, I want to hear their story.
If they're an enemy of the Jedi,
then they're a friend of mine.
Load 'em up.
Savage...
You're not Jedi.
So what are you?
We are Sith.
Do you serve Count Dooku?
I serve no one.
I thought there could only be two Sith;
a master and an apprentice.
We are brothers.
The true Lords of the Sith.
What happened to your ship?
Destroyed by Jedi.
Do you know which Jedi?
Kenobi.
And what do you seek now, Sith?
Fortune and power.
Repair this one's legs,
and do what you can for the other.
Yes, sir.
Go on.
Get moving.
In time for tea.
Come join me.
Made with the florets of a Cassius tree.
It's good for your health.
Your mark?
The sign of Clan Vizsla.
I am Pre Vizsla.
We are the Death Watch,
descendants of the true warrior faith
all Mandalorians once knew.
Now my people are living in exile
because we will not abandon
our heritage.
Our people were warriors;
strong, feared.
Now they're ruled
by the new Mandalorians
who think that being a pacifist
is a good thing.
They've given away our honor
and tradition
for peace.
Duchess Satine
and her corrupt leadership
are crushing our souls,
destroying our identity.
That is our struggle.
If they are weak, why do you wait?
The duchess has powerful allies,
including your Jedi friend, Kenobi.
He is also responsible for our exile.
Perhaps fortune brought us together.
It is the will of the Force.
We can help you reclaim Mandalore.
And punish Kenobi for his trespasses.
We allied ourselves with Sith before.
Count Dooku, he betrayed us.
Sith are no better than Jedi.
They claim to be powerful,
but we put these two
back together
after the Jedi gutted them.
Doubt will only lead to failure.
Hold!
Our combined strength will be rewarded.
Mandalore will be yours,
and Kenobi, this Sith pretender Dooku,
and all our enemies will fall.
Check on your brother.
We'll put it to a vote.
Rest, apprentice.
You're safe.
Our crash was discovered
by enemies of the Jedi,
and we are in their care.
Are we prisoners?
No.
Allies.
They have much to offer,
including their planet.
They are strong, and unlike pirates,
they possess honor.
Another weakness.
They know nothing of our intentions.
Those revelations will come too late.
I see you have your strength back.
Ugh.
I never got your names.
I am Maul.
This is Savage.
Our brothers are in favor of an alliance
to liberate Mandalore.
This duchess of yours will soon discover
the true burden of peace.
Your people are strong and skilled,
but you will need an army
to free Mandalore.
There are more on Mandalore
who'll join us.
Their help would come too late.
We can assemble an army,
beginning with the Black Sun.
They're a crime syndicate.
Hardly a force to rally with.
They can provide us
with the resources we need
to sustain a war without
the scrutiny of the Republic.
A battalion, brother.
They will serve us well.
We request an audience
with your leaders.
It'll be your funeral.
Why do you come here?
We seek an army.
Fools.
We are not mercenaries.
Dispose of them.
Keep their ships and weapons.
Give me that one's sword.
This is your last opportunity
to join us.
Quiet.
We are the Black Sun!
Hmm.
Very well, then.
It would seem the decision
to join us is now yours.
After careful consideration,
we will join you.
Show us your supplies.
We have our army now.
I have a plan to undermine Satine.
The army is weak.
We are not ready for the duchess.
With my plan,
we won't need a bigger force.
There is only one plan.
One vision.
And it belongs to Death Watch.
Your vision lacks clarity.
Without us, you have no army
and no reason to replace the duchess.
The depth of this opportunity
eludes you.
You shall watch and learn.
More criminals.
Spice dealers connected
to all the crime families
of Coruscant.
The Pykes.
They will be the next to join us.
We know you've been forming an army.
Were you expecting us?
Underworld's a small community.
I have no desire to oppose you.
We come to join you.
Very good.
Then ready our troops.
We leave for Nal Hutta immediately.
Da wanga oo Stuka Crispo,
pa ranna hi dopa.
There are many things
the Hutts influence and possess
that would be useful to us.
Ah'chu apenkee?
We have no credits.
Chut chut,
bargon de moolee-rah?
Your lives
in exchange for Hutt Space
and everything in its borders.
Bunta chupo.
Stoopa yatuka.
Uh!
Ah!
Wah.
Uh!
Killya hooha!
I see negotiations have gone as planned.
Secure this platform!
Ugh!
Gah!
Retreat!
Back inside!
Yah!
Uh!
Whoa!
Ugh!
Come on, let's get out of here.
Ahh.
Let them go.
They're only bounty hunters;
they have no allegiance.
Sir, the Hutts have escaped.
Except one.
Where are the others?
Hopa!
Kill him.
Hagwa.
Give me a location.
Tatooine.
Jabba's palace.
So the only thing that you can tell me
is that I will find Jabba
at Jabba's palace?
Do dee chabwon geesa bonkee bolla.
Give up, Jabba.
You're the only ones left.
Submit or suffer.
Weeteebah fa foonta granee, meendeeya.
The mighty Jabba and the Hutt families
have decided to join you.
Between the Hutts, Black Sun,
and the Pykes,
we'll have a large reserve
of muscle and supplies.
Yes.
Then Mandalore and Kenobi
are still our priority?
They are vital.
I'm curious to hear the rest
of your plan.
The vision has expanded.
You will still rule Mandalore,
and under your protection,
I will command
a new galactic underworld.
Mandalore influences a league
of 2,000 neutral systems.
It gives you a great deal
of options for your enterprise.
You have learned
from your previous oversights.
With their combined forces,
the Republic and the Separatists
will be irrelevant.
Then are we ready?
Mobilize the army.
Send an advanced guard to the capital.
I want a list of targets
vital to Mandalore's security.
Choose wisely.
There will be no second chances.
Stay focused.
Mandalore will soon be ours,
and Maul and his brother
will be dead alongside the duchess.