Going somewhere, Solo?
It's too late.
You should have paid him when you had the chance.
Jabba's put a price on your head so large
every bounty hunter in the galaxy
will be looking for you...
I'm lucky I found you first.
If you give it to me, I might forget I found you.
Jabba's through with you.
He has no time for smugglers
who drop their shipments at the first
sign of an Imperial cruiser.
You can tell that to Jabba.
He may only take your ship.
That's the idea.
I've been looking forward to this for a long time.
Solo, come out of there, Solo!
Have you now.
Han, my boy, you disappoint me.
Why haven't you paid me...
and why did you fry poor Greedo?
Han, I can't make exceptions.
What if everyone who smuggled for me
dropped their cargo at the first sign
of an Imperial starship?
It's not good business.
Han, my boy, you're the best.
So, for an extra twenty percent...
Okay, fifteen percent.
But, if you fail me again...
I'll put a price on your head so big,
you won't be able to go near a civilized system.
Come on!