As the Clone Wars
scorches its destructive path
across the galaxy,
it is the Jedi
who bring order to the chaos.
Though as the war progresses, the
number of Jedi have declined,
and new younglings are harder to find.
When a youngling is located, they
are brought to the Jedi Temple
and learn quickly that their true
family is now the Jedi Order.
The trials are hard.
Tests must be passed.
But none is as important
as The Gathering.
It is then that a Jedi's path
will truly begin.
Hurry, younglings.
You have proved to be
the top of your class.
And so now is the time
of The Gathering.
For a Jedi, there is no greater
challenge or honor.
What is The Gathering, Padawan Tano?
Petro, Ganodi, Byph,
Katooni, Zatt, and Gungi,
the time has come for you
to build your own lightsabers.
I knew it.
That's so wizard.
Whoa!
I knew it.
This is no simple task,
and many perils lie ahead of you.
Where we are going, there is no
place more sacred to the Jedi.
Not the most hospitable place.
I think that's the point.
It's a dead end.
Younglings, outstretch your
hands and focus the Force.
Together, and only together,
can we enter.
Now hurry.
The sun has already risen,
and we must begin.
Master Yoda.
The Force made physical, a Jedi is.
Comes great responsibility
with that, yes?
Protect others, how does a Jedi, hmm?
Build your own lightsaber, you shall.
But first, harvest your crystal,
each one of you must.
- See, I told you.
- Yoda, wow.
- No, I told you.
The heart of the lightsaber,
the crystal is.
Focuses the Force
from the Jedi, it does.
If Jedi you are to become, enter
the crystal cave, you must.
Trust yourself, trust each
other, and succeed, you will.
Once you have found your
crystal, do not remain inside.
As daylight ends, the door will freeze
over again, and you will be trapped.
For how long?
For one rotation.
There will be nothing
anyone can do for you.
How will we know
which crystal to pick?
Only you can know which one is yours.
Now, hurry.
How do they expect us
to find our crystals
when the whole place
is made up of ice?
I don't see the big deal, though.
I could easily last a night in here.
From my calculations, taking into
account the planetary movements
in this system, um... the sun
only rises on Ilum every 19 days.
That's a very long night.
Well, I don't know about you
lad, but enough with the chatter.
I'm gonna be the first to get
my crystal and get out of here.
Petro, wait.
Maybe we should stay together.
No, thank you.
You're on your own.
Come on.
We need to keep moving.
You're right.
He is selfish.
Ugh!
Which way now?
We don't have much time, and we
have no idea where the crystals are.
We need to break into groups.
What?
No.
Are we Jedi or cowards?
On the count of three, close
your eyes and point to a door,
and that's the direction
each of us will go.
One, two, three.
Uh, sorry, Byph.
Looks like you're on your own.
Byph, your instincts
told you to go that way.
You have to follow your instincts.
You shouldn't be
afraid of monsters, Byph.
You're a Jedi.
That must be a crystal.
I don't think this is the right way.
We'd better go back.
Wait.
Up there!
Look!
Something's flashing.
I can't see anything.
Why can't you see it?
Maybe because it's your crystal.
They said only we would know.
You'll have to climb.
But up there?
It's... it's just so high.
I can't do that.
I believe in you.
What if I get up there
and there's nothing?
Well, that's a risk
you'll have to take.
Hey, you're lucky.
I haven't even seen anything
resembling my crystal yet.
Good luck.
A whistling?
I can't hear anything.
You think it's your crystal?
Gungi, no.
You'll never make it.
You'll freeze to death if you fall in.
You need to be patient.
See how the sun is setting
and moving away from the lake?
Just like the door we came
through, it's freezing over again.
Once the water freezes over,
you'll have very little time
to get your crystal and get out.
Now excuse me.
I have a crystal to find.
And I'm running out of time.
Good luck, Gungi.
This whole thing is ridiculous.
I don't even think
there are any crystals.
You hear me?
You just have us walking in
circles until we freeze to death!
I'm never gonna find a crystal, never!
Whoa!
Now what?
Looks like I'm the first back
with my crystal.
That wasn't so hard.
And the others?
Who knows?
I didn't wanna gloat,
since I found mine so quickly.
Show us.
A crystal you have found.
Water you have brought.
But that's impossible.
It was my crystal.
I was sure of it.
Mm.
So certain were you.
Go back, and closer you must look.
But the door is already half closed.
Then you better hurry.
Oh!
You can do this, Katooni.
You can do it.
That's impossible.
It's saying there's crystals
everywhere, but I can't see anything.
Where?
Which way?
Ah!
You're useless!
Stupid, useless, dumb thing.
You can't even find
a simple small crystal.
There's so many.
How am I supposed to know
which one is mine?
It's hopeless, hopeless.
Well, that's going to take too long.
I... I'm not afraid.
I can do this.
I'm a Jedi.
I'm one with the Force,
and the Force will guide me.
I'm running out of time.
Where is it?
Come on, Zatt.
You're gonna have to trust yourself
instead of relying on technology.
You can do it.
I can feel it.
It's close.
I can sense it.
That must be it.
Ah!
Oh, great.
Oh, no.
It's a dead end.
Is anyone there?
Can you hear me?
Great.
I have my crystal, but I'll
never get out of this place.
Well done, Gungi.
But two still remain.
Ugh!
I'm running in circles.
Petro!
Katooni?
I'm trapped.
Can you help me get out?
I...
I can't.
I still haven't found my crystal.
Petro, you can't leave me.
I... I have to go.
Petro, no!
Petro!
Will they make it, Master?
We should help them.
Left the cave, you have.
Help them, you will not.
Come on!
Katooni.
Katooni!
Petro?
Petro!
There's no time.
Put your hand on the ice.
Together, we can break it.
I knew you'd come back.
Come on!
The doors are closing.
Petro?
Go ahead.
I think I see something.
But it's too late.
Trust me.
Go.
I have my crystal,
but Petro is still inside.
Give up on your friend, do not.
Petro!
You made it.
How did he break the ice?
Only water made solid was the door.
Easy to break if you have the will.
You-you said we would be trapped.
Not by the cave you were,
but by your mind.
Lessons, you have learned.
Find courage, you did.
Hope, patience,
trust, confidence, and selflessness.
Yes?
Take your crystals back to the temple
and keep them safe, young Jedi.
- Yes!
- So exciting.
- Yay!
- All right!