ANNOUNCER: Hard-pressed Jedi and
their valiant clone troopers
have thwarted an insidious
Separatist plot to plant bombs
Loaded with the deadly Blue Shadow virus
in key Republic systems.
Obi-Wan Kenobi and Anakin Skywalker
have captured the vile scientist
behind the nefarious scheme,
Dr. Nuvo Vindi.
Now, the Jedi prepare to transport Vindi
to the Republic capital for trial.
That was close.
If that virus had escaped,
everyone on Naboo would be dead now.
Oh, well, just another boring day
saving the universe.
All right, let's take
this slemo back to Theed
so we can help Padmé
and Ahsoka clean up down there.
Senator, you should see this.
It's one of the virus bombs.
It looks like the chamber
that holds the virus is missing.
-A droid must have taken it.
-PADMÉ: Sound the alarm!
(ALARM BLARING)
CLONE 1: How could droids have gotten
a hold of the virus containers?
CLONE 2: I don't know, but I don't want
to be around when they set it off.
CLONE 1: We've already taken
the virus containers out of these bombs.
CLONE 2: We'll just have
to check them again.
The virus is liberated.
(LAUGHS)
You are doomed, young Jedi,
along with the rest of the planet.
(ALARM BLARING)
Hey, you! Get away from there!
(RUMBLING)
What was that?
(ALARM BLARING)
Virus leak.
Get to the safe room, come on!
REX: There's the safe room.
CLONE: No chance.
-REX: Hurry, the doors are closing!
-Don't worry...
Get inside, Captain!
Hurry!
Ahsoka, what is going on down there?
AHSOKA: The droids released the virus,
but we managed to seal the lab.
-And Padmé?
-Haven't heard from her since the bomb.
Anakin, can you hear me? Anakin?
ANAKIN: Padmé, I'm here. Are you all right?
(JAR JAR SCREAMING)
Yes, for the time being.
Jar Jar and I were in a safety chamber
when the alarm went off.
We're wearing protective suits.
The virus is loose, but Ahsoka has
sealed off the entire facility.
Yes, but any remaining droids
will try to break out.
I'll do what I can to stop them.
I cannot let that virus escape.
Be careful.
(JAR JAR EXCLAIMING IN PANIC)
Put this on.
Come on, Jar Jar.
We're going to find Ahsoka.
We'll need her help to find those droids.
Where's the antidote, Vindi?
(LAUGHS)
You mistake my role, Jedi.
My job was to manufacture a plague,
not to cure it.
-We don't have time for games.
-Patience, Anakin.
There's more than one way
to skin a womp rat.
I said, where?
Yes, kill me now
and spare these old bones
the Blue Shadow's dire embrace,
because once the first droid breaks out
of that laboratory,
all Naboo is doomed.
Anakin, the fastest way
to save Senator Amidala and Ahsoka
is to get Vindi back to the capital
and find an actual antidote.
(ALARM BLARING)
No, no, no! Some of the virus got in here!
We didn't close the door fast enough!
We may be dead men,
but we could still stop those droids.
Don't worry.
My master will find a cure for this virus.
We're not dead yet.
PADMÉ: (ON COMLINK) Is anyone out there?
-Can anyone hear...
-Senator Amidala!
We're trapped in a safe room
at the end of Complex B.
We'll be right there.
Are you contaminated?
(CLONES COUGHING)
I'm afraid so.
(COUGHING)
Dr. Vindi, you'll pay for your treachery.
Take him away.
-Now we'll need to find an antidote.
-I think I found an answer for you.
So you think you found a cure?
Possibly. A little-known extract
made from reeksa root,
a weed-like vine found only on Lego,
the world of a thousand moons,
deep in Separatist-controlled space.
Let's go.
-You must move cautiously if you...
-There's no time for caution.
My Padawan is trapped down there,
and so is Padmé...
I mean Senator Amidala.
I applaud your courage,
General Skywalker, but it's suicide.
Once we contain the virus,
we can send troops.
-No. Obi-Wan and I can handle it.
-I concur, Anakin.
Padmé and Ahsoka will be fine.
They will be if we succeed.
DROID 1: All the doors are locked.
How are we going to get out?
DROID 2: It's not our problem.
DROID 1: Boy, that's a relief.
(COUGHS)
Senator Amidala, where are you?
-We're right outside your safety room.
-Can you get the door open?
Go ahead, Jar Jar.
(BUZZING)
(COUGHING)
I'm sorry, Ahsoka.
Don't worry about us, Senator.
We still have a job to do.
There aren't very many droids left.
We saw some heading
toward the south entrance.
As long as we're able,
we'll help you destroy those droids
before they breach the compound.
You take the north corridor,
and we'll take the south.
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
The droids are close.
I can hear them cutting through the wall.
(WEAPONS FIRING)
REX: Stop!
PADMÉ: Don't open that hatch.
Ha! Too late.
(DROID SCREAMS)
OBI-WAN: There it is. Lego.
What do you make of this?
It looks like a graveyard of ships.
-Let's go.
-Anakin.
(FOOTSTEPS MARCHING)
ANAKIN: Not good.
ALL: Welcome to Lego. Roger, roger.
Anakin, wait. Wait!
-Welcome to Lego. Roger, roger.
(DROIDS CHANTING)
-Welcome to Lego.
Very impressive.
You just destroyed 17 defenseless
battle droids without suffering a scratch.
Welcome...
Eighteen, actually.
The venerable Jaybo Hood
requests an audience.
-Jaybo?
Hey! Do you guys have any idea
how long it took me
to repurpose those droids?
-You're Jaybo?
-Well, do you?
I apologize for my friend's
rather rash behavior.
Nine months, man.
It took me nine months.
(CLATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Oh, that's our cue.
Channel two.
(STATIC WARBLING)
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYING)
ANAKIN: How'd a kid like you come by
this many battle droids, anyway?
Simple. When the Separatists took off,
they left all this junk behind.
I got a whole warehouse
full of them right over there.
So you programmed them to serve you?
No reason to let a good droid rust, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Looks like you used a macro protocol
to wipe them all simultaneously.
-Impressive.
-I see you know your droids.
You're Jedi, aren't you?
Want me to show you how I did it?
Perhaps another time.
What we need now is reeksa root.
Do you know where we can find some?
Here, there. Everywhere.
(REGGAE MUSIC PLAYING)
We don't have time for games, kid.
Where's the root?
What my friend is trying to say
is that we are in a bit of a hurry.
-(CHUCKLES) Not anymore, you're not.
-Look, you little...
This system is haunted,
cursed, whatever...
Anyway, Jedi or not,
no one gets off this rock alive.
-Not past Drol.
-Drol.
-Drol?
-Yeah, Drol.
The phantom ruler of Lego.
He destroys anything
that leaves the planet.
Fifty of the best star pilots
in the galaxy have tried.
Fifty tried,
fifty died.
I suppose that explains
the ruined ships in the moon belt.
First things first.
We'll have to deal with this Drol later.
(LIGHTSABERS WHOOSHING)
-Mesa help.
-Jar Jar, no.
(JAR JAR EXCLAIMS)
(GAS HISSING)
Senator!
REX: Senator,
your suit's been compromised.
(GASPS)
I'm so sorry.
Don't blame yourself.
These things tend to happen
in a war zone.
-Are you coming?
-You've got to be kidding.
No way I'm going down there.
(GRUNTING) Are you trying
to tell us something?
Don't worry, it's simple.
Follow the vines to the bottom,
dig up the roots,
but don't touch the vine.
Aside from the obvious, why not?
Because the plants don't like it
and they have big, sharp teeth.
Teeth?
This is getting better by the minute.
And watch out for the flying Xandu.
-What's a Xandu?
-I'm not sure.
(RUMBLING)
(SCREECHES)
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa!
Master, hop on.
OBI-WAN: This isn't going to work.
DROID: How are you doing up there?
I'm almost through.
There they are!
Whoa!
(CLATTERING)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
-PADMÉ: Ahsoka?
-(GASPS) I'm all right.
There, those are the roots
we're looking for.
(WINGS FLAPPING)
Oh, poodoo.
(GRUNTING)
(CRACKING)
(RUMBLING)
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't take too long with that.
I'll go as fast as I can.
(SCREECHING)
Anakin, hurry!
-Anakin, now!
-Okay, okay.
Got it.
(ROARING)
-Hold still.
-We've got to get out of here now.
(SCREECHING)
(LIGHTSABERS ACTIVATING)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS WITH RELIEF)
You made it! I knew you would.
Oh, did you?
Place dried up once
the spice convoys stopped running.
Out here, we're just one of the millions
of little backwaters no one cares about.
Those of us who are left
can't leave because of the curse.
Cursed we are. The planet is cursed.
Cursed by whom, my twitchy friend?
The ghost of Drol, that's who.
A ghost?
The spirit of the thousand moons.
Our protector and destroyer.
-If you ask me, it sounds like a load of...
-Superstition?
That's one word for it.
Superstition, you say?
Can't hold on much... Someone help me!
(GROANS)
That was Taquito. He was a friend of mine.
Try to leave this planet,
and your fate will be the same.
They'll never make it past Drol.
The ghost of Drol
may be a local superstition,
but something real blew up those ships.
Real, we can handle.
-Too bad, I really liked those guys.
-ANAKIN: Thanks for your help, kid.
Couldn't have done it without you.
-Have you run into Drol yet?
-Not to worry, Jaybo.
(BEEPING NERVOUSLY)
What's the matter, Artoo?
Afraid of a ghost?
Drol is just a superstition.
-There's our ghost!
-Lasers!
OBI-WAN: We've triggered an energy field.
Oh, no!
Turn the ship around!
We'll never make it through.
The Separatists
must have installed those lasers
to prevent people from leaving the planet.
They're coming back!
(WEAKLY) Master, can you hear me?
Artoo, amplify the signal.
(WHIRRING)
We've destroyed all the battle droids
inside the compound, Master.
Naboo is safe from further contamination.
I repeat, Naboo is safe.
(COUGHING)
Promise me that
no one will ever open this bunker.
Goodbye, Anakin. I...
(COUGHS)
No!
We'll borrow a power converter
from Jaybo and reprogram it to feed our...
-Slow down, Anakin.
-Slow down? Slow down?
You saw them, Master. They're dying.
A great leap forward often
requires first taking two steps back.
And, sometimes, all it requires
is the will to jump.
At least hear me out on this.
Citizens of Lego, Drol is not a ghost.
Rather, it is a Separatist security system.
Nonsense. You were lucky to escape alive,
simple as that.
And who says we didn't
make our own luck?
The ghost of Drol does, that's who.
Did anyone inhabit Lego's moons
before the Separatists arrived?
-The angels, of course.
-Angels?
We were a peaceful people before
the Separatists drove us from our homes
and stole our moon.
And which moon was that?
Millius Prime.
The primary node,
it must be near Millius Prime.
Hmm. Vulture droids. Jaybo,
can you reactivate those Vulture droids?
Sure, I can even fly them
by remote control.
Good. We can have Artoo fly the Vulture
droids as a decoy into the laser field,
and since we know
what we're up against this time,
we can destroy the laser emitter.
And cut a path right to Millius Prime.
(ALL COUGHING)
What a waste!
(SIGHING) With all due respect, Senator,
it's what these men were born to do.
I hope that their sacrifice
brings us closer to peace.
(AHSOKA COUGHING)
-It will, Padmé. You must believe that...
-Ahsoka!
-Ready, General Kenobi.
-Jaybo, activate the droids.
(BEEPS)
Transfer control
of the Vulture droids to Artoo.
(WHIRRING)
Artoo, intercept the lasers.
(BEEPING)
Send the Vulture droids
directly into the laser generator.
Whoa! You guys okay? Guys?
ANAKIN: We're fine, kid.
I'm afraid you'll need
some new droids to boss around, Jaybo.
The ones you lent us are
pretty much toast.
(ALL CHEERING)
But the good news is that you are now
free to leave Lego whenever you choose.
Artoo, set a course for Naboo.
(R2-D2 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
Padmé.
I spoke with the medical droid.
He expects you to make a full recovery.
I never lost faith in you. None of us did.
Well, that's good to hear,
'cause there were a few moments
where we weren't so sure of ourselves.
Well, you did make it.
By the way, your Padawan was brilliant.
I trust I'll see you soon,
General Skywalker.
Of course, my lady.
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
I heard you were quite brave
fending off the battle droids, Jar Jar.
Really?
Senator Amidala suggested
we offer you training
to help hone your skills with a blaster.
-Really?
-Really.
Oh, boy! Ima gonna be trained!
I am not training him.
You did a fantastic job today, Snips.
All thanks to your training, Master.
Yeah, you're right, I probably
do deserve most of the credit,
but not all of it.
Good thing I know you don't mean
everything you say.
Pilot, get these two out of here.
Thank you, Master.
English - SDH