Lock onto him, R2.
Master, General Grievous's ship is directly ahead-
the one crawling
with vulture droids.
Oh, I see it.
Oh, this is going to be easy.
- Oddball, do you copy?
- Copy, Red Leader.
Mark my position.
Form your squad up behind me.
We're on your tail,
General Kenobi.
Set S-foils in attack position.
This is where the fun begins.
Let them pass between us.
They're all over me. Get them off my-
- I'm gonna go help them out.
- No.
No, they are doing their job
so we can do ours.
Missiles. Pull up.
- They overshot us.
- They're coming around.
All right, R4.
No, no, no, no-
No, nothing too fancy.
Surge all power units, R2.
Stand by reverse thrusters.
We got 'em, R2.
Flying is for droids.
- I'm hit. Anakin?
- I see them. Buzz droids.
R4, be careful.
You have a-
Oh, dear.
They're shutting down
all the controls.
- Move to the right so I can
get a clear shot at them.
- The mission.
Get to the command ship. Get the chancellor.
I'm running out of tricks here.
Oh! In the name of-
- Hold your fire! You're not helping here.
- I agree. Bad idea.
I can't see a thing.
My cockpit's fogging.
They're all over me.
Anakin!
- Move to the right.
- Hold on, Anakin. You're gonna get us both killed.
Get out of here.
There's nothing more you can do.
I'm not leaving
without you, Master.
Get him, R2.
Watch out.
R2, hit the buzz droid's
center eye.
- Yeah, you got him!
- Great, R2.
The general's command ship
is dead ahead.
Well, have you noticed
the shields are still up?
Sorry, Master.
Oh, I have a bad feeling
about this.
There they are.
Get them.
R2, locate the chancellor.
The chancellor's signal is coming from right there-
the observation platform
at the top of that spire.
I sense Count Dooku.
- I sense a trap.
- Next move?
Spring the trap.
R2, go back.
I need you to stay with the ship.
Here. Take this
and wait for orders.
What's the situation, Captain?
Two Jedi have landed in the main hangar bay.
We're tracking them.
Just as Count Dooku predicted.
Destroyers.
Drop your weapons.
I said drop 'em.
- Roger.
- Roger, roger.
Roger, roger.
Those are Jedi fighters
all right.
- Did you press the stop button?
- No. Did you?
- No.
- Well, there's more than one way out of here.
We don't want to get out.
We want to get moving.
R2, activate elevator 31174.
- Come in, R2.
- What that?
R2, do you copy?
R2, activate
the elevator number...
31174.
Get back to work.
That nothin'.
Activate the elevator 31174.
R2, we-
Always on the move.
R2, switch on the comlink.
R2, can you hear me?
R2?
Whoa!
R2! R2!
Stop. Stop.
R2, we need to be going up.
Hands up, Jedi.
R2, do you copy?
R2, do you hear me?
R2, we need to be going up, not down.
Hey, you!
Now, that's better.
You stupid little astro droid.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's you.
My eyes! My eyes!
- What was that all about?
- Well, R2 has been-
- Uh, no loose wire jokes.
- Did I say anything?
- He's trying.
- I didn't say anything.
- Chancellor.
- Are you all right?
Count Dooku.
- This time we will do it together.
- I was about to say that.
Get help. You're no match for him.
He's a Sith lord.
Chancellor Palpatine,
Sith lords are our speciality.
Your swords, please.
We don't want to make a mess of things
in front of the chancellor.
You won't get away
this time, Dooku.
I've been looking forward
to this.
My powers have doubled since
the last time we met, Count.
Good. Twice the pride,
double the fall.
Get-
I sense great fear
in you, Skywalker.
You have hate.
You have anger.
But you don't use them.
Good, Anakin. Good.
Kill him.
Kill him now.
I shouldn't.
Do it.
You did well, Anakin.
He was too dangerous
to be kept alive.
Yes, but he was
an unarmed prisoner.
I shouldn't have done that.
It's not the Jedi way.
It is only natural. He cut off your arm,
and you wanted revenge.
It wasn't
the first time, Anakin.
Remember what you told me
about your mother and the Sand People?
Now we must leave before
more security droids arrive.
Anakin,
there's no time.
We must get off this ship
before it's too late.
- He seems to be all right.
- Leave him, or we'll never make it.
His fate will be
the same as ours.
Prepare for attack!
All batteries, fire!
Fire!
Elevator's not working.
R2, activate elevator 3224.
- Reverse stabilizers.
- Reversing stabilizers.
Magnetize!
Fire the emergency
booster engines.
We're leveling out, sir.
Oh!
Easy. We're in a bit of a situation here.
- Did I miss something?
- Hold on.
- What is that?
- Uh, oops.
R2. R2, shut down
the elevator.
Too late. Jump!
Let's see if we can find something
in the hangar bay that's still flyable.
R2, get down here.
R2, do you copy?
General, we found the Jedi.
- They're in hallway 328.
- Activate ray shields.
Ray shields.
Wait a minute.
How did this happen?
- We're smarter than this.
- Apparently not.
- I say patience.
- Patience?
Yes. R2 will be along
in a few moments...
and then... he'll release
the ray shields.
See? No problem.
Don't move.
Ow!
Do you have a plan "B"?
Ah, yes.
The negotiator.
General Kenobi.
We've been waiting for you.
Excuse me.
- That wasn't much of a rescue.
- You're welcome.
And-
Anakin Skywalker.
I was expecting someone with
your reputation to be a little... older.
General Grievous.
You're shorter than I expected.
Jedi scum.
We have a job to do, Anakin.
Try not to upset him.
Your lightsabers will make
a fine addition to my collection.
Not this time.
And this time, you won't escape.
R2.
Crush them!
Make them suffer!
Come. Now!
- Stay at your stations!
- Whoa!
Get him! Get him!
Ow!
Run!
- Don't bother with them. Keep the ship in orbit.
- Yes, sir.
You lose, General Kenobi.
Get out of here! Run!
Time to abandon ship.
All the escape pods have been launched.
Grievous. Can you fly a cruiser like this?
- You mean, do I know how to land
what's left of this thing?
- Well?
Well, under the circumstances,
I'd say the ability to pilot this thing is irrelevant.
Strap yourselves in.
Open all hatches.
Extend all flaps and drag fins.
We lost something.
Not to worry. We are still
flying half a ship.
Now we're really picking up speed.
Eight plus 60.
- We're in the atmosphere.
- Grab that. Keep us level.
Steady.
Easy, R2.
5000. Fire ships on
the left and the right.
- We'll take you in.
- Copy that.
- Landing strip, straight ahead.
- We're coming in too hot.
Another happy landing.
- Are you coming, Master?
- Oh, no. I'm not brave enough for politics.
I have to report
to the council.
Besides, someone needs
to be the poster boy.
Hold on.
This whole operation was your idea.
Let us not forget, Anakin,
that you rescued me from the buzz droids.
And you killed Count Dooku,
and you rescued the chancellor...
carrying me unconscious
on your back.
All because of
your training.
Anakin, let's be fair.
Today you were the hero...
and you deserve your glorious day
with the politicians.
All right. But you owe me one, and not for
saving your skin for the 10th time.
Ninth time. That business
on Cato Neimoidia doesn't- doesn't count.
I'll see you
at the briefing.
Chancellor Palpatine,
are you all right?
Yes. Thanks to your
two Jedi knights.
They killed Count Dooku,
but General Grievous has escaped once again.
General Grievous will run and hide,
as he always does. He's a coward.
But with Count Dooku dead,
he is the leader of the droid army.
And I assure you, the senate will vote
to continue the war as long as Grievous is alive.
Then the Jedi Council will make
finding Grievous our highest priority.
- Watch it.
- Excuse me.
- Come along, R2.
- The Republic cannot praise you enough.
Thank you, Senator Organa.
Well, it couldn't possibly be as bad as all that.
Now there I agree with you.
In fact, I could do with a tune-up myself.
But the fighting will continue
until General Grievous is spare parts.
Well, I will do everything I can in the senate.
- Excuse me.
- Certainly.
Oh, Anakin.
I've missed you, Padmé.
There were whispers
that you'd been killed.
I'm all right.
It feels like we've been
apart for a lifetime.
And it might have been,
if the chancellor hadn't been kidnapped.
I don't think they would have ever
brought us back from the outer rim sieges.
- Wait. Not here.
- Yes, here.
I'm- I'm tired of all this deception.
I don't care if they know we're married.
Anakin, don't say
things like that.
Are you all right?
You're trembling.
What's going on?
Something wonderful
has happened.
Ani, I'm pregnant.
That's-
Well, that's won-
That's wonderful.
What are we gonna do?
We're not gonna worry
about anything right now. All right?
This is a happy moment.
The happiest moment
of my life.
Yes, Lord Sidious?
General Grievous...
I suggest you move
the separatist leaders to Mustafar.
It will be done,
my lord.
The end of the war
is near, General.
But the loss
of Count Dooku-
His death was
a necessary loss.
Soon I will have
a new apprentice-
one far younger
and more powerful.
Ani, I want to have our baby
back home on Naboo.
We can go to the lake country
where no one will know...
where we can be safe.
I can go early
and fix up the baby's room.
I know the perfect spot.
Right by the gardens.
You are so... beautiful.
It's only because
I'm so in love.
No.
No, it's because
I'm so in love with you.
So love has blinded you?
Well, that's not
exactly what I meant.
But it's probably true.
Anakin, help me!
What's bothering you?
Nothing.
I remember when
I gave this to you.
How long is it gonna take
for us to be honest with each other?
It was a dream.
Bad?
Like the ones I used to have
about my mother...
just before she died.
And?
And it was about you.
Tell me.
It was only a dream.
You die in childbirth.
And the baby?
I don't know.
It was only a dream.
I won't let this one
become real.
This baby will change
our lives.
I doubt the queen will continue
to allow me to serve in the senate.
And if the council discovers
you're the father, you'll be expelled-
I-I know. I know.
Do you think Obi-Wan
might be able to help us?
We don't need his help.
Our baby is a blessing.
Premonitions?
Premonitions. Hmm.
These visions you have-
They're of pain,
suffering.
Death.
Yourself you speak of,
or someone you know?
Someone.
Close to you?
Yes.
Careful you must be when
sensing the future, Anakin.
The fear of loss is a path
to the dark side.
I won't let these visions
come true, Master Yoda.
Death is
a natural part of life.
Rejoice for those around you
who transform into the Force.
Mourn them, do not.
Miss them, do not.
Attachment leads
to jealousy.
The shadow of greed that is.
What must I do, Master Yoda?
Train yourself
to let go...
of everything
you fear to lose.
You've missed the report on the outer rim sieges.
I'm sorry. I was held up.
- I have no excuse.
- In short, they are going very well.
Saleucami has fallen, and Master Vos
has moved his troops to Boz Pity.
What's wrong, then?
The senate is expected...
to vote more executive powers
to the chancellor today.
Well, that can only mean less deliberating
and more action. Is that bad?
It'll make it easier
for us to end this war.
Be careful of
your friend Palpatine.
Be careful of what?
- He has requested your presence.
- What for?
- He would not say.
- He didn't inform the council?
- That's unusual, isn't it?
- All of this is unusual.
And it's making me feel uneasy.
I hope you trust me, Anakin.
Of course.
I need your help, son.
What do you mean?
- I'm depending on you.
- For what? I don't understand.
To be the eyes, ears
and voice of the Republic.
Anakin...
I'm appointing you to be my personal
representative on the Jedi Council.
Me? A master?
I'm overwhelmed, sir.
But the council elects its own members.
They'll never accept this.
I think they will.
They need you.
More than you know.
Allow this appointment lightly
the council does not.
Disturbing is this move
by Chancellor Palpatine.
I understand.
You are on this council,
but we do not grant you the rank of master.
What?
How can you do this?
This is outrageous.
It's unfair.
How can you be on the council
and not be a master?
Take a seat,
young Skywalker.
Forgive me, Master.
We have surveyed all systems in the Republic...
but have found no sign
of General Grievous.
Hiding in the outer rim
Grievous is.
The outlying systems
you must sweep.
We do not have
many ships to spare.
What about the droid attack
on the Wookiees?
It is critical we send an attack group
there immediately.
He's right. It's a system
we cannot afford to lose.
Go I will.
Good relations
with the Wookiees I have.
It's settled then.
Yoda will take a battalion of clones...
to reinforce
the Wookiees on Kashyyyk.
May the Force
be with us all.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Put me on the council
and not make me a master?
It's never been done in the history of the Jedi.
It's insulting.
Oh, calm down, Anakin.
You have been given a great honor.
To be on the council at your age-
it's never happened before.
The fact of the matter is
you are too close to the chancellor.
The council doesn't like it
when he interferes in Jedi affairs.
- I swear to you, I didn't ask
to be put on the council.
- But it's what you wanted.
Your friendship with Chancellor Palpatine
seems to have paid off.
That has nothing
to do with this.
The only reason the council
has approved your appointment...
is because
the chancellor trusts you.
- And?
- Anakin, I am on your side.
- I didn't want to put you in this situation.
- What situation?
The council wants you to report on
all the chancellor's dealings.
They want to know
what he's up to.
They want me to spy
on the chancellor?
- But that's treason.
- We are at war, Anakin.
Why didn't the council give me
this assignment when we were in session?
This assignment
is not to be on record.
The chancellor
is not a bad man, Obi-Wan.
He befriended me.
He's watched out for me ever since I arrived here.
That is why
you must help us.
Anakin, our allegiance is to the senate,
not to its leader...
who has managed to stay in office
long after his term has expired.
The senate demanded
that he stay longer.
Yes, but use your feelings, Anakin.
Something is out of place.
You're asking me to do something
against the Jedi code...
against the Republic,
against a mentor and a friend.
That's what's out of place here.
Why are you asking this of me?
The council
is asking you.
Anakin did not take to his new assignment
with much enthusiasm.
It's very dangerous, putting them together.
I don't think
the boy can handle it.
I don't trust him.
With all due respect, Master,
is he not the chosen one?
Is he not to destroy the Sith
and bring balance to the Force?
So the prophecy says.
A prophecy
that misread could have been.
He will not let me down.
He never has.
I hope right you are.
Sometimes I wonder
what's happening to the Jedi order.
I think this war is destroying
the principles of the Republic.
Have you ever considered
that we may be on the wrong side?
What do you mean?
What if the democracy we thought
we were serving no longer exists...
and the Republic has become
the very evil we've been fighting to destroy?
I don't believe that.
And you're sounding
like a separatist.
This war represents
a failure to listen.
Now you're closer
to the chancellor than anyone.
Please, ask him to stop the fighting
and let diplomacy resume.
Don't ask me to do that.
Make a motion in the senate,
where that kind of a request belongs.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Don't do this. Don't shut me out.
Let me help you.
Hold me.
Like you did
by the lake on Naboo.
So long ago, when there was
nothing but our love.
No politics,
no plotting, no war.
- You wanted to see me, Chancellor.
- Yes, Anakin. Come closer.
I have good news.
Our clone intelligence units have discovered
the location of General Grievous.
He's hiding
in the Utapau system.
At last.
We'll be able to capture
that monster and end this war.
I would worry about
the collective wisdom of the council...
if it didn't select you
for this assignment.
You're the best
choice, by far.
Hmm. Sit down.
Leave us.
Anakin...
you know I'm not able
to rely on the Jedi Council.
If they haven't included you
in their plot, they soon will.
I'm not sure
I understand.
You must sense
what I have come to suspect.
The Jedi Council want
control of the Republic.
They're planning
to betray me.
- I don't think that-
- Anakin.
Search your feelings.
You know, don't you?
- I know they don't trust you.
- Hmm. Or the senate.
Or the Republic, or democracy,
for that matter.
I have to admit,
my trust in them has been shaken.
Why?
They asked you
to do something...
that made you feel dishonest,
didn't they?
They asked you to spy
on me, didn't they?
I don't, uh-
I don't know
what to say.
Remember back
to your early teachings.
All who gain power
are afraid to lose it.
- Even the Jedi.
- The Jedi use their power for good.
Good is a point of view,
Anakin.
The Sith and the Jedi
are similar in almost every way...
including their quest
for greater power.
The Sith rely on their passion
for their strength.
They think inwards-
only about themselves.
And the Jedi don't?
The Jedi are selfless.
They only care about others.
Did you ever hear the tragedy
of Darth Plagueis the Wise?
- No.
- I thought not.
It's not a story
the Jedi would tell you.
It's a Sith legend.
Darth Plagueis...
was a dark lord of the Sith
so powerful and so wise...
he could use the Force to
influence the midi-chlorians...
to create... life.
He had such a knowledge
of the dark side...
he could even keep
the ones he cared about...
from dying.
He could actually...
save people from death?
The dark side of the Force is
a pathway to many abilities...
some consider to be unnatural.
Wh-What happened to him?
He became so powerful...
the only thing
he was afraid of was...
losing his power.
Which eventually,
of course, he did.
Unfortunately, he taught his apprentice
everything he knew.
Then his apprentice
killed him in his sleep.
It's ironic.
He could save
others from death...
but not himself.
Is it possible
to learn this power?
Not from a Jedi.
All Red units, over here!
Palpatine thinks General Grievous is on Utapau?
A partial message was intercepted
in a diplomatic packet...
- from the chairman of Utapau.
- Hmm.
Act on this we must.
The capture of General Grievous
will end this war.
Quickly and decisively
we should proceed.
The chancellor has requested...
that I lead the campaign.
The council will make up
its own mind who is to go...
not the chancellor.
A master is needed,
with more experience.
I concur.
Master Kenobi should go.
- I agree.
- Aye.
Aye.
Very well. Council adjourned.
- The droids have started up
their main power generators.
- Then now the time is, Commander.
- Yes, sir.
Charge!
Head for cover!
- You're gonna need me on this one, Master.
- Oh, I agree.
- However, it may turn out
just to be a wild bantha chase.
- Master.
I've disappointed you. Uh, I haven't been
very appreciative of your training.
I've been arrogant,
and I apologize.
I've just been so frustrated
with the council.
You are strong and wise, Anakin,
and I am very proud of you.
I have trained you since
you were a small boy.
I have taught you
everything I know.
And you have become a far greater Jedi
than I could ever hope to be.
But be patient, Anakin.
It will not be long before the council
makes you a Jedi master.
Obi-Wan.
May the Force be with you.
Good-bye, old friend.
Fortunately, most of the cities are
concentrated on this small continent here.
- On the far side.
- I'll keep them distracted until you get there.
- Just don't take too long.
- Come on. When have I ever let you down?
Very well.
The burden is on me not to destroy
all the droids until you arrive.
Save your energy.
I can't.
Don't give up, Padmé.
Obi-Wan's been here,
hasn't he?
He came by this morning.
What did he want?
He's worried about you.
He says you've been under a lot of stress.
I feel lost.
Lost? What do you mean?
Obi-Wan and the council
don't trust me.
They trust you
with their lives.
Something's happening.
I'm not the Jedi
I should be.
I want more.
And I know I shouldn't.
You expect too much
of yourself.
- I found a way to save you.
- Save me?
From my nightmares.
Is that what's
bothering you?
I won't lose you, Padmé.
I'm not gonna die
in childbirth, Ani.
- I promise you.
- No, I promise you.
Greetings, young Jedi.
What brings you to
our remote sanctuary?
Unfortunately, the war.
There's no war here-
unless you brought it with you.
With your kind permission,
I should like some fuel...
and to use your city as a base as I search
nearby systems for General Grievous.
He is here.
We are being held hostage.
- They are watching us.
- I understand.
Tenth level,
thousands of battle droids.
Tell your people
to take shelter.
If you have warriors,
now is the time.
Take the fighter back to the ship.
Tell Cody I've made contact.
- Is he bringing additional warriors?
- He didn't say.
It won't be long before the armies
of the Republic track us here.
I am sending you to the Mustafar system
in the outer rim.
It is a volcanic planet.
- You will be safe there.
- Safe?
Hmph! Chancellor Palpatine
managed to escape your grip, General.
Without Count Dooku, I have doubts
about your ability to keep us safe.
Be thankful, Viceroy...
you have not
found yourself in my grip.
Your ship is waiting.
Hello there.
General Kenobi.
You are a bold one.
Kill him.
Back away.
I will deal with
this Jedi slime myself.
Your move.
You fool.
I've been trained in your
Jedi arts by Count Dooku.
Attack, Kenobi.
Army or not...
you must realize
you are doomed.
Oh, I don't think so.
Uh-oh.
Hyah!
Cover that corner.
Master Windu, may I interrupt?
General Kenobi has made contact
with General Grievous...
and we have begun our attack.
Thank you, Commander.
Anakin, deliver this report
to the chancellor.
His reaction will give us
a clue to his intentions.
Yes, Master.
I sense a plot
to destroy the Jedi.
The dark side of the Force
surrounds the chancellor.
If he does not give up his emergency powers
after the destruction of Grievous...
then he should be removed
from office.
The Jedi Council would have to
take control of the senate...
in order to secure
a peaceful transition.
To a dark place this line
of thought will carry us.
Hmm. Great care
we must take.
Chancellor.
We've just received a report
from Master Kenobi.
He has engaged
General Grievous.
We can only hope that Master Kenobi
is up to the challenge.
I should be there with him.
It's upsetting to me
to see that the council...
doesn't seem to fully appreciate
your talents.
Don't you wonder
why they won't make you a Jedi master?
I wish I knew.
More and more I get
the feeling that...
I'm being excluded
from the council.
I know there are things about the Force
that they're not telling me.
They don't trust you, Anakin.
They see your future.
They know your power
will be too strong to control.
You must break through the fog of lies
the Jedi have created around you.
Let me help you to know
the subtleties of the Force.
How do you know the ways of the Force?
My mentor taught me
everything about the Force.
Even the nature of
the dark side.
You know the dark side?
Anakin...
if one is to understand
the great mystery...
one must study
all its aspects...
not just the dogmatic
narrow view of the Jedi.
If you wish to become
a complete and wise leader...
you must embrace a larger view
of the Force.
Be careful of the Jedi,
Anakin.
Only through me...
can you achieve a power
greater than any Jedi.
Learn to know
the dark side of the Force...
and you will be able to
save your wife...
from certain death.
What did you say?
Use my knowledge.
I beg you.
You're the Sith lord.
I know what's been troubling you.
Listen to me.
Don't continue to be a pawn
of the Jedi Council.
Ever since I've known you,
you've been searching for a life...
greater than that
of an ordinary Jedi.
A life of significance...
of conscience.
- Are you going to kill me?
- I would certainly like to.
I know you would.
I can feel your anger.
It gives you focus...
makes you stronger.
- I'm going to turn you over to the Jedi Council.
- Of course. You should.
But you're not sure
of their intentions, are you?
I will quickly discover
the truth of all this.
You have great wisdom,
Anakin.
Know the power
of the dark side.
Power to save Padmé.
Aaah!
So uncivilized.