[orchestral fanfare]
[star wars theme]
¶
Male announcer:
Ahsoka tano captured!
While on the run
to prove her innocence,
Padawan tano teamed up
with the deadly asajj ventress
To find the rogue jedi
who framed ahsoka for murder.
The jedi council
sent anakin skywalker
And master plo koon
to track ahsoka down
And bring her back
to the temple.
Now captured and imprisoned,
Ahsoka faces punishment
for crimes she did not commit.
- The senate requests
that ahsoka tano be indicted
For acts of treason
against the republic.
- A fair trial
padawan tano will have
In accordance
with jedi tradition.
- Ah, yes, jedi tradition.
I'm afraid, master yoda,
That the senate believes
that an internal jedi trial
Would seem biased.
Therefore, the senate asks
That the council expel
ahsoka tano from the jedi order
So that she may be put
to a republic military tribunal,
Where she will receive
more impartial judgment.
- And who would represent ahsoka
in this tribunal, admiral?
- That would be up
to the council, general,
But I would recommend
someone outside the order.
- Of course.
- The council will act
as they deem necessary.
Thank you, admiral.
- Surely we cannot do
what tarkin suggests.
We need to stand together
with ahsoka.
- And yet there's evidence
that she is indeed
The mastermind behind the attack
on the temple.
- She was found in possession
of nanodroid explosives.
This alone is enough
to convict her.
- I understand your sentiment,
obi-wan,
But if the council does
as you suggest,
It could be seen
as an act of opposition
To the senate.
I'm afraid
we have little choice.
- Hmm.
To the chamber of judgment,
Summon skywalker
and his padawan,
And in our decision,
may the force guide us.
[dramatic music]
¶
- You're not helping.
- [groans]
I'm sorry, snips.
I just--I just don't know
what to do.
- It's okay.
I don't either.
[chime resounds]
¶
- Padawan tano,
Serious charges
have been levied against you.
How plead you?
- Not guilty, master.
I would never take the lives
of innocents.
The values of the jedi
are sacred to me.
- There is evidence
to the contrary.
You were alone with
letta turmond when she died.
Can you explain this?
- Someone used the force
against her.
- Which brings us to ventress.
Can you explain your association
with her?
- We had a mutual understanding.
I thought she was helping me.
- Did you she help you acquire
the nanodroid weaponry
Found when you were apprehended,
The same devices used
in the bombing of the temple?
- No, I was set up
and deceived,
As you are being deceived now.
- The question is,
padawan tano,
Who is deceiving us?
Ventress, you, or someone else?
- I am not deceiving you.
I would assume ventress is,
But I can't be sure.
My sense is clouded.
- Clouded by the dark side
These things are,
padawan tano.
Dangerously clouded,
But not just surrounding you,
Surrounding many things
in these times.
- You've already made
your decision, haven't you?
This meeting
is just a formality!
- [sighs]
Reached a decision, we have,
Though not in total agreement
are we.
- It is the council's opinion
That padawan ahsoka tano
has committed sedition
Against the republic,
And thus, she will be expelled
from the jedi order.
- You can't do this!
- Your padawan status
will be stripped from you,
And you shall forfeit
all rank and privileges
Within the grand army
of the republic.
You will be turned over
to the republic courts
To await your trail
And whatever punishment
they will set for you.
Henceforth, you are barred
from the jedi order.
[door whooshes]
- Padmé has agreed to represent
you before the senate.
- I will do everything I can
to prove your innocence, ahsoka.
- I am almost certain
that the person behind this
Is ventress,
And you know
I wasn't working with her.
She was at the warehouse...
In the room.
We fought,
but she got away.
Didn't any of the clones
see anything?
- No, none of the clones
reported seeing ventress
At the scene.
I thought you said
ventress left
Before you went
into the warehouse.
- That's what I thought, too,
But then she attacked me
when I got inside.
I'd know
her red lightsabers anywhere.
- Well, if that's our only lead,
then I know what I have to do.
- Wait, where are you going?
You can't leave now.
- Yes, I can.
I have to find ventress
and get to the bottom of this.
- Until we hear from anakin,
Let's work on your defense.
- [sighs]
Forgive me
if I'm not optimistic.
I thought
I was part of that order,
But everyone, except anakin,
has abandoned me.
I'm not holding out much hope
The senate
will treat me any better.
[ominous music]
¶
[indistinct conversation]
- Anakin skywalker.
- I know you're behind
all of this.
- Prove it.
[intense orchestral music]
[both grunting]
- Leave me alone.
[grunts]
¶
[choking and gagging]
- Tell me what happened.
- [choking and gasping]
When I heard your little brat
was on the run,
I thought she might bring
a large bounty.
- Bounty?
- I was going
to catch your pet
And turn her over
to the authorities,
Collect whatever bounty
was due.
- What stopped you?
- [coughing]
At first--I admit--I was
just interested in the money
And a little bit
of revenge,
But then I realized
your fallen padawan and I
Had a lot in common.
- How dare you compare yourself
to ahsoka?
- It's true.
My master abandoned me,
And that's exactly what you did
to her,
You and your precious
jedi order.
[suspenseful orchestral music]
¶
[staff clanging]
- Ahsoka tano,
You have been charged
with sedition
Against the jedi order
and the republic itself.
This court
will decide your fate.
Prosecution, you may begin
your arguments.
- Former padawan tano,
I shall prove
that you were the mastermind
Behind the attack
on the jedi temple
And that once your accomplices
carried out your orders,
You eliminated them
one by one.
When you are found guilty,
I ask the court
that the full extent of the law
Be brought down upon you,
Including penalty of death.
[dramatic musical flourish]
- After I left the warehouse,
After I left
your little padawan alone,
I was walking away,
And I thought she came up
behind me to talk more.
But I was wrong.
Someone came out of nowhere
and hit me from behind.
Not just anyone
can sneak up behind me.
It had to be another jedi.
- I don't believe you.
- Believe it.
Whoever you're looking for
has my lightsabers.
That's how you'll know
you've found the criminal.
- [sighs]
Well, this leads me
to a dead end.
You're the only one
ahsoka had talked to.
- That's not true.
- What do you mean?
- Your padawan
contacted the temple.
She spoke to someone
named barriss.
That's why we knew
to go to the warehouse
In the first place.
It was this barriss
that told us to go there.
- If you're lying,
you're dead.
- Such promises.
- Look at the facts.
Letta turmond called ahsoka
to her cell
To reveal the name
of the true mastermind
Behind the bombing
of the jedi temple.
Letta told ahsoka
she was afraid.
She told her
the mastermind was a jedi,
And before she could reveal
the jedi's name,
Letta turmond
was strangled to death
By way of the force.
Why would ahsoka kill letta
With a method
that would so obviously
Tie the murder to her?
A jedi may be responsible
for the murder,
But that jedi
is not ahsoka tano.
Members of the court,
You are prosecuting
the wrong jedi.
- [clapping slowly]
Well said, senator amidala.
However, if she is innocent,
Then why was she seen conspiring
with known separatist terrorist
Asajj ventress?
- Ventress set me up.
My master will prove that.
- And where is your master?
- He's trying to find
the real murderer.
- Then maybe
he should be looking at you.
[dramatic orchestral music]
¶
[electronic beep]
- Enter.
- Barriss,
I need to talk to you.
- Master skywalker,
How can I help you?
- I was told
that you spoke with ahsoka
Before she was arrested.
What did you say to her?
- We've been friends
for a long time.
I was only trying to help her.
I hope I'm not in any trouble.
- It's no trouble.
I just need to know
what you told her
And if you told anyone else.
- No, I thought
I had a clue for her,
But I really couldn't
tell her anything.
Who told you
I spoke to her?
- Ventress.
She told me.
- Ventress?
Isn't she the one ahsoka says
is really behind all this?
- That's what ahsoka says,
But I think she's wrong.
Ventress thinks
someone else is involved.
- And you believe her?
Who else could it be
if not her?
Surely not ahsoka.
- No, I don't think
it was ahsoka either.
I think both ahsoka and ventress
are telling the truth,
But there's only one way
to find out.
Funny.
Those belong to ventress.
[lightsabers whooshing, zapping]
You should've gotten rid
of them!
- I think they suit me.
[yelps]
[intense orchestral music]
- I'm sure many of you
look at this former jedi
And think, "surely
she cannot be this murderer
Or saboteur that they speak of."
And yet think of all the times
we have been fooled
By the separatists
And how they have infiltrated
the republic
And ask yourself,
"is this yet another
separatist scheme?"
Another way to rip the jedi,
And subsequently
all of us,
Apart.
¶
- [grunts]
- Ahsoka trusted you,
and you betrayed her.
- I've learned that trust
is overrated.
The only thing
the jedi council believes in
Is violence.
[lightsabers whooshing,
crackling]
¶
- Cease hostility!
- Barriss!
[glass shattering]
[grunts]
[lightsabers zapping]
¶
[screaming and grunting]
- Look out!
¶
[lightsabers crackling
intensely]
- [grunts]
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[whimpers]
- The members of the court
have reached a decision.
[device beeps]
- Ahsoka tano,
By an overwhelming count of--
- Chancellor.
- I hope you have a reason
For bursting
into our proceedings,
Master skywalker.
- I'm here with evidence
and a confession
From the person responsible
for all the crimes
Ahsoka has been accused of.
Barriss offee,
member of the jedi order
And traitor.
- Barriss, is that true?
- Tell them the truth.
- I did it
Because I've come to realize
What many of people
in the republic
Have come to realize,
That the jedi are the ones
responsible for this war,
That we've so lost our way
That we have become villains
in this conflict,
That we are the ones
that should be put on trial,
All of us!
And my attack on the temple
was an attack
On what the jedi
have become,
An army
fighting for the dark side,
Fallen from the light
that we once held so dear.
This republic is failing!
It's only a matter of time.
- Take her away.
[melancholy orchestral music]
¶
- Ahsoka,
I am so sorry
About everything.
- You have
our most humble apologies,
Little 'soka.
The council was wrong
to accuse you.
- You have shown such
great strength and resilience
In your struggle
to prove your innocence.
- This is the true sign
of a jedi knight.
- This was actually
your great trial.
Now we see that.
We understand that the force
works in mysterious ways,
And because of this trial,
You have become a greater jedi
than you would have otherwise.
- Back into the order
you may come.
- They're asking you back,
ahsoka.
I'm asking you back.
[dramatic orchestral music]
¶
- I'm sorry, master,
But I'm not coming back.
[melancholy orchestral music]
¶
- Ahsoka, wait!
Ahsoka, I need to talk to you.
[sighs]
Why are you doing this?
- The council didn't trust me,
So how can I trust myself?
- What about me?
I believed in you.
I stood by you.
- I know you believe in me,
anakin,
And I'm grateful for that.
But this isn't about you.
I can't stay here
any longer,
Not now.
- The jedi order
is your life.
You can't just throw it away
like this.
Ahsoka,
you are making a mistake.
- Maybe, but I have
to sort this out on my own,
Without the council
And without you.
- I understand.
More than you realize,
I understand wanting
to walk away from the order.
- I know.
¶
[brooding orchestral music]
[r2-d2 whirring]