ANNOUNCER: Danger looms despite
recent victories on the Outer Rim.
Criminal minds plot at the very heart
of the Republic.
The bounty hunter Cad Bane
has assembled some of the deadliest
criminals in the galaxy
and plans a daring attack
to seize members of the Senate.
What could be the aim
of this despicable act?
Here we go.
CLONE: (ON PA) Attention! Attention!
This is a restricted area.
No landing is permitted
without permission.
Violators will be prosecuted
to the full extent of the law.
Put up your hands.
I got business with the Senate.
How about you fellows step aside?
On your knees! Raise your hands. Slowly.
Son, I wouldn't be so hasty if I were you.
Cuff him.
(FIRING)
-Where's that coming from?
-I see the shooter up in the tower.
Over there...
(GRUNTS)
(WEAPONS FIRING)
(CLICKING)
You two, get these uniforms on
and get this platform clear.
(COMLINK BEEPS)
DROID: Base to platform.
What was all that? Report.
Protesters against the war.
We've taken care of them.
Finish getting those uniforms on
and clear this platform now.
Everybody else, follow me.
ANAKIN: Hey, I'm supposed to be
on a meditative retreat.
We should go away together.
I know a place far away from here
where no one would recognize us.
Yeah, it'll be like we're actually
husband and wife
instead of senator and Jedi.
(STUTTERS)
-I can't, Ani.
-What do you mean, you can't?
Oh, it's only two weeks.
We'll be back before anyone
even notices we're gone.
I have to bring this bill before the Senate.
It's important.
Uh-huh.
More important
than the way you feel about me?
(SIGHS) Not more important,
but important.
The work I do... The work we both do
is in service to the Republic,
to protect those who would otherwise
be powerless to protect themselves.
Of course, but those are ideals.
Isn't our love more important to you?
-But, I...
-No! No "but".
To me, there's nothing more important
than the way I feel about you. Nothing.
-Anakin, don't be so...
-Oh, you don't believe me.
-I didn't say I...
-I'll prove it. Just watch.
When I finished constructing
my lightsaber, Obi-Wan said to me,
"Anakin, this weapon is your life".
This weapon is my life.
No, Anakin, I can't. A Jedi lightsaber is...
-Wow, it's heavier than I thought.
-It's yours. Believe me now?
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
If all you want to do is make fun of me,
-I think you should just go.
-That's not what I want.
Not at all.
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
Stop!
(EXCLAIMING)
-You know what to do?
-I'll figure it out.
You better not fail me, bubble brain.
Don't worry.
I'll have the power off in no time.
The rest of you come with me.
C-3PO: But, Senator Organa,
it just wouldn't be...
-Quick. Hide.
-ORGANA: The situation cannot be delayed.
Now stand aside.
I apologize for my abruptness.
Oh, Senator Organa, how good to see you.
What is it?
Senator Philo
has called a meeting in the lobby
before we vote on
the enhanced privacy invasion bill.
Right. Privacy invasion bill.
We must hurry if we are to stop the vote.
-Coming, Senator Amidala?
-Of course.
(DOOR OPENS)
BANE: Quietly.
Guard change happens now.
Here we go.
(TIMER TICKING)
(EXPLOSION)
Now, let's go talk to some senators.
(WEAKLY) Help me.
(GRUNTS) No.
(FIRES)
ORGANA: We cannot allow the Chancellor
to move this enhanced
privacy invasion bill forward.
We're all in agreement, then.
Morning, Senators.
You should all consider yourselves
to be in my power.
As long as everybody behaves,
this will be quick and painless.
Do nothing, and it will all be over soon.
I don't know who you think you are,
but I, for one, have no intention
of listening to this kind of insolence.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
All right, then. If you'll all gather
at the center of this lovely atrium,
my co-workers and I will relieve you
of any communication devices.
I see five of them here in the room. If we...
What are you going to do?
It's not like we carry weapons.
-Chancellor Palpatine.
-What is it, Senator Free Taa?
I think you should see this.
Sorry to bother you, Chancellor,
but I've taken control of the east wing
of your Senate building,
and the occupants are now my hostages.
If you care about them,
I'd advise you to free Ziro the Hutt
from your detention center.
You should know that the Republic
does not take kindly to such threats.
If you have attempted such a foolhardy
action as to kidnap a senator,
I assure you that it will be met
with appropriate force.
This ought to do it.
(POWERING DOWN)
What's going on?
I'm in control. I make the rules now.
Orn Free Taa, help me with this door.
It's no use, sir. Someone's gotten
to the central control panel.
They've triggered the security system.
The Senate buildings
have sealed themselves.
(BEEPS)
This is Chancellor Palpatine.
There is an emergency
at the Senate building.
Jedi Council, come in. Is anyone there?
That's no use either, sir.
They've cut off all communication
with the outside.
Hand over
your communication devices, please.
-I can't let them search me.
-What? Why not?
-I have something they must not find.
-What is it?
Well, hello there, little lady.
And who might you be?
I'm Padmé Amidala, Senator from Naboo,
and I demand that
you release us immediately.
The Galactic Senate will not treat
with terrorists.
Ain't you awful young and pretty
to be a senator?
Skywalker! After him!
(COMLINK BEEPS)
Hello? Come in. Anyone there?
Uh-oh.
(SQUEAKING)
-Oh!
-Shh!
(COMLINK BEEPS)
This is General Skywalker.
Chancellor Palpatine, can you hear me?
My dear boy,
I'm glad to know you're there and all right.
-ANAKIN: What is going on down there?
-I hear it, too. Coming from up ahead.
PALPATINE: He sealed the entire building.
Nobody can get in, and we cannot get out.
It's up to you.
You have to get to the power control room
and turn off the security seal.
You have two more floors to check.
Come on.
We've got two more floors to check.
You take downstairs, I'll go up.
We'll meet on the other side.
(BEEPS IN AGREEMENT)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(CLANKING)
No lightsaber cuts.
Interesting.
-What happened? Where's the droid?
-The droid's gone, but there's good news.
-The Jedi's unarmed.
-What?
-It doesn't look like he has his lightsaber.
-Go. Bring him back to me.
(DOOR BEEPING)
(HUMMING)
Oopsie!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
(BEEPING)
-The lightsaber. I've got it.
-What?
Why do you have a Jedi's lightsaber?
The question is whether we should try
and get it back to...
-SENATOR: ...not now, too risky!
-...the Jedi knight or use it ourselves.
(WEAPON FIRING)
Everybody, quiet. I've got a call to make.
So here's what you're going to do.
First, you're going to make a pardon disk.
You can give it to your friend there.
Who? Me?
My ship will come and pick him up
and take him to the prison.
Once Ziro has been released
and is handed over to me,
then your associates will be released.
Understand?
Oh, I do, but I feel it is my duty
to warn you
that you will end up paying
for this outrage.
I can live with that.
Come on. Open the door. I won't hurt you.
Well, well! What have we here?
Blast it!
(GRUNTING)
Tie your little pet up.
We'll bring him to Bane.
(CHUCKLING)
Here's the pardon disk.
(DOOR OPENS)
Let's go.
-Why do I have to go to the jail for this?
-Move it.
Sorry, Senator,
but everyone has a job to do.
Hurry up.
(DOOR OPENS)
Young Skywalker.
Not so impressive
without your lightsaber, are you, Jedi?
Toss him in with the others.
3D, are we on schedule?
Arriving at the prison now.
Unlock the doors.
(EXCLAIMING)
-It's so bright out here.
-CLONE: Oh, my God.
Why couldn't we do this at night
when it's cooler?
Go and get the parting gifts.
(BEEPS)
(EXPLOSIVES BEEPING)
(CHUCKLES)
Look at Senator Orn Free Taa.
He looks so unhappy.
(ORN FREE TAA WHIMPERS)
Now get me as far away from Coruscant
as possible!
Now!
Well, Mr. Chancellor,
thanks to your calm leadership,
the crisis is passed.
I got what I want, so I'll return
your Senate and your senators.
Enjoy them, but don't try anything
until the sun has set.
Understand?
Oh!
We are to rendezvous
back at the Senate building.
What? No, no, no, no! The Outer Rim,
not the Senate, you stupid machine.
But I don't want to go to the Senate!
We need to get to the landing platform.
-Is everything ready?
-Yep, yep.
Turn on the field.
If you so much as breathe
on one of these lasers,
the whole room will blow up.
Senators, Jedi, I bid you all
a most respectful farewell.
Let's go.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
All clear!
Sir, are you all right?
-Yes, yes, I'm fine.
-Mission accomplished, sir.
-The Chancellor is safe.
-(SIGHS) Well done, trooper.
(COMLINK BEEPS)
You were foolish to think you could
get away with this, bounty hunter.
Now lay down your arms
and come quietly.
No, Chancellor,
I'm afraid it is you who have been foolish
with your senators' lives.
One false move and the east wing
of the Senate building goes up in smoke.
Please, Ani, wake up.
You win, bounty hunter.
Holster.
Stand down.
(GROANS)
What are you looking so sad about?
FARR: The bounty hunter said
we should just sit here.
-I think we should just sit here.
-Well, that's not a very good idea.
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Come on.
Let's get going.
(EXCLAIMS)
(SIGHS) Too bad I don't have my lightsaber.
You mean this?
I found it where you dropped it.
Now, quickly! We don't have much time.
Well, Hutt, it doesn't look like prison
had too adverse an effect on you.
Oh, you can't imagine
the unspeakable things I've suffered.
The horror! I doubt I'll ever really recover.
How about some dead senators
as payback?
(EXPLOSIVES POWERING UP)
(SENATORS GROANING)
(PADMÉ COUGHING)
-Another daring rescue, Master Jedi.
-I do my best, Senator.
Congratulations on a job well done,
bounty hunter.
Time to pay up, Hutt. I don't work for free.
(SIGHS)
English - SDH