ANNOUNCER: Republic outpost overrun!
The Jedi have lost all contact
with the clone security force
stationed on the bleak,
snow-covered planet of Orto Plutonia.
Obi-Wan Kenobi and Anakin Skywalker,
accompanied by dignitaries
from the nearby moon of Pantora,
are sent to investigate
the disappearance of the clone troopers
on the desolate and forbidding Landscape.
And this is the planet's tropical zone.
It's not Tatooine, that's for sure.
Captain Rex!
Have your men survey the area.
Place as many sensor beacons
as you can before dark.
Right away, sir. Unload that gear!
Let's move!
Why would the Republic
want an outpost way out here?
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
The Chairman of Orto Plutonia
requested it? But why?
-General Kenobi.
-Chairman Cho, Senator Chuchi,
I suggest you wait here
until we can secure the area.
I respect your judgment, General Kenobi,
but I will go where I choose.
This is sovereign Pantora territory.
I thought this planet was uninhabited,
and therefore it's not aligned.
Our moon of Pantora
is the only civilization in this system.
I'm the one who asked the Senate
to protect this planet.
This wasteland belongs to us.
With all due respect, Chairman,
this is for the Senate to decide, not us.
Ah, but the Jedi report to the Senate,
which is Senator Chuchi of Pantora.
Technically speaking, Master Jedi,
the Chairman is correct.
Since the planet is uninhabited,
the moon of Pantora reserves the right
to continue as its protectorate.
Point taken, Senator.
Anakin, stay here with the Senator
and the droids while we secure the base.
-I don't get it.
-It must be Separatists.
I'm not sure.
Might we go inside, Master Anakin?
Artoo would like to get out of the cold.
(BEEPING)
We'll go inside
as soon as Obi-Wan signals that it's safe.
Do you think the Separatists are building
a forward base to attack Pantora?
I don't think
we're dealing with Separatists.
These computers haven't been touched.
Sir! Our scouts have spotted a droid base
on the other side of the ice ridge.
By the look of things,
I'd say whoever attacked our base
took out the droids, also.
Rex, help Anakin
place the sensor beacons.
-You four, come with me.
-REX: Yes, General.
Let's go.
Did you find anything?
ANAKIN: I found some large footprints.
Have one of your men make a cast.
(BEEPING)
ANAKIN: Sensors are in place.
I think I found something.
Blast it!
Six-eight-five to command.
There are too many of them!
They've overrun the base!
We need reinforcements!
(ROARING)
-What was that?
-Whatever it was, it's a good warrior.
The droids' log indicates they were
investigating the southern canyon.
Sounds like a good place to start.
CHO: I want the weapons system back
online and the shields operational.
There's no telling
what the Separatists have planned.
Chairman, what makes you so certain
the Separatists are behind this attack?
Look around, Senator.
Isn't this carnage proof enough?
I know, but there are no dead droids here,
no blast marks.
The clones' injuries were not consistent
with what...
So, you're an expert on war now,
are you, Senator?
-No, Chairman. No, I only...
-Let me tell you something, Senator.
I have led our people
since before you were born.
I've seen a hundred planets
rise and fall through force of arms.
If it's not the Separatists out there,
then it's a malevolent and aggressive
enemy nonetheless,
and I will not let whoever it is
jeopardize the security
of the people of Pantora.
But if the Jedi discover
that the Separatists aren't behind this,
then perhaps there is
a peaceful resolution.
Senator, I am willing to fight and die
for my people.
It's time to ask yourself
if you are brave enough to do the same.
There's some kind of reflection up there.
Do you see it?
Yep.
Well, they know we're coming. Let's go.
(GROWLING)
Steady, Anakin. They're only curious.
Let's not provoke them as the droids
and our troops must have done.
Too bad we didn't bring Threepio along.
How do you plan on communicating
with these things?
Patience.
Maybe they're smarter than we are.
(SPEAKING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Well? Say something.
Just shut up.
(SPEAKING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
We come to you in peace.
We will not bring harm.
Peace.
(MUMBLES)
Right.
Glad you made it back, sir.
It's getting nasty out there.
You don't know the half of it.
CHO: What did you find?
It seems we've stumbled onto
an inhabited planet.
Impossible.
Our explorers have spent much time here
over the long history of Pantora.
No one lives here. They're trespassers.
With respect, Chairman Cho,
these creatures, the Talz,
aren't advanced enough
to master space travel.
I think they may have been here
longer than Pantora.
Whoever they are, they belong to us.
This whole system belongs to us.
Your Majesty, if there are life forms here,
then the Senate must decide jurisdiction.
They are savages.
Look at what they've done.
They've slaughtered your troops.
They only want to be left alone.
The droids attacked them,
and I'm afraid our outpost
got caught in the middle.
They must be subdued. They're dangerous.
Captain Rex,
prepare your troops for battle.
We promised their chief
there would be no retaliation.
We've arranged a meeting
between their high council
and you and the Senator.
They want peace.
We can't send troopers.
They'll think we lied.
These creatures
are little more than animals.
You can't lie to an animal.
They can't be trusted.
-But, Your Majesty...
-No!
It is obvious
these creatures are not covered
by the Convention of Civilized Systems.
The Jedi Council has no say in the matter.
If the Jedi are able
to communicate with them,
their status is in doubt.
Do you stand
against your Chairman, Senator?
Of course not, Your Majesty.
If we are going to meet with Thi-Sen
and his council at the arranged time,
we will have to leave now.
Sir, the gunships can't take off
in this storm.
We don't have enough bikes
for the entire platoon.
Have the rest of the men standby here.
No matter what the Chairman thinks,
we're not going to war.
(BEEPING)
Captain! Put your men on that ice ridge.
We will attack
as soon as the savages arrive.
There will be no attack, Chairman.
You will do as I command!
This planet is under my jurisdiction!
Nothing is under your control, Chairman.
The Talz are already here.
Their scouts have been following us
for some time.
It seems Thi-Sen doesn't trust you
any more than you trust him.
Rex, tell your men to stand down.
Stay here,
and don't do anything to provoke them.
Yes, sir.
-Your Highness.
-We have returned,
as promised.
(CHATTERING IN TALZZI)
These savages have no rights here.
Chieftain Thi-Sen welcomes you
to his home and hopes you come in peace.
He wishes to be good neighbors,
but he does not wish you
to remain on his planet.
Listen, droid, translate everything I say,
and exactly as I say it.
Would you like me to represent Pantora
in this matter?
Not on your life, Senator.
There will be no diplomacy this time.
Listen here, you savage.
This world belongs
to the moon of Pantora,
and as the Supreme Chairman
and Exalted Ruler of Pantora,
you will not command me
to leave this planet,
or do anything else.
Your Majesty, we can't.
-Droid! Tell him.
-Oh, dear.
I recommend
a less confrontational discussion.
The Talz are easily provoked.
(GROWLING)
(SPEAKING TALZZI)
That didn't go over very well.
Chairman, I promised the Talz
that we would leave them in peace.
This is now an internal affair of Pantora.
(SPEAKING TALZZI)
The great Thi-Sen, "Son of Suns,"
asks again that you leave,
or it will mean war.
Then war it is.
(SPEAKING TALZZI)
(GROWLS)
Troopers, mount up and follow me.
REX: What's up, General?
You're going to have to stay
with the Chairman
until we can work things out.
Protect him at all costs.
REX: Mount up! We're moving out!
Senator, you know
a preemptive strike is illegal.
Isn't there anything you can do to stop it?
I'm afraid not.
He has proclaimed this conflict
an internal affair.
You could petition the Jedi Council
for an intervention.
You mean without his authorization?
There must be someone on your moon
who could approve it.
The Speaker of the Assembly.
He has the power.
Let's get back to the base.
The storm is letting up.
Maybe we can get a transmission through.
Here they are! Fire when you're in range!
(GROWLING)
Sir, with all due respect,
we're only here to protect you.
-Ambush!
-It's a trap! Kill them!
We're surrounded. Defensive formation!
Chairman, get down!
(GROWLS)
(GROANS)
We've got to hold out!
Fall back! First squad, cover the retreat!
Retreat?
We can't retreat from these animals!
(GROANS)
Savages.
(ROARING)
The Assembly has decided that the actions
of Chairman Cho are out of order.
Senator Chuchi, you're given the authority
to negotiate a peaceful settlement
between the sovereign planet of Pantora
and the Talz.
It is decided, then.
Pilot, let's get moving.
(WAILING)
Here they come!
Senator, now that you have the authority,
how do you plan on making peace
with the Talz?
Actually, Master Jedi,
since you are far more experienced,
I was hoping you could negotiate
on Pantora's behalf.
I'm afraid that's not possible, Senator.
But I don't understand.
The Jedi serve the Senate.
-I must order you...
-Senator,
it is your people the Talz are at war with.
If the violence is to stop,
it is you who must represent your people.
(SCREAMING)
(AIRCRAFTS HOVERING)
-Good to see you, sir.
-You okay, Rex?
-It's just a scratch.
-What's going on?
We're in quite a mess, sir. Eleven dead,
the rest wounded, including the Chairman.
Chairman, can you hear me?
Senator. Good.
You must avenge me.
As my final command
as Chairman of Pantora,
I order you to destroy the Talz.
I'm afraid I cannot do that, Chairman.
The Pantoran Assembly
has called you out of order.
I am to negotiate peace.
No. Impossible!
Peace? Never!
I died for our people.
(HOWLING)
Senator, now is the time.
Protocol droid, come with me.
-Threepio, get going.
-Yes, Master Ani.
(BEEPS)
-Droid, translate for me.
-Yes, Mistress.
To die for one's people is a great sacrifice.
To live for one's people,
an even greater sacrifice.
(SPEAKING TALZZI)
I choose to live for my people.
What do you choose?
(SPEAKING TALZZI)
He chooses to live as well.
We will leave Orto Plutonia
under the watchful eyes of the Talz
from this day forth,
and recognize your sovereignty
as a free and equal people.
-Well done, Senator.
-Yes. Most impressive.
Thank you, Master Jedi.
Now that you have created peace
between your people and the Talz,
remember one crucial thing.
Yes, Master Kenobi?
Make it last, Senator.
Make it last.
And be an example to others,
so not only this war, but every war waged
may come to an end as well.
I will. I promise you.
English - SDH