Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Neutral start systems in peril.
Darth Maul and Savage Opress
command the planet Mandalore
through the puppet Prime Minister Almec
while they expand
their criminal enterprise.
With the Death Watch removed from power
and the Jedi unaware
of the villainous plot,
nothing stands in the way
of Darth Maul's vision
for a vast criminal empire.
We now find Duchess Satine imprisoned
as her few remaining loyal subjects
make a desperate attempt to rescue her.
What do you want, you traitor?
I would never betray you, Auntie Satine.
I'm here to rescue you.
Korkie.
Freeze!
Hold it there.
Death Watch.
Bo.
It's been a long time.
It's okay, Auntie.
She's on our side now.
Why are you helping now?
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
There was a time
when we weren't enemies.
Perhaps that time has come again.
Come on.
Let's go.
It's all clear.
Come on.
We need to contact the Jedi Council.
Korkie, give me your comlink.
It won't be any good
unless we get outside the city.
All of the frequencies are jammed.
You are all taking
a terrible risk by helping me.
Nothing we haven't done before.
Right, Auntie?
Let's get going.
Take 'em out.
Get the duchess clear.
The transmission is still blocked.
You're clear.
This is a message
for Obi-Wan Kenobi.
I've lost Mandalore.
My people have been massacred.
Obi-Wan, I need your help.
You summoned me, Masters?
This is a message
for Obi-Wan Kenobi.
I've lost Mandalore.
My people have been massacred,
and Almec is now the prime minister.
I can't explain everything now
but Almec has the support
of the crime families.
Obi-Wan, I need your help.
Your thoughts on this, Master Kenobi.
Satine has been at odds
with the Death Watch for years.
And according to a report
from Padawan Tano,
they're no longer in league
with the Separatists.
If there was a takeover on Mandalore,
it was most likely an independent act
caused by the Death Watch alone.
Without involvement
from the Separatists,
this is an internal affair
for the Mandalorians.
I'm afraid we cannot help.
We cannot just hand Mandalore
over to these crime families
and let Satine become a martyr.
I'm afraid her decision
to keep Mandalore neutral
makes this situation difficult.
Understand your feelings I do,
Obi-Wan.
But to take action,
support from the Republic Senate
we will need.
You know what the Senate will decide.
They will not send aid
to a neutral system.
At this time, nothing more can we do.
Satine's accomplices have escaped,
including the renegade
Death Watch soldiers.
But we will find them.
The duchess appears
to have contacted the Jedi
just as anticipated.
Good.
You have done well.
What of the people?
You are the legitimate prime minister.
Mandalore is a sovereign planet
and you will maintain its neutrality.
And what of the Jedi?
Because of Mandalore's neutrality,
the Jedi have no jurisdiction here.
If Kenobi comes to rescue his friend,
he will have to come alone.
Ah.
Ah!
Anakin, that's the last time
I borrow a ship from you.
You better get your ship looked at.
Oh, it's my friend's ship.
He told me it was perfectly fine.
Terribly sorry about that.
Do you have a landing permit?
Um, I think I left it in the ship.
Come with me, and I'll get it.
Here to do more
of your master's bidding?
I do my own bidding.
Obi-Wan.
Are you alone?
Yes.
The Jedi Council and Galactic Senate
will be of no help to us here.
I trust you have an escape plan then?
As always, my dear.
There's no record
of a prisoner transfer here.
The orders came from upstairs.
What's the authorization code?
Oh, um...
Hey, you!
Stop!
It's the duchess.
She's getting away.
We have to contact my sister for help.
She'll send reinforcements.
Who's your sister?
Brace yourself!
Let's get out of here.
Obi-Wan!
No.
It can't be.
We meet again, Kenobi.
Welcome to my world.
Take them back to the palace.
Your noble flaw is a weakness
shared by you...
and your duchess.
You should have chosen the dark side,
Master Jedi.
Your emotions betray you.
Your fear,
and yes, your anger.
Let your anger deepen your hatred.
Don't listen to him, Obi--
- Quiet.
You can kill me,
but you will never destroy me.
It takes strength
to resist the dark side.
Only the weak embrace it.
It is more powerful than you know.
And those who oppose it
are more powerful
than you'll ever be.
I know where you're from.
I've been to your village.
I know the decision to join
the dark side wasn't yours.
The Nightsisters made it for you.
Silence!
You think you know me?
It was I who languished for years
thinking of nothing but you.
Nothing but this moment.
And now the perfect tool
for my vengeance
is in front of us.
I never planned on killing you.
But I will make you share
my pain, Kenobi.
Satine.
Remember, my dear Obi-Wan...
I've loved you always.
I always will.
Do we kill him now, brother?
No.
Imprison him below.
Let him drown in his misery.
Take him to his cell to rot.
You summoned me, Chancellor?
Prepare my ship.
- Ah!
- It's the rebels!
Sorry, I don't believe we've met.
You are?
Bo-Katan.
I'm here to rescue you.
That's all you need to know.
Sounds good to me.
You ever use one of these before?
No, but in this case,
I'm a fast learner.
Let's go.
Halt!
Maul must really want you dead.
You have no idea.
Hmm, I sense a presence.
A presence
I haven't felt since--
Master.
I am most impressed to see
you have survived your injuries.
I used your training, Master.
And I have built all this
in hopes of returning to your side.
Hmm.
How unfortunate
that are attempting to deceive me.
Master?
You have become a rival!
Go back to your Republic
and tell them what has happened.
That would likely lead
to a Republic invasion
of Mandalore.
Yes, and Maul will die.
But Mandalore will survive.
We always survive.
Now go.
Your Satine's sister, aren't you?
I'm so sorry.
Oof.
Ugh!
Uh!
Brother.
Brother, I am an unworthy apprentice.
I'm not like you.
I never was.
Remember, the first
and only reality of the Sith:
there can only be two.
And you are no longer my apprentice.
You have been replaced.
Ugh!
Have mercy.
Please.
Please!
There is no mercy.
Do not worry.
I'm not going to kill you.
I have other uses for you.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com