ANNOUNCER: Manhunt!
After a long and perilous search,
the Jedi finally track down
Separatist leader Count Dooku.
During a heroic attempt
to capture the Count,
Anakin Skywalker has gone missing.
Having lost contact with Skywalker,
Obi-Wan Kenobi heads toward
his friend's last known location,
a lone Separatist frigate
in the far reaches of the Outer Rim.
(MUTTERING)
Don't bother to get up.
You're not the prisoner I'm looking for.
(LIGHTSABER ACTIVATING)
Oh. It's you.
This is how you thank me
for rescuing you?
Pounce on me from the ceiling?
Kind of difficult
without a lightsaber. Thanks.
Did you manage to locate Dooku
before landing in jail?
Well, I know he's onboard.
I might have been able to do something
about it if I'd had my weapon.
It was important for you
to arrive without it,
so your capture would be convincing.
Oh, they were convinced, all right.
But how come I'm the one
getting caught all the time?
It doesn't look good.
When you're a Jedi Master,
you can make the plan.
That's just it.
How can I become a Jedi Master
if I'm always getting caught?
At least you're a master at getting caught.
Very funny.
Surprise, surprise.
-OBI-WAN: If it isn't Count Dooku.
-Obi-Wan Kenobi.
I thought I sensed
an unpleasant disturbance in the Force.
I see you've freed young Skywalker.
Where might he be if you weren't
always around to rescue him?
(THUDDING)
Sir! There's a Jedi Cruiser attacking!
Let's try not to blow up the ship
before they get off this time.
Your ship is surrounded, Count.
Republic troops are boarding as we speak.
Jedi fools.
I should have seen that coming.
-What are you doing?
-Following him.
Not that way! We need to cut him off!
You cut him off.
I'll follow him and meet you at the hangar.
Why do I even try?
Oh, great.
(DROIDS EXCLAIM)
-Your ship is ready, sir.
-Good.
-I thought you were following Dooku.
-I was. I followed him here.
Hang on!
(COMLINK BEEPS)
Ahsoka, Dooku managed to escape.
We're in pursuit,
but we could use reinforcements.
Follow us in what ships you can round up.
We'll get there as soon as we can.
(RUMBLING)
That was easy.
Lucky for you, I'm an excellent shot.
-Well, now those fighters are attacking.
-I'm on it.
ANAKIN: He's getting too close.
Lucky for you, I'm an excellent pilot.
For all your expertise,
this is not a very smooth landing.
And if you'd hit that second fighter,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
-I've had better landings.
-Dooku.
(BEEPING)
What's this? A homing beacon?
Which means the distinguished Count
is waiting for help,
so he can't be far off.
His engine is damaged.
He's not going anywhere.
ANAKIN: Not without a homing beacon.
There. Caves are a good start.
ANAKIN: Strange.
You sense it, too. Many life forms in there.
And Dooku's one of them.
Let's try to get him
before something else does.
(RUMBLING)
What's that?
OBI-WAN: Run!
You won't be needing this
anymore, Skywalker.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(LAUGHING)
Well, well. What do we have here?
Who are you?
More importantly, my friend, who are you?
Master! Obi-Wan, can you hear me?
Master!
Anakin, when I tell you to run, run.
Master! You're alive!
-And where's your lightsaber?
-It got knocked out of my hand.
-By a rock?
-Yeah, by a rock.
-It's got to be here somewhere.
-That is a feeble excuse.
You know what would be helpful?
A little light.
Certainly.
Silly thing.
It was just working a minute ago.
(MOCKINGLY) You don't suppose it was
hit by a rock, do you?
(GUNDARK SQUEALING)
Oh! This should be interesting.
Your Solar Sailor is very beautiful.
It's a pretty rare ship. Very expensive.
What are you doing all the way out here?
I sustained some damage
in an asteroid storm
and had to make a landing.
Feel free to help yourself to it.
If you need transport,
the nearest planet is Florrum.
-It's six parsecs away.
-Is it civilized?
That depends
on your definition of "civilized".
But you would certainly be
more comfortable there than here.
Vanqor is no place to be after dark.
Perhaps I shall take you up on your offer.
Very good.
Now all that's left to do is settle my fee.
Fee?
Just a little something
to cover my expenses.
It shouldn't be a problem for someone
so obviously wealthy as yourself.
I'd be happy to compensate you
for your services.
That's it, boys! We're heading home!
Jump in anytime!
Oh, you're doing fine.
She seems to like you.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, lucky me!
This isn't as much fun as it looks!
I thought gundarks were only found
on Vanqor!
Then this system must be Vanqor.
-So that would make this one...
-The mother of all gundarks. Precisely.
(GRUNTING) Are you gonna help me?
Well, you took your time.
(SQUEALING)
It's a pity.
I was just starting to sense a connection.
Should I leave you two alone?
Or would you prefer to find a way out
of this hole before she wakes up?
Welcome to Florrum.
Lose your flashy sword?
Are these what you were looking for, Jedi?
I am more powerful than any Jedi.
Know that you are dealing
with a Sith Lord.
You're still outnumbered.
The leader of the clanker army,
and a Sith Lord, no less.
Someone is sure to pay a pretty price
for you.
Provide me with the proper means
of communications,
I will arrange for any ransom to be paid.
And you will arrange for your armies
to crush us, as well.
You don't survive in the Outer Rim
by being stupid.
If the Separatists will pay to get you back,
chances are the Republic
will offer even more.
(DISTANT SQUEALING)
-Sounds like another gundark.
-That's too far away to worry about.
It won't stay far away.
Uh-oh. New problem!
(COUGHING)
-That's not good.
-It's just gas.
Yes, probably toxic gas.
That's good. Maybe it'll kill your gundark.
And maybe it'll kill us!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
(COUGHING)
This isn't gonna work. I can't breathe!
As always, I'm open to...
(GROANS)
Come on, Obi-Wan. Don't give up now.
-(COUGHING) What was that?
-(COUGHING) I have no idea.
Master!
(COUGHING)
Looks like I got here just in time.
What do you mean, "just in time"?
You were in very big trouble!
Trouble? We were simply searching
for Count Dooku.
Yeah. We had the situation
well under control, my little Padawan.
Oh! I see.
So, which part of the situation
did you have under control?
The blocked entrance? The poison gas?
Or that gundark behind you?
-Gundark?
-Oh.
You mean the one
that's too far away to worry about?
(SQUEALING)
Block the entrance!
-There's still Dooku to deal with.
-You let him get away?
No, not "get away," exactly, just...
Chime in, any time.
Oh, no. I'm enjoying this far too much.
If you want the Sith Lord,
it will cost you a million credits.
The payment will be in spice,
delivered in an unarmed diplomatic ship.
We will need proof he's alive
before agreeing to your terms.
Let me present your fearless Sith Lord.
I'm afraid he's too embarrassed to speak.
A hologram can be faked.
You want proof? This is his lightsaber.
Hmm. Yes. Belongs to Dooku,
that lightsaber does.
This scum having possession
of Dooku's lightsaber proves nothing.
If you refuse,
I'm sure the Separatist Council will be
more than willing to meet my price.
We may never have a better chance
to capture Count Dooku.
We would like to send two Jedi
to confirm you have Count Dooku
before delivering the ransom.
Send your Jedi.
But they must be unarmed.
-Impossible.
-They will be safe.
We have no interest
in getting involved in your war.
We've reestablished contact
with Kenobi and Skywalker.
-They're in a system close to Florrum.
-And most eager to find Dooku they are.
His only stipulation
is that you arrive unarmed.
-Unarmed?
-We know very little about these pirates.
We may be walking blind
into what could very well be
a hostile situation.
We can't let Dooku
slip through our fingers again.
Report back as soon as you arrive.
Well, this should be fun.
(WARBLING)
Follow me.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING SOFTLY)
Gentlemen! Can I offer you
something to drink?
No, thank you.
Congratulations on your capture
of Count Dooku.
-Very impressive.
-Yes, it was.
(EXCLAIMS DISMISSIVELY)
Even a Sith Lord
is no match for my warriors.
(LAUGHING)
He put up quite a fight. Blasters, cannons,
that glowy thing...
(IMITATES LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
-You mean a lightsaber?
-That's it.
And I don't need to tell you,
those things can do some damage.
Carved up some of my best men
pretty good
before I could get the jump on him.
And how, exactly, did you get
the jump on him?
With this?
(CHATTERING)
We have no interest
in disagreeing with you.
All we want is to confirm
you are holding Dooku, and we'll go.
I will arrange a meeting.
-Look how the mighty Sith Lord has fallen.
-This place suits you, Count.
It wasn't so long ago that you yourself
were in similar surroundings on my ship.
Yeah, but now I'm free and you're not.
I'm confident the situation
will rectify itself soon.
Soon, you'll be brought to trial
by the Senate
and most likely spend a very long time
in a cell just like this one.
And that's if you're lucky.
Oh, my naive young Jedi,
you must be overly optimistic
if you think these Weequayans plan
to let you leave this planet.
(CHUCKLES) They're planet-hopping thieves
looking for a quick score.
They have no interest
in picking a fight with Jedi.
They are devious and deceitful,
and, most importantly, stupid.
It's a wonder
you don't get along with them, Dooku.
You have so much in common.
You underestimate them
at your own peril, Kenobi.
I don't know about you,
but I could use some rest.
Remember, Anakin,
this could still be a trap.
You're not worried about Dooku, are you?
No. I'm worried about these pirates.
(JAWA EXCLAIMS)
Jedi! Now that your business
is completed,
we invite you to join us
in the Grand Hall for a banquet.
And a true Weequay banquet
is not to be missed.
No question they have Dooku.
Send the ransom.
-He's being securely held?
-Yeah, and very cranky about it.
Good.
Senator Kharraus and Representative Binks
will be dispatched immediately.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Now can I persuade you
to join us for a drink?
It's a tradition. In the name of friendship!
All right. But nothing too strong.
He's flying.
Bring our guests some refreshments!
To a successful transaction!
(ALL CHEERING)
To powerful pirates
and new friends of the Republic!
Enjoy your evening, gentlemen.
-I still don't get it.
-Get what?
How a bunch of drunken pirates managed
to catch Dooku when we couldn't.
Maybe there's a lesson to be learned here.
(SIGHS) I still don't get it.
It's to remind us to be humble
and never too proud to accept a gift
when it comes our way.
-Well, to unexpected gifts, then.
-Hear, hear!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH