Ahsoka Tano captured!
While on the run to prove her innocence,
Padawan Tano teamed up
with the deadly Asajj Ventress
to find the rogue Jedi
who framed Ahsoka for murder.
The Jedi Council sent
Anakin Skywalker and Master Plo Koon
to track Ahsoka down
and bring her back to the Temple.
Now, captured and imprisoned,
Ahsoka faces punishment
for crimes she did not commit.
The Senate requests that Ahsoka Tano
be indicted for acts of treason
against the Republic.
A fair trial Padawan Tano will have,
in accordance with Jedi tradition.
Ah, yes, Jedi tradition.
I'm afraid, Master Yoda, that the Senate
believes that an internal Jedi trial
would seem biased.
Therefore, the Senate asks
that the Council expel Ahsoka Tano
from the Jedi Order
so that she may be put
to a Republic military tribunal,
where she will receive
more impartial judgment.
And who would represent Ahsoka
in this tribunal, Admiral?
That would be up to the Council, General,
but I would recommend
someone outside the Order.
Of course.
The Council will act
as they deem necessary.
Thank you, Admiral.
Surely, we cannot do
what Tarkin suggests.
We need to stand together with Ahsoka.
And yet there's evidence that she is indeed
the mastermind
behind the attack on the Temple.
She was found in possession
of nano-droid explosives.
This alone is enough to convict her.
I understand your sentiment, Obi-Wan,
but, if the Council does as you suggest,
it could be seen as an act
of opposition to the Senate.
I'm afraid we have little choice.
To the Chamber of Judgment,
summon Skywalker and his Padawan.
And, in our decision,
may the Force guide us.
You're not helping.
I'm sorry, Snips, I just...
I just don't know what to do.
It's okay.
I don't, either.
Padawan Tano, serious charges
have been levied against you.
How plead you?
Not guilty, Master.
I would never take the lives of innocents.
The values of the Jedi are sacred to me.
There is evidence to the contrary.
You were alone with Letta Turmond
when she died. Can you explain this?
Someone used the Force against her.
Which brings us to Ventress.
Can you explain your association with her?
We had a mutual understanding.
I thought she was helping me.
Did she help you acquire
the nano-droid weapons we found on you
when you were apprehended,
the same devices used in the bombing
of the Temple?
No!
I was set up and deceived,
as you are being deceived now.
The question is, Padawan Tano,
who is deceiving us,
Ventress, you, or someone else?
I am not deceiving you!
I would assume Ventress is,
but I can't be sure.
My sense is clouded.
Clouded by the dark side
these things are, Padawan Tano.
Dangerously clouded.
But not just surrounding you,
surrounding many things, in these times.
You've already made your decision,
haven't you?
This meeting is just a formality!
Reached a decision we have,
though not in total agreement are we.
It is the Council's opinion
that Padawan Ahsoka Tano has committed
sedition against the Republic,
and thus she will be expelled
from the Jedi Order.
You can't do this!
Your Padawan status
will be stripped from you,
and you shall forfeit all rank and privileges
within the Grand Army of the Republic.
You will be turned over
to the Republic courts to await your trial
and whatever punishment
they will set for you.
Henceforth, you are barred
from the Jedi Order.
Padmé has agreed
to represent you before the Senate.
I will do everything I can
to prove your innocence, Ahsoka.
I am almost certain that
the person behind this is Ventress,
and you know I wasn't working with her.
She was at the warehouse, in the room.
We fought, but she got away.
Didn't any of the clones see anything?
No, none of the clones reported
seeing Ventress at the scene.
I thought you said Ventress left
before you went into the warehouse.
That's what I thought, too,
but then she attacked me when I got inside.
I'd know her red lightsabers anywhere.
Well, if that's our only lead,
then I know what I have to do.
Wait. Where are you going?
You can't leave now.
Yes, I can.
I have to find Ventress
and get to the bottom of this.
Until we hear from Anakin,
let's work on your defense.
Forgive me if I'm not optimistic.
I thought I was part of that Order,
but everyone, except Anakin,
has abandoned me.
I'm not holding out much hope
the Senate will treat me any better.
Anakin Skywalker.
I know you're behind all of this.
Prove it.
Leave me alone!
Tell me what happened!
When I heard your little brat
was on the run,
I thought she might bring a large bounty.
Bounty?
I was going to catch your pet
and turn her over to the authorities,
collect whatever bounty was due.
What stopped you?
At first, I admit,
I was just interested in the money,
and a little bit of revenge.
But then I realized
your fallen Padawan and I
had a lot in common.
How dare you compare yourself to Ahsoka?
It's true!
My master abandoned me,
and that's exactly what you did to her.
You and your precious Jedi Order.
Ahsoka Tano,
you have been charged with sedition
against the Jedi Order
and the Republic itself.
This court will decide your fate.
Prosecution, you may begin
your arguments.
Former Padawan Tano, I shall prove
that you were the mastermind
behind the attack on the Jedi Temple,
and that, once your accomplices
carried out your orders,
you eliminated them one by one.
When you are found guilty,
I ask the court that the full extent
of the law be brought down upon you,
including penalty of death.
After I left the warehouse,
after I left your little Padawan alone,
I was walking away
and I thought she came up behind me
to talk more,
but I was wrong.
Someone came out of nowhere
and hit me from behind.
Not just anyone can sneak up behind me.
It had to be another Jedi.
I don't believe you.
Believe it.
Whoever you're looking for
has my lightsabers.
That's how you'll know
you've found the criminal.
Well, this leads me to a dead end.
You're the only one Ahsoka had talked to.
That's not true.
What do you mean?
Your Padawan contacted the Temple.
She spoke to someone named Barriss.
That's why we knew to go
to the warehouse in the first place.
It was this Barriss that told us to go there.
If you're lying, you're dead.
Such promises.
Look at the facts.
Letta Turmond called Ahsoka to her cell
to reveal the name of the true mastermind
behind the bombing of the Jedi Temple.
Letta told Ahsoka she was afraid.
She told her the mastermind was a Jedi,
and before she could reveal
the Jedi's name,
Letta Turmond was strangled to death
by way of the Force.
Why would Ahsoka kill Letta
with a method that would
so obviously tie the murder to her?
A Jedi may be responsible for the murder,
but that Jedi is not Ahsoka Tano.
Members of the court,
you are prosecuting the wrong Jedi.
Well said, Senator Amidala.
However, if she is innocent,
then why was she seen conspiring with
known Separatist terrorist Asajj Ventress?
Ventress set me up.
My master will prove that.
And where is your master?
He's trying to find the real murderer.
Then maybe he should be looking at you!
Enter.
Barriss.
I need to talk to you.
Master Skywalker.
How can I help you?
I was told that you spoke with Ahsoka
before she was arrested.
What did you say to her?
We've been friends for a long time.
I was only trying to help her.
I hope I'm not in any trouble.
It's no trouble.
I just need to know what you told her,
and if you told anyone else.
No.
I thought I had a clue for her,
but I really couldn't tell her anything.
Who told you I spoke to her?
Ventress. She told me.
Ventress? Isn't she the one
Ahsoka says is really behind all this?
That's what Ahsoka says,
but I think she's wrong.
Ventress thinks someone else is involved.
And you believe her?
Who else could it be, if not her?
- Surely not Ahsoka.
- No.
I don't think it was Ahsoka, either.
I think both Ahsoka and Ventress
are telling the truth.
But there's only one way to find out.
Funny, those belong to Ventress.
You should've gotten rid of them.
I think they suit me.
Ah!
I'm sure many of you
look at this former Jedi and think,
"Surely she cannot be this murderer
or saboteur that they speak of."
And yet, think of all the times
we have been fooled by the Separatists,
and how they have infiltrated
the Republic,
and ask yourself,
"Is this yet another Separatist scheme,
another way to rip the Jedi,
and subsequently all of us, apart?"
Ahsoka trusted you and you betrayed her.
I've learned that trust is overrated.
The only thing the Jedi Council believes in
is violence.
Cease hostilities!
Barriss!
Look out!
The members of the court
have reached a decision.
Ahsoka Tano,
- by an overwhelming count of...
- Chancellor!
I hope you have a reason for bursting
into our proceedings, Master Skywalker.
I'm here with evidence and a confession
from the person responsible
for all the crimes
Ahsoka has been accused of,
Barriss Offee,
member of the Jedi Order
and traitor.
Barriss, is that true?
Tell them the truth.
I did it,
because I've come to realize
what many people in the Republic
have come to realize,
that the Jedi are the ones
responsible for this war,
that we've so lost our way
that we've become villains in this conflict,
that we are the ones
that should be put on trial,
all of us!
And my attack on the Temple was
an attack on what the Jedi have become,
an army fighting for the dark side,
fallen from the light
that we once held so dear.
This Republic is failing!
It's only a matter of time.
Take her away.
Ahsoka, I am so sorry,
about everything.
You have our most humble apologies,
little Ahsoka.
The Council was wrong to accuse you.
You have shown
such great strength and resilience
in your struggle to prove your innocence.
This is the true sign of a Jedi Knight.
This was actually your great trial.
Now we see that.
We understand that the Force works
in mysterious ways,
and, because of this trial,
you have become a greater Jedi
than you would have otherwise.
Back into the Order you may come.
They're asking you back, Ahsoka.
I'm asking you back.
I'm sorry, Master,
but I'm not coming back.
Ahsoka! Wait!
Ahsoka, I need to talk to you!
Why are you doing this?
The Council didn't trust me,
so how can I trust myself?
What about me?
I believed in you. I stood by you!
I know you believe in me, Anakin,
and I'm grateful for that.
But this isn't about you.
I can't stay here any longer,
not now.
The Jedi Order is your life.
You can't just throw it away like this!
Ahsoka, you are making a mistake.
Maybe.
But I have to sort this out on my own,
without the Council
and without you.
I understand. More than you realize,
I understand wanting
to walk away from the Order.
I know.