Like fire, across the galaxy,
the Clone War spread.
In league with
the wicked Count Dooku...
more and more planets slip.
Against this threat
upon theJedi knights...
falls the duty to lead
the newly formed army of the Republic.
And as the heat of war grows,
so too grows the prowess...
of one most gifted student
of the Force.
The Banking Clan
has hidden huge factories on Muunilinst...
building huge droid armies
and massive warships.
- We must act quickly.
- I agree.
But who to send?
Master Windu still fights
on Dantooine.
Lead the assault
Master Obi-Wan can.
My army is ready, Chancellor.
We can leave immediately.
Yes, and young Skywalker as well.
I suggest that we give him
special command of your space forces.
His exceptional skill
will be quite useful.
Chancellor, I feel
that Padawan Anakin...
is not yet ready
for such responsibility.
True. With his master
a Padawan's place is.
But undeniably strong
he has become. Perhaps--
Then it is decided.
I doubt even Master Qui-Gon
could have prepared a Jedi for this.
ARC troopers,
you have been selected for this task...
because you are the best, the elite.
You all know what to do.
The success of your mission
is our key to a swift victory.
When you get into position,
send word, as planned...
then I will join you.
Master, I know you don't think I'm ready
for a command of my own...
but I am the best pilot
in the order.
Chancellor Palpatine knows it.
I don't know why you can't--
Padawan, your skills have never been
in question. It is your maturity.
I've argued this before.
But the decision has been made.
May the Force be with you,
Commander.
All squadrons to me.
- ARC troopers, deploy!
- Yes, sir.
Evasive action!
Roger, roger.
General Kenobi, target sighted.
Very good, Sergeant.
Proceed with the next phase.
Troubled is the planet Mon Calamari.
Its races have divided.
The droid army of
the Quarren Isolation League...
moves against
the Calamari Council.
Alone, the Calamari
are no match.
Intervene we must.
Master Fisto, in these matters,
trust your insight we do.
May the Force be with you.
Those guns are destroying
our forward positions.
The Republic is breaking through.
Sir, our cannon at the base of the tower
has been destroyed.
Their range is greater
than we thought.
It must be their artillery.
What are we going to do?
I don't know why Dooku sent you here
if all you're going to do is stand arou--
I mean, whenever you're ready.
Everything has been arranged
precisely as you have requested...
most illustrious Count Dooku.
Indeed.
I trust you will find
what you seek.
Impressive.
You mask your presence well.
Flawless timing.
Perfect control.
You have great skill of infiltration.
My host would applaud
your abilities posthumously.
However, I am not looking
for a spy.
You are more powerful
than I had sensed.
The dark side is strong in me.
For I am Sith.
A bold claim.
But you are not Sith.
You wear the trappings of the Sith,
you fight like the Sith...
but this can be
imitated, however.
You lack a vital quality
found in all Sith.
Sith have no fear.
And I sense much fear in you.
You are a foolish old man
who knows nothing of the dark side.
Indeed.
Truly if you were Sith...
would this contest be not over?
It would not be so easy
to defeat a Sith.
So finish it.
We have other plans.
Have you been watching, Master?
I have indeed, Lord Tyranus.
The child's skill with a lightsabre
are most impressive.
You have found a promising disciple,
my apprentice.
- She shall serve us well.
- I am honoured.
Let me introduce my master...
the true lord of the Sith...
Darth Sidious.
What is your bidding?
AJedi named Anakin Skywalker.
You will find him for us
and eliminate him.
Jedi. Their order
is a fading light in the dark.
Corrupt and arrogant.
They must be punished.
The Jedi shall fall!
Consider this a gift.
She will be more than a match
for young Skywalker.
It matters not.
She is merely an instrument...
to bring forth
the eradication of theJedi.
General Kenobi,
our cannons are being destroyed.
- Mount up.
- Yes, sir.
General Kenobi,
we are in position.
I'm on my way.
- We're set, General.
- Very well.
Let's end this battle, Commander.
General.
Mercy, I beg you.
I am merely a banker.
That is entirely up to you
and your unconditional surrender.
Control room secure, General.
One can never be
too sure, Commander.
- General, are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Seems I've created
quite the mess now.
- Haven't I?
- Yes, sir.
Now, where were we? Yes.
I believe you were surrendering.
We lost Gold Leader.
Commander, enemy reinforcements
coming in .35.
Clear out, Gold 2.
I'm coming in.
R4, switch all power
to forward shields.
I know. I know.
Red Leader, fire all your missiles
across the bow of Cruiser 8.
But, Commander,
there's nothing out there.
- No targets.
- Do it now, trooper!
Commander Skywalker...
almost all the gun platforms
are destroyed and only--
Wait. What's that?
Commander, wejust lost
Blue Squadron.
- A rogue fighter has--
- I see it.
Mop up the fighters as planned.
This one's mine.
Got you.
I have you now.
Increase power to the thrusters, R4.
This is no droid pilot.
Come on.
- What was that?
- I don't know, General.
- That's not one of ours.
- No, General.
- That was Anakin.
- Yes, General.
- Anakin!
- It's under control, Master.
You're supposed to be in space,
leading our forces.
It's under control.
Under control?
I don't think so.
Your place is with your squadrons,
young one...
not chasing one ship
through the city streets.
Master, this is no droid pilot.
And the Force is with him.
I can't let him get away.
Anakin, I'm also sensing
something strange.
But you must let that ship go.
It's baiting you.
Jumping into hyperspace?
You have his coordinates?
Then plug them in.
He's not losing us.
Master, the battle up here
is more than won.
- I can handle this.
- Do not follow that ship.
Do you hear me?
Do not follow that ship!
That is an order! Anakin!
Sorry, sir.
Your signal is breaking up.
Padawan, if you--
You have the coordinates?
- Yes, General.
- Take a squad and follow him.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
- Fire at will.
- Roger, roger.
- Recharge accelerators.
- Fire.
- Roger, roger.
Internal explosions all over.
We are losing control.
What?
The crystal is
the heart of the blade.
The heart is
the crystal of the Jedi.
The Jedi is the crystal
of the Force.
The Force is the blade
of the heart.
All are intertwined.
The crystal, the blade...
the Jedi.
You are one.
You have taught me well,
Master Luminara.
Remember always,
the crystal is the heart of the blade.
Barriss Offee,
your training is complete.
Something trespasses
on sacred ground.
The temple is breached.
- I sense a presence, yet see nothing.
- They are here.
To Ilum we must go.
Absolutely not.
You cannot risk the senator's life
like this. Milady, I must protest.
Very little time
there is, Senator.
Our only hope to rescue Jedi.
To Ilum we must go now.
This is not a rescue ship.
May I remind our master Jedi
we have a more pressing mission?
A slight detour.
Jeopardize the mission it will not.
Be put in danger
the senator will not.
Save the lives of Jedi we must.
Master Yoda, I am convinced.
I will not require
my captain's further... persuasion.
Captain. Make best
possible speed to Ilum.
Yes, milady.
Ilum? That planet is
on the other side of the system.
A slight detour?
Well, actually, I don't have
a more important place to be.
Stay on the ship you must.
Much danger I sense.
Master Yoda, I can't let you go off
to attempt a rescue mission alone.
Yet alone I must be
for the rescue to succeed.
Call you I will
if assistance I require.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Master Yoda has been gone
far too long.
I should have never
let him go alone.
He's a Jedi master, milady.
He's quite capable of handling
whatever may be out there.
Master Yoda did assure you
he would contact you if he required help.
Travelling alone in a blizzard
on an uncharted planet...
is commonplace for a Jedi...
but not a senator.
Miss Padme is safer where she is.
3PO is right, R2.
I'll run a diagnostic
on the communication array.
This weather has been giving us
some low-band interference.
R2, does this weather
affect your sensors?
Not in the slightest.
Or so he says.
Good. I'm going to
look for Master Yoda.
- Alone?
- No. You two will accompany me.
Oh, dear.
What is it, R2?
It seems there are multiple objects
approaching from that direction.
Where?
Ambush! I knew
this was a bad idea!
Gotcha.
R2 says there are
two more still out there.
Two more?
3PO, could you get my coat?
Of course, Miss Padme.
I must be out of my circuit.
Help! Help!
I've been buried alive!
Thanks, 3PO.
It was a pleasure, Miss Padme.
What is it, R2? More droids?
More? Oh, no!
Master Yoda!
I'm so glad you're all right.
Successful my mission was.
Safe the Jedi are.
But pain my heart is.
What troubles you, Master Yoda?
Nearly destroyed the temple was.
Revealed its secret location is.
But by who I know not.
You will find the temple on Ilum.
Destroy it.
Do you have his position?
That's close enough, R4. We'll just have
to search the immediate area on foot.
Watch the ship, R4.
This won't take long.
Hut, hut!
Secure the area.
- Sergeant.
- Commander Skywalker.
- Obi-Wan?
- Yes, sir.
- Gave you orders to follow me.
Fine. Have some men
protect the ships.
The rest encircle the clearing.
Prepare to sweep the jungle.
Something's not right.
I can feel it.
Trooper?
Trooper, are you all right?
What happened?
I'm going to make you pay
for what you've done.
Come, Padawan.
Your fall will be
my ascension to the Sith.
Blast him.
The IG Banking Clan
has surrendered. The day is ours.
The Republic is victorious.
General Kenobi,
a ship is approaching...
that matches the one Commander
Skywalker followed into hyperspace.
I have batteries standing by.
Hold your fire, Captain.
Commander Skywalker!
I'm sorry, Master.
You were right.
It was a trap--
laid out by the Sith.
And I ran headlong into it.
But I emerged victorious.
Indeed. But that battle
should never have been fought.
I find the Sith's interest
in you most troublesome.
This is precisely why
you must follow my orders, young one.
Another defiance
could lead us into a dan--
General Kenobi!
Yes, Master Barrek.
Need immediate evac
from planet Hypori!
Our forces are totally destroyed.
Only a few of us left.
New droid general.
He's unstoppable.
Can't hold out for long.
General Grievous is hunting us.
- Must hurry!
- Master Barrek, come in.
Come in. Master Barrek!
Come in!
Why have they stopped?
- Master?
- Go. Go.
Unstoppable.
He is unstoppable.
Never have we been
outmanoeuvred by droids.
His strategy is without flaw.
This is the end.
We're all doomed.
Our predicament is dire,
but do not despair.
Focus. We are Jedi.
Jedi.
You are surrounded.
Your army is decimated.
Make peace with the Force now...
for this is your final hour.
But know that I, General Grievous,
am not completely without mercy.
I will grant you
a warrior's death. Prepare.
I can't see anything.
That noise.
He is coming alone.
- We can't face him.
- We must try, Padawan.
- It's close, but where?
- It's all around us.
Calm yourself.
Steady.
Get back.
Ki-Adi.
Hurry.
Shaak Ti.
Darker the coming storm
grows, I fear.
The dark cloud of the Sith
shrouds us all.