<SAMI>
<HEAD>
<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
<!--  Generated by KMPlayer
.ENCC
-->
</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY>
<SYNC Start=16460><P Class=ENCC>
Sync By Rahul Sarker
<SYNC Start=19980><P Class=ENCC>
Too late, the melody is over
<SYNC Start=23289><P Class=ENCC>
The joke seems to be on me cause I'm the one not laughing
<SYNC Start=28980><P Class=ENCC>
Down here on the floor
<SYNC Start=31420><P Class=ENCC>
Deflate, the mystery of living
<SYNC Start=36229><P Class=ENCC>
In the most heartless fashion I could ever Imagine
<SYNC Start=41170><P Class=ENCC>
No pretense of decor
<SYNC Start=48920><P Class=ENCC>
Another place and time, without a great divide
<SYNC Start=51979><P Class=ENCC>
And we could be flying deadly high
<SYNC Start=55859><P Class=ENCC>
I'll sell my soul to dream you wide awake
<SYNC Start=61479><P Class=ENCC>
Another place and time, without a warning sign
<SYNC Start=64799><P Class=ENCC>
And we could be dying angel style
<SYNC Start=68550><P Class=ENCC>
I'll sell my soul to dream you wide awake
<SYNC Start=75859><P Class=ENCC>
I'll dream you... wide awake
<SYNC Start=94979><P Class=ENCC>
With me, disaster finds a playfield
<SYNC Start=99859><P Class=ENCC>
Love seems to draw dark, twisted pleasure tearing at me
<SYNC Start=105299><P Class=ENCC>
cause I can't let you go
<SYNC Start=107920><P Class=ENCC>
Mercy, like water in a desert
<SYNC Start=112299><P Class=ENCC>
Shine through my memory like jewelry in the sun
<SYNC Start=118049><P Class=ENCC>
Where are you now
<SYNC Start=125110><P Class=ENCC>
Another place and time, without a great divide
<SYNC Start=128300><P Class=ENCC>
And we could be flying deadly high
<SYNC Start=132169><P Class=ENCC>
I'll sell my soul to dream you wide awake
<SYNC Start=151989><P Class=ENCC>
I'll dream you... wide awake
<SYNC Start=167299><P Class=ENCC>
It's like I'm racing to the sun, blindly face the blazing gun
<SYNC Start=173240><P Class=ENCC>
cause I'm afraid I will be left here without you
<SYNC Start=179179><P Class=ENCC>
Like I'm racing not to run, give more when I have none
<SYNC Start=185860><P Class=ENCC>
cause I'm afraid I will be left here without you... wide awake
<SYNC Start=215119><P Class=ENCC>
Another place and time, without a great divide
<SYNC Start=217299><P Class=ENCC>
And we could be flying deadly high
<SYNC Start=220869><P Class=ENCC>
I'll sell my soul to dream you wide awake
<SYNC Start=241120><P Class=ENCC>
I'll dream you... wide awake.
</BODY>
</SAMI>
