Boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Willy?
It's all right.
I came back.
Why, what happened?
Did something happen, Willy?
- Nothing happened.
- You didn't smash the car?
I said nothing happened!
- Didn't you hear me?
- Don't you feel well?
I'm tired to the death.
I, uh, I couldn't make it.
I just couldn't make it, Linda.
Where were you all day?
You look terrible.
Oh, I got as far
as a little above Yonkers.
I stopped for a cup of coffee.
- Maybe it was the coffee.
- What?
I suddenly couldn't drive anymore.
The car kept going off
onto the shoulder.
Maybe it's the steering.
I don't think
Angelo knows the Studebaker.
No, it's me. Suddenly I realise
I'm going 60 miles an hour
and I don't remember
the last five minutes.
I can't seem to keep my mind to it.
Maybe it's your glasses.
You never went for new glasses.
I see everything.
I came back ten miles an hour.
It took me nearly four hours
from Yonkers.
You just gotta take a rest.
You can't continue like this.
Aw, I just got back from Florida.
But you didn't rest your mind.
Your mind is overactive
and the mind is what counts, dear.
I'll start out in the morning.
Maybe I'll feel better in the morning.
Oh, these... these arch supports
are killing me.
Take an aspirin.
Should I get you an aspirin?
Lt'll soothe you.
I was driving along, understand?
I was fine.
I was even observing the scenery.
You can imagine me looking at scenery
on the road every week of my life.
But it's so beautiful up there, Linda.
The trees are thick and the sun is warm.
I just open the windshield
and let the warm air bathe over me.
And then all of a sudden I'm...
...l'm going off the road.
I'm telling you,
I absolutely forgot I was driving.
If I'd have gone the other way
over the white line
I might have killed somebody.
So, I went on again and five minutes
later I'm dreaming again and I nearly...
I have such thoughts.
I have such strange thoughts.
Talk to them again, Willy.
There's no reason
why you can't work in New York.
I'm the New England man.
I'm vital in New England.
You're 60 years old. They can't expect
you to keep driving every week.
I'll have to send a wire to Portland.
I'm supposed to see Brown and Morrison
tomorrow morning to show the line.
- Oh, I could sell them.
- Now, Willy.
Go down to that place again.
Talk to Howard.
Tell him you gotta work in New York.
You're too accommodating.
If old man Wagner was alive,
I'd have been in charge of New York now.
That man was a prince.
He was a masterful man.
That boy of his, Howard,
he don't appreciate.
When I went north the first time,
the Wagner Company didn't know
where New England was.
Why don't you
tell these things to Howard?
Oh, I will. I definitely will.
- Oh, is there any cheese?
- I'll make you a sandwich.
Go to sleep. I'll take some milk.
Geez.
Maybe he smashed up the car again.
He's gonna get his licence taken away
if he keeps that up.
I'm getting nervous about him, you know.
- His eyes are gone.
- No, I've driven with him.
He sees all right.
Just, he doesn't keep his mind on it.
I drove into the city
with him last week.
He stops at a green light.
It turns red and he goes.
- Maybe he's colour blind.
- Pop?
He's got the finest eye for colour
in the business.
- The boys in?
- They're sleeping.
- Happy took Biff on a date tonight.
- Is that so?
It was so thrilling,
seeing them shaving together,
one behind the other in the bathroom
and going out together.
- Did you notice?
- Hm?
The whole house smells
of shaving lotion.
Figure it out.
Work a lifetime to pay off a house.
You finally own it.
There's nobody to live in it.
Life's a casting off.
It's always that way.
No, no, some people
accomplish something.
Did Biff say anything
after I went this morning?
You shouldn't have criticised him,
after he just got off the train.
- You must not lose your temper at him.
- When did I lose my temper?
I simply asked him
if he was making any money.
- Is that criticism?
- Willy, how could he make any money?
There's such an undercurrent in him.
He became a moody man. Did he apologise
when I left this morning?
He was crestfallen, Willy.
Now, you know how he admires you.
I think when he finds himself you'll
both be happier and you won't fight.
How can he find himself on a farm?
Is that a life?
A farmhand in the beginning
when he was young,
I thought, a young man, it's good
for him to travel, take differentjobs.
It's more than ten years and
he has yet to make 35 dollars a week.
He is finding himself, Willy.
Not finding yourself at the age of 34
is a disgrace.
- Shh!
- The trouble is, he's lazy!
- Willy, please, they are sleeping.
- Biff is a lazy...
...bum!
- Go down!
Get yourself something to eat
and be quiet.
Why did he come home?
I would like to know
what brought him home.
Well, I don't know.
I think he's still lost, Willy.
I think he's very lost.
Biff Loman is lost
in the greatest country in the world.
A young man with such
personal attractiveness gets lost?
And such a hard worker.
There's one thing about Biff.
He's not lazy.
Never.
I'll see him in the morning, have
a talk with him, get him a job selling.
He'd be big in no time.
Remember the way they used to
follow him around in high school?
Oh, when he just smiled at them
their faces lit up.
When he walked down the
street with a crowd of kids behind him.
Will you ever forget that?
- You smoking?
- You want one?
I can never sleep when I smell it.
It's funny, Biff, you know... us.
Sleeping in here again, huh?
The old beds.
All the talk that went across
those two beds, huh?
- Our whole lives.
- Yeah.
A lotta dreams and plans.
About 500 women would like to know
what was said in this room.
- Remember that big Betsy something?
- Mm-hmm.
What the hell was her name?
Over on Bushwick Avenue.
- With the collie dog.
- Yeah, that's the one.
- I got you in there, man.
- That was my first time, I think.
Boy, there was a pig.
You taught me everything I know
about women. Don't forget that.
I bet you forgot how bashful
you used to be, especially with girls.
Oh, I still am, Biff.
I just control it, that's all.
I think I got less bashful.
You got more so.
What happened, Biff?
Where's your old humour?
The old confidence?
What's the matter?
- Why does Dad mock me all the time?
- He's not mocking you, Biff.
Everything I say there's mockery
on his face. I can't get near him.
I think the fact
that you're not settled,
that you're still up in the air.
I think there's other things
depressing him.
- What do you mean?
- Never mind. Don't lay it all to me.
But I think if you just got started...
I mean, is there any future
for you out there?
I don't know what the future is.
I don't know what I'm supposed to want.
What do you mean?
I spent six or seven years after
high school trying to work myself up.
Shipping clerk, salesman,
business of one kind or another.
It's a measly manner of existence.
To get on that subway
in the hot mornings in the summer,
to devote your whole life
to keeping stock or making phone calls.
And the selling, the buying.
To suffer 50 weeks of the year
for the sake of a two week vacation,
when all you really desire
is to be outdoors with your shirt off.
And always to have to get ahead
of the next fellow.
Still, that's how you build a future.
I bought a new kind
of American type cheese. It's whipped.
Why do you get American?
I like Swiss.
- I thought you'd like a change.
- I don't want a change.
- Why am I always being contradicted?
- I wanted it to be a surprise.
- Why don't you open a window in here?
- They're all open.
They boxed us in here.
Bricks and windows, windows and bricks.
We should have bought
the land next door.
There's not a breath of fresh air
in the neighbourhood.
The grass don't grow anymore.
You can't raise a carrot.
They should have had a law
against apartment houses.
Remember those two beautiful elm trees?
When I and Biff
hung the swing between them, huh?
Like being a million miles
from the city.
They should have arrested the builder
for cutting those down.
They massacred the neighbourhood.
More and more I think of those days,
Linda, this time of year.
It was lilacs and wisteria
and then the peonies
would come out... daffodils.
What fragrance in this room.
- People had to move somewhere.
- There's more people now.
- I don't think...
- There's more people!
That's what's ruining this country!
Population is getting out of control!
The competition is maddening!
Smell the stink from that apartment
house and another on the other side!
How can they whip cheese?
Go down, try it and be quiet.
You're not worried about me,
are you, sweetheart, huh?
No, you've got too much on the ball
to be worried about, my darling.
You're my foundation
and my support, Linda.
Oh, just try to relax.
You make mountains out of molehills.
I won't fight with him anymore.
If he wants to go to Texas, let him go.
- He'll find his way.
- Sure.
Certain men just don't get started
till later in life.
Like Thomas Edison, I think,
or B.F. Goodrich.
One of them was deaf.
I'll put my money on Biff.
And Willy, if it's warm Sunday
we'll drive in the country.
We'll open the windshield,
we'll take lunch.
The windshields don't open
on the new cars.
- But you opened it today.
- Me?
I didn't.
Now, isn't that peculiar?
- Isn't that remarkable?
- What, dear?
That is the most remarkable thing.
What, darling?
I was thinking of the Chevy.
1928, when I had that red Chevy.
Isn't that funny?
I could have sworn
I was back in that Chevy today.
That's nothing.
Something must have reminded you.
Remarkable.
Remember those days, huh?
The way Biff used to simonise that car?
Dealer refused to believe
there was 80,000 miles on it.
Close your eyes.
I'll be right up.
Now, you be careful on the stairs.
- The cheese is on the middle shelf.
- Eighty thousand mi...
Eighty-two thousand.
No, I've always made a point
of not wasting my life.
Whenever I come back here I know that
all I've done is to waste my life.
You're a poet, Biff.
You know that?
- You're an idealist.
- No, I'm mixed up very bad.
Maybe I ought to get married, right?
Maybe I ought
to get stuck into something.
Maybe that's my trouble.
I'm like a boy.
I'm not married, I'm not in business.
I'm just like a boy.
Are you content, Hap?
You're a success, aren't you?
Are you content?
- Hell, no.
- Why not? You're making money.
All I can do now is wait for
the merchandise manager to die.
Listen, kid, why don't you
come out West with me?
And you and I?
Maybe we can buy a ranch,
raise cattle, use some muscles.
Men built like we are
should be working in the open.
- The Loman brothers?
- We'd be known all over.
Biff, Biff, that's
what I dream of sometimes.
Sometimes I want to rip my clothes off
and outbox the merchandise manager.
I can outbox, out lift,
outrun anybody in the store
and I have to take orders
from those sons of bitches.
If you were with me I'd be happier.
Everybody around me is so false
that I am constantly lowering my ideals.
Together we'd stand up for one another.
We werert brought up to grub for money.
I don't know how.
- Neither can I.
- Let's go.
The only thing is,
what can you make out there?
Hap!
I got to show some
of those pompous executives there
that Hap Loman can make the grade, huh?
Then I'll go with you, Biff.
We'll be together yet.
I swear, huh?
But take those two we had tonight.
Werert they gorgeous creatures?
Yeah, most gorgeous I've had in years.
I get that any time I want, Biff.
Whenever I feel disgusted.
The only trouble is,
it gets like bowling or something.
I just keep knocking them over.
It doesn't mean anything.
- You still run around a lot?
- Nah.
I'd like to find a girl steady,
somebody with substance.
- Mm-hmm. That's what I long for.
- Go on.
- You'd never come home.
- I would.
Somebody with character, like Mom.
You're gonna call me a bastard
when I tell you this.
That girl Charlotte I was with,
engaged to be married.
- No kidding.
- Sure.
Guy's in line
for the vice-presidency of the store.
I don't know what gets into me.
Maybe I have an overdeveloped
sense of competition.
I went and ruined her.
Furthermore, I can't get rid of her.
He's the third executive
I've done that to.
Isn't that a crummy characteristic?
And to top it all,
I go to their weddings.
Don't get your sweater dirty!
Biff!
Doesrt he know Mom can hear that?
Oh, what a simonising job. Huh?
Look, Biff, don't leave again, will you?
You'll find a job here, Biff.
- You gotta stay.
- Hey, Biff-o!
I don't know what to do.
It's getting embarrassing.
Oh, boy, what a simonising job.
Look, you go to sleep now but
talk to him in the morning, will ya?
- With her in the house?
- We should have a good talk with him.
- That selfish, stupid...
- Shh. Sleep, Biff.
No kidding, Biff.
You got a date?
Listen, um, you just want
to be careful with those...
...those girls, Biff.
That's all.
Don't make any promises,
no promises, Biff.
No promises of any kind.
'Cause the girls, you know,
they always believe what you tell them.
You're very young, Biff.
You're too young
to be talking seriously to girls.
You want to watch your schooling first.
Stand where you were.
When you're all set, though,
there will be plenty of girls
for a boy like you.
That so?
The girls pay for you?
Boy, you must really be making a hit.
I've been wondering why
you polished the car so careful there.
Uh...
Don't leave the hubcaps.
Get the chamois to the hubcaps.
Happy, use newspaper on the windows.
It's easy.
Use it like a pad.
That's it, good work.
You're going all right.
Biff, um...
First thing we gotta do
when we get time,
we gotta clip that big branch
over the house.
I'm afraid it's gonna fall on the roof.
Tell you what, we get a, uh...
We get a rope and sling her around,
we climb up there with saws
and take her down.
Soon as you finish the car, boys,
I want to see you.
I got a surprise for you, boys.
- What do you got, Dad?
- No, no, you finish first.
Never leave a job till you finish.
You remember that.
Biff?
Up in Albany I saw a beautiful hammock.
I think I'll buy it next trip
and we'll hang it
between those two elms there, huh?
Wouldrt that be...
Huh?
Wouldrt that be something?
Just hanging... Just swinging there
under those branches?
Oh, boy, that would be something.
How's that, Pop? Professional?
Terrific. That's a terrific job, boys.
- Good work, Biff. - Where's the
surprise? - In the back seat of the car.
What is it? Tell me. What did you buy?
-Never mind, something I want you to have.
- What is it, Happy?
- It's a punching bag.
- It's got Gene Tunney's signature.
- How'd you know?
- The finest thing for the timing.
- I'm losing weight.
- Jumping rope is good, too.
- See the football I got?
- Where'd you get a new ball?
- Coach told me to practice passing.
- He gave you the ball?
- I borrowed it from the locker room.
- I want you to return that.
- I told you.
- I'm bringing it back.
- He's gotta practice with a ball.
Coach will congratulate you
on your initiative.
- He keeps congratulating my initiative.
- He likes you.
Somebody else took that ball,
there'd be an uproar.
What's the report, boys?
What's the report?
Where'd you go this time, Pop?
We were lonesome for you.
I'll tell you a secret, boys.
Don't breathe it to a soul.
Someday I'll have my own business
and I'll never have to leave home.
- Like Uncle Charley?
- Bigger than Uncle Charley.
Charley is not liked.
He's liked but he's not well liked.
- Where'd you go this time?
- I went to Providence. Met the mayor.
- The mayor of Providence?
- He was in the hotel lobby.
- What did he say?
- He said, "Good morning".
I said, "You got a fine state here".
He had coffee with me,
then I went to Waterbury.
Waterbury is a fine city, a big clock
city. The famous Waterbury clock.
Sold a nice bill there. And then Boston.
Boston was the cradle of the Revolution.
A fine city.
A couple other towns in Mass,
on to Portland, Bangor
and straight home.
- Love to go with you.
- As soon as summer comes.
- Promise?
- You, Hap and I, I'll show you.
One thing, boys, I have friends.
I can park my car on any street
and the cops protect it like their own.
This summer we'll take
our bathing suits...
- We'll carry your bags.
- That'd be something,
coming to the Boston stores
with you boys carrying my bags!
A sensation.
- You nervous about the game?
- Not if you're gonna be there.
What do they say
now that you're captain?
There's a crowd of girls around him
when classes change.
This Saturday, just for you,
I'm gonna break through for a touchdown.
- You are supposed to pass...
- I'm doing one play for Pop.
When I take off my helmet
that means I'm breaking out.
- Watch me cross that line.
- Wait till I tell this in Boston.
- Biff, where are you?
- Hey, look at Bernard!
What are you looking so anaemic about?
Gotta study, Uncle Willy.
He's got Regents next week.
Come on, let's box.
I heard Mr. Birnbaum say
if you don't start studying math
he's gonna flunk you and you won't
graduate. -You better study with him.
- Pop, you didn't see my sneakers.
- A beautiful job of printing.
Just because he prints University of
Virginia doesn't mean they gotta graduate him.
With scholarships to three universities
they're gonna flunk him?
- I heard Mr. Birnbaum say...
- Don't be a pest.
What an anaemic.
I'm waiting for you in my house, Biff.
Bernard is not well-liked, is he?
He's liked but he's not well-liked.
Bernard can get
the best marks in school,
but when he gets out to the business
world you'll be ahead of him.
That's why I thank Almighty God
you're both built like Adonises.
The man who makes an appearance
in the business world,
the man who creates personal interest,
is the man who gets ahead.
Be liked and you will never want, hm?
Take me, for instance. I never
have to wait in line to see a buyer.
Willy Loman is here,
that's all they have to know.
- I go straight through.
- Did you knock 'em dead?
Knocked them cold in Providence,
slaughtered in Boston.
- I'm losing weight, Pop.
- Hello, dear. - Sweetheart.
- How'd the Chevy run?
- Chevrolet's the greatest car ever.
Since when do you
let your mother carry wash?
Where to, Ma? -Just hang it on the
line. Biff, you gotta go to your friends.
- The cellar is filled with boys.
- When Pop comes home they can wait.
- Better go tell them what to do, Biff.
- Sweep out the furnace room.
- Good work, Biff. - The way they
obey him. - That's the training.
I was selling thousands,
but I had to come home.
The block will be at that game.
You sell anything?
I did 500 gross in Providence,
700 gross in Boston.
Wait, wait, I got a pencil.
That makes your commission 200...
My God!
- Two hundred and twelve dollars!
- I didn't figure it yet.
- How much did you do?
- A hundred eighty gross in Providence.
It comes to roughly 200 gross
on the whole trip.
See, three of the stores
were half closed for inventory.
I would have broke records.
It makes 70 dollars and some pennies.
Very good.
- What do we owe?
- Well...
- Sixteen dollars on the refrigerator.
- Why 16?
- The fan belt broke. It was $1.80.
- It's brand new.
Well, it's like the man says.
It's got to work itself in.
I hope we didn't get stuck
on that machine.
It's got the biggest ads of any of them!
It's a fine machine.
What else?
Well, there's $9.60
for the washing machine,
for the vacuum cleaner there's three and
a half due on the 15th, then the roof.
- You've got 21 dollars. - It don't
leak? - They did a wonderful job.
- You owe five for the carburettor.
- I'm not gonna pay that man.
That lousy, rotten Chevrolet, they ought
to prohibit the manufacture of that car.
Well, you owe him three and a half.
And odds and ends comes to
around 120 dollars by the 15th.
A hundred and twenty dollars?
If business don't pick up I don't know.
- Next week you'll do better.
- I'll knock them dead.
I'll go to Hartford.
I'm well-liked in Hartford.
You know what the trouble is, Linda?
People don't seem to take to me.
- Don't be so foolish.
- I know it when I walk in.
- They seem to laugh at me.
- Why would they laugh at you?
- Don't talk like that.
- They just pass me by.
- You're making 70 to 100 dollars a week.
- I gotta be at in 10, 12 hours a day.
Other men, I don't know why,
they do it easier.
I don't know why I can't stop myself.
I talk too much.
- Oh! - A man ought to come
in with a few words.
Charley, he's a man of few words
and they respect him.
You don't talk too much.
You're just lively.
Well, I figure, what the hell.
Life is short.
A couple of jokes...
- I joke too much.
- Why, you're...
I'm short.
I'm very foolish to look at, Linda.
I didn't tell you, but at Christmastime
I happened to be calling on F.H. Stewarts,
another salesman I know
as I was going to see the buyer.
I heard him say something
about "the shrimp".
And I cracked him...
I cracked him right across the face.
I won't take that.
I simply will not take that.
But they do laugh at me.
Oh, I know that.
- Darling?
- No, I gotta overcome it.
- I know I gotta overcome it.
- Darling?
I'm not dressing to advantage, maybe.
Willy, darling, you're
the handsomest man in the world.
You're the best. You're a pal.
On the road I want to grab you sometimes
and just kiss the life out of you.
I get so lonely,
especially when business is bad,
I get the feeling
I'll never sell anything.
I want to make a living for you.
Or business. Business for the boys.
There's so much I want to make for them.
Me? You didn't make me, Willy.
I picked you.
- You picked me, huh?
- I did.
I'm sitting at that desk, watching all
the salesmen go by, day in and day out.
You got such a sense of humour.
And we do have a good time together.
- Sure, sure. Why do you have to go?
- It's 2:00.
- Come on.
- My sisters will be scandalised.
- When will you be back?
- Two weeks. Will you come up?
Sure thing. You do make me laugh.
That's good for me.
And I think you're a wonderful man.
- You picked me, huh? - I did, 'cause
you're so sweet and such a kidder.
I'll see you next time I'm in Boston.
- I'll put you through to the buyers.
- Right. Well.
Well, bottoms up.
Willy! You just kill me, Willy!
You just kill me!
And thanks for the stockings.
I love a lot of stockings.
- Well, good night.
- Good night.
Oh, and keep your pores open.
Willy!
You are, Willy, the handsomest.
I'll make it all up to you, Linda.
There's nothing to make up.
You're doing fine.
- What's that?
- I'm mending my stockings.
- They're so expensive.
- I won't have you mending stockings!
- Willy...
- Where is he? If he doesn't...
- Give him the answers.
- I do, but I can't on a Regents.
- It's a state exam.
- Biff! Where is he?
You better give back that football.
- Biff, where is he?
- He's too rough with the girls.
- He's driving without a licence.
- Shut up.
Willy.
- Get out of here.
- If he doesn't buckle down he'll flunk.
- You gotta do something about that boy.
- There's nothing the matter with him.
You want him to be a worm like Bernard?
Aw, he's got spirit, personality.
He's loaded with it, loaded.
What is he stealing?
He's giving it back, isn't he?
Why is he stealing?
What did I tell him?
I never in my life told him anything...
Come on up, Pop.
Let's go up.
Huh?
Why did she have
to wax the floors herself?
Every time she waxes the floors
she keels over.
- She knows that.
- Take it easy, Pop.
- Hey, what brought you back tonight?
- I got an awful scare.
I nearly hit a kid in Yonkers.
Why didn't I go to Alaska
with my brother Ben that time?
Ben, that man was a genius.
That man was success incarnate.
What a mistake.
He begged me to go.
The man started with the clothes on his
back and ended up with diamond mines.
I'd like to know how he did it.
The man knew what he wanted, got it.
Walks into a jungle, comes out
the age of 21 and he's rich.
The world is an oyster, but
you don't crack it open on a mattress.
Pop, I told you,
I'm gonna retire you for life.
You're gonna retire me for life
on 70 dollars a week
and your women and your car
and your apartment. You retire me?
I couldn't get past Yonkers today.
Where are you guys? Where are you?
The woods are burning. I can't
drive a car. - Everything all right?
- What's the matter?
- Everything's fine.
- I thought something happened.
- No. - Can't we do something about the walls?
You sneeze in here, in my house hats
blow off. - Come on, let's go up, huh?
- You go ahead. I'm not tired.
- All right. Take it easy.
- What are you doing up?
- I couldn't sleep. I had a heartburn.
- You don't know how to eat.
- I eat with my mouth.
You gotta know about vitamins
and things like that.
- Come on, let's shoot. Tire you out.
- All right.
- You got cards?
- I got them someplace.
What is it with those vitamins?
They build up your bones. Chemistry.
- There's no bones in a heartburn.
- What are you talking about?
- You don't know about it.
- I'll get insulted.
Don't talk about something
you don't know anything about.
- What are you doing home?
- A little trouble with the car.
Oh.
- I'd like to take a trip to California.
- Don't say.
You want a job? - I got a job, I told you
that. What are you offering me a job for?
- Don't get insulted.
- Don't insult me.
- You don't have to go on this way.
- I got a good job.
- What do you keep coming in here for?
- You want me to go?
I can't understand it.
He's going back to Texas again.
- What is that?
- Let him go.
I've got nothing to give him.
I'm clean.
- I'm clean.
- He won't starve. None of them starve.
- Forget about it.
- Then what have I got to remember?
You take it too hard. When a deposit bottle
is broken you don't get your nickel back.
- That's easy for you to say.
- That ain't easy for me to say.
You see the ceiling
I put up in here, hmm?
Yeah, that's a piece of work.
Putting up a ceiling is a mystery to me.
How do you do it?
What's the difference?
- Huh?
- Well, talk about it.
- You gonna put up a ceiling?
- How can I?
- What are you bothering me for?
- You're insulted.
A man who can't handle tools
is not a man.
- You're disgusting.
- Don't call me disgusting, Willy.
Oh, I'm getting...
- I'm getting awfully tired, Ben.
- Keep playing. You'll sleep better.
Did you call me Ben?
That's funny. For a second
you reminded me of my brother, Ben.
- I only have a few minutes.
- You never heard from him again?
Didn't Linda tell you? A couple weeks ago
we got a letter from his wife in Africa.
- He died. - Is that so?
- This is Brooklyn, huh?
- Maybe you're in for some of his money.
- He had seven sons.
There was one opportunity
I had with that man.
There are several properties
I'm looking at.
If I'd have gone with him to Alaska
everything would have been different.
- You'd have froze to death.
- What are you talking about?
Opportunity is tremendous in Alaska.
I'm surprised you're not up there.
There's the only man I ever met
who knew the answers.
- How are you all?
- Fine.
- Pretty sharp tonight.
- Is Mother living with you?
- She died long ago.
- Who?
- Fine specimen of a lady, Mother.
- I'd hoped to see the old girl.
- Who died?
- You heard from Father?
- What do you mean, who died?
- What are you talking about?
- What are you talking about!
- It's half past eight.
- That's my bill.
- I put the ace.
- If you don't know how to play...
- It's my ace, for God's sake.
- I'm through!
- When did Mother die?
- Long ago.
- You never knew how to play cards.
- All right.
Next time I'll bring a deck
with five aces.
- I don't play that kind of game.
- You ought to be ashamed of yourself.
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
- Ignoramus.
- So, you're William?
Oh, Ben.
I've been waiting for you so long.
What's the answer?
How did you do it?
There's a story in that.
- Is this Ben?
- How do you do?
Where have you been?
Willy's been wondering...
Where is Dad?
How did you get started?
- I don't know how much you remember.
- I was just a baby, 3 or 4 years old.
- Three years, eleven months.
- What a memory.
I have many enterprises
and I've never kept books.
I was sitting under the wagon.
What was it, Nebraska?
South Dakota and I gave you wildflowers.
- I remember you walking down some road.
- I was going to find Father in Alaska.
In those days
I had a very faulty view of geography.
I discovered after a few days
I was heading south.
Instead of Alaska I ended up in
Africa. - Africa? - The Gold Coast!
- Principally, diamond mines.
- Diamond mines!
Yes, but I'm afraid
I only have a few minutes.
Boys, boys, listen to this!
This is your Uncle Ben!
A great man!
Ben, tell my boys.
Why, boys, when I was 17
I walked into the jungle.
When I was 21, I walked out.
- And by God, I was rich!
- See what I've been talking about?
- The greatest things can happen.
- I have an appointment in Ketchikan.
Tell about Dad.
I want my boys to hear.
I want them to know
the stock they spring from.
All I remember is a man with a big beard.
I was sitting on Mama's lap around the fire.
- There was some kind of high
music. - He played the flute.
- The flute, that's right. - Father was
a very great, very wild-hearted man.
He'd start in Boston
and toss the whole family in the wagon,
and he'd drive the team
right across the country.
Through lowa, Michigan, Illinois
and all the western states.
We'd stop in the towns and
he'd sell the flutes he made on the way.
A great inventor, Father.
With one gadget he made more in one week
than a man like you makes in a lifetime.
That's the way I'm bringing them up,
rugged, well-liked, all around.
- Yeah? Hit me, boy, hard as you can.
- No.
Oh, come on, get to me.
Go ahead, show him.
Like I taught you.
Give him the old shoulderjab.
Hey!
- How's that?
- Very good, Willy, very good.
- Shake hands, boys. Attaway.
- Look out, Biff.
Never fight fair with a stranger, boy.
You'll never get
out of the jungle that way.
It was an honour and a pleasure
to meet you, Linda.
Have a nice trip.
Oh, and good luck with your, uh...
What do you do?
- Oh, uh, selling.
- Oh, yes, really?
I don't want you to think...
It's Brooklyn, but we hunt too.
- Really, now?
- There's snakes and rabbits
That's why I moved out.
Biff can fell any one of these trees.
Go over to where they're building
the apartment and get some sand.
We're gonna rebuild the front stoop.
Watch us.
I lost weight, Pop, you notice?
They steal more
they'll put the cops on them.
- Don't let Biff take any more.
- The load they brought last week,
at least a dozen six by tens,
won'th all kinds of money.
If that watchman sees them...
I got a couple of fearless characters.
Willy, the gaols are full
of fearless characters.
- And the Stock Exchange.
- Uncle Willy!
Uncle Willy,
the watchmars chasing Biff!
Shut up.
He's not stealing anything.
Where is he?
Oh, there's nothing wrong.
What is the matter with you?
Nervy boy, good.
Nerves of iron, that Biff.
I don't know what it is.
My New England man comes back
and he's bleeding.
- Couldrt sell a nickel for five cents.
- It's contacts, Charley.
- I got important contacts.
- Glad to hear it, Willy.
Come in later,
we'll shoot a little casino.
I'll take some of your Portland money.
All business is bad, it's murderous.
But not for me, of course.
- I'll stop by on my way
back to Africa. - Ben, wait.
Can't you stay a few days, huh?
You're just what I need, Ben.
You know, I have a fine position here,
but Dad left when I was such a baby,
I never had a chance to talk to him.
I still feel
kind of temporary about myself.
- I'll be late for my train.
- Ben, my boys. Can't we talk?
See, they'd go
into the jaws of hell for me, but I...
You're being first-rate with your boys.
Outstanding, manly chaps.
Ben, that's good to hear
because sometimes I'm afraid
I'm not teaching them
the right kind of...
How should I teach them?
William, when I walked
into the jungle, I was 17.
When I walked out I was 21.
And by God, I was rich!
Was rich!
That's just the spirit
I want to imbue them with,
to walk into a jungle...
Oh, boy.
I was right. I was right. I was right!
- I was right!
- Willy?
Willy, dear, did you get some cheese?
It's awful late, darling.
Come to bed.
You gotta break your neck
to see a star in this yard.
Are you coming up, Willy?
Whatever happened
to that diamond watch fob?
When Ben came from Africa that time,
didn't he give me a watch fob
with a diamond in it?
You pawned it, dear, 12, 13 years ago
for Biff's radio correspondence course.
That was a beautiful thing.
I'll take a walk.
But in your slippers, Willy?
What a man, huh?
Now, there was a man won'th talking to.
- But in your slippers!
- I was right.
I was, I was right!
- What is he doing out here?
- Shh!
- God Almighty, Mom.
- How long's he been doing this?
- Don't. He'll hear you.
What the hell is the matter with him?
- It'll pass by morning.
- Shouldn't we do anything?
Oh, my dear,
you should do a lot of things.
There's nothing to do.
Go to bed.
- I never heard him so loud, Mom.
- You'll hear him.
- Why didn't you write me about this?
- How would I?
For over three months
you've had no address.
I was on the move.
I thought of you all the time.
But he likes to have a letter
just to know there's still
the possibility of better things.
- He's not like this all the time.
- When you come home he's the worst.
When you write you're coming,
he's all smiles, he talks about
the future, he's wonderful.
The closer you come the more shaky
he gets and by the time you get here,
he's arguing,
he seems to be angry at you.
I think it's just because he can't
bring himself to open up to you.
- Why are you so hateful to each other?
- I'm not hateful.
Oh! You no sooner walk through
that door than you're fighting.
I don't know why.
I mean to change, Mom. I'm trying.
- Are you home to stay now?
- I don't know.
- I'll look around.
- You can't look around all your life.
I just can't take hold.
I can't take hold to some kind of life.
Biff, a man is not a bird
to come and go with the springtime.
Your hair.
Your hair's getting so gray.
It's been gray
since you were in high school.
- I just stopped dying it.
- Well, dye it again, Mom.
I don't want my pal looking old.
You are such a boy!
You think you can go away for a year?
You've got to get it into your head now.
One day you'll knock on this door,
there will be strange people here.
What are you talking about?
You're not even 60 yet.
What about your father?
- Well, I meant him, too.
- He admires Pop.
If you don't have feeling for him,
you can't have feelings for me.
- Sure, I can.
- No, Biff.
You can'tjust come to see me!
Because I love him.
He's the dearest man in the world to me
and I won't have anyone making him feel
unwanted and low and blue.
You have got to make up your mind now.
There's no leeway anymore.
Either he's your father,
and you pay him that respect,
or else you're not to come here.
- Hey, Biffo!
- What the hell is the matter with him?
- Don't go near him.
- Stop making excuses for him.
He always wiped the floor with you.
He never had an ounce of respect.
- He always had respect for her.
- What do you know?
- Don't call him crazy.
- He's got no character.
Charley wouldn't do this,
not in his house.
- Peeling that vomit from his mind.
- Charley never had what he's got.
People are worse off than Willy Loman,
I've seen them.
Then make Charley your father.
You can't do that, can you?
I am not saying he's a great man.
Willy Loman never earned a lot of money.
His name was never in the paper.
He's not the finest character.
But he's a human being.
And a terrible thing is happening
to him. So attention must be paid.
He must not be allowed
to fall into his grave like an old dog.
Attention! Attention must
finally be paid to such a person.
- You called him crazy?
- Mom, I didn't...
Wait a minute. A lot of people think
he's lost his balance,
but you don't have to be very smart
to know what his trouble is.
- The man is exhausted.
- Sure.
A small man can be
just as exhausted as a great man.
He works for a company
36 years this March,
he opens up uneard of territories
to their trademark,
and now, in his old age,
they take his salary away!
- I didn't know that, Mom.
- You never asked, my dear!
Now you get your spending money
somewhere else
- you don't trouble your mind with him.
- I gave you money.
Christmastime, 50 dollars.
To fix the hot water it cost $97.50!
For five weeks
he's been on straight commission,
like a beginner, an unknown.
Those ungrateful bastards!
Are they any worse than his sons?
He drives 700 miles,
and when he gets there no one
knows him anymore, no one welcomes him.
And what goes through a mars mind
driving 700 miles home
without having earned a cent?
Why shouldn't he talk to himself?
Why not, when
he has to go to Charley every week
and borrow 50 dollars from him,
and pretend to me it's his pay.
How long can that go on?
How long?
And you tell me he has no character?
The man who never worked a day
in his life but for your benefit!
And when does he get the medal for that?
Is this his reward?
To turn around at the age of 63
and find his sons,
who he loved better than his life,
- one a philandering bum...
- Mom!
That is all you are, my baby.
And you! What happened
to the love you had for him?
You were such pals.
How you used to talk every night
on the phone,
how lonely he was
till he could come home to you.
All right, Mom.
I'll live in my room, I'll get a job,
I'll just keep away from him.
No, Biff, you can't stay here
and fight all the time.
He threw me out of this house.
Why did he do that?
- Because I know he's a fake.
- A fake!
- In what way? What do you mean?
- Just don't lay it all at my feet.
It's between me and him.
That's all I have to say.
I'll chip in from now on.
He'll settle for half my paycheque.
- He'll be all right.
- He won't be all right!
I hate this city and I'll stay here.
Now, what do you want?
- He's dying, Biff.
- Why is he dying?
He's been trying to kill himself.
How?
Do you remember I wrote you that
he smashed the car again in February?
Well?
The insurance inspector came.
There's evidence that all the accidents
in the last year werert accidents.
How can they tell?
That's a lie.
- It seems there's a woman...
- What woman?
What?
- Nothing.
- What did you say?
- I said, "What woman?"
- What about her?
She was walking down the road.
She saw his car.
She said he wasrt driving fast at all.
He didn't skid, she said.
He came to that little bridge and
deliberately smashed into the railing.
It was the shallowness of the water
that saved him.
Mom, he probably just fell asleep again.
- No. I don't think he fell asleep.
- Why not?
Last month...
Oh, boys, it's so hard
to say a thing like this.
I was looking for a fuse, the lights
blew out, I went down in the cellar.
Behind the fuse box,
it happened to fall out,
was this length of rubber pipe,
just short.
No kidding.
There was an attachment
on the end of it.
I knew right away, and sure enough.
On the bottom of the hot water heater
there's a new nipple on the gas pipe.
- Thatjerk.
- Did you have it taken off?
I'm ashamed to.
How can I mention it to him?
Every day I go down
and I take away
that little rubber pipe.
But when he comes home
I put it back where it was.
How can I insult him that way?
It sounds so silly and old-fashioned,
but I tell you,
he's put his whole life into you.
And you've turned your backs on him.
Biff, his life is in your hands.
I feel like a damn fool.
All right.
It's settled now.
I've been remiss, I know that.
But now I'll stay and I swear to you,
Mama, I'll apply myself.
It's just that, see,
I don't fit in business.
Not that I won't try.
I'll try and I'll make good.
The trouble was,
you never tried to please people.
It's like when you worked
for Bob Harrison.
He said you were tops.
Then you go and do some damn fool thing
like whistling songs in the elevator.
So what? I like to whistle.
You don't raise a guy
to a responsible job who whistles.
Don't argue about it.
You'd go for a swim
in the middle of the day.
You don't take off?
You run off sometimes, on a nice day.
- Sure, but I cover myself.
- Oh, boys.
I'll tell you something.
In the business world
some of them think you're crazy.
- Screw the business world.
- Right. Great. But cover yourself.
I don't care!
They've laughed at Dad for years.
You know why? Because we don't belong
in this nuthouse of a city.
We should be mixing cement somewhere
on some open plain, or carpenters.
A carpenter's allowed to whistle.
Even your grandfather was better
than a carpenter.
You never grew up.
Bernard does not whistle
in the elevator, I assure you.
- I bet you do.
- I never whistled in an elevator.
And who in the business world
thinks I'm crazy, hmm?
I didn't mean it like that.
Don't make a thing out of it.
Go back to the West.
Be a carpenter or a cowboy.
- Enjoy yourself.
- He was just saying things.
- I heard what he said.
- Come on.
They laugh at me, huh?
Go to Filene's, go to the Hub,
go to Slattery's, Boston
and call out the name Willy Loman.
- See what happens. Big shot. Big.
- All right, Pop.
All right.
Why do you always insult me?
Dad, I didn't say a word.
- Did I say a word?
- He didn't say anything, Willy.
No.
- All right, good night.
- Willy! He's decided...
If you get tired hanging around
tomorrow, paint the ceiling I put up.
I'm leaving early tomorrow.
He's gonna see Bill Oliver, Pop.
Oliver?
For what?
Well, he always said he'd stake me
and I'd like to go into business,
so maybe I'll take him up on it.
- Isn't that wonderful?
- What's wonderful about it?
There's 50 men in the city of New York
that would stake him.
- Sporting goods?
- I guess so.
- I know something about it.
- He knows something about it!
You know sporting goods
better than Spalding, for God's sake.
- How much is he giving you?
- I don't know. I haven't seen him yet.
- Then what are you talking about?
- All I said was I was gonna go see him.
- You're counting your chickens again.
- Jesus.
- Don't curse in this house.
- Since when did you get so clean?
Don't use that language to me.
I won't have it!
I got an idea, a feasible idea. Let's
talk this over. Let's talk sense.
When I was in Florida last time I thought
of a great idea to sell sporting goods.
It just came back to me.
We have a line, the Loman line.
- We put on a couple of exhibitions.
- That's an idea. - Wait!
We form two basketball teams,
two water polo teams.
We play each other.
It's a million dollars of publicity.
Two brothers, see?
The Loman brothers.
- We could sell sporting goods.
- That is a one million dollar idea.
Marvellous.
I'm in great shape
as far as that's concerned.
It wouldn't be like a business at all.
We'd be out playing ball again.
- That's what I was talking about.
- You won't get fed up. It'd be family.
Lick the world. You guys together could
absolutely lick the civilised world.
I'll see Oliver.
If we could work that out...
- I think everything is...
- Stop interrupting!
Don't wear a sports jacket and slacks.
A business suit
and talk as little as possible.
- And don't crack any jokes.
- Hey, he did like me.
- He always liked me.
- Oh, he loved you.
Will you stop!
Walk in very serious.
You're not applying for a boy's job.
Money is to pass.
Be quiet, fine and serious.
Everybody likes a kidder
but nobody lends them money.
- I'll try to get some myself.
- I see great things for you.
I think your troubles are over.
Start big, you'll end big. Ask for 15.
How much you gonna ask for?
- Gee, I don't...
- Don't say gee. Gee is a boy's word.
A man walking in for $15,000
does not say "gee".
- Ten would be top.
- Don't be so modest.
You always start it too low.
Walk in with a big laugh.
Start off with a couple of your
good stories to lighten things up.
It's not what you say
but how you say it,
because personality always wins the day.
- Oliver always thought...
- Will you let me talk!
Dad, stop yelling at her.
I was talking, wasrt I?
I just don't like you
yelling at her all the time.
- I'm telling you.
- You taking over this house?
- Willy, he didn't mean...
- Don't take his side all the time!
Stop yelling at her.
Give my best to Bill Oliver.
- He may remember me.
- Why did you have to start that?
Did you see how sweet he was
as soon as you talked hopefully?
Go up.
Say good night to him.
- Don't let him go to bed that way.
- Biff, let's buck him up.
Please, dear.
It takes so little to make him happy.
Come.
Your pyjamas are hanging
in the bathroom, Willy.
What a woman.
They broke the mould when they made her.
You know that, Biff?
He's off salary.
My god, working on commission.
Let's face it.
He's no hotshot selling man.
Sometimes you gotta admit
he's a sweet personality.
Lend me ten bucks.
I'm gonna buy some new ties.
I'll take you to a place I know.
Wear one of my striped shirts.
Mom got so gray.
She got awful old.
I'm gonna go in and see Oliver tomorrow
and I'm gonna knock him...
Come on up and tell Dad.
Let's give him a whirl.
With ten thousand bucks... boy.
That's the first time
I've heard the old confidence.
You're gonna live with me, kid,
and I'm telling you, any babe you want.
You say the word.
Can you do something about the shower?
It drips.
Oh, all of a sudden
everything falls to pieces.
That damn plumbing.
They ought to be sued, those people.
- Hardly finished putting it in...
- I'm wondering if Oliver will remember.
- You think he might? -Remember him?
What's the matter with you? Are you crazy?
If he'd have stayed with Oliver,
he'd be on top now.
Wait till Oliver gets a look at him. You
don't know the average calibre anymore.
The average young man today
has got a calibre of zero.
The greatest thing for him
was to bum up...
Willy.
- Glad to hear it, boy.
- He wanted to say good night to you.
Oh, yeah, you knock them dead, boy.
What do you want to tell me?
Take it easy, Pop, good night.
If anything falls off the desk
while you're talking to him,
like a package or something,
don't you pick it up.
- They have office boys.
- I'll make a big breakfast.
Will you let me finish, hmm?
Tell him you were in business
in the West, not farm work.
- All right, Dad. I will.
- I think everything's gonna be...
And don't undersell yourself.
No less than $15,000.
- OK. Good night, Mom.
- Because you got a greatness in you.
Biff!
Remember that.
- You got all kinds of greatness.
- Sleep well, darling.
- I'm gonna get married, Mom. I wanted
to tell you. - Go to sleep, dear.
I just wanted to tell you.
Keep up the good work.
Do you remember that Ebbets Field
game, the championship of the city?
Hmm?
Just rest, dear.
- Should I sing to you?
- Yeah, you sing to me.
You know, when that team came out,
he was the tallest.
You remember?
- All in gold.
- Oh, like a young god.
Hercules, something like that. And
the sun, the sun all around him.
Remember how he waved to me?
Right from the field, with the representatives
from three colleges standing by,
and the buyers I brought.
Oh, the cheers when he came out.
Loman! Loman!
Loman!
God Almighty, he'll be great yet.
A star like that, magnificent,
can never really fade away.
- Oh, boy.
- Willy?
Dear?
What has he got against you?
I'm so tired. Don't talk anymore.
Will you ask Howard
if he'll let you work in New York?
First thing in the morning.
Everything will be all right.
Gee.
Look at the moon
moving between the buildings.
Oh, oh, wonderful coffee!
- A meal in itself.
- Can I make you some eggs?
- Take a breath.
- You look so rested, dear.
I slept like a dead one.
First time in months.
Imagine sleeping till 10
on a Tuesday morning.
- Boys left nice and early? - They
were out of here by 8:00. - Good work.
It was thrilling, them leaving together.
I cannot get over the smell
of shaving lotion in this house.
Biff was very changed this morning.
His attitude seemed to be hopeful.
- He couldn't wait to see Oliver.
- He's heading for a change.
- Certain men take longer to get...
- Solidified.
- How did he dress?
- His blue suit.
He looked so handsome.
He could be anything in that suit.
Boy, there's no question.
No question at all.
Gee, on the way home tonight
I'd like to buy some seeds.
Wonderful, but not enough sun
gets back there. Nothing will grow.
Before it's over
we'll get a place in the country,
- I'll raise vegetables, chickens.
- You'll do it.
They'll get married and visit.
I'll build a guest house.
I've got so many tools. All I'd need
would be lumber and peace of mind.
- I sewed the liner.
- I could build two houses
- so they'd both come.
- Yes.
- He decide how much he's gonna ask for?
- He didn't, but I imagine ten.
Fifteen thousand.
You're gonna talk to Howard today?
Oh, yeah, I'll, uh...
I'll put it to him straight and simple.
- He'll have to take me off the road.
- Ask for a little advance.
We've got the insurance premium.
It's the grace period.
It's $108.68 because
we're a little short this month.
- Why are we short?
- You had the job done on the car.
- That damn Studebaker.
- One more payment on the refrigerator.
- Itjust broke again.
- It's old, dear.
We should have bought
a well advertised machine.
Charley bought a General Electric.
It's 20 years old and it's good.
- Willy, please! - Whoever heard
of a Hastings refrigerator?
Once in my life I'd like to buy
something outright before it's broken.
I am always in a race with the junkyard.
I just finished paying for the car.
It's on its last legs.
The refrigerator consumes belts.
- Willy.
- They time those things!
They time them so when you finally
pay for them they're used up.
All told, about 200 dollars
would carry us dear,
but that includes the last payment
on the mortgage.
When we've made that payment, Willy,
the house belongs to us.
- That's 25 years.
- Biff was nine when we bought it.
Well, that's a great thing,
to weather a 25 year mortgage.
It's an accomplishment.
All the cement, the lumber. The
reconstruction I put in this house.
There ain't a crack
to be found in it anymore.
- Well, it served its purpose.
- What purpose?
Some stranger will come along,
move in, and that's that.
If only Biff would take this house
and raise a family.
- Good-bye. I'm late.
- I forgot to tell you.
You're supposed to meet them for dinner.
Frank's Chop House, near Sixth Avenue.
Is that so? How about you?
Just the three of you.
They are gonna blow you to a big meal.
- Who thought of that?
- Biff came to me this morning.
He said, "Tell Dad we're gonna blow
him to a big meal. Be there 6:00".
You and your two boys
are gonna have dinner.
- Gee whiz, that's really something.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna knock Howard for a loop, kid.
I'll get an advance
and I'll come home with a New York job!
- I'm gonna do it!
- That's the spirit, Willy!
I will never get behind the wheel
the rest of my life!
It's changing, Willy.
I can feel it changing.
- Beyond a question.
- Oh!
- You got your glasses?
- Yeah.
And your handkerchief?
And your saccharine?
- And my saccharine.
- Be careful on the subway stairs.
Will you stop mending stockings?
It gets me nervous. I can't tell you.
And don't forget,
Frank's Chop House.
- Maybe beets would grow out there.
- Oh, Willy, you tried so many times.
- Yeah, well, don't work hard.
- Now, you be careful.
Come on, give me a little something.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
- Psst.
- Hello, Willy.
- I'd like to talk to you, Howard.
- I'll be with you in a minute.
- What's that?
- Didrt you ever see one of these?
- It's a wire recorder.
- Can we talk a minute?
It records things.
I just got delivery yesterday.
It's the most terrific machine
I ever saw in my life.
- I was up all night with it.
- What do you do?
I bought it for dictation
but you can do anything with it.
Listen to this. I had it home.
Listen to what I picked up.
The first one is my daughter.
Get this.
Listen to that kid whistle.
That is lifelike, isn't it?
- Seven years old. Get that tone.
- I'd like to ask a little favour.
It's your turn now, Daddy.
She's crazy for me.
- That's me. - You're very
good. - Now this is my son.
The capital of Alabama is Montgomery.
The capital of California is Sacramento.
- Five years old.
He'll make an announcer someday.
- The capital of Colorado...
- That is alphabetical order.
- The maid kicked the plug.
- That certainly is...
Shh! For God's sake.
It is 9:00 so I have to go to sleep.
- It really is...
- Wait. The next is my wife.
- Talk!
- I can't think of anything.
- It's time.
- Hello. Howard, I can't talk.
- That was my wife.
- That is a wonderful machine. Can we...
I'm gonna take my camera and my bandsaw
and all my hobbies and out they go.
- This is the most fascinating
relaxation ever. - I think I'll get one.
They're a hundred and a half.
You can't do without it.
Supposing you want to hear Jack Benny,
see. But you can't be home at that hour.
You tell the maid to turn the radio on
when Jack Benny comes on,
and this automatically comes on
with the radio.
- When you come home...
- You come home any time you like.
You get yourself a Coke,
sit down, throw the switch,
and there is Jack Benny's programme,
in the middle of the night.
I'm gonna get one,
'cause lots of times I'm on the road,
and I think, "What I must
be missing on the radio".
- Don't you have a radio in the car?
- Yeah. Whoever thinks of turning it on?
- Arent you supposed to be in Boston?
- That's what I want to talk about.
- You got a minute?
- What happened?
- You didn't crack up again, did you?
- Oh, no.
Oh!
Geez, you got me worried there
for a minute.
- Well, what's the trouble?
- Well, to tell you the truth,
I've come to the decision
that I'd rather not travel anymore.
- Not travel? Well, what would you do?
- Remember Christmastime at the party
you said you'd think
of a spot for me here in town?
- With us? - Sure. - Oh,
yeah, yeah, I remember.
I couldn't think of anything for you.
I'll tell you, Howard, the kids
are all grown up now, you know.
I don't need much anymore.
If I could take home $65 a week
I could swing it.
- Yeah, but Willy...
- I'll tell you why.
Speaking frankly
between the two of us, you know,
I'm just a little tired.
Oh.
I can understand that, Willy.
But you're a road man, Willy.
We're a road business.
We've got half a dozen salesmen here.
God knows, Howard,
I never asked a favour of any man,