but I was with the firm when
your father used to carry you in here.
- I know.
- Your father came to me
the day you were born and asked me
what I thought of the name Howard.
I appreciate that, Willy,
but there just is no spot here for you.
If I had a spot I would slam you
right in there, but I just don't.
- All I need is 50 dollars a week.
- Where am I gonna put you, kid?
It's not a question
of whether I can sell, huh?
No, but it's a business and
everybody's gotta pull his own weight.
- Let me tell you a story.
- Business is business.
This is definitely business.
Listen. You don't understand this.
When I was a boy, 18, 19,
I was already on the road.
There was a question in my mind
whether selling had a future for me.
In those days
I had a yearning to go to Alaska.
There were three gold strikes
in one month in Alaska.
I felt like going out,
just for the ride, you might say.
- You don't say?
- My father lived many years in Alaska.
He was an adventurous man.
We got quite a streak of self-reliance
in our family.
I thought I'd go out with
my older brother, try to locate him,
maybe settle in the North.
I was almost decided to go...
...when I met a salesman
in the Parker House.
His name was Dave Singleman.
He was 84 years old and
he'd drummed merchandise in 31 states.
Old Dave would go up to his room,
put on his green velvet slippers,
pick up the phone and call the buyers.
Without ever leaving his room
at the age of 84,
he made his living.
When I saw that, I realised that selling
was the greatest career a man could want
because what could be more satisfying
than to be able to go at the age of 84
into 20 or 30 different cities
and pick up a phone
and be remembered and loved
and helped by many different people.
You know, when he died...
And by the way, he died
the death of a salesman,
in his green velvet slippers
in the smoker of the New York,
New Haven and Hartford
going into Boston.
When he died, hundreds of salesmen
and buyers were at his funeral.
Things were sad on a lot of trains
for months after that.
You see, in those days there was
personality in it, Howard.
There was respect and comradeship and...
...and gratitude.
Today it's all cut and dry.
And there's no chance for bringing
friendship to bear or personality.
You see what I mean.
- They don't know me anymore.
- That's just the thing, Willy.
If I had 40 dollars a week,
that's all I need.
- I can't take blood from a stone.
- Howard!
The year Al Smith was nominated
your father came to me...
I'm talking about your father!
There were promises made
across this desk!
You mustnt tell me
that you got people to see!
I put 34 years into this firm,
Howard! Now I can't pay my insurance!
You can't eat the orange
and throw the peel away!
A man is not a piece of fruit!
Pay attention.
No, your father...
Howard...
In 1928 I had a big year.
I averaged 170 dollars a week.
- You never averaged 170 dollars a week.
- No, no, no!
I averaged 170 dollars a week
in the year 1928!
And your father came to me, Howard,
right across this desk,
put his hand on my shoulder...
You have to excuse me, Willy!
I have got to see some people.
Pull yourself together.
I'll be back in a little while.
Ah, pull myself together!
What did I say to him?
Oh, my god.
I was yelling at him.
Frank, Frank, don't you remember
what you told me that time?
You put your hand on my shoulder...
The capital of Delaware...
Oh, Howard!
Howard!
Howard, Howard, shut it off!
Shut it off!
- Look, Willy...
- I gotta get myself some coffee.
- I'll get coffee.
- Willy, look...
Look, Willy,
you can't go to Boston for us.
- Why can't I go?
- I don't want you to represent us.
I've been meaning to tell you
for a long time now.
- Howard, are you firing me?
- I think you need a good long rest.
When you feel better come back
and we'll try to work something out.
I gotta earn money, Howard.
Where are your sons?
Wort your sons give you a hand?
Oh, they're working on a very big deal.
This is no time for false pride.
Go to your sons
and tell them you're tired.
You got two great boys there.
- No question.
- That's that, huh?
In the meantime. All right.
I'll go to...
I'll go to Boston tomorrow.
No!
No.
I can't throw myself on my kids.
I'm not a freeloader.
- Kid, I am busy this morning.
- Let me go to Boston.
I have got a line
of people to see this morning.
- Sit down. Sit.
- What?
Oh.
Take five minutes
and pull yourself together.
And then go home, will you?
I need the office.
Whenever you can this week,
drop off the samples.
You'll feel better, Willy,
and then come back. We'll talk.
Pull yourself together, kid.
There's people outside.
Oh, Ben!
How did you do it, huh?
What's the answer?
Did you wind up the Alaska deal already?
Doesrt take much time if you know what
you're doing. I wanted to say good-bye.
- I gotta talk to you.
- I haven't the time.
Nothing's working out.
I don't know what to do.
I bought timberland in Alaska. I need
a man to look after things for me.
God, timberland!
Me and my boys and those grand outdoors!
A new continent on your doorstep.
Get out of these cities. They're full of
talk, time payments and courts of law.
- You can fight for a fortune up there.
- Linda! Linda!
- Linda.
- You're back.
- I haven't much time.
- Wait.
He's got a proposition for me in Alaska.
- But you've got a job here.
- But in Alaska, kid, I could...
- You are doing well enough.
- Enough for what, dear?
Don't say things like that to him.
Enough to be happy right here, now.
Why must everyone conquer the world?
You're well-liked, the boys love you.
The other day old man Wagner told him
he'll be a member of the firm.
- Didn't he, Willy?
- I'm building something with this firm.
If a man is building
he must be on the right track.
- What are you building? Where is it?
- That's true, Linda, there's nothing.
Why, there's a man 84 years old, Willy.
That's right, Ben, that's right!
When I look at that man
I say what's there to worry about?
All he has to do is go into any city,
pick up a phone
and he's making his living. Know why?
- I gotta go.
- Oh, look at this boy.
Without a penny to his name, three
great universities are begging for him.
From there the sky's the limit! It's
not what you do, Ben, it's who you know!
And a smile on your face.
It's contacts, Ben, contacts!
The whole wealth of Alaska passing over
the lunch table of the Commodore Hotel.
And that's the wonder,
the wonder of this country,
that a man can end with diamonds
on the basis of being liked.
That's why, when you get
on that field today, it's important,
'cause thousands of people
will be rooting for you, loving you.
When he walks into a business office,
his name will sound out like a bell,
and all the doors will open to him.
I seen it, Ben.
I seen it a thousand times. You can't
feel it in your hands, but it's there.
- Good-bye.
- Don't you think I'm right?
- I value your advice.
- A new continent at your doorstep.
You could walk out rich.
Rich!
We're gonna do a hit, Ben, you hear me?
We're gonna do a hit!
Gee, I was afraid you left already.
- What time is it?
- Ten past one.
Oh, come on everybody,
Ebbets Field, next stop.
- Where's the pennants?
- Did you pack fresh underwear?
- I want to go. - I'm
carrying your helmet. - I am.
You promised me.
How am I gonna get in the locker room?
Let him carry the shoulder guards.
Can I? I told everybody
I was gonna be in the locker room.
- It's the Clubhouse.
- I meant the Clubhouse.
- Let him carry the shoulder guards.
- Stay close to us.
- Wave when Biff comes out on the
field! You set, boy? - Ready to go, Pop.
- Every muscle is ready.
- You realise what this means.
You're coming home this afternoon
captain of the All-Scholastic
Championship Team
- of the city of New York.
- That's right, Pop, and remember,
when I take off my helmet,
that touchdowrs for you.
Let's go over.
I got no room for you, Charley.
- Room for what?
- In the car.
Going for a ride?
I want to shoot some casino.
Don't you realise what today is?
Oh, he knows, Willy.
He's just kidding you.
That's nothing to kid about. I'm
not kidding, Linda. What's going on?
He is playing at Ebbets Field today.
- Baseball in this weather?
- Don't talk to him. We're late.
- Didn't you hear the news?
- What?
Don't you listen to the radio?
Ebbets Field just blew up.
You go to hell! Everybody in?
Knock a homer, Biff.
Knock a homer!
I don't think that was funny, Charley.
Did you hear me, huh?
This is the greatest day in his life.
When are you gonna grow up?
When this game is over
you won't be laughing anymore.
They'll be calling him
another Red Grange, 25,000 a year.
- That so?
- Yeah!
- Wait a minute, Willy. I'm sorry.
- Yeah?
But tell me something.
Who is Red Grange?
Put up your hands.
Put up your hands, come on.
Put up your hands. Who do you think
you are, better than everybody?
Put up your hands! Put up your hands!
Put up your hands.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You don't know everything,
you big ignorant stupid...
Put up your hands.
What are you walking away for?
Don't walk away. You gonna say
something to me, say it to my face.
I know you laugh at me behind my back.
You'll be laughing out of the other
side of your face after this game.
The woods are burning.
Touchdown! Touchdown!
Eighty thousand people!
Right between the goal posts.
Touchdown! Touchdown!
Hello, baby! Touchdown!
Touchdown! Ah, Jenny.
Jenny, good to see you.
How are you?
- Working? Or still honest?
- Fine.
- How you been feeling?
- Not much any more.
- Oh!
- Hello, Uncle Willy.
Bernard.
- Look who's here.
- How are you?
- What are you doing here?
- I just stopped by to see Pop.
To get off my feet till my train leaves.
I'm going to Washington.
- Is he in?
- He's with the accountant.
Sit down. What are you
gonna do in Washington?
- Just a case I've got there.
- That so? You gonna play tennis there?
I'm staying with a friend
who's got a court.
You don't say.
Their own tennis court?
- Those are fine people, I bet.
- They're very nice.
- Dad tells me Biff's in town.
- Yeah.
Biff's in. He's working
on a very big deal, Bernard.
- What's Biff doing? - He's been
doing very big things in the West,
but he decided
to establish himself here.
Very big. We're having dinner.
Did I hear your wife had a boy?
That's right. Our second.
Two boys.
- What do you know?
- You still with the old firm, Willy?
I'm overjoyed to see how
you made the grade, Bernard, overjoyed.
It's an encouraging thing to see.
A young man really... really...
Ah, it looks very good for Biff.
Very good.
- Bernard. - What is it, Willy?
- What... What's the secret?
- What secret?
- How did you...?
- Why didn't he ever catch on?
- Willy, I wouldn't know that.
Oh, you were his friend,
his boyhood friend.
It's something I don't understand.
His life ended
after that Ebbets Field game.
From the age of 17
nothing good ever happened to him.
- He never trained himself for anything.
- He took correspondence courses.
Radio mechanics, television...
He never made the slightest mark.
- Do you want to talk candidly?
- Bernard.
I regard you as a very brilliant man.
Bernard, I value your advice.
The hell with advice.
I couldn't advise you.
There's one thing
I have always wanted to ask you.
When he was supposed to graduate
and the teacher flunked him...
Ruined his life.
All he had to do was go
to summer school, make up that subject.
- That's right. That's right!
- Did you tell him not to go?
Me? I begged him to go.
I ordered him to go.
- Why wouldn't he go?
- Why? Why, Bernard!
That questiors been trailing me
like a ghost for 15 years.
He flunked the subject and he laid down
and died like a hammer hit him.
Let me talk to you, Bernard.
I got nobody to talk to.
It wasn't my fault. It keeps going
around in my head, maybe I did something.
I got nothing to give him.
Don't take it so hard.
Why did he lay down?
- What is the story there?
- Willy...
You're his friend. Come on.
Willy, I remember it was June.
Our grades came out. He'd flunked math.
That son of a bitch ruined his life.
Then Biff just got very angry and
he was ready to enrol in summer school.
- He was?
- He wasn't beaten by it at all.
But then, Willy, see...
What?
He disappeared from the block
for almost a month.
I got the idea that he'd gone
up to New England to see you.
Did he ever talk with you then?
- Willy?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
He came to Boston.
What about it?
Well, it's just
that when he came back...
I'll never forget this.
It always mystifies me
because I thought so well of Biff.
I loved him, Willy, you know.
He came back after that month
and took his sneakers.
Remember those sneakers with the
University of Virginia on them?
He was so proud of them.
Wore them every day.
He took them down into the cellar,
burned them up in the furnace.
We had a fistfight.
It lasted at least half an hour,
just the two of us,
punching each other down in the cellar,
crying right through it.
I often thought how strange it was
that I knew he'd given up his life.
What happened in Boston, Willy?
I just bring it up because you asked me.
What's that got to do with it?
- Don't get sore.
- What are you trying to do, blame me?
If a boy lays down is that my fault?
- Don't take it...
- Don't you talk to me that way.
What does that mean,
huh, what happened?
Hey!
- You're gonna miss that train.
- Yeah, I'm going.
Good-bye, Willy.
- Don't worry about it. If at first you
don't succeed... - Yes, I believe in that.
Sometimes, Willy, it's better for a man
just to walk away.
- Walk away?
- That's right.
What if you can't walk away?
I guess that's when it's tough.
Good-bye, Willy.
Good-bye, boy.
How do you like this kid?
Gonna argue a case in the Supreme Court.
- Pop!
- No.
- The Supreme Court?
- I gotta run.
- Bye, Dad.
- Knock 'em dead, Bernard.
The Supreme Court.
And he didn't even mention it?
He don't have to.
He's gonna do it.
And you never told him what to do.
You never took any interest in him.
My salvation is that I never
took any interest in anything.
Here's some money, 50 dollars.
I got an accountant inside.
Uh, Charley, look, uh...
I got my insurance to pay.
If you could manage it, I...
I need 110 dollars.
- I'd draw from my bank, but...
- Sit down, Willy.
I'm keeping an account of everything.
- Listen to me.
- I'll pay every penny back.
- I want you to know I appreciate...
- What's going on inside your head?
- Why? I'm simply...
- I offered you a job.
You can make 50 dollars a week
and I won't send you on the road.
- I got a job.
- Without pay?
What kind of a job is a job without pay?
Now, look, kid. Enough is enough.
I'm no genius, but I know
when I'm being insulted.
- Insulted?
- Why don't you want to work for me?
What does it matter with you?
I got a job.
What do you walk in here every week for?
Well, if... if you don't
want me to walk in here...
- I am offering you a job.
- I don't want your job.
When the hell are you gonna grow up?
You big ignoramus! If you say
that to me again I'll rap you one.
I don't care how big...
...how big you are.
- How much do you need, Willy?
- Ah, Charley, I'm strapped.
I'm strapped. I don't know
what to do. I was just fired.
- Howard fired you?
- That's not no...
Imagine that. I named him Howard.
I named him! I named him Howard!
Willy, when are you gonna realise
that them things don't mean anything?
You named him Howard
but you can't sell that.
The only thing you got in this
world is what you can sell.
The funny thing is, you're a salesman
and you don't know that.
I always try to think otherwise,
I guess. I always felt...
...if a man was impressive
and well-liked then nothing...
Why must everybody like you?
Who liked JP Morgan?
Was he impressive? In a Turkish bath
he looked like a butcher.
With his pockets on
he was very well-liked.
Now, listen, Willy,
I know you don't like me.
And nobody can say I'm in love with you.
But I'll give you a job
just for the hell of it.
- What do you say?
- No. No, I just...
No, I just can't work for you, Charley.
- What are you, jealous of me?
- No!
I can't work for you, that's all.
Don't ask me why.
You've been jealous of me
all your life, you damn fool.
Here.
- Pay your insurance.
- I'm keeping strict accounts.
I got some work to do. Take care
of yourself. And pay your insurance!
It's funny, after all the highways
and the trains and the appointments
and the years...
...you end up worth
more dead than alive.
Willy, nobody's worth nothing dead.
You hear what I said?
Willy!
Oh, apologise to Bernard for me
when you see him.
I didn't mean to argue with him.
He's a fine boy.
They're all fine boys. And they'll
end up big, all of them someday.
They'll all play tennis together.
Wish me luck, Charley.
He saw Bill Oliver today.
Good luck.
Oh, Charley,
you're the only friend I got.
Isn't that a remarkable thing?
Jesus.
In the front
you're in the middle of noise.
Whenever you've got a party, Mr. Loman,
tell me, I'll put you back here.
You look French.
How's it coming, Stanley?
It's a dog's life. I only wish that
during the war they took me in the Army.
- I could have been dead.
- You got lobsters?
- A hundred percent big. - With the claws.
- Don't worry, I don't give you no mice.
How about some wine?
Put a hat on the meal.
No, the recipe I brought you from
overseas with the champagne in it
I still got that in the kitchen,
but it'll cost you a buck a piece.
- That's all right.
- You hit a number?
My brother, I think
he pulled off a deal today.
- I think we're going into business.
- That's the best, family business.
- That's the best.
- That's what I think.
What's the difference?
Somebody steals, it's in the family.
Shh. Strudel.
- Ma'am?
- I'm expecting someone.
Oh, look at that mouth. Oh, God,
and the binoculars. Wait on her.
- Would you like a menu?
- I'd like a...
Why don't you bring her...
Do you mind?
I sell champagne and I'd like her
to try my brand. Bring her a champagne.
- That's awfully nice of you.
- It's all company money.
That's a charming product
to be selling, isn't it?
Like everything else,
selling is selling.
- I suppose? - You don't happen
to sell? - No, I don't sell.
Would you object to a compliment?
You ought to be on a magazine cover.
- I have been. -W hat did I say before?
See, Stanley, she's a cover girl.
- Oh, I could see, I could see.
- What magazine?
A lot of them.
Thank you.
You know what they say in France?
Champagne is the drink
of the complexion.
- Hiya, Biffo.
- Sorry I'm late.
- No. No, no, I just got here.
Miss, um...? - Forsythe.
Miss Forsythe, this is my brother.
Is Dad here?
You might have heard of him.
He's a great football player.
- Really? What team?
- You're familiar with football?
- I'm afraid I'm not.
- Biff's with the New York Giants.
- Well, it is nice, isn't it?
- Good health.
- Happy to meet you.
- That's my name.
It's Harold, but at West Point
they called me Happy.
I see. How do you do?
- Isn't Dad coming?
- You want her?
- What? - You want her?
- I could never make that.
I remember the time that idea
would never come into your head.
- I just saw... - Wait, please. I've
got to see the old confidence.
If you want her she's on call.
I'm telling you, watch this.
Honey, are you busy?
Well, I am
but I could make a phone call.
Go and do that, will you, honey,
and see if you can get a friend.
We'll be here for awhile. Biff,
one of the greatest football players.
- I'm certainly happy to meet you.
- Come back soon.
- I'll try.
- Don't try, honey. Try hard.
Isn't that a shame?
Beautiful girl like that.
- That's why I can't get married.
- Hap, look...
- I told you she's on call.
- Cut it out.
I want to say something.
- Did you see Oliver?
- I saw him, all right.
I want to tell Dad a couple of things.
I want you to help.
- Is he gonna back you?
- Are you crazy?
You're out of your head,
do you know that?
Why, what happened?
I did a terrible thing today, Hap.
It's been the strangest day
I ever went through.
- I'm a little numb.
- What, he wouldn't see you?
I waited six hours for him, see.
All day I kept sending my name in.
Even tried to date his secretary
so she got me through. Not so.
You're not showing the confidence.
But he remembered you?
Finally at 5:00 he comes out,
didn't remember who I was or anything.
Biff, did you tell him my Florida idea?
Hap, he walked away.
I saw him and for one minute I got
so mad I could have torn the walls down.
How the hell did I ever get the idea
that I was a salesman there?
I believed myself
that I'd been a salesman for him.
Then he gave me one look and I realised
what a ridiculous lie my life's been.
We have been talking in a dream
for 15 years.
- I was a shipping clerk.
- What did you do?
Well, he... he left, see.
His secretary went out
and I was alone in the waiting room.
And next thing I know,
I was in his office.
Panel walls and everything.
I can't explain it, Hap.
I took his fountain pen.
Geez. Did he catch you?
I ran out. I ran down all 11 flights.
I ran and ran and ran.
Boy, that was dumb, Biff.
Why did you do that?
I don't know.
I just wanted to take something.
You gotta help me, Hap.
I want to tell Pop.
Are you crazy? What for?
He's gotta understand I'm not the man
somebody lends that kind of money to.
He thinks I've been spiting him
all these years.
Tell him something nice.
Say you got a date with Oliver tomorrow.
- What do I do tomorrow?
- Dad is never so happy
as when he's
looking forward to something.
Gee, I haven't been here in years!
- Sit down. You want a drink?
- Sure, I don't mind.
- You look worried.
- No.
Uh, Scotch all around.
Make it doubles.
You had a couple already, didn't you?
Did everything go all right?
- I had an experience today, Pop.
- That so? What happened?
I wanted to tell you everything
from first to last.
It's been a strange day.
I had to wait quite a while.
- Oliver?
- Yeah, Oliver.
All day, as a matter of cold fact.
And a lot of instances, Pop,
facts about my life came back to me.
Who was it, Pop, whoever said
I was a salesman with Oliver?
- Well, you were.
- No, I was a shipping clerk, Dad.
I don't know who said it first
but I was never a salesman for Oliver.
- What are you talking about?
- Hold onto the facts.
I was a shipping clerk.
- Listen to me...
- Dad, let me finish.
I'm not interested in stories
about the past.
The woods are burning, boys.
There's a big blaze going on all around.
I was fired today.
How could you be?
And I'm looking for a little good news
to tell your mother
- because the woman has suffered.
- Dad!
I haven't got a story left in my head
so don't give me a lecture about facts.
I am not interested.
Now, what have you got to say to me?
Did you see Oliver, huh?
- Geez, Dad.
- You didn't go up there?
- Sure, he went up there.
- I saw him. How could they fire you?
- What kind of welcome did he give you?
- He won't let you work on commission?
- I'm out! He gave you a warm welcome?
- Sure, Pop.
I was wondering if he'd remember you.
A man doesn't see him in ten years,
he gives him a welcome.
You know why he remembered?
- You impressed him in those days.
- Dad, can we talk and get this down?
What happened? Did he take you in
his office or talk in the waiting room?
- He came in...
- I bet he threw his arms around you.
- He's a fine man, a hard man to see.
- Oh, I know that.
- Is that where you had the drinks?
- Yeah.
- He told him my Florida idea.
- Don't interrupt.
- How'd he react to the Florida idea?
- Give me a minute to explain.
I've been waiting for you to explain
since I sat down here. What happened?
- I talked, he listened to me.
- Oh, the way he listens.
- What was his answer?
- An... Answer...
You're not letting me tell you
what I want to tell you.
- You didn't see him.
- I did.
- You insult him or something?
- Dad! Will you let me out of it?
- Will you just let me out of it?
- What happened?
- I can't talk to him.
- Tell him.
- Shut up and leave me alone.
- No, no. You had to go and flunk math.
- Dad, what are you talking about?
- Math, math, math.
- Take it easy, Pop.
- If you hadrt of flunked you'd be set.
I'm gonna tell you what happened
and you're gonna listen to me.
I waited six hours and I kept sending
my name in but he wouldn't see me.
- Finally he came.
- Biff flunked mathl
- They won't graduate him.
- Where is he?
He ran off.
He went to Grand Central.
Is Uncle Willy in Boston?
See, so I'm washed up with Oliver,
Pop, do you understand that?
- Are you listening?
- If you hadrt have flunked...
- Dad, what are you talking about?
- I didn't flunk math. What pen?
- That was dumb, Biff.
- You took Oliver's pen.
- I just explained it.
- You stole Bill Oliver's fountain pen.
I didn't exactly steal it.
I was trying to tell you.
He had it in his hand,
Oliver walked in, he got nervous.
- My god, Biff.
- I never intended to do it...
- I'm not in my room. I'm not there.
- Ringing Mr Loman.
- Now, stop it.
- Mr Loman does not answer.
- I'm not there.
- Shall I page him?
- You're no good, no good for anything.
- I am, Dad.
I'll find something.
Don't worry about anything.
- Talk to me.
- Paging Mr Loman.
- No! No!
- He'll strike something, Pop, please.
- No!
- Dad, I'm telling you something good.
Oliver talked to his partner
about the Florida idea.
- You listening, Dad? Dad?
- Yeah.
He talked to his partner and he came
to me and I'm gonna be all right, Pop.
He said it's just a question
of the amount.
- Then you... Then you got it?
- It's gonna be terrific, Pop.
Aw, then you got it, haven't you?
- You got it, haven't you? You got it!
- No.
I'm supposed to have lunch
with him tomorrow.
I'm telling you so you'll know
I can make an impression.
I'll make good somewheres,
but I can't go tomorrow.
- Why not? You simply...
- The pen, Pop.
You give him the pen,
tell him it was an oversight.
- You have lunch.
- I can't.
You were doing a crossword puzzle,
you used his pen.
No, listen, kid,
I took those balls years ago, Pop,
and now I walk in with this fountain pen
that clinches it.
Don't you understand? I can't face him.
I'll try elsewhere.
- Don't you want to be anything?
- How can I go back?
Pop!
You don't want to be anything,
that what's behind it?
Don't take it that way! You think
it was easy walking into that office?
A team of horses couldn't
have dragged me to Oliver.
- Then why did you go?
- Why did I go?
Why did I go? Dad, look at you.
Look at what's become of you.
- You're gonna go to that lunch.
- I can't. I've got no appointment.
- Are you spiting me?
- Don't take it that way!
You rotten little louse.
Are you spiting me?
Dad. I'm no good.
Can't you see what I am?
You're in a restaurant.
Cut it out, both of you!
- Someone's at the door.
- Hello, girls. Sit down.
Yes, we might as well.
This is Letta.
- What do you drink?
- Letta might not be able to stay.
I gotta get up very early
tomorrow. I've got jury duty.
I'm so excited.
Were you fellas ever on a jury?
No, I've been in front of a jury.
- This is my father.
- Isn't he cute. Sit down with us, Pops.
- Biff, sit him down.
- Come on, sit down.
- Drink us under the table.
- Willy, are you coming?
Willy, I'm waiting.
- Where are you going?
- To open the door.
- What door?
- The washroom. Where is the door?
Just go straight down.
Will you stop laughing. Stop. Shh.
Will you stop!
Shh!
I think it's sweet you bring your daddy.
Oh, he isn't really your father.
Miss Forsythe, you've just seen
a prince walk by.
A fine troubled prince. A
hard-working, unappreciated prince.
A pal, do you understand,
a good companion.
Always for his boys.
- That's so sweet.
- Girls, we're wasting time here.
What's the programme?
Biff, gather round now.
Where would you like to go?
- You do something for me?
- Me?
- Don't you give a damn for him?
- What are you talking about?
- I'm the one...
- You don't give a damn about him.
Look what I found in the cellar, Hap.
- How can you bear to let that go on?
- Me? Who goes off? Who runs away?
He doesn't mean anything to you.
You could help him, I can't.
Don't you understand what he's gonna do?
He's gonna kill himself.
- Don't you know that?
- Don't yell at me.
Hap, help him.
Help him!
Help me.
Help me!
I can't bear to look in his face.
Biff...
- Biff, where you going?
- What's he so mad about?
We're gonna catch up with him.
- I don't like that temper of his.
- He's overstrung.
- Do you want to tell your father?
- That's not my father, just a guy.
Come on, we're gonna catch up with Biff
and honey, we'll paint this town.
I love those bedroom eyes.
- That's how I knew you were friends.
- Mr Loman! Mr Loman! Mr Loman!
Hey! Mr Loman!
- Willyl
- What?
Oh.
No.
Willy, aren't you gonna answer the door?
Willy...
Willyl
- Arert you gonna answer the door?
- Sure.
Oh.
Someone's at the door, Willy.
Are you gonna answer the door?
He's gonna wake up the whole hotell
I'm not expecting anybody.
Why don't you have another drink, honey?
- Stop being so damn self-centred.
- I'm so Ionely.
You know you ruined me, Willy. From
now on, when you come to the office,
I'll see you
go right through the buyers.
No waiting at my desk anymore.
Willy, you ruined me.
Oh, that's nice of you to say that.
Oh, gee, you're self-centred.
Why so sad?
You're the saddest, self-centredest soul
I ever did see-saw.
Oh, boy, huh? What?
Boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Oh, to be dressing
in the middle of the night.
Arert you gonna answer the door?
They're knocking on the wrong door.
But they're knocking
and hear us talking.
- Maybe the hotel's on fire.
- It's a mistake.
- Tell them to go away.
- There's nobody there.
Willy!
There's somebody standing out there
and it's getting on my nerves.
All right. Stay in the bathroom
and don't come out.
There's a law in Massachusetts,
so don't come out.
It may be the new room clerk.
He looked mean. It's a mistake.
There's no fire.
- Dad. Why didn't you answer?
- Biff.
- What are you doing in Boston?
- Why didn't you answer?
I was knocking for five minutes.
I called you.
I just heard you. I was in the bathroom
and had the door shut.
Did anything happen at home, huh?
- Dad, I let you down.
- Excuse me?
Biffo, what's this about?
Come on, let's go get you a malt.
Dad, I...
- I flunked math. - Not for the term? -
I haven't got enough credits to graduate.
- Bernard wouldn't give you the answers?
- He did. He tried. I only got a 61.
They wouldn't give you four points?
Birnbaum refused absolutely.
I begged him to give me those points
but he won't listen.
You gotta talk to him.
Dad, before they close the school.
'Cause if he saw the kind of man you are
and you talked to him in your way,
I'm sure he'd come through for me, Pop.
The class came right before practice,
so I didn't go enough.
Would you talk to him?
He'd like you, the way you can talk.
- I'm gonna drive right back.
- Dad, good work.
- I'm sure he'll change it.
- Tell the clerk I'm checking out.
Go right down.
The reason he hates me
is one day he was late for class,
so I got up at the blackboard
and imitated him.
- Crossed my eyes, talked with a lisp.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- The kids like it?
- They nearly died laughing.
- Yeah, what did you do?
The square root of 63 is...
In the middle of it he walks in.
He walked in! All right.
- Is somebody in there?
- That was next door.
- Somebody got in your bathroom.
- In the next room there's a party.
Can I come in?
There's something in the bathtub, Willy,
and it's moving.
Uh, you better go back to your room now.
They must be finished painting by now.
See, they're painting her room,
so I let her shower here.
- Go back.
- I gotta get dressed, Willy.
You get out of here.
This is Miss Francis. She's a buyer.
She lives down the hall
and they're painting her...
- Go back, go back!
- My clothes, Willy!
- I can't go naked.
- Will you get out of here.
Where's my stockings?
You promised me stockings.
- I have no stockings.
- You had 2 boxes of sheers. I want 'em.
Yeah, here, here, here.
Here.
For God's sake, now get out of here.
I just hope there's nobody in the hall,
that's all I hope.
You, uh, football or baseball?
Football.
That's me, too.
Good night.
Well, better get going.
I want to get to the school
first thing in the morning.
So, get my suits out of the closet
and I'll get my valise.
What's the matter?
She's a buyer, Biff.
She buys for...
She lives down the hall.
She buys for J.H. Simmons
and you know, they're painting...
Oh, now, you don't imagine that I...
Now, look, pal, she's just a buyer!
She sees merchandise in her room and
they have to keep it looking just so.
- Come on, now, get my suits.
- No.
You stop crying and do as I say.
I gave you an order, Biff.
Biff, I gave you an order.
Is that what you do
when I give you an order?
Is it?
Then how dare you cry!
Oh, now.
Look, Biff, when you grow up
you'll understand about these things.
No, you mustrt overemphasise
a thing like this.
Come on, III see Birnbaum
first thing in the morning.
- Never mind.
- Never mind?
He's gonna give you those points.
I'll see to it.
- He won't listen to you.
- He certainly will!
You need those for the U of Virginia.
- I'm not going there.
- What? - I'm not going there.
If I can't get him to change that mark
you'll make it up in summer school.
- You got all summer to...
- Dad.
My... my boy.
She's nothing to me, Biff.
I was Ionely. I was terribly Ionely.
Dad, you gave her Mama's stockings.
I gave you an order!
- I gave...
- Don't touch me, you liar!
- You apologise for that.
- You fake!
I gave you an order!
- Now, you come back here.
- You phoney little fake.
- Come back here!
- You fake!
I gave you an order!
Come back or I'll beat you. I'II...
- Hey.
- I'll whip you.
I gave you...
Pick it up, Mr Loman.
Your boys just left with the chippies.
They said they'd see you home.
We were supposed
to have dinner together.
- Can you make it?
- Oh, yeah. Sure, I'll make it.
- Mr Loman.
- OK.
I'll make it.
- I look all right.
- Sure, you look all right.
Uh... Uh...
Here. Here. Here's a dollar.
- Your son paid. It's all right.
- You're a good boy.
- You don't have to.
- Here's more. I don't need it anymore.
Tell me, is there a seed store
in the neighbourhood?
Seeds?
- You mean, like to plant?
- Yes, like carrots, peas.
There's a hardware store
on Sixth Avenue.
- It may be too late now.
- I better hurry.
I gotta get some seeds.
Gotta get some seeds right away.
Well, what are you looking at?
Nothing is planted right.
I don't have a thing
in the ground right now.
"Carrots.
Quarter inch apart,
one foot rows..."
One foot.
Beets.
Lettuce.
One foot.
Oh, what a proposition.
Terrific, terrific,
'cause she's suffered, man.
The woman has suffered.
A man can't go out the way he came in.
A man has got to add up to something.
You can't...
You can't. You gotta consider now.
Don't answer so quick.
Remember, it's a guaranteed
$20,000 proposition, huh?
Now, look, Ben, I want you to go through
the ins and outs of this thing with me.
I got nobody to talk to. And the
woman has suffered, you hear me?
- What's the proposition? - It's $20,000
on the barrel head, guaranteed.
Gilt edge, you understand?
You don't want
to make a fool of yourself.
- They might not honour the policy.
- How can they refuse? I worked.
I met every premium on the nose
and now they don't pay off? Impossible.
It's called a cowardly thing.
Why does it take more guts to stand here
the rest of my life ringing up a zero?
That's a point, William.
And 20,000. That is something
one can feel with their hands.
That's the whole beauty of it, Ben.
I see it like a diamond
shining in the dark
that I can pick up and touch in my hand.
Not like an appointment.
This would not be another appointment
and it changes all the aspects.
Because he thinks I'm nothing,
so he spites me.
But the funeral.
Oh, Ben, that funeral will be massive!
Oh, they'll come
from Maine, Massachusetts,
Vermont, New Hampshire.
All the old-timers
with the strange licence plates.
That boy will be thunderstruck, Ben,
because he never realised I am known.
Rhode Island, New York, New Jersey,
I am known, Ben!
He'll see it with his eyes!
Once and for all,
he'll see what I am, oh!
He's in for a shock, that boy.
He'll call you a coward, William.
Oh, no, no, that would be terrible.
- Yes, and a damn fool.
- No, no!
He'll hate you, William.
He mustn't. Oh, I won't have that.
Mom, what are you doing up?
Where's Pop? Is he sleeping?
- Where were you?
- We met two girls, very fine types.
We brought you some flowers.
Put 'em in your room.
What did you do that for?
I want you to have flowers.
Don't you care whether he lives or dies?
- Biff, let's go up.
- Go away from me.
What do you mean, lives or dies?
Nobody's dying around here, pal.
Get out of here!
Get out of my sight!
I want to talk to the boss, Mom.
- You're not going near him.
- Where is he?
You invite him for dinner,
he looks forward to it all day.
- And then you desert him there?
- Dad?
There's no stranger you'd do that to.
He had a swell time with us.
When I desert him I hope I do it...
- Get out of here!
- Ma!
- Mom?
- Did you have to go to women tonight?
You and your rotten, lousy whores!
Mom, all we did was follow Biff around
trying to cheer him up.
- Boy, what a night you gave me.
- Get out of here.
Both of you, and don't come back.
I don't want you tormenting him anymore.
- Dad, are you down there?
- You can sleep in his apartment.
And pick up this stuff!
I'm not your maid anymore.
Go on, pick it up, you bum, you!
You're a pair of animals.
There's not one, not a living soul,
who would have the cruelty
to walk out on that man
in a restaurant.
- Is that what he said?
- He didn't have to say anything.
He was so humiliated,
he nearly limped when he came in.
- Look, Mom, he had a great time.
- Shut up!
You! Didn't even go to
see if he was all right.
No, Mom, I didn't. I didn't do
a damn thing. How do you like that?
I left him babbling in a toilet.
- You louse, you.
- You hit it on the nose.
The scum of the earth.
You're looking at him.
- Get out of here.
- I want to talk to the boss, Mom.
You're not going near him. Get out.
We're gonna have
an abrupt conversation, him and me.
You're not talking to him.
Please, leave him alone.
What is he doing out there?
He's planting the garden.
Now?
Oh, my god.
Never even let me carry
the valises in the house.
And simonising, simonising...
...that little red car.
Why?
Why can't I give him something
and not have him hate me, huh?
Let me think about it.
I still have a little time.
A remarkable proposition.
Oh.
You gotta be sure
you're not making a fool of yourself.
Dad?
Where is that seed?
You can't see nothing here, boxed in.
Dad, there are people all around.
- Don't you realise?
- Don't bother me.
- I'm saying good-bye to you, Pop.
- Huh?
I'm not coming back anymore.
- You're not gonna see Oliver?
- Dad, I've got no appointment.
- He put his arm around you.
- Dad, get this now.
Every time I've left
it's been a fight that's sent me out.
Today I realise something about
myself. I tried to explain it to you.
I think I'm just not smart enough
to make sense out of it for you.
To hell with whose fault it is
or anything like that.
Let's just wrap it up.
- Come in and we'll tell Mom.
- I don't want to see her.
- Come on.
Don't bother me, will ya?
Dad, what do you mean?
You don't want to see her?
Pop, you don't want them
calling you yellow, do you?
Dad, it's not your fault.
It's me. I'm a bum.
Now, come on inside.
Dad, did you hear what I said to you?
Did you plant, dear?
All right, Mom.
We had it out.
I'm going and I'm not writing anymore.
I think it's best, Willy.
There's no use drawing it out.
You two will never get along.
If people ask where I am,
what I'm doing, you don't know or care.
That way it'll be off your mind
and you can start brightening up again.
All right?
That... That clears it, then, huh?
- You gonna wish me luck, scout?
- Shake his hand, Willy.
What do you say?
There's no necessity to mention...
He put his arm...!
Dad, you're never gonna see what I am,
so what's the use of arguing?
If I strike oil I'll send you a cheque.
Meantime, forget I'm alive.
Spite, see?
- Shake hands, Dad.
- Not my hand.
Dad?
- I was hoping not to go this way.
- This is the way you're going. Bye.
May you rot in hell
if you leave this house!
Exactly what is it
that you want from me?
I want you to know on the train,
in the mountains, in the valleys,
wherever you go,
that you cut down your life for spite!
- No, no!
- Spite!
When you are rotting somewhere
beside a railroad track, remember.
- Don't you blame it on me.
- I'm not blaming you.
I'm not taking the rap for this, hear?
- That's what I'm telling you.
- You're putting a knife in me.
Don't think I don't know
what you're doing.
All right, phoney.
Leave it there. Don't move it.
- What is that?
- You know damn well.
- I never saw that.
- You saw it, all right.
Mice didn't bring it into the cellar.
Is that supposed to make you a hero?
That supposed to make me sorry for you?
There will be no pity for you.
- Hear that? No pity.
- Hear the spite?
You're gonna get the truth,
what you are, what I am.
- Spite!
- Cut it out!
The man don't know who we are.
The man is gonna know.
We never told the truth
for ten minutes in this house.
- We always told truth.
- Are you the assistant buyer?
You're one of
the two assistants to the assistant.
- I'm practically...
- You are practically full of it.
- We all are. I'm through with it.
- Yeah.
- Hear this, Willy. This is me.
- I know you.
Do you know why I had no
address for three months?
I stole a suit in Kansas City
and I was in gaol.
- I suppose it's my fault.
- Stop crying, I'm through with it!
I stole myself
out of every good job since high school.
Whose fault is that?
I could never get anywhere
'cause you blew me so full of hot air
that I could never stand
taking orders from anybody.
- I hear that.
- Stop it!
I had to be boss big shot
in two weeks and I'm through.
- Then hang yourself for spite!
- No! No!
No, nobody is hanging himself, Willy.
I ran down 11 flights with a pen
in my hand today.
And suddenly I stopped.
Do you hear me?
In the middle of that office building...
Do you hear this?
I stopped...
...in the middle of the building
and I saw the sky!
And I... I... I saw the things
that I love in this world.
The work and the food
and the time to sit and smoke.
I looked at that pen in my hand and
I said, "What am I grabbing this for?
Why am I trying to become
what I don't want to be?
What am I doing in an office?
Making a contemptuous begging
fool of myself,
when all that I want
is out there waiting for me?"
The minute I say it, I know who I am.
Why can't I say that, Willy?
The door to your life is wide open!
Pop, I am a dime a dozen and so are you.
I am not a dime a dozen!
I am Willy Loman and you are Biff Loman!
I am not the leader of men, Willy!
And neither are you!
You were never anything
but a hard-working drummer
who landed in the ashcan
like all the rest of them.
I am one dollar an hour, Willy!
I am not bringing home
any prizes anymore,
and you're gonna stop waiting for me!
- You vengeful, spiteful mutt!
- Yeah, Pop!
Pop, I'm nothing.
I'm nothing, Pop.
Can't you understand that?
There's no spite in it anymore.
I'm just what I am, that's all.
What are you doing?
Aw, what are you doing?
- Why is he crying?
- Dad...
Will you let me go, for God's sake?
Will you take that phoney dream
and burn it before something happens?
I'll go in the morning.
Put him to bed.
Isn't that...
Isn't that remarkable?
Biff, he...
He likes me.
- He loves you, Willy.
- Always did, Pop.
Aw, Biff, he...
He cried. He cried to me.
Aw, that boy.
That boy, he's going to be magnificent.
Yes, outstanding,
with 20,000 behind him.
Come to bed, Willy.
It's all settled now.
Oh, yes, we'll sleep.
Come on, let's go to sleep.
It takes a great man
to crack thejungle.
I'm getting married.
Don't forget. I'm changing everything.
I'm gonna run that department
before the year is up.
Thejungle is dark
but full of diamonds.
Be good. You're both good boys.
Just act that way, that's all.
- Night, Pop.
- Night, boy.
- Come, dear. -S hh. One must
go in to fetch a diamond out.
I just want to get settled down
for a little while.
- I want you upstairs.
- A few minutes. I couldn't sleep now.
- Go. You look awful tired.
- Not like an appointment.
- A diamond is rough and hard to touch.
- I'll be right up.
- I think it's the only way.
- Sure, it's the best thing.
Best thing. The only way.
Everything is gonna be...
Aw, go on, kid. Get to bed.
- You look so tired. - Now, you
come right up. - Two minutes.
Loves me. Always loved me.
Isn't that a remarkable thing?
- Ben, he'll worship me for it.
- It's dark there.
But full of diamonds, Willy.
Can you imagine that magnificence
with $20,000 in his pocket?
Willy, come up.
Yes, yes, coming, coming!
It's very smart,
you realise, don't you, sweetheart?
Even Ben sees it.
I gotta go, baby.
Bye-bye.
When the mail comes
he'll be ahead of Bernard again.
- A perfect proposition all around.
- Did you see how he cried to me?
- Aw, I could kiss him, Ben.
- Time, William, time.
Ben, I always knew one way or another
we were gonna make it, Biff and I.
Boat! We'll be late.
Now, when you kick off,
I want a 70 yard boot.
And get right down the field
under the ball.
And when you hit,
hit low and hit hard,
because it's important, boy.
There's all kinds of
important people in the stands.
The first thing that you know...
Willy?
- Ben? Ben, where do I...?
- Willy?
- Ben! Ben!
- Willy!
Shh. Shh.
Shh! Shh!
- Willy, please come up.
- Oh.
- Willy!
- Shh!
Willy?
- Pop?
- Willy, answer me!
Willy!
- Willy!
- Pop! No!
- No!
It's getting dark, Linda.
How about it, Ma? Better get
some rest. They'll be closing the gates.
He had no right to do that.
There was no necessity.
- We would have helped him.
- Come on.
- Why didn't anybody come?
- It was a very nice funeral.
Where were the people he knew?
Maybe they blame him.
It's a rough world, Linda.
They wouldn't blame him.
I can't understand it.
First time in just about 35 years
we were almost free and clear.
He only needed a little salary.
He was even finished with the dentist.
No man only needs a little salary.
I can't understand it.
There were a lot of nice days when he'd
come home from a trip or on Sundays,
making the stoop,
finishing the cellar
when he built the extra bathroom
and put up the garage.
You know, Charley, I think there was
more of him in that front stoop
than in all the sales he ever made.
Yep. He was a happy man
with a bunch of cement.
He was wonderful with his hands.
He had the wrong dreams.
AII, all wrong.
Don't say that.
The man didn't know who he was.
Nobody dast blame this man.
You don't understand.
Willy was a salesman.
For a salesman,
there is no rock bottom to the life.
He don't put a bolt to a nut,
he don't tell you the law,
don't give you medicine.
He's a man way out there in the blue,
riding on a smile and a shoeshine.
When they start not smiling back,
that's an earthquake.
You get yourself a couple of spots
on your hat and you're finished.
Nobody dast blame this man.
A salesman has got to dream, boy.
Comes with the territory.
- The man didn't know who he was.
- Don't say that!
Why don't you come with me, Happy?
I'm not licked that easily.
I'm staying right in the city
and I'm gonna beat this racquet.
- Loman brothers.
- I know who I am, kid.
All right, boy,
I'm gonna show you and everybody
that Willy Loman did not die in vain.
He had a good dream.
It's the only dream you can have,
to come out number one man.
He fought it out here and this is where
I'm gonna win it for him.
Oh, I'll be with you in just a minute.
You go on, Charley.
Just... just a minute.
I never had a chance to say good-bye.
Help me, Willy.
I can't cry.
Seems to me you're just away on
another trip and I keep expecting you.
Why did you do it?
I search and I search,
and I search,
and I can't understand it, Willy.
I made the last payment
on the house today.
Today!
And there'll be nobody home.
We're free and clear.
We're free.