1
00:01:00,800 --> 00:01:04,340
In The Name Of God

2
00:01:04,800 --> 00:01:08,000
In memory of Yadollah Najafi

3
00:02:46,420 --> 00:02:51,700
Mr Etesami! Rana! Come outside!

4
00:02:52,000 --> 00:02:54,580
The building is collapsing!

5
00:03:06,000 --> 00:03:08,060
What's going on? What's happened?

6
00:03:08,060 --> 00:03:09,420
What's the matter?

7
00:03:11,060 --> 00:03:12,460
What's happened?

8
00:03:13,660 --> 00:03:17,260
Get out now, the building's collapsing!

9
00:03:18,780 --> 00:03:20,940
Rana! Rana!

10
00:03:20,940 --> 00:03:22,000
What's going on Emad?

11
00:03:22,000 --> 00:03:22,500
Rana hurry! Come quickly!
What's going on Emad?

12
00:03:22,500 --> 00:03:23,300
Rana hurry! Come quickly!

13
00:03:29,000 --> 00:03:30,340
Mr Falaad, what happened?

14
00:03:30,340 --> 00:03:32,340
I don't know, just get out quickly

15
00:03:33,380 --> 00:03:34,300
Rana...

16
00:03:37,700 --> 00:03:38,400
Come on! Come on!

17
00:03:38,400 --> 00:03:39,620
What..?
Come on! Come on!

18
00:03:39,620 --> 00:03:39,820
Come on! Come on!

19
00:03:41,820 --> 00:03:43,140
Are you coming?

20
00:03:48,900 --> 00:03:52,500
Mr Emad! For the love of God, someone come and help me with this kid.

21
00:03:52,500 --> 00:03:53,500
I'll come, one second
Mr Emad! For the love of God, someone come and help me with this kid.

22
00:03:53,500 --> 00:03:54,260
I'll come, one second

23
00:03:54,260 --> 00:03:56,800
Aren't you coming? I'll come with you too

24
00:03:57,220 --> 00:03:59,020
No no, you go and wait outside

25
00:03:59,100 --> 00:04:00,980
Tell everyone to wait outside

26
00:04:01,860 --> 00:04:02,900
Where's Hossein?

27
00:04:02,900 --> 00:04:04,900
I can't bring the kids down by myself

28
00:04:07,800 --> 00:04:08,800
Hossein?

29
00:04:09,660 --> 00:04:09,940
Hossein

30
00:04:09,940 --> 00:04:10,180
Hossein get up!
Hossein

31
00:04:10,180 --> 00:04:11,540
Hossein get up!

32
00:04:11,540 --> 00:04:13,580
Hossein get up and come!

33
00:04:13,580 --> 00:04:15,580
Come on, our house is collapsing! Get up!

34
00:04:15,580 --> 00:04:17,580
Get up Hossein

35
00:04:20,100 --> 00:04:21,460
Go and wait in the alley

36
00:04:21,460 --> 00:04:23,420
Tell everyone to wait in the alley

37
00:04:23,420 --> 00:04:25,780
Mr Falaa, get everyone down to the alley

38
00:04:25,780 --> 00:04:27,620
Come on Hossein

39
00:04:27,620 --> 00:04:29,140
What are they doing?!

40
00:04:32,260 --> 00:04:34,660
My glasses!

41
00:04:35,140 --> 00:04:37,020
I'll bring your glasses

42
00:04:56,020 --> 00:04:57,620
The Salesman

43
00:04:57,620 --> 00:05:02,340
Written and directed by Asghar Farhadi
The Salesman

44
00:05:10,700 --> 00:05:11,740
Guys!

45
00:05:12,420 --> 00:05:14,860
Don't bring too much bric-a-brac with you

46
00:05:15,300 --> 00:05:17,020
Our house has everything

47
00:05:17,180 --> 00:05:18,000
Okay

48
00:05:21,420 --> 00:05:22,580
I can't find it

49
00:05:22,780 --> 00:05:24,380
I don't know, keep looking

50
00:05:24,380 --> 00:05:24,580
Should I take it?
I don't know, keep looking

51
00:05:24,580 --> 00:05:25,260
Should I take it?

52
00:05:25,260 --> 00:05:26,300
Thanks
Should I take it?

53
00:05:26,300 --> 00:05:26,580
You were supposed to just bring a towel and toothbrush
Thanks
Should I take it?

54
00:05:26,580 --> 00:05:28,140
You were supposed to just bring a towel and toothbrush

55
00:05:28,140 --> 00:05:30,020
It has my towel and toothbrush in it

56
00:05:34,060 --> 00:05:35,260
Have you locked it?

57
00:05:35,260 --> 00:05:36,460
Yep

58
00:05:36,900 --> 00:05:38,460
Keys, keys!

59
00:05:38,860 --> 00:05:40,860
Excuse me

60
00:05:41,780 --> 00:05:43,100
Guys?

61
00:05:46,180 --> 00:05:47,140
Hey

62
00:05:47,140 --> 00:05:47,220
Hey Kati
Hey

63
00:05:47,220 --> 00:05:48,140
Hey Kati

64
00:05:48,140 --> 00:05:49,740
You're alive!

65
00:05:49,740 --> 00:05:54,420
When Sia said the house had collapsed, I thought we'd have to drag you from the rubble

66
00:05:55,220 --> 00:05:57,300
Oh jeez... what's going on here?

67
00:05:57,820 --> 00:05:59,940
It smells of gas...

68
00:06:00,900 --> 00:06:02,300
It's from last night

69
00:06:02,300 --> 00:06:04,220
Let's get out of quickly here then

70
00:06:08,860 --> 00:06:09,340
Hey

71
00:06:09,860 --> 00:06:11,340
Why have you come up?

72
00:06:11,340 --> 00:06:13,380
Cut off the electricity - this is dripping

73
00:06:23,500 --> 00:06:25,300
I still can't find the card

74
00:06:25,300 --> 00:06:28,340
Is it not under your paperwork?

75
00:06:28,700 --> 00:06:30,500
Don't go there Kati, it's dangerous

76
00:06:31,740 --> 00:06:33,900
Oh my God...

77
00:06:36,620 --> 00:06:42,860
<i>You could only hear the sobbing of Mashti Hassan's wife, sitting alone with a lantern on the stable roof</i>

78
00:06:42,860 --> 00:06:45,180
<i>and the moans of a cow that had been left behind</i>

79
00:06:45,940 --> 00:06:48,260
Sir! Is it a true story?

80
00:06:48,260 --> 00:06:57,940
True? No, but it's argued that Sa'edi's characters and relationships contain a lot of truth

81
00:06:57,940 --> 00:06:59,500
Sir, how can someone turn into a cow?

82
00:06:59,500 --> 00:07:01,380
Try looking in the mirror?

83
00:07:02,300 --> 00:07:03,580
Good one...

84
00:07:03,580 --> 00:07:06,300
Seriously though Sir, how does a person become a cow?

85
00:07:08,780 --> 00:07:10,100
Slowly...

86
00:07:10,660 --> 00:07:12,740
Sir, are we watching the film of this story?

87
00:07:12,740 --> 00:07:16,500
Good idea. I might bring it next time and we can watch it together.

88
00:07:16,500 --> 00:07:17,420
Yes?

89
00:07:17,420 --> 00:07:19,180
Sir, when can we watch your play?

90
00:07:19,180 --> 00:07:23,940
The performance begins next week. Once we've had a few days to settle in, I'll invite you all to come.

91
00:07:23,940 --> 00:07:24,660
Thank you!

92
00:07:24,660 --> 00:07:25,140
Sir, what's the name?
Thank you!

93
00:07:25,140 --> 00:07:25,780
Sir, what's the name?

94
00:07:25,780 --> 00:07:25,940
"Death of a Salesman", who's read it?
Sir, what's the name?

95
00:07:25,940 --> 00:07:27,540
"Death of a Salesman", who's read it?

96
00:07:27,540 --> 00:07:28,700
His enemy!

97
00:07:29,540 --> 00:07:32,460
Joking aside, have any of you read it?

98
00:07:32,460 --> 00:07:34,340
Sir, who's the author?

99
00:07:34,340 --> 00:07:35,220
Arthur Miller

100
00:07:35,220 --> 00:07:36,340
Hmm... nope.
Arthur Miller

101
00:07:36,340 --> 00:07:36,900
Hmm... nope.

102
00:07:37,460 --> 00:07:38,670
Very good.

103
00:07:38,670 --> 00:07:40,740
Excuse me guys

104
00:07:41,820 --> 00:07:42,940
Yes?

105
00:07:43,620 --> 00:07:44,940
Hello.

106
00:07:45,940 --> 00:07:46,940
Yes.

107
00:07:47,180 --> 00:07:53,460
I can't speak sorry, I'm in class. If you call back in 10 minutes, I'll be free.

108
00:07:54,700 --> 00:07:58,060
Yes, a ring. Silver...

109
00:08:02,300 --> 00:08:04,460
Sir, what's your role?

110
00:08:04,460 --> 00:08:05,740
The Salesman

111
00:08:05,740 --> 00:08:07,180
What are you selling Sir?

112
00:08:07,180 --> 00:08:09,180
Potatoes!

113
00:08:09,180 --> 00:08:10,540
If you come then you can find out

114
00:08:10,540 --> 00:08:11,460
Sir, what model is it?

115
00:08:11,460 --> 00:08:12,500
What?
Sir, what model is it?

116
00:08:12,500 --> 00:08:12,540
200???
What?
Sir, what model is it?

117
00:08:12,540 --> 00:08:13,300
What?
200???

118
00:08:13,300 --> 00:08:13,540
200???

119
00:08:13,540 --> 00:08:13,900
What do you want it for?
200???

120
00:08:13,900 --> 00:08:14,660
What do you want it for?

121
00:08:14,660 --> 00:08:16,740
Aren't you a salesman Sir?

122
00:08:16,740 --> 00:08:17,540
Sir, his dad is a parking officer, if you tell him then he'll scrap your fines
Aren't you a salesman Sir?

123
00:08:17,540 --> 00:08:20,380
Sir, his dad is a parking officer, if you tell him then he'll scrap your fines

124
00:08:20,380 --> 00:08:20,500
Do you even commit driving offenses Sir?
Sir, his dad is a parking officer, if you tell him then he'll scrap your fines

125
00:08:20,500 --> 00:08:22,060
Do you even commit driving offenses Sir?

126
00:08:22,060 --> 00:08:25,460
Sir, why do Iranians call BMWs "Bee-Em-Veh"s?

127
00:08:25,980 --> 00:08:27,740
Sorry, what did you say?

128
00:08:27,740 --> 00:08:30,820
Why do Iranians call BMWs "Bee-Em-Veh"s?

129
00:08:35,260 --> 00:08:39,900
Hey! It's fine - we learn by asking questions!

130
00:08:39,900 --> 00:08:40,940
But I have no idea

131
00:08:43,260 --> 00:08:44,300
Guys...

132
00:08:44,300 --> 00:08:54,780
Write a summary of this story for next time. I don't want any excuses!

133
00:09:05,900 --> 00:09:08,300
Could you please try and spread out a bit less?

134
00:09:19,660 --> 00:09:22,820
Excuse me driver, could I swap with the man in the front seat please?

135
00:09:50,820 --> 00:09:51,820
Father...

136
00:09:52,540 --> 00:09:53,740
Is anyone here?

137
00:09:54,620 --> 00:09:58,300
No, I think the noise was from the room next door.

138
00:09:58,300 --> 00:09:58,460
No no, there's a person in your en-suite
No, I think the noise was from the room next door.

139
00:09:58,460 --> 00:10:00,660
No no, there's a person in your en-suite

140
00:10:00,660 --> 00:10:00,740
No way, there's nobody there!
No no, there's a person in your en-suite

141
00:10:00,740 --> 00:10:01,940
No way, there's nobody there!

142
00:10:01,940 --> 00:10:05,300
No, it's next door - they always have noisy guests

143
00:10:05,300 --> 00:10:06,100
Do I have permission to come out?
No, it's next door - they always have noisy guests

144
00:10:06,100 --> 00:10:07,140
Do I have permission to come out?

145
00:10:08,020 --> 00:10:10,900
Willy, something is walking in the bathroom

146
00:10:14,780 --> 00:10:21,180
Miss Francis, I think your room's been painted now and you can go back to it.

147
00:10:21,180 --> 00:10:22,820
But I can't, first I need to get dressed!

148
00:10:22,820 --> 00:10:24,140
You can, you can!
But I can't, first I need to get dressed!

149
00:10:24,140 --> 00:10:25,620
You can, you can!

150
00:10:25,620 --> 00:10:29,100
Biff this is Miss Francis, my next-door neighbor

151
00:10:29,100 --> 00:10:37,540
I said she could use my bathroom while her room was being painted.

152
00:10:37,540 --> 00:10:39,260
You can go back to your room now
I said she could use my bathroom while her room was being painted.

153
00:10:39,260 --> 00:10:41,060
But Willy, I don't have any clothes on!

154
00:10:41,060 --> 00:10:43,340
Okay, please leave quickly, please go back to your room

155
00:10:43,340 --> 00:10:44,300
You promised me stockings, Willy!
Okay, please leave quickly, please go back to your room

156
00:10:44,300 --> 00:10:45,420
You promised me stockings, Willy!

157
00:10:45,420 --> 00:10:46,180
I don't have any stockings here!
You promised me stockings, Willy!

158
00:10:46,180 --> 00:10:46,820
I don't have any stockings here!

159
00:10:46,820 --> 00:10:47,500
You had two boxes of size 9 stockings for me Willy and I want them!
I don't have any stockings here!

160
00:10:47,500 --> 00:10:51,380
You had two boxes of size 9 stockings for me Willy and I want them!

161
00:10:51,380 --> 00:10:53,980
For God's sake, will you please get out of here?

162
00:10:55,060 --> 00:10:56,580
Go on

163
00:11:09,500 --> 00:11:13,820
I just hope there’s nobody in the hall. That’s all I hope.

164
00:11:17,820 --> 00:11:23,500
By the way, do you play football or...

165
00:11:25,540 --> 00:11:26,820
Screw you!

166
00:11:27,540 --> 00:11:28,820
Siavash!

167
00:11:28,820 --> 00:11:29,820
What happened mom?

168
00:11:29,820 --> 00:11:30,620
I've kept quiet about it but he's getting worse every night!
What happened mom?

169
00:11:30,620 --> 00:11:32,020
I've kept quiet about it but he's getting worse every night!

170
00:11:32,020 --> 00:11:33,340
Come down Sadra, let's go!

171
00:11:33,340 --> 00:11:35,340
Just ignore it Sanam

172
00:11:35,340 --> 00:11:37,340
He thinks he can do whatever he wants, just because I'm playing a prostitute!

173
00:11:37,340 --> 00:11:38,660
How's that relevant?
He thinks he can do whatever he wants, just because I'm playing a prostitute!

174
00:11:38,660 --> 00:11:38,700
How's that relevant?

175
00:11:38,700 --> 00:11:40,300
Why don't you laugh at the others then?

176
00:11:40,300 --> 00:11:40,740
I was laughing at your clothes, not you
Why don't you laugh at the others then?

177
00:11:40,740 --> 00:11:40,820
I was laughing at your clothes, not you

178
00:11:40,820 --> 00:11:42,460
Shut up!
I was laughing at your clothes, not you

179
00:11:42,460 --> 00:11:42,700
Siavash come over here!
I was laughing at your clothes, not you

180
00:11:42,700 --> 00:11:43,820
Siavash come over here!

181
00:11:43,820 --> 00:11:44,460
Sanam...
Siavash come over here!

182
00:11:44,460 --> 00:11:44,780
Sanam...

183
00:11:44,780 --> 00:11:46,460
Sanam don't be childish on the final night
Sanam...

184
00:11:46,460 --> 00:11:46,780
Sanam don't be childish on the final night

185
00:11:46,780 --> 00:11:47,100
Sir, I fucked up... I fucked up
Sanam don't be childish on the final night

186
00:11:47,100 --> 00:11:49,860
Sir, I fucked up... I fucked up

187
00:11:49,860 --> 00:11:54,620
I've been rehearsing every night in this cold weather, with this child.

188
00:11:54,620 --> 00:11:56,620
We're screwed!

189
00:11:56,620 --> 00:11:58,620
Why are you telling us, it was her husband's doing

190
00:11:58,620 --> 00:12:00,620
Let me take the k...

191
00:12:00,620 --> 00:12:02,620
Get off!

192
00:12:02,620 --> 00:12:04,620
Sanam don't...

193
00:12:04,620 --> 00:12:05,980
I said get off!

194
00:12:05,980 --> 00:12:06,620
I was joking...
I said get off!

195
00:12:06,620 --> 00:12:07,860
I was joking...

196
00:12:14,260 --> 00:12:19,860
She came out of the shower with a raincoat, asking "How do I get out without clothes?"

197
00:12:21,780 --> 00:12:24,660
I couldn't not laugh

198
00:12:24,660 --> 00:12:25,020
Go after her or she'll get annoyed and won't come tomorrow
I couldn't not laugh

199
00:12:25,020 --> 00:12:26,220
Go after her or she'll get annoyed and won't come tomorrow

200
00:12:26,220 --> 00:12:27,340
Don't make me go out without clothes! I'm shy!
Go after her or she'll get annoyed and won't come tomorrow

201
00:12:27,340 --> 00:12:30,900
Don't make me go out without clothes! I'm shy!

202
00:12:30,900 --> 00:12:33,580
How can I go out without clothes...

203
00:12:33,580 --> 00:12:34,820
Sanam!

204
00:12:34,820 --> 00:12:36,380
I swear he's crazy

205
00:12:45,940 --> 00:12:47,740
Did you find a place?

206
00:12:47,740 --> 00:12:52,060
60 square metres / 3rd floor / no elevator. 40,600 tomans.

207
00:12:52,060 --> 00:12:53,340
Where?

208
00:12:53,340 --> 00:12:54,100
Amirataval

209
00:12:54,100 --> 00:12:54,540
What sort of place are you at?
Amirataval

210
00:12:54,540 --> 00:12:55,380
What sort of place are you at?

211
00:12:55,380 --> 00:12:55,500
Just a temporary place
What sort of place are you at?

212
00:12:55,500 --> 00:12:56,740
Just a temporary place

213
00:12:56,740 --> 00:12:57,620
If we don't find something soon, we'll have to come and live in the set
Just a temporary place

214
00:12:57,620 --> 00:13:00,180
If we don't find something soon, we'll have to come and live in the set

215
00:13:01,340 --> 00:13:03,340
Are you free tomorrow afternoon?

216
00:13:03,340 --> 00:13:04,540
How come?

217
00:13:04,540 --> 00:13:05,860
I'm taking you somewhere

218
00:13:05,860 --> 00:13:06,020
Come on guys - one more time from the top, without stopping
I'm taking you somewhere

219
00:13:06,020 --> 00:13:09,100
Come on guys - one more time from the top, without stopping

220
00:13:12,660 --> 00:13:13,660
Are you tired?

221
00:13:13,660 --> 00:13:15,660
Nope

222
00:13:15,660 --> 00:13:17,500
Oh, you're here too!

223
00:13:17,500 --> 00:13:21,380
Aww kitty! Who's this?

224
00:13:35,860 --> 00:13:37,460
This place has a good vibe!

225
00:14:06,180 --> 00:14:07,340
Babak

226
00:14:07,340 --> 00:14:09,780
Is that the storage room?

227
00:14:10,740 --> 00:14:11,580
Which one?

228
00:14:11,580 --> 00:14:12,300
This one
Which one?

229
00:14:12,300 --> 00:14:12,900
This one

230
00:14:12,900 --> 00:14:15,060
No! It's the second bedroom

231
00:14:15,140 --> 00:14:15,980
Really?

232
00:14:16,020 --> 00:14:17,060
Yep!

233
00:14:17,260 --> 00:14:18,260
Is it not too small?

234
00:14:18,260 --> 00:14:18,380
It's a two-bedroom!
Is it not too small?

235
00:14:18,380 --> 00:14:19,220
It's a two-bedroom!

236
00:14:19,220 --> 00:14:20,500
So it's good?

237
00:14:20,500 --> 00:14:22,580
What do two people need all this space for anyway?

238
00:14:22,580 --> 00:14:23,140
Who knows, what about if we become three people...
What do two people need all this space for anyway?

239
00:14:23,140 --> 00:14:27,340
Who knows, what about if we become three people...

240
00:14:27,340 --> 00:14:27,740
Rana, is he serious?
Who knows, what about if we become three people...

241
00:14:27,740 --> 00:14:29,700
Rana, is he serious?

242
00:14:29,700 --> 00:14:29,780
No way!
Rana, is he serious?

243
00:14:29,780 --> 00:14:31,500
No way!

244
00:14:31,500 --> 00:14:31,780
Doesn't look like it
No way!

245
00:14:31,780 --> 00:14:32,780
Doesn't look like it

246
00:14:32,780 --> 00:14:33,500
Is this door locked?
Why not?

247
00:14:33,500 --> 00:14:35,180
Is this door locked?

248
00:14:35,180 --> 00:14:38,460
The previous tenant's stuff is in there; they're supposed to be collecting it

249
00:14:38,460 --> 00:14:42,620
Don't worry kitty, it's me

250
00:14:48,580 --> 00:14:50,060
How long's it been vacant?

251
00:14:50,060 --> 00:14:51,180
Three weeks

252
00:14:58,860 --> 00:15:01,220
What are they doing to this city?

253
00:15:01,820 --> 00:15:06,140
I wish we could tear it all down and start again

254
00:15:06,140 --> 00:15:07,020
They've already destroyed and rebuilt it and look how it's turned out...
I wish we could tear it all down and start again

255
00:15:07,020 --> 00:15:10,820
They've already destroyed and rebuilt it and look how it's turned out...

256
00:15:10,820 --> 00:15:11,940
Babak?

257
00:15:11,940 --> 00:15:12,380
Yes dear

258
00:15:12,380 --> 00:15:12,740
God have mercy on us
Yes dear

259
00:15:12,740 --> 00:15:13,380
God have mercy on us

260
00:15:13,380 --> 00:15:14,060
When do you think they'll clear out their stuff?
God have mercy on us

261
00:15:14,060 --> 00:15:15,180
When do you think they'll clear out their stuff?

262
00:15:15,180 --> 00:15:16,180
They promised they'll be here in the next day or two
When do you think they'll clear out their stuff?

263
00:15:16,180 --> 00:15:17,580
They promised they'll be here in the next day or two

264
00:15:26,420 --> 00:15:29,660
There's no parking, you'll have to leave your car on the road

265
00:15:29,660 --> 00:15:33,540
We don't need parking, we're selling our car to cover the first year's rent

266
00:15:33,540 --> 00:15:34,860
Who mentioned money?

267
00:15:34,860 --> 00:15:35,380
Nobody, but still...

268
00:15:35,380 --> 00:15:36,260
Hello Mr Salili
Nobody, but still...

269
00:15:36,260 --> 00:15:36,540
Hello Mr Salili

270
00:15:36,540 --> 00:15:36,940
Hello
Hello Mr Salili

271
00:15:36,940 --> 00:15:37,500
Hello

272
00:15:37,500 --> 00:15:40,460
Mr Shanazari and his wife own one of the apartments here

273
00:15:40,460 --> 00:15:42,100
How's it going?

274
00:15:42,100 --> 00:15:45,220
Hello, hello. How do you do Ma'am?

275
00:15:45,220 --> 00:15:45,260
Babak, whereabouts is the storage?
Hello, hello. How do you do Ma'am?

276
00:15:45,260 --> 00:15:48,020
Babak, whereabouts is the storage?

277
00:15:48,020 --> 00:15:50,020
It's here, come and see

278
00:15:54,180 --> 00:15:54,620
Mr Salimi?

279
00:15:54,620 --> 00:15:55,340
Yes?
Mr Salimi?

280
00:15:55,340 --> 00:15:55,740
Yes?

281
00:15:55,740 --> 00:15:58,260
The door's open, take a look

282
00:16:00,620 --> 00:16:03,580
Please make sure they don't turn out to be like the last one

283
00:16:03,580 --> 00:16:04,540
No no, I know these guys

284
00:16:04,540 --> 00:16:06,500
You said you knew the last one too

285
00:16:06,500 --> 00:16:07,140
Don't worry about it

286
00:16:07,140 --> 00:16:07,820
Babak, what do they do?
Don't worry about it

287
00:16:07,820 --> 00:16:08,820
Babak, what do they do?

288
00:16:08,820 --> 00:16:10,860
They're my friends, very cultured

289
00:16:10,860 --> 00:16:12,020
I hope so

290
00:16:12,140 --> 00:16:13,540
It's okay for a few months

291
00:16:14,220 --> 00:16:18,860
But just make sure he lets us pay him for it

292
00:16:19,660 --> 00:16:22,380
It looks like we've finally caught a break

293
00:16:28,340 --> 00:16:30,020
Careful, don't rush

294
00:16:30,020 --> 00:16:30,340
Can I help?
Careful, don't rush

295
00:16:30,340 --> 00:16:30,420
Can I help?

296
00:16:30,420 --> 00:16:31,220
No thanks, go ahead
Can I help?

297
00:16:31,220 --> 00:16:32,580
No thanks, go ahead

298
00:16:42,340 --> 00:16:45,300
Be careful it doesn't hit the lightbulb

299
00:16:46,860 --> 00:16:49,140
Sorry sir, thanks for helping

300
00:16:51,540 --> 00:16:52,780
Are the keys here?

301
00:16:52,780 --> 00:16:53,380
They took the one to that room with him
Are the keys here?

302
00:16:53,380 --> 00:16:54,900
They took the one to that room with him

303
00:17:01,540 --> 00:17:02,940
Where's Ali?

304
00:17:13,620 --> 00:17:14,140
Ali...

305
00:17:14,140 --> 00:17:14,220
Yep?
Ali...

306
00:17:14,220 --> 00:17:14,700
Yep?

307
00:17:14,700 --> 00:17:14,940
For the love of God leave it, I'll call an electrician tomorrow
Yep?

308
00:17:14,940 --> 00:17:17,820
For the love of God leave it, I'll call an electrician tomorrow

309
00:17:17,820 --> 00:17:18,660
It'll only take a second

310
00:17:18,660 --> 00:17:19,820
Leave it, please!
It'll only take a second

311
00:17:19,820 --> 00:17:20,140
Leave it, please!

312
00:17:21,820 --> 00:17:24,460
If he'd said, we wouldn't have hired movers

313
00:17:24,460 --> 00:17:24,940
How would I know? He sounded so sure that I didn't think he'd bail on us
If he'd said, we wouldn't have hired movers

314
00:17:24,940 --> 00:17:30,660
How would I know? He sounded so sure that I didn't think he'd bail on us

315
00:17:32,940 --> 00:17:34,020
Okay, what's he saying now?

316
00:17:34,020 --> 00:17:34,220
He hasn't answered since this morning
Okay, what's he saying now?

317
00:17:34,220 --> 00:17:35,940
He hasn't answered since this morning

318
00:17:35,940 --> 00:17:38,060
Why don't you try from a different number?

319
00:17:38,740 --> 00:17:40,660
Bring your phone Nana

320
00:17:42,180 --> 00:17:46,300
We really need to get into the room, we've brought a van full of our things

321
00:17:49,860 --> 00:17:51,060
Yes

322
00:17:53,100 --> 00:17:54,060
Okay

323
00:17:54,060 --> 00:17:57,300
He's here if you'd like to speak to him

324
00:18:02,260 --> 00:18:03,740
Thanks

325
00:18:05,260 --> 00:18:07,220
He's said all he has to say to you

326
00:18:07,780 --> 00:18:08,940
What did he say now?

327
00:18:09,500 --> 00:18:14,100
He signed the contract on a new place two days ago, but the landlord pulled out at the last minute

328
00:18:14,100 --> 00:18:17,380
He's looking for a place, but can't come until he finds somewhere

329
00:18:19,500 --> 00:18:22,780
He said to tell you not to let anyone touch his stuff

330
00:18:27,060 --> 00:18:29,420
And he doesn't want to speak to you again

331
00:18:30,260 --> 00:18:31,500
What's the news?

332
00:18:31,500 --> 00:18:33,980
No idea, nothing for now.

333
00:18:35,820 --> 00:18:36,860
Ali

334
00:18:36,860 --> 00:18:38,180
Yes?

335
00:18:38,180 --> 00:18:38,860
Is the screwdriver in the car?
Yes?

336
00:18:38,860 --> 00:18:39,900
Is the screwdriver in the car?

337
00:18:47,260 --> 00:18:49,620
This is enough stuff for a dowry!

338
00:18:49,620 --> 00:18:51,580
I thought it was just a few bits

339
00:18:51,580 --> 00:18:53,260
Maybe we should leave it...

340
00:18:53,260 --> 00:18:53,820
It's fine, I'll take responsibility for it
Maybe we should leave it...

341
00:18:53,820 --> 00:18:56,620
It's fine, I'll take responsibility for it

342
00:19:06,660 --> 00:19:07,820
Rana...

343
00:19:08,820 --> 00:19:11,220
<i>mumbling</i>

344
00:19:11,900 --> 00:19:13,700
These are people's belongings

345
00:19:13,700 --> 00:19:15,580
What else can we do when he keeps delaying
These are people's belongings

346
00:19:15,580 --> 00:19:17,340
What else can we do when he keeps delaying

347
00:19:17,340 --> 00:19:18,500
What if he turns up?
What else can we do when he keeps delaying

348
00:19:18,500 --> 00:19:18,580
What if he turns up?

349
00:19:18,580 --> 00:19:19,340
Well he should've kept his word then
What if he turns up?

350
00:19:19,340 --> 00:19:22,580
Well he should've kept his word then

351
00:19:22,580 --> 00:19:24,620
I can't carry anything heavy!

352
00:19:27,660 --> 00:19:28,820
Mr?

353
00:19:42,900 --> 00:19:44,260
Come and have some food

354
00:19:48,420 --> 00:19:49,380
Rana dear?

355
00:19:49,380 --> 00:19:50,100
Yes dear?

356
00:19:53,420 --> 00:19:54,460
The charger

357
00:20:51,780 --> 00:20:54,460
Go to the door and bring over one of these boxes

358
00:20:54,460 --> 00:20:56,460
Hi guys

359
00:20:56,460 --> 00:20:57,940
Are these the English version Sir?

360
00:20:57,940 --> 00:20:58,340
Go to the office and call the librarian, then come to class
Are these the English version Sir?

361
00:20:58,340 --> 00:21:00,980
Go to the office and call the librarian, then come to class

362
00:21:01,500 --> 00:21:05,140
Very good guys, learn the poem for next time

363
00:21:05,140 --> 00:21:05,260
Okay
Very good guys, learn the poem for next time

364
00:21:05,260 --> 00:21:06,020
Okay

365
00:21:06,020 --> 00:21:06,220
Thank you
Okay

366
00:21:06,220 --> 00:21:07,260
Thank you

367
00:21:08,020 --> 00:21:09,500
Bye Sir

368
00:21:09,500 --> 00:21:11,500
Bye

369
00:21:22,420 --> 00:21:23,580
Bye

370
00:21:40,940 --> 00:21:42,220
Thanks Sir

371
00:21:42,220 --> 00:21:44,220
Goodbye

372
00:21:45,580 --> 00:21:46,940
Mr Simini?

373
00:21:47,300 --> 00:21:48,180
What's up son?

374
00:21:48,180 --> 00:21:51,340
Sir, I felt really bad the other day

375
00:21:51,740 --> 00:21:52,580
Which day?

376
00:21:52,580 --> 00:21:52,940
The day that that woman insulted you in the Taxi
Which day?

377
00:21:52,940 --> 00:21:56,100
The day that that woman insulted you in the Taxi

378
00:21:57,860 --> 00:21:59,300
Was it an insult?

379
00:21:59,300 --> 00:22:03,420
The one that said we should swap places

380
00:22:03,420 --> 00:22:07,940
When you got out of the car I told them that you were my teacher

381
00:22:07,940 --> 00:22:11,060
And that everyone really loves you

382
00:22:12,260 --> 00:22:13,700
What was your first name again?

383
00:22:13,700 --> 00:22:14,100
Amid
What was your first name again?

384
00:22:14,100 --> 00:22:14,580
Amid

385
00:22:15,900 --> 00:22:22,340
Amid, you can be sure that a man had done something previously to make her react the way she did

386
00:22:22,340 --> 00:22:24,620
And now whoever sits next to her is untrustworthy

387
00:22:24,620 --> 00:22:28,060
Don't worry about it, the first 100 years of life are tough

388
00:22:28,060 --> 00:22:28,980
See you

389
00:22:28,980 --> 00:22:29,220
Bye
See you

390
00:22:29,220 --> 00:22:29,900
Bye

391
00:23:09,020 --> 00:23:09,740
Okay

392
00:23:16,100 --> 00:23:18,860
I don't know what to do about them

393
00:23:19,540 --> 00:23:20,260
Who?

394
00:23:20,460 --> 00:23:22,100
This woman

395
00:23:22,380 --> 00:23:27,140
I called and asked when she'll clear out her stuff. She got angry and abusive.

396
00:23:27,140 --> 00:23:28,300
Over what?
I called and asked when she'll clear out her stuff. She got angry and abusive.

397
00:23:28,300 --> 00:23:28,540
"Why did you touch my personal things? I'm going to lodge a complaint"
Over what?

398
00:23:28,540 --> 00:23:32,580
"Why did you touch my personal things? I'm going to lodge a complaint"

399
00:23:32,580 --> 00:23:33,340
I've been constantly running around and saving her stuff from the flooding
"Why did you touch my personal things? I'm going to lodge a complaint"

400
00:23:33,340 --> 00:23:35,740
I've been constantly running around and saving her stuff from the flooding

401
00:23:35,740 --> 00:23:36,380
Her problem's something else...
I've been constantly running around and saving her stuff from the flooding

402
00:23:36,380 --> 00:23:37,260
Her problem's something else...

403
00:23:37,740 --> 00:23:39,780
Who Babak, the woman?

404
00:23:39,780 --> 00:23:39,980
When's she coming to get her stuff?
Who Babak, the woman?

405
00:23:39,980 --> 00:23:41,540
When's she coming to get her stuff?

406
00:23:41,540 --> 00:23:42,340
She's still saying whenever she finds a place
When's she coming to get her stuff?

407
00:23:42,340 --> 00:23:42,700
She's still saying whenever she finds a place

408
00:23:42,700 --> 00:23:43,940
Hey
She's still saying whenever she finds a place

409
00:23:43,940 --> 00:23:44,020
She's still saying whenever she finds a place

410
00:23:47,780 --> 00:23:50,460
Sadra darling, come here with me

411
00:23:52,100 --> 00:23:56,300
Hurry up guys, the audience will be coming in in five minutes

412
00:24:03,300 --> 00:24:06,220
Emad, they're coming here again after the performance.

413
00:24:06,220 --> 00:24:11,780
They've approved 3 of the 6 revisions, if you stay around after the performance then you can speak to them.

414
00:24:11,780 --> 00:24:11,980
Tonight after the performance?
They've approved 3 of the 6 revisions, if you stay around after the performance then you can speak to them.

415
00:24:11,980 --> 00:24:12,780
Tonight after the performance?

416
00:24:12,780 --> 00:24:13,180
Yes
Tonight after the performance?

417
00:24:13,180 --> 00:24:13,700
Yes

418
00:24:13,700 --> 00:24:15,660
If it's useful, I'll stay.

419
00:24:15,660 --> 00:24:17,540
Of course! If you don't then you might not be performing tomorrow

420
00:24:17,540 --> 00:24:17,900
How many did they say?
Of course! If you don't then you might not be performing tomorrow

421
00:24:17,900 --> 00:24:18,340
How many did they say?

422
00:24:18,340 --> 00:24:18,580
Three. Guys will you please speed up!
How many did they say?

423
00:24:18,580 --> 00:24:19,940
Three. Guys will you please speed up!

424
00:24:19,940 --> 00:24:20,340
I'll go then
Three. Guys will you please speed up!

425
00:24:20,340 --> 00:24:21,020
I'll go then

426
00:24:21,020 --> 00:24:22,620
Won't you wait around?

427
00:24:22,620 --> 00:24:22,860
No, you'll be stuck here until midnight
Won't you wait around?

428
00:24:22,860 --> 00:24:24,860
No, you'll be stuck here until midnight

429
00:24:24,860 --> 00:24:26,700
Take the car then

430
00:24:26,700 --> 00:24:28,100
Where are the house keys?

431
00:24:28,100 --> 00:24:29,220
In my coat pocket

432
00:24:29,220 --> 00:24:30,620
Have a good performance

433
00:24:30,620 --> 00:24:30,940
You too!
Have a good performance

434
00:24:30,940 --> 00:24:31,580
You too!

435
00:26:11,620 --> 00:26:15,940
See if the supermarket's open on your way back - we have nothing for breakfast

436
00:26:18,180 --> 00:26:21,020
Yes, I said if it's open. If it's open!

437
00:26:23,820 --> 00:26:26,460
Also pick up some hand soap

438
00:26:29,540 --> 00:26:33,740
No not at all, I'm shattered. I haven't even wiped off my stage makeup.

439
00:26:36,060 --> 00:26:43,700
Come home soon. I love you. Bye.

440
00:27:37,020 --> 00:27:37,780
Anything else?

441
00:27:37,780 --> 00:27:38,780
That's all thanks

442
00:27:40,660 --> 00:27:41,820
Are you paying by card?

443
00:27:41,820 --> 00:27:43,340
No, cash

444
00:27:55,740 --> 00:27:56,540
Hello Ma'am

445
00:27:56,540 --> 00:27:56,980
Hello?

446
00:27:56,980 --> 00:27:57,140
Good evening, I'm your upstairs neighbor
Hello?

447
00:27:57,140 --> 00:27:59,420
Good evening, I'm your upstairs neighbor

448
00:27:59,420 --> 00:28:02,820
We've just moved in, could you open the door please?

449
00:28:03,620 --> 00:28:04,700
Thank you

450
00:28:22,140 --> 00:28:22,780
Rana?

451
00:28:24,820 --> 00:28:25,700
Rana?

452
00:28:28,620 --> 00:28:29,820
Rana?

453
00:28:59,300 --> 00:29:00,260
Rana!

454
00:29:00,260 --> 00:29:01,380
What happened to you?

455
00:29:01,380 --> 00:29:02,980
Please step outside Sir

456
00:29:02,980 --> 00:29:06,460
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.

457
00:29:06,460 --> 00:29:07,260
Rana...
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.

458
00:29:07,260 --> 00:29:07,780
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.

459
00:29:07,780 --> 00:29:08,100
Look at me Rana...
You can't be in here Sir. I'll call you when we do the CT scan.

460
00:29:08,100 --> 00:29:08,660
Look at me Rana...

461
00:29:08,660 --> 00:29:09,100
Everything's fine, I'll call you for the CT scan. Please.
Look at me Rana...

462
00:29:09,100 --> 00:29:13,740
Everything's fine, I'll call you for the CT scan. Please.

463
00:29:16,140 --> 00:29:20,300
Make sure you change the locks first thing tomorrow.

464
00:29:21,460 --> 00:29:26,660
Why? Did someone get into the house? I thought she'd fainted and hit her head

465
00:29:26,660 --> 00:29:27,180
We don't know what happened yet
Why? Did someone get into the house? I thought she'd fainted and hit her head

466
00:29:27,180 --> 00:29:28,140
We don't know what happened yet

467
00:29:28,140 --> 00:29:28,700
All of a sudden we heard shouting and screaming from upstairs.
We don't know what happened yet

468
00:29:28,700 --> 00:29:31,860
All of a sudden we heard shouting and screaming from upstairs.

469
00:29:31,860 --> 00:29:40,340
Not just screaming but howling. I told my husband we should go up and check, but he said it was just a domestic argument.

470
00:29:40,340 --> 00:29:46,140
Then we heard some heavy bangs and I told him "Muhammad, something bad's happened!"

471
00:29:46,140 --> 00:29:47,020
Who was it?

472
00:29:47,020 --> 00:29:47,300
By the time we reached the stairs, we just saw someone fleeing up the road
Who was it?

473
00:29:47,300 --> 00:29:50,660
By the time we reached the stairs, we just saw someone fleeing up the road

474
00:29:50,660 --> 00:29:51,260
I don't know what happened to their foot but it had bled all the way down the stairs
By the time we reached the stairs, we just saw someone fleeing up the road

475
00:29:51,260 --> 00:29:53,580
I don't know what happened to their foot but it had bled all the way down the stairs

476
00:29:53,580 --> 00:29:54,180
If I'd caught them, they'd be dead now
I don't know what happened to their foot but it had bled all the way down the stairs

477
00:29:54,180 --> 00:29:56,980
If I'd caught them, they'd be dead now

478
00:29:56,980 --> 00:30:02,820
Then we went upstairs and found your wife unconscious, with the bathroom was covered in blood. I dressed her and we brought her here.

479
00:30:02,820 --> 00:30:04,300
Let's stop talking about it anyway and thank God that nothing worse happened
Then we went upstairs and found your wife unconscious, with the bathroom was covered in blood. I dressed her and we brought her here.

480
00:30:04,300 --> 00:30:07,820
Let's stop talking about it anyway and thank God that nothing worse happened

481
00:30:07,820 --> 00:30:14,020
Could you do me a favour please dear and go and check if there's any news from the Emergency Room

482
00:30:15,380 --> 00:30:19,020
Sorry about all of this...

483
00:30:19,020 --> 00:30:21,460
Have a seat

484
00:30:26,460 --> 00:30:28,780
Was anything missing from the house?

485
00:30:29,540 --> 00:30:32,300
I didn't notice anything

486
00:30:32,300 --> 00:30:32,860
I don't think it was a robbery - what would a thief be doing in the bathroom?
I didn't notice anything

487
00:30:32,860 --> 00:30:36,140
I don't think it was a robbery - what would a thief be doing in the bathroom?

488
00:30:37,220 --> 00:30:38,820
Then who was it?

489
00:30:38,820 --> 00:30:41,060
He was a customer of the woman

490
00:30:41,060 --> 00:30:42,300
Who? What woman?

491
00:30:42,300 --> 00:30:42,820
The woman that lived there before you
Who? What woman?

492
00:30:42,820 --> 00:30:44,980
The woman that lived there before you

493
00:30:45,500 --> 00:30:53,940
She had some problems... I think he came around looking for her

494
00:31:07,220 --> 00:31:08,660
Don't shut the door, Ali's coming up

495
00:31:08,660 --> 00:31:09,180
Sure
Don't shut the door, Ali's coming up

496
00:31:09,180 --> 00:31:09,620
Sure

497
00:31:15,700 --> 00:31:17,740
Come and lie down

498
00:31:23,980 --> 00:31:26,300
Take my sleeve, hold this bit

499
00:31:28,980 --> 00:31:29,900
Thanks

500
00:31:36,140 --> 00:31:38,860
Wait, let me take your scarf off

501
00:31:40,300 --> 00:31:42,140
Should I put two pillows for you?

502
00:31:42,140 --> 00:31:43,060
No
Should I put two pillows for you?

503
00:31:43,060 --> 00:31:43,300
Should I put two pillows for you?

504
00:31:51,260 --> 00:31:53,420
Turn the light off too so she can sleep

505
00:31:53,420 --> 00:31:53,620
Don't turn it off
Turn the light off too so she can sleep

506
00:31:53,620 --> 00:31:54,380
Don't turn it off

507
00:31:56,140 --> 00:31:57,580
Can I get you anything?

508
00:31:57,580 --> 00:31:58,380
No, thanks
Can I get you anything?

509
00:31:58,380 --> 00:31:58,620
No, thanks

510
00:32:06,940 --> 00:32:08,540
Where are you going Emad?

511
00:32:09,860 --> 00:32:10,820
Darling?

512
00:32:10,820 --> 00:32:12,300
Where are you going?

513
00:32:12,300 --> 00:32:15,140
I'm not going anywhere, I'll be here. Do you need anything?

514
00:32:15,140 --> 00:32:18,860
Nope. Leave the door open please.

515
00:32:28,700 --> 00:32:29,420
Okay, thanks

516
00:32:29,420 --> 00:32:30,060
Her blood pressure's low - be careful when she's walking around
Okay, thanks

517
00:32:30,060 --> 00:32:31,940
Her blood pressure's low - be careful when she's walking around

518
00:32:31,940 --> 00:32:32,900
Thanks for everything
Her blood pressure's low - be careful when she's walking around

519
00:32:32,900 --> 00:32:33,580
Thanks for everything

520
00:32:33,580 --> 00:32:34,900
Sit down guys, I'll make breakfast
Thanks for everything

521
00:32:34,900 --> 00:32:36,420
Sit down guys, I'll make breakfast

522
00:32:36,420 --> 00:32:36,980
No thanks, I'm fine

523
00:32:36,980 --> 00:32:38,420
Come on, you haven't eaten since last night
No thanks, I'm fine

524
00:32:38,420 --> 00:32:41,100
Come on, you haven't eaten since last night

525
00:32:44,220 --> 00:32:46,780
Should I stay back and make some soup or something?

526
00:32:47,940 --> 00:32:48,620
No no

527
00:32:48,620 --> 00:32:48,980
Are you sure?
No no

528
00:32:48,980 --> 00:32:49,860
Are you sure?

529
00:32:50,460 --> 00:32:52,620
You must be tired. Go and get some rest

530
00:32:52,620 --> 00:32:53,340
Call if you need anything
You must be tired. Go and get some rest

531
00:32:53,340 --> 00:32:53,580
Call if you need anything

532
00:32:53,580 --> 00:32:54,460
Really, let us know
Call if you need anything

533
00:32:54,460 --> 00:32:57,780
Really, let us know

534
00:32:57,780 --> 00:32:59,780
Thanks again for everything

535
00:35:02,940 --> 00:35:12,180
<i>I'm buying scrap metal... Iron doors... Aluminium doors... Fences... Metal dishes...</i>

536
00:35:16,060 --> 00:35:24,340
Scrap metal... Samovars... Anything you have, I'll buy it...

537
00:36:46,900 --> 00:36:49,580
Come and stand here while I use the bathroom

538
00:37:02,820 --> 00:37:04,300
What are you doing?

539
00:37:04,300 --> 00:37:06,820
Leave it, I can wash that

540
00:37:06,820 --> 00:37:07,180
Come and wash it then
Leave it, I can wash that

541
00:37:07,180 --> 00:37:07,780
Come and wash it then

542
00:37:07,780 --> 00:37:08,100
Okay, turn off the water and come out
Come and wash it then

543
00:37:08,100 --> 00:37:09,420
Okay, turn off the water and come out

544
00:37:13,220 --> 00:37:15,260
Come and clean it before I use it

545
00:37:15,980 --> 00:37:18,060
The police might need to see it

546
00:37:22,700 --> 00:37:23,380
Yes?

547
00:37:25,700 --> 00:37:26,740
Of course, sorry

548
00:37:26,740 --> 00:37:26,940
Who was it?
Of course, sorry

549
00:37:26,940 --> 00:37:27,780
Who was it?

550
00:37:28,380 --> 00:37:29,420
A neighbor

551
00:37:29,420 --> 00:37:29,780
What did they say?
A neighbor

552
00:37:29,780 --> 00:37:30,340
What did they say?

553
00:37:30,460 --> 00:37:31,180
I'll be right back

554
00:37:37,180 --> 00:37:38,500
Sorry

555
00:37:51,380 --> 00:37:54,100
I'm really sorry you were disturbed by everything last night

556
00:37:54,100 --> 00:37:59,660
Not at all, what are you saying? I think you should call the police and they'll be able to track him down through the car

557
00:37:59,660 --> 00:38:02,860
Sure, I'll definitely do that. I need to find somewhere...

558
00:38:02,860 --> 00:38:03,500
I'd hoped that woman had taken her trouble with her when she left
Sure, I'll definitely do that. I need to find somewhere...

559
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:05,980
I'd hoped that woman had taken her trouble with her when she left

560
00:38:06,460 --> 00:38:08,740
Have you ever seen this car's owner around here?

561
00:38:08,740 --> 00:38:09,180
Who knows, people were constantly coming and going from that apartment
Have you ever seen this car's owner around here?

562
00:38:09,180 --> 00:38:12,460
Who knows, people were constantly coming and going from that apartment

563
00:38:12,460 --> 00:38:16,940
I might have to trouble you again when the police come if they have any questions about exactly what you saw

564
00:38:16,940 --> 00:38:17,180
Of course, it's our duty. Would you like to take my mobile number?
I might have to trouble you again when the police come if they have any questions about exactly what you saw

565
00:38:17,180 --> 00:38:20,460
Of course, it's our duty. Would you like to take my mobile number?

566
00:38:20,460 --> 00:38:21,380
Yes please

567
00:38:21,380 --> 00:38:22,500
I'll get going

568
00:38:22,500 --> 00:38:23,420
Thank you ma'am

569
00:38:23,420 --> 00:38:24,420
They should start putting these people in the stocks again and shaming them
Thank you ma'am

570
00:38:24,420 --> 00:38:28,220
They should start putting these people in the stocks again and shaming them

571
00:38:28,220 --> 00:38:30,220
0-900-12

572
00:38:48,620 --> 00:38:50,500
Why are you out here? Come in

573
00:38:50,500 --> 00:38:52,740
I'm scared of being alone in the house

574
00:38:54,140 --> 00:38:55,340
Where did you go?

575
00:38:57,340 --> 00:39:00,100
I went to thank the neighbors for last night

576
00:39:00,860 --> 00:39:01,940
What did they say?

577
00:39:01,940 --> 00:39:03,340
Nothing

578
00:39:03,500 --> 00:39:04,900
They asked how you were

579
00:39:04,900 --> 00:39:08,460
You didn't tell Kati what happened?

580
00:39:08,620 --> 00:39:09,700
No

581
00:39:10,580 --> 00:39:12,020
Okay, I'm going to the police station

582
00:39:12,860 --> 00:39:15,700
We have to lodge a complaint before they'll start looking for him

583
00:39:16,220 --> 00:39:18,100
How will they find him?

584
00:39:18,100 --> 00:39:19,940
He left his van behind

585
00:39:19,940 --> 00:39:23,980
His mobile too, but it's disconnected

586
00:39:26,420 --> 00:39:27,780
Who was it Emad?

587
00:39:30,580 --> 00:39:34,340
The neighbors are saying that the woman that lived here before was dodgy

588
00:39:35,020 --> 00:39:38,940
This scumbag must have been one of her customers

589
00:39:42,180 --> 00:39:43,940
Do you remember what he looked like?

590
00:39:44,460 --> 00:39:45,660
No

591
00:39:46,300 --> 00:39:47,700
Didn't you get a look at him?

592
00:39:56,580 --> 00:39:58,380
Come inside, you'll catch a cold

593
00:40:11,780 --> 00:40:12,900
Pass it here

594
00:40:19,780 --> 00:40:21,700
Who helped me out of the bathroom?

595
00:40:23,860 --> 00:40:25,540
One of the neighbors

596
00:40:25,540 --> 00:40:27,020
Which?

597
00:40:27,020 --> 00:40:29,300
I don't know, don't worry about it

598
00:40:32,860 --> 00:40:36,660
Eat some breakfast. Have something and then sleep

599
00:40:39,380 --> 00:40:43,740
I can't. As soon as I close my eyes that scene replays in my mind

600
00:40:53,060 --> 00:40:54,700
How did he get in?

601
00:40:57,180 --> 00:40:59,980
I opened the door thinking it was you

602
00:41:00,900 --> 00:41:05,500
I came out of the bathroom, buzzed him up and then went back in

603
00:41:12,700 --> 00:41:16,500
I was shampooing my hair when I realised someone had come in

604
00:41:17,980 --> 00:41:21,220
He put his hand in my hair from behind and I thought it was you

605
00:41:22,700 --> 00:41:25,460
But then I saw his hand and after that it's blank

606
00:41:40,980 --> 00:41:42,220
Rana...

607
00:41:43,140 --> 00:41:45,940
Darling, have some breakfast

608
00:41:51,660 --> 00:41:52,780
Rana my darling

609
00:41:54,980 --> 00:41:56,140
Sweetie

610
00:42:52,180 --> 00:42:53,940
What's happening with tonight's performance

611
00:42:55,140 --> 00:42:57,140
I called and told them to cancel it

612
00:42:57,140 --> 00:42:57,340
No, call and say I'm coming
I called and told them to cancel it

613
00:42:57,340 --> 00:42:58,500
No, call and say I'm coming

614
00:42:58,500 --> 00:42:58,700
How when you're in this condition?
No, call and say I'm coming

615
00:42:58,700 --> 00:43:00,180
How when you're in this condition?

616
00:43:00,460 --> 00:43:02,220
It's harder to stay at home

617
00:43:08,140 --> 00:43:11,900
Put this on and we'll go to the police station. We might get held up there for a while anyway

618
00:43:12,540 --> 00:43:13,900
No, leave it. Let's not go to the station.

619
00:43:13,900 --> 00:43:14,540
We can't just do nothing!
No, leave it. Let's not go to the station.

620
00:43:14,540 --> 00:43:15,700
We can't just do nothing!

621
00:43:17,380 --> 00:43:22,700
I don't want to have to go there and tell a bunch of officers what happened

622
00:43:23,620 --> 00:43:26,420
Did something happen that you can't tell them?

623
00:43:27,620 --> 00:43:28,540
No

624
00:43:28,540 --> 00:43:31,300
Then you don't have to say anything. I'll explain what happened.

625
00:43:31,300 --> 00:43:32,500
I can't, it'll be too much
Then you don't have to say anything. I'll explain what happened.

626
00:43:32,500 --> 00:43:33,900
I can't, it'll be too much

627
00:43:44,300 --> 00:43:46,500
No, this isn't foolish talk

628
00:43:46,780 --> 00:43:54,180
When I'm walking in the street I see these things clearly. They pass by indifferently, but it's as though they're mocking me with their gazes.

629
00:43:54,180 --> 00:43:58,660
Why? Why would they laugh at you? Don't say these things about yourself Willy

630
00:43:58,660 --> 00:43:59,420
Sometimes they pass me by as if I don't exist
Why? Why would they laugh at you? Don't say these things about yourself Willy

631
00:43:59,420 --> 00:44:01,940
Sometimes they pass me by as if I don't exist

632
00:44:03,020 --> 00:44:06,980
As though nobody sees me. Nobody notices me

633
00:44:12,500 --> 00:44:13,740
Linda?

634
00:44:21,340 --> 00:44:26,020
How long are you going to spend repairing those socks?

635
00:44:26,540 --> 00:44:32,700
You know doing it will make me angry. At least don't do it while I'm at home and talking to you. Okay?

636
00:44:37,660 --> 00:44:44,260
Okay we'll talk about something else, for example my income.

637
00:44:44,820 --> 00:44:51,100
My never-changing income. God, this is really ridiculous

638
00:44:51,540 --> 00:44:53,380
<i>Whispers a prompt</i>

639
00:44:53,380 --> 00:44:58,460
Willy. Darling. You're the most handsome man in the world to me.

640
00:45:02,100 --> 00:45:07,300
You always say this to me Linda, but it doesn't help me at all.

641
00:45:07,300 --> 00:45:09,660
I'll never be able to make you happy and do you know why?

642
00:45:09,660 --> 00:45:13,900
Because I'm just a salesman. I'm nothing! I'm nothing Linda!

643
00:45:13,900 --> 00:45:14,020
But I always tried... why are you crying?
Because I'm just a salesman. I'm nothing! I'm nothing Linda!

644
00:45:14,020 --> 00:45:18,580
But I always tried... why are you crying?

645
00:45:22,460 --> 00:45:23,980
Wait, where are you going?

646
00:45:24,940 --> 00:45:26,460
Linda, come back...

647
00:45:31,780 --> 00:45:36,260
Sorry, I have to stop the play. I apologise to you all.

648
00:45:36,620 --> 00:45:43,100
My wife, the other actor, isn't feeling well. Please give us a ten minute intermission. I'm really sorry

649
00:45:46,300 --> 00:45:47,820
Can you carry on?

650
00:45:47,820 --> 00:45:51,980
What do you mean Kati? Can't you see she's not well? Go and cancel it

651
00:45:52,060 --> 00:45:54,820
Do you need to go and lie down?

652
00:45:54,820 --> 00:45:58,580
No, let's give her some space

653
00:46:00,900 --> 00:46:02,740
Sanam dear

654
00:46:02,740 --> 00:46:04,620
I'm coming

655
00:46:04,620 --> 00:46:06,620
Can I bring you anything?

656
00:46:12,260 --> 00:46:13,500
Kati darling...

657
00:46:13,940 --> 00:46:15,860
Go and cancel the show

658
00:46:25,860 --> 00:46:27,860
What happened there?

659
00:46:31,780 --> 00:46:35,780
The way one of the audience members was staring unsettled me

660
00:46:38,460 --> 00:46:42,260
The audience have come to watch the play, of course they'll be looking at you

661
00:46:42,300 --> 00:46:44,780
They were looking at me like that man did

662
00:46:50,540 --> 00:46:52,500
You said that you didn't see him

663
00:46:52,500 --> 00:46:56,700
I'm really unwell, I need help

664
00:46:59,700 --> 00:47:01,180
Babak, come here a minute

665
00:47:01,180 --> 00:47:02,700
Coming...

666
00:47:11,100 --> 00:47:12,900
Is she feeling better?

667
00:47:13,660 --> 00:47:19,500
What can I say...? You didn't say a word to me about who was living there before

668
00:47:19,940 --> 00:47:20,580
What's happened?

669
00:47:20,660 --> 00:47:22,020
You're supposed to be my friend

670
00:47:22,020 --> 00:47:25,900
Seriously, what's happened? What is it to you who lived there before?

671
00:47:26,140 --> 00:47:28,900
That apartment's infamous in the neighborhood

672
00:47:29,220 --> 00:47:30,380
Who's said such a thing?

673
00:47:30,580 --> 00:47:34,340
Let's say nobody's said anything - why isn't this woman coming to collect her things?

674
00:47:34,340 --> 00:47:39,820
I just wanted to help. Have you forgotten the state you were in last week - ready to sleep on the set?

675
00:47:39,820 --> 00:47:42,500
Regardless, should you have hidden that woman's profession from me?

676
00:47:42,500 --> 00:47:44,780
What hiding?
Regardless, should you have hidden that woman's profession from me?

677
00:47:44,780 --> 00:47:45,140
What hiding?

678
00:47:45,180 --> 00:47:45,860
Is that not true?

679
00:47:45,860 --> 00:47:46,980
Then explain it to me

680
00:47:46,980 --> 00:47:53,180
Should I have passed on some unfounded gossip to you?

681
00:47:53,180 --> 00:47:55,020
Where's this coming from?

682
00:47:55,020 --> 00:47:56,420
Babak, I'm going

683
00:47:56,420 --> 00:47:57,260
I'm coming

684
00:47:57,660 --> 00:48:00,740
Why don't you go and look at Rana and see what the matter is

685
00:48:00,820 --> 00:48:03,180
They said she'd slipped in the bathroom

686
00:48:06,300 --> 00:48:10,860
We said in front of you we might be having a kid and you didn't say a word

687
00:48:10,860 --> 00:48:13,540
You were joking!

688
00:48:14,180 --> 00:48:16,460
If we hadn't been, would you have told us?

689
00:48:16,460 --> 00:48:20,020
Would I have said what?

690
00:48:20,020 --> 00:48:26,980
Put yourself in my shoes - how many strange men have been with that woman in the bed that we sleep in each night?

691
00:48:27,460 --> 00:48:32,100
Feel free not to - I haven't cashed your check yet

692
00:48:32,100 --> 00:48:38,900
Whenever you find an apartment whose previous tenants you approve of, you can leave

693
00:48:50,020 --> 00:48:50,540
Hello

694
00:48:50,540 --> 00:48:50,940
Hello
Hello

695
00:48:50,940 --> 00:48:51,340
Hello

696
00:48:51,340 --> 00:48:52,060
How are you doing

697
00:48:52,220 --> 00:48:57,060
Be careful not to slip on the stairs Mrs Shahnazari, they're wet

698
00:48:57,060 --> 00:49:04,420
I was actually going to ask the cleaner to come early and sort these out

699
00:49:04,420 --> 00:49:08,660
But I thought you'd want the report it to the police and have them see them first

700
00:49:08,660 --> 00:49:11,380
It's okay, it wasn't such a big deal

701
00:49:11,660 --> 00:49:18,620
You wouldn't say that if you'd been there and had seen the state of your wife on the bathroom floor

702
00:49:19,340 --> 00:49:26,500
When Mr Alimoradi opened the bathroom door, he thought your wife was dead

703
00:49:26,500 --> 00:49:29,300
Say hello from me

704
00:49:34,940 --> 00:49:36,580
Get up, I've made some breakfast for you

705
00:49:36,820 --> 00:49:37,860
I'm heading out

706
00:49:37,860 --> 00:49:38,620
Wait

707
00:49:44,460 --> 00:49:46,860
Wait, I'll get ready and come with you

708
00:49:46,860 --> 00:49:48,820
Where to? I have class

709
00:49:48,900 --> 00:49:50,580
I know, I'll wait in the car

710
00:49:50,860 --> 00:49:53,420
It's not just an hour or two, you'll get tired

711
00:49:53,620 --> 00:49:54,780
Then don't go today

712
00:49:54,900 --> 00:49:55,780
What?

713
00:49:55,780 --> 00:49:58,100
Don't go today

714
00:49:58,420 --> 00:50:00,980
If I don't go today then what about tomorrow?

715
00:50:00,980 --> 00:50:03,580
The day after tomorrow?

716
00:50:03,580 --> 00:50:06,300
I can't stay here alone

717
00:50:07,300 --> 00:50:09,980
I don't want to be here alone

718
00:50:10,540 --> 00:50:17,260
What can I do? I can get you a ticket to visit your parents for a few days if you like?

719
00:50:17,940 --> 00:50:19,500
Looking like this?

720
00:50:20,980 --> 00:50:26,700
I've decided - we're either going to the police or we forget this entirely

721
00:50:27,700 --> 00:50:31,260
Okay forget it, but let's find a new apartment

722
00:50:31,260 --> 00:50:32,540
Okay, we'll start looking

723
00:50:32,540 --> 00:50:36,580
But until we find somewhere, you need to try and pick yourself up

724
00:50:36,580 --> 00:50:38,140
What do you mean? It's not something I can control

725
00:50:38,140 --> 00:50:38,380
It's within your power to take your medicine and not stay up all night getting worked up about it, right?

726
00:50:42,980 --> 00:50:47,140
Go take a shower, I'll wait here

727
00:50:48,460 --> 00:50:50,180
I don't want to go in that bathroom

728
00:50:54,300 --> 00:50:56,220
I'll drop you off at a friend's place. Use theirs.

729
00:50:56,220 --> 00:50:58,700
Go and tell them we've come to take a shower?

730
00:50:59,020 --> 00:51:01,140
What do you want me to do?

731
00:51:03,340 --> 00:51:05,260
You keep changing your mind

732
00:51:05,940 --> 00:51:10,820
At night you tell me not to come near you, then in the morning you tell me not to leave you

733
00:51:10,820 --> 00:51:12,740
Tell me what to do and I'll do it

734
00:51:12,740 --> 00:51:13,380
Just go, you're late

735
00:51:13,380 --> 00:51:19,820
It'll take a couple of weeks to find a place. You're not going to wash that wound until then?

736
00:51:38,260 --> 00:51:40,300
I love you

737
00:51:42,540 --> 00:51:45,300
Just think, it could've been worse

738
00:51:45,300 --> 00:51:50,220
What if a piece of glass had gone in your eye or your head had been hit harder?

739
00:51:50,220 --> 00:51:52,260
What would I have done then?

740
00:51:52,780 --> 00:51:54,740
I wish my head had been hit harder

741
00:51:56,580 --> 00:51:59,660
Come on, don't say things like that

742
00:52:59,020 --> 00:53:00,980
Hello Mr Etesami

743
00:53:13,060 --> 00:53:15,820
Hello Sir, how are you doing?

744
00:53:16,460 --> 00:53:18,860
Mr Yeganeh gave me these books for you

745
00:53:19,780 --> 00:53:22,260
Be quiet. What's so funny?

746
00:53:24,700 --> 00:53:25,820
Why?

747
00:53:25,820 --> 00:53:28,340
He said they're not suitable for children

748
00:53:29,060 --> 00:53:30,780
Quiet!

749
00:53:32,060 --> 00:53:35,020
Mr Yeganeh decided these weren't suitable for children?

750
00:53:36,420 --> 00:53:38,220
Go and throw them in the bin

751
00:53:38,420 --> 00:53:39,140
Why bin them?

752
00:53:39,140 --> 00:53:41,140
Just throw them away

753
00:53:52,140 --> 00:53:53,260
Give me your phone

754
00:53:53,260 --> 00:53:54,540
Did you forget yours?

755
00:53:54,540 --> 00:53:55,260
Give it to me

756
00:53:55,260 --> 00:53:56,380
It's my phone

757
00:53:56,940 --> 00:53:58,580
Sir, wait a minute

758
00:54:02,060 --> 00:54:02,940
Give it to me

759
00:54:02,940 --> 00:54:03,940
Sir we don't have any footage of you

760
00:54:03,940 --> 00:54:04,540
I want to see what you have
Sir we don't have any footage of you

761
00:54:04,540 --> 00:54:05,340
I want to see what you have

762
00:54:05,340 --> 00:54:06,260
I've deleted it

763
00:54:06,260 --> 00:54:07,620
Let me see it

764
00:54:07,620 --> 00:54:09,420
Sir please, I've deleted it

765
00:54:09,420 --> 00:54:12,460
Sir, I have private photos on there

766
00:54:12,700 --> 00:54:13,900
Put your hand down

767
00:54:13,900 --> 00:54:15,180
That's not fair

768
00:54:16,860 --> 00:54:18,180
Mr Etesami?

769
00:54:19,700 --> 00:54:21,100
Sir?

770
00:54:22,700 --> 00:54:26,700
I have personal things on there. I deleted the video.

771
00:54:28,700 --> 00:54:30,900
On my mother's life I deleted it

772
00:54:31,340 --> 00:54:35,220
Sir, send it on Telegram so that everyone can see

773
00:54:35,220 --> 00:54:38,100
Don't say anything else or I'll throw you out

774
00:54:38,580 --> 00:54:39,500
Mr Etesami

775
00:54:39,500 --> 00:54:40,100
Sorry Sir

776
00:54:40,100 --> 00:54:40,980
Don't interfere

777
00:54:40,980 --> 00:54:41,860
Mr Etesami?

778
00:54:41,860 --> 00:54:44,140
I'm talking to all of you

779
00:54:45,820 --> 00:54:47,300
I deleted it

780
00:54:48,220 --> 00:54:49,300
Please

781
00:54:52,980 --> 00:54:56,500
Tell your father to come to the school and see the kind of photos you have on here

782
00:54:58,340 --> 00:55:00,420
Sir, his dad's dead

783
00:55:53,740 --> 00:55:55,300
Hi, sorry about that

784
00:55:55,300 --> 00:56:00,980
Hi, no problem - if it's a hassle for you to keep moving it then you can leave it in the corner

785
00:56:00,980 --> 00:56:02,060
By the boiler room

786
00:56:02,060 --> 00:56:05,420
When my husband gets back he'll move it to a better place

787
00:56:05,420 --> 00:56:08,820
I don't want you to have to keep going up and down the stairs

788
00:56:08,820 --> 00:56:12,060
I'm going out for a couple of hours - you can take my spot

789
00:56:12,060 --> 00:56:14,100
Don't worry, I'll find a better place for it

790
00:56:14,100 --> 00:56:15,620
As you wish

791
00:56:15,620 --> 00:56:15,900
Sorry

792
00:56:15,900 --> 00:56:18,460
If you give me the keys, I can do it

793
00:56:18,460 --> 00:56:19,140
Thanks

794
00:56:21,420 --> 00:56:25,220
My wife said you're not going to report it

795
00:56:25,220 --> 00:56:25,860
No

796
00:56:25,860 --> 00:56:29,180
You're doing the right thing - they won't do anything even if they catch him

797
00:56:29,180 --> 00:56:37,220
And you'll have to explain over and over why you opened the door, plus trekking back and forth to the court

798
00:56:37,220 --> 00:56:39,140
Endless hassle for nothing

799
00:56:39,140 --> 00:56:43,540
But he'll probably be back for his car. Call me if he shows up

800
00:56:43,540 --> 00:56:45,540
I'll sort out that bastard

801
00:56:58,620 --> 00:57:02,180
I'll take mine out and then come and park yours

802
00:57:02,180 --> 00:57:03,940
Don't worry about it, I'll do it myself

803
00:57:03,940 --> 00:57:05,420
Okay, goodbye then. Thanks

804
00:57:06,100 --> 00:57:07,740
Goodbye

805
00:57:35,620 --> 00:57:36,420
How's it going?

806
00:57:36,420 --> 00:57:38,780
Hey, you okay? Is Rana here?

807
00:57:38,780 --> 00:57:40,180
No, wasn't she with you?

808
00:57:40,180 --> 00:57:41,300
She's coming on her own

809
00:57:41,300 --> 00:57:43,100
Any news on him?

810
00:57:46,540 --> 00:57:48,020
Who?

811
00:57:49,300 --> 00:57:52,140
Babak had heard some things from your neighbors

812
00:57:54,940 --> 00:57:56,500
Where is he? Is he here?

813
00:57:56,500 --> 00:57:57,580
Babak?

814
00:57:57,580 --> 00:57:59,340
Yep, he's in the back

815
00:58:06,580 --> 00:58:07,780
Hi

816
00:58:07,900 --> 00:58:08,700
Hi

817
00:58:08,700 --> 00:58:10,380
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?

818
00:58:11,700 --> 00:58:13,020
What should I have told you?

819
00:58:13,020 --> 00:58:15,140
About the man turning up the other night

820
00:58:16,460 --> 00:58:18,060
How's Rana?

821
00:58:18,580 --> 00:58:20,340
The neighbors told you

822
00:58:22,580 --> 00:58:24,660
They're also worried...

823
00:58:24,660 --> 00:58:26,860
Tell everyone nothing happened

824
00:58:26,860 --> 00:58:29,020
Then why are you holding onto his van?

825
00:58:29,020 --> 00:58:31,020
Why's it still in the parking lot?

826
00:58:31,340 --> 00:58:36,220
Tell them we'll be gone soon - we're looking for a new place

827
00:58:36,220 --> 00:58:38,100
Where will you go?

828
00:58:38,100 --> 00:58:40,620
I won't let you

829
00:58:40,860 --> 00:58:44,820
Can you find the previous tenant and arrange a meeting for me?

830
00:58:45,500 --> 00:58:46,620
Why?

831
00:58:46,620 --> 00:58:48,620
I want to speak with her

832
00:58:48,620 --> 00:58:50,620
Ask her why she did this

833
00:58:50,620 --> 00:58:51,540
Did what?

834
00:58:51,940 --> 00:58:53,620
Did what?

835
00:58:53,620 --> 00:58:56,260
Sent this thug to our house

836
00:58:56,260 --> 00:58:57,380
Why would she have done that?

837
00:58:57,380 --> 00:59:01,140
You said yourself, she made threats about us touching her stuff

838
00:59:01,140 --> 00:59:08,100
She's not that sort of person. She hasn't taken her stuff because she still hasn't found a place. She was just annoyed with me that day.

839
00:59:09,620 --> 00:59:10,740
Hello

840
00:59:11,700 --> 00:59:13,340
Feeling better?

841
00:59:13,340 --> 00:59:15,380
Yep, I'm fine thanks

842
00:59:23,620 --> 00:59:25,700
Did you tell them happened?

843
00:59:26,060 --> 00:59:26,780
No

844
00:59:26,780 --> 00:59:28,380
Then how do they know?

845
00:59:28,380 --> 00:59:31,060
The neighbor had called Babak

846
00:59:31,060 --> 00:59:32,900
I'm not sure what they said

847
00:59:33,940 --> 00:59:36,340
Emad, get dressed and come out

848
00:59:39,540 --> 00:59:41,460
My outfit's not here

849
00:59:41,980 --> 00:59:44,020
Kati's going to take your place tonight

850
00:59:54,460 --> 00:59:56,300
And you just accepted that?

851
00:59:56,300 --> 00:59:58,460
What can I do? I'm not in charge

852
00:59:58,580 --> 01:00:01,660
The director wanted her to replace you tonight

853
01:00:01,660 --> 01:00:05,020
Are you okay? Are you up to it? Go and let him know

854
01:00:05,020 --> 01:00:06,700
No, I don't want to

855
01:00:07,620 --> 01:00:09,380
Have you started househunting?

856
01:00:10,540 --> 01:00:12,260
No, I will do

857
01:00:13,700 --> 01:00:14,860
As soon as I get time

858
01:00:14,860 --> 01:00:18,460
When you get time! As though everything's fine at our current place!

859
01:00:18,460 --> 01:00:19,940
You haven't done anything

860
01:00:19,940 --> 01:00:21,380
What?

861
01:00:23,060 --> 01:00:25,860
I want us to go to the police, but you won't come. What do you mean?

862
01:00:25,860 --> 01:00:29,420
You said you'd find a substitute teacher and pick me up in an hour

863
01:00:29,420 --> 01:00:31,740
I couldn't find anyone to cover my class

864
01:00:39,340 --> 01:00:40,340
Auntie?

865
01:00:40,780 --> 01:00:42,340
Yes Baby?

866
01:00:42,340 --> 01:00:45,060
Why aren't you acting tonight?

867
01:00:45,740 --> 01:00:47,900
I'm not feeling well tonight darling

868
01:00:47,900 --> 01:00:50,220
Why did you come here then?

869
01:00:50,220 --> 01:00:52,540
I get bored at home

870
01:00:52,540 --> 01:00:54,020
What?

871
01:00:54,020 --> 01:00:56,380
I get bored at home

872
01:00:56,980 --> 01:01:01,900
Oh, I get bored here

873
01:01:04,020 --> 01:01:06,900
Would you like to come to our house this evening?

874
01:01:07,260 --> 01:01:09,300
Do you have Spongebob?

875
01:01:09,300 --> 01:01:11,540
No, but we can go to the shops on the way home

876
01:01:11,540 --> 01:01:14,100
From tomorrow evening you really need to join us again

877
01:01:14,100 --> 01:01:18,300
Everything's topsy turvy. Everybody's making mistakes

878
01:01:19,500 --> 01:01:20,740
Why?

879
01:01:20,740 --> 01:01:22,740
I don't know, everyone's upset

880
01:01:22,740 --> 01:01:25,140
You're better now, you should act again tomorrow

881
01:01:25,140 --> 01:01:25,780
Mum?

882
01:01:25,780 --> 01:01:26,540
Darling?

883
01:01:26,540 --> 01:01:27,660
I'm going to Auntie's house

884
01:01:27,660 --> 01:01:28,580
No you're not baby

885
01:01:28,580 --> 01:01:33,460
Let him come with me, I'm alone tonight. I'll bring him back tomorrow evening

886
01:01:33,460 --> 01:01:38,020
He can't, his dad will be picking him up to go to his house tomorrow

887
01:01:41,820 --> 01:01:44,540
That's okay - his Dad can pick him up from our place

888
01:01:49,580 --> 01:01:50,980
Do you want to go?

889
01:01:50,980 --> 01:01:51,820
Yes!

890
01:01:52,060 --> 01:01:54,060
You won't be a nuisance for Auntie Rana?

891
01:01:54,060 --> 01:01:55,660
He won't be

892
01:01:55,900 --> 01:01:59,020
Tell Emad we're taking the car

893
01:02:00,100 --> 01:02:02,220
I'll bring his things over

894
01:02:07,580 --> 01:02:08,860
I need to pee

895
01:02:08,860 --> 01:02:10,860
I know, go on, go inside

896
01:02:13,140 --> 01:02:15,500
Whose bike is this?

897
01:02:15,500 --> 01:02:17,660
That one... is a kid's

898
01:02:24,060 --> 01:02:25,580
Where's the kid?

899
01:02:25,580 --> 01:02:28,100
They left here

900
01:02:28,100 --> 01:02:29,300
Where did they go?

901
01:02:29,300 --> 01:02:30,100
Huh?

902
01:02:30,100 --> 01:02:31,780
Where'd they go?

903
01:02:32,220 --> 01:02:34,700
They moved to a new house. Do you not need to pee?

904
01:02:34,700 --> 01:02:35,420
Oh yes!

905
01:02:35,420 --> 01:02:36,700
Go on then

906
01:02:38,260 --> 01:02:40,420
Not that one, over here

907
01:02:41,420 --> 01:02:42,300
Okay...

908
01:02:43,620 --> 01:02:44,620
It's dark!

909
01:02:44,620 --> 01:02:45,940
I'm coming...

910
01:02:49,180 --> 01:02:51,260
It's scary in there

911
01:02:51,260 --> 01:02:53,260
Come on

912
01:02:54,620 --> 01:02:57,140
No, I don't need to go now

913
01:02:58,020 --> 01:02:59,140
Let me help

914
01:02:59,140 --> 01:03:04,060
No, but... I... I'll do it

915
01:03:05,020 --> 01:03:06,540
Are you feeling shy in front of me?

916
01:03:06,540 --> 01:03:07,420
No!

917
01:03:08,820 --> 01:03:10,340
Can you do it yourself?

918
01:03:30,940 --> 01:03:33,300
I'm drawing his mustache

919
01:03:42,220 --> 01:03:43,340
Yes?

920
01:03:44,060 --> 01:03:45,300
Come up dear

921
01:03:45,740 --> 01:03:47,060
Who was it?

922
01:03:47,780 --> 01:03:49,060
Uncle Emad

923
01:03:49,060 --> 01:03:52,980
If it's my dad, tell him Sadra's not here

924
01:03:52,980 --> 01:03:54,100
Why?

925
01:03:55,340 --> 01:03:57,540
Because I love my Mom

926
01:03:57,540 --> 01:03:58,620
Okay

927
01:04:12,300 --> 01:04:13,460
Rana?

928
01:04:13,700 --> 01:04:14,300
Hey

929
01:04:14,300 --> 01:04:16,060
The van isn't in the car park

930
01:04:16,060 --> 01:04:18,060
I parked it outside this morning

931
01:04:18,060 --> 01:04:19,660
Why outside?

932
01:04:19,660 --> 01:04:23,180
I didn't fancy moving it every ten minutes

933
01:04:23,180 --> 01:04:24,100
Hello!

934
01:04:24,100 --> 01:04:26,980
Helloooo, how are you kid?

935
01:04:26,980 --> 01:04:28,380
Where are the keys?

936
01:04:28,380 --> 01:04:29,900
Where you'd left them

937
01:04:30,980 --> 01:04:32,700
How are things with my favorite?

938
01:04:32,700 --> 01:04:34,580
Welcome to our house, all good?

939
01:04:35,020 --> 01:04:36,180
Welcome!

940
01:04:40,460 --> 01:04:42,460
Leave it where it is Emad

941
01:04:42,460 --> 01:04:43,260
I'll be right back

942
01:04:43,260 --> 01:04:45,260
Emad... Emad...

943
01:04:47,260 --> 01:04:50,300
Let's forget all that for tonight, just leave it

944
01:04:50,300 --> 01:04:53,500
I've made dinner, go and wash your hands and change

945
01:04:53,940 --> 01:04:55,220
Go on darling

946
01:05:06,300 --> 01:05:09,620
Ready for takeoff ladies and gentleman!

947
01:05:13,300 --> 01:05:15,020
Sadra?

948
01:05:15,420 --> 01:05:16,500
Yes!

949
01:05:16,500 --> 01:05:18,500
Emad it's ready, come before it gets cold

950
01:05:18,500 --> 01:05:19,700
Coming

951
01:05:19,980 --> 01:05:21,700
Let's go and wash those hands

952
01:05:21,700 --> 01:05:23,380
My hands are clean!

953
01:05:23,380 --> 01:05:24,700
Let's wash them again anyway

954
01:05:24,700 --> 01:05:27,940
Wow wow wow, look at this!

955
01:05:29,500 --> 01:05:31,540
Thanks so much

956
01:05:34,060 --> 01:05:35,060
Get your hands off it!

957
01:05:35,060 --> 01:05:39,180
<i>Rana, where are you?</i>

958
01:05:39,180 --> 01:05:41,820
<i>Sadra, come and eat!</i>

959
01:05:42,420 --> 01:05:44,860
Helllllo

960
01:05:44,860 --> 01:05:48,580
Hello trouble, have you two been having fun without me?

961
01:05:48,580 --> 01:05:48,940
We went shopping and then hung out

962
01:05:48,940 --> 01:05:50,460
Well done!
We went shopping and then hung out

963
01:05:50,460 --> 01:05:52,020
We went shopping and then hung out

964
01:05:52,020 --> 01:05:52,220
But we didn't find Spongebob
We went shopping and then hung out

965
01:05:52,220 --> 01:05:54,660
But we didn't find Spongebob

966
01:05:54,660 --> 01:05:56,660
Yes, unfortunately not

967
01:05:56,660 --> 01:06:01,300
<i>Don't worry Patrick, eventually a good day will come when you and I will find someone</i>

968
01:06:01,900 --> 01:06:05,380
<i>Look at this Spongebob!</i>

969
01:06:05,900 --> 01:06:09,500
Look at what Auntie Rana made, macaroni!

970
01:06:11,420 --> 01:06:12,300
More?

971
01:06:12,300 --> 01:06:13,620
No no, that's enough

972
01:06:14,020 --> 01:06:15,780
Okay, just let me know

973
01:06:15,780 --> 01:06:17,580
Thank you

974
01:06:19,740 --> 01:06:22,860
Wow, what macaroni!

975
01:06:22,860 --> 01:06:23,860
Bon appetit!

976
01:06:23,860 --> 01:06:25,820
Let's eat it all

977
01:06:26,100 --> 01:06:27,620
Look at what she's made

978
01:06:27,620 --> 01:06:28,820
Wow, I know!

979
01:06:30,220 --> 01:06:31,940
How was tonight's performance?

980
01:06:32,780 --> 01:06:34,180
Very...

981
01:06:34,620 --> 01:06:35,780
It wasn't great

982
01:06:36,020 --> 01:06:37,380
It was terrible

983
01:06:37,380 --> 01:06:38,700
You're lying

984
01:06:38,700 --> 01:06:40,980
That's how it is without you

985
01:06:42,780 --> 01:06:44,260
Did you find the credit card?

986
01:06:44,260 --> 01:06:45,620
No

987
01:06:47,900 --> 01:06:49,260
How did you go shopping?

988
01:06:49,620 --> 01:06:51,380
With the money you'd left

989
01:06:52,700 --> 01:06:54,260
What money?

990
01:06:54,260 --> 01:06:55,300
From the drawer

991
01:07:09,900 --> 01:07:11,940
Why aren't you eating? Do you not like it?

992
01:07:12,380 --> 01:07:14,780
Is it not tasty?

993
01:07:23,500 --> 01:07:25,260
Don't eat it

994
01:07:26,940 --> 01:07:28,100
What's up?

995
01:07:37,020 --> 01:07:39,860
That scumbag had left it behind the other night

996
01:08:06,420 --> 01:08:07,780
Sadra?

997
01:08:08,940 --> 01:08:10,780
I've got an idea

998
01:08:11,140 --> 01:08:12,260
Do you like pizza?

999
01:08:12,260 --> 01:08:13,220
Yep

1000
01:08:13,980 --> 01:08:15,500
Then let me call the pizzeria

1001
01:08:15,740 --> 01:08:17,660
Don't eat that, it's not good

1002
01:08:20,180 --> 01:08:22,020
Do you like fries?

1003
01:08:22,900 --> 01:08:24,700
And after that Ice Cream?

1004
01:08:35,620 --> 01:08:39,500
Hello? Mum? Mummy?

1005
01:08:41,580 --> 01:08:45,380
Hello? Uncle? Are you there?

1006
01:08:46,580 --> 01:08:50,340
<i>Muffled</i>

1007
01:08:51,820 --> 01:08:53,660
Aahoo darling, it's Babak

1008
01:08:55,820 --> 01:09:00,180
Aahoo... Aahoo...

1009
01:09:01,260 --> 01:09:03,380
Are you there?

1010
01:09:07,860 --> 01:09:13,260
Give me a call when you get home, I'll be up late

1011
01:09:16,460 --> 01:09:18,340
What are you doing?

1012
01:09:19,380 --> 01:09:20,820
Nothing

1013
01:09:21,340 --> 01:09:22,860
Come and sleep

1014
01:09:23,180 --> 01:09:24,700
You haven't slept for two nights

1015
01:09:25,060 --> 01:09:26,980
I can't fall asleep

1016
01:09:34,580 --> 01:09:36,980
Why did you open her letters?

1017
01:09:36,980 --> 01:09:38,420
It's their private belongings

1018
01:09:38,420 --> 01:09:40,300
I wanted to find out who the hell that scumbag is 

1019
01:09:40,300 --> 01:09:42,220
Let's say you find out how it was...

1020
01:09:43,060 --> 01:09:44,300
He'll say it was a mistake

1021
01:09:44,300 --> 01:09:46,060
He came inside by mistake?

1022
01:09:46,060 --> 01:09:48,500
He rang the bell and I opened the door

1023
01:09:48,500 --> 01:09:51,940
He must've thought it was that woman since I opened the door so easily

1024
01:09:51,940 --> 01:09:53,100
He came here by mistake?

1025
01:09:53,420 --> 01:09:55,540
Any when he realized his mistake?

1026
01:09:55,540 --> 01:09:57,260
Why not leave?

1027
01:09:57,260 --> 01:10:00,020
Because he saw the bathroom light on and a woman in there

1028
01:10:00,020 --> 01:10:01,060
How would he know that?

1029
01:10:01,060 --> 01:10:03,340
From your clothes on the sofa

1030
01:10:06,300 --> 01:10:09,100
If I'd just used the intercom...

1031
01:10:09,100 --> 01:10:11,620
If I'd just asked who it was...

1032
01:10:12,380 --> 01:10:14,300
None of this would have happened

1033
01:10:14,300 --> 01:10:17,420
Do you think it's that simple?

1034
01:10:18,020 --> 01:10:20,300
We can just tell all the neighbors about the intercom

1035
01:10:20,300 --> 01:10:22,020
Why are you talking about the neighbors?

1036
01:10:22,020 --> 01:10:23,700
They know what was going on in this house

1037
01:10:23,700 --> 01:10:25,660
If they didn't know, would that be fine?

1038
01:10:25,660 --> 01:10:27,660
What are you on about?

1039
01:10:45,580 --> 01:10:47,380
The van wasn't there

1040
01:10:47,380 --> 01:10:48,020
What?

1041
01:10:49,980 --> 01:10:50,860
Sorry

1042
01:10:52,380 --> 01:10:53,540
Where was it?

1043
01:10:54,140 --> 01:10:55,020
There

1044
01:10:55,020 --> 01:10:56,500
Sorry

1045
01:11:00,060 --> 01:11:01,260
Where did you leave it?

1046
01:11:01,260 --> 01:11:02,460
I left it there

1047
01:11:05,500 --> 01:11:06,180
Where?

1048
01:11:06,300 --> 01:11:08,860
Over there, where the Peugeot is

1049
01:11:15,820 --> 01:11:17,140
He's taken it

1050
01:11:18,500 --> 01:11:20,380
I have to find that asshole

1051
01:11:37,300 --> 01:11:39,060
Donkey!

1052
01:11:44,860 --> 01:11:46,740
Okay, don't speed

1053
01:12:12,500 --> 01:12:13,860
You'll freeze

1054
01:12:14,020 --> 01:12:14,940
It doesn't matter

1055
01:12:14,940 --> 01:12:17,140
What do you mean it doesn't matter? You'll get sick

1056
01:12:17,140 --> 01:12:18,260
Let's go to the public baths

1057
01:12:18,260 --> 01:12:20,660
No, I'll be quick. Just wait here

1058
01:12:30,140 --> 01:12:31,620
Hasanpoor, come here a sec

1059
01:12:31,620 --> 01:12:33,380
<i>Hello</i>

1060
01:12:40,100 --> 01:12:41,420
What can I do for you Sir?

1061
01:12:41,420 --> 01:12:42,300
Hi

1062
01:12:42,300 --> 01:12:44,300
How's it going?

1063
01:12:44,580 --> 01:12:46,700
Your dad was a traffic cop, right?

1064
01:12:46,700 --> 01:12:48,180
He's retired now, why?

1065
01:12:49,300 --> 01:12:51,260
A car hit my wife and drove off

1066
01:12:51,260 --> 01:12:52,300
I hope nothing serious Sir!

1067
01:12:52,300 --> 01:12:54,300
No, thank God

1068
01:12:55,300 --> 01:12:58,420
It was a van, if I give you the number plate...

1069
01:12:58,420 --> 01:13:02,380
If it's not too much trouble, could your Dad find the driver's address?

1070
01:13:02,380 --> 01:13:06,500
Sure, he has contacts in the office. Give me the license plate and he can find out

1071
01:13:06,500 --> 01:13:08,540
But I think you should report it

1072
01:13:08,540 --> 01:13:12,460
It wasn't anything major, I don't want to have to involve the police here

1073
01:13:12,460 --> 01:13:15,020
Okay, give me the registration and I'll call my Dad