Cheers..
Ready? Go..
Woo.. l'm on top of the world!!
Enough!
No, no, no, baby one more
one more one more please..
Harpreet! You passed!!
Bunty, you bum, congrats!
Come.. l'll get you a drink.
Sai.. Sai do something..
lt's your party dude
and the DJ is leaving.
What's happening?
Nonsense! Give him some more money.
He can't stop now,
the party is just warming up.
l just did that,
he wont take my money,
says it's past 2 am
and he has to wake up early.
Well it is past 2 am
- Wake up early.. why become a DJ?
Let me talk to him..
HP if he doesn't want money it
must be something serious. Leave it.
Hello Prince Charles,
not everyone is motivated by money.
So how else are they motivated?
Have you ever heard of the word
- Persuasion?
You can't get anywhere
with B.com 39 percent.
l keep telling him to apply
for an MBA, doesn't listen to me.
Life is not all fun and games no..
Ok grandpa
Wow, what did you do?
A little conversation, a little
persuasion, a little negotiation..
Done with your negotiation, can we
talk about something worthwhile?
Do you talk about anything else?
Not my work, l'm talking about yours.
l'm starting with my dad's law firm,
l don't care.. what about you?
Why? What about me?
He graduated, isn't that enough?
You won't take the MBA exam?
lf my grandfather was rich as your
father, l would have taken the exam..
So what will you do?
S-a-l-e-s
What.. you'll be a salesman?
Why? Aren't salesmen human beings?
They are.. of course they are..
but not very rich human beings.
My son, do you remember
Randy Bahadur, from arts?
He is a salesman..
He gets 40,000 rupees
without blinking.
Half of that is commission, which
he gets only after he gets an order.
And do you even know
what all a salesman has..
.. to go through to get an order?!
Why do you find fault
in everything l do?
Bloody negative bastard you are!
Dude he has a habit of lecturing
people.. come on, let's dance.
No, once and for all
let's get this straight,
these management exams
are not my cup of tea,
and my family doesn't have money
for a private MBA.
Sales is the only field where common
sense matters more than grades.
And now you'll say that
l don't even have common sense.
What'll l say..
Come.. come.. come.. Let's dance.
l don't want to.
Oh come on
l told you l don't want to.
l don't do things that
don't have power or money.
Just try it once. People will pay
just to watch you dance.
Good morning.. morning.. morning,
morning.. morning.. Good morning
Good morning.. morning..
Good morning
Good morning.. Good morning sir.
This is Harpreet Singh Bedi,
Harpreet Singh. Harpreet Singh..
Good morning sir l'm Harpreet
Singh Bedi.. Can l have a seat?
Good morning sir
l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi.. ca..ca
Morning gentlemen, morning ma'am.
l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi..
l can't tell you how much l admire
this unique company and.. Unique?
Good morning unique-
Come on son, come have
some sweet curd for luck.
Have all your certificates?
Especially your character
certificate? - Yes
Brushed up on your general knowledge?
- Yes
Have you memorized an essay?
lt's an interview, not an exam.
Have you memorized today's newspaper?
- Ya.
Put in money on your phone card?
- Ya
Emptied your bowels?
Oh man, on one side
you're feeding me sweet curd and
on the other.. ok l'm leaving.
lf you'd used your brains studying,
you wouldn't need sweet curd for luck
lf Einstein studied
with your snoring..
..he'd also have to eat sweet curd.
Had l taken to snoring again?
You weren't taking, you were giving
it to the world.. for free. Ok bye
At least straighten your turban.
What does the company make?
Don't know, will find out on the way
They make computers grandpa.
My grades are low not my lQ.
Oh lord, all is up to you now.
However he is, he is your son.
Watch over him.
Good morning AYS.. transferring sir
Good morning AYS.. line 2 sir
Excuse me ma'am..
Good morning AYS..
Transferring you to sales sir,
Nitin, enquiry! - He's inside
the Taj Mahal, l'll speak to them.
l may look it, but l am not..
You'll burn your fingers..
.. if you take a peek
at other people's clients or wives.
Everyone's suspicious here!
l'm going to leave this place.
l've heard it for 3 years.
Those who do things
don't talk about it.
Hello.. l haven't received a single
call since morning. l am not fasting.
Could you hold sir? What can l do
if your territory's dead?
When you get your territory,
you don't say anything.
lf you say something
in the Taj Mahal, you hear an echo.
This month's commission is gone.
l had narrowed in on an LCD..
wife will be upset.
Just try to get back home
on time everyday, she'll be happy.
Who troubles you more,
your motorcycle or your wife?
Connecting sir
Go pick up, it's your client.
He's been trying you for four days.
Call them once in a while,
clients don't die after sale.
Even the clients wonder, what
happens to a salesman after a sale?
Excuse me ma'am
- At Your Service good morning
Sir please try and reboot.
No Mr. Puri is not in lndia..
Chotelal, have you served
Mr. Puri his coffee?
He has had four since morning.
Nitin is inside
with the sales figures.
lt's a wonder
he doesn't want a drink instead.
What are you looking at?
Nothing
You want to get killed?!
Hello.. Can l help you?
Oh l'm sorry ma'am, l'm Harpreet
Singh Bedi, for the sales interview
One minute..
Sir a call for you on line two.
You should have told me earlier.
You looked busy
so l did not want to disturb.
Afraid of disturbing people..
How will you become a salesman?
Harpreet Singh?
- Yeah.. l mean Yes
Nitin sir has called you
to the conference room.
Where is the conference room please?
Up, in the sky. Follow me
Hello sir, l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi,
uh-it's an honour to be
in this fantastic company-
Why, what is so fantastic
about this company?
Sales sir,
your sales team's reputation is..
Good.. but it can be better.
1 2th 35 percent.. B.com 39 percent
no experience nothing,
'put together college magazine'
You want to be a salesman?
- Yes Sir..
Ok, sell yourself, come on.
Sir, uh..
l think l am a hard worker and-
You think, or you are..
l mean l-l am sir.. and l want to
learn everything about products,
markets, customer relations and
- Enough! Enough!
Do you know selling?
- Uh, of course sir
Sell this pencil to me,
for 1 00 rupees.
Sir this eraser
l took it off, but you convince me
that it's still there.
Sir, how can l convince you
if it's not there?
lf you can't sell,
how can we give you a job?
Apply elsewhere.
Hello sir, l'm Harpreet Singh
from Singh Pencils,
this is our new pencil, HS-1 01 6
Sorry we have already stocked up
pencils for the year
No problem sir, let me give you
a quick two-minute demo.
Why watch a demo of a pencil
with no eraser?
This is not a pencil
without an eraser.
lt's a pencil
with a detachable eraser.
Come up with something new!
Sir, the lead on this pencil
is unbreakable.
Sir, if you apply that much pressure,
anything will break.
But see, this pencil this can be
sharpened easily too.
Telling lies doesn't make a sale.
But perfume can make a sale.
Sir, this eraser sir, it is
a specially imported perfumed eraser.
Should we put
the pencil up our noses?
No sir, in the AC vent.. See?
There are many other uses for this.
lt's an ear bud for cleaning ears.
A Tooth pick for cleaning teeth.
Hair.. l mean comb.
Reboot your mobile.
You can make a 3 pin socket
into a pin socket.
ln case, you're still not satisfied,
you can kill time with it.
Like you are..
What's going on?
- Sir
Puri sir
Hello sir
Sir, those sales interviews.
Nothing special sir.
Take him
- Sir?
You did not give up, l like that
Thank you, sir
- Okay you can go now
Your mark sheets
He failed a year, sir!
Not failed exactly,
fell short on attendance.
Sales' doesn't run on mark sheets,
it runs on balance sheets.
Selling a two rupee
pencil like a Mercedes..
He must be something.
Thank you sir,
l-l won't disappoint you
Don't.
1 5,000.. per month.. no medical,
no gratuity, no provident fund..
six months training, no commitment
from our side.. yes, or no-
Yes!
Everyone, this is..
uh, Singh.. sales trainee
Welcome to wonderland
- Disneyland
Koena
- Sexy
His mother's name!
- Rajess
Rumaan, double A
- Narayan
Tanmay
- Taxi
Bastard.. - Chotelal give the new kid
the product brochure, rate list, etc.
Tomorrow is Sunday,
memorize everything. - Yes sir
Now go settle down.. over there..
Go on
- Yes sir
This way..
Okay Monday morning's meeting,
everyone's gonna get it.
So everyone please keep
your sales figures ready.
We still have eight months
to go and we know..
One who sells the most will be
the salesman of the year,
will receive a commission
of 5 lakh and a Goa vacation
And you'll get a London vacation,
after adding up everyone's sales.
l heard that..
- Where are you going this year boss?
We beat around in the sun
and he gets a London trip.
You know, you guys need to improve..
personal attack is
a below the belt game.
Let us be professional here, okay?
Yesterday, he coined a new slogan
"those who sell.. come by,
and those who don't.. goodbye"
Shut up, cup-plate.
Sit down
Those who sell.. come by
And those who don't.. goodbye.
What does that mean?
That's what happens in sales. Those
who can't perform they have to go.
Where will he go?
He can go anywhere,
join another company if he likes.
What if that company turns out
to be the same?
Of course, it'll be the same.
Today's companies have
become so unethical.
Professional.. Professional grandpa.
Not like in your times,
go to office everyday,
sign in, eat lunch and come home.
As if we didn't work all our lives,
companies ran by themselves?
l am not talking about you..
you believe work is worship.
These professionals..
what does work mean to them?
Nothing, just work.
How does it matter? As long as
my grandson worships his work.
Rest, leave it to god.
Yes.
Hold him, hold the Sardar
Oh.. No no please,
let go of me Sardar..
He failed.
Mr. lnamdar. Honest man.
He got his due!
Meaning?
- Nitin sir wants to see you.
They want 56 computers
So, put in a quote for 1 6..
we'll see.
Yes sir
Read it all? All set?
- Of course
Anyone want to volunteer
for his field induction?
Haven't been on a field visit
in along time,
let's see what's going
on in whose territory.
Yeah! As if a manager becomes
a salesman again..
..by riding a motorcycle.
The Wife must have taken the car..
Letterheads.. visiting cards.
1 0 in pocket, 1 0 in wallet.
20 in bag.
Let's go.
350 huh?
Now that's a motorcycle, sir.
Zip it up.
You are wearing it the wrong way sir.
Does your dad run a laundry?
By evening the shirt will
get dirtier than your tongue.
From this signal to the next
is your territory.
No other AYS sales executive will
venture into the offices here.
Any inquiries from here,
Koena will let you know..
But this is a residential area, sir!
Where will l find an office here?
Even if you did, what would you do?
Sell pencils?
Sign in.
What are you doing?
Filling in our names
and our company's name.
You want to become a salesman?
First rule of the field,
never write your or your company's
correct details anywhere.
Why?
- Put an ad in the paper instead!
No one looks at the register
in the company.
But a competing salesman
always scans..
.. the entries for names of fools,
like you.
Are all these names incorrect then?
Of course! The salesmen names are
incorrect, like this James Bond.
He is from Monovo. He is marking his
territory here. He is teasing us..
He thinks he's already got the order.
So then?
l have a trump card.
Let me see, if l can use it now.
Mr. Pandey!
Sir! lt's been a while..
Thanks!
What news?
The guy from Monovo has been
hovering here since morning.
Saw him photocopying some documents
in a hurry.
Server quotation
Thanks.
Sorry boss
What is it?
Nothing boss, he's crazy.
Oh look, your floor!
Boss..
Ha! He got off on the wrong floor.
New kid from Wintel.
By the time he reaches
the client he'll grow up.
Ok sir.. yeah.. 6.30? Ok sir.
l'll just convey it to him.
Have a nice day.
Yes?
Are you going to say something
or keep smiling like a fool?
How are you?
- Sharma sir is busy.
Couldn't l have come to meet you?
You wouldn't meet your
wife without a reason.
First become the wife,
then we'll see.
Sit down, let me see, idiot.
ls she your girl friend?
l am not that desperate.
What if she'd taken offense?
You were taking a big risk, sir!
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
At least you're a salesman.
Ok.. go ahead!
ldiot.
Mr. Sharma's Australia trip canceled.
Bonuses announced.
Mr. Mavalankar promoted. Ha!
My next trump card.
You go in first. He's in bad a mood.
- Why?
Because Mavalankar has
been promoted. Go in!
Good morning sir, l am
Harpreet Singh, this is my colleague-
Nitin, how are you?
Now that you're a sales manager,
we don't exist anymore?
No sir, nothing like that. Tanmay
must be dropping by now and then!
You must be busy planning
your Australia trip?
No l canceled it.
There's a lot of work in office.
l thought this company
has other people as well?
Yes l have heard that there are,
but till date l haven't seen any..
Anyway, tell me more.. - Tanmay
must have mailed you the quotation?
ls that a quotation?
This.. you people mail anything.
He is a kid.
Still learning the ropes.
So what range are you looking at?
l will send you a fresh one.
Ok, l'll let you know.
By the way the Monovo
people were saying that..
.. Mr. Mavalankar asked
to keep it less than 1 0 lakh
Mavalankar? What has he
got to do with this quote?
This is not even his department!
No sir they said that
he has been promoted,
and now heads
the purchase department.
One minute. Do me a favour!
Send in a new quote of 1 0 lakh,
1 0 thousand.
Throw in a year of free service
and warranty.
Then let's see who gives,
l mean, who gets the order?
Right sir
But l must say these Monovo
people are very unprofessional,
l never expected this from them.
Now what can l say sir!
We have a policy of not
talking about Competition
Yes l know, sorry you?
Hello sir l'm.. - My cousin sir,
l was dropping him off to college.
You're too good boss
Weren't you getting too familiar
with Tanmay's client?
No, no sir,
l was introducing myself.
Started already? Sales freak!
Good good.
But sir, how did you
know of the Monovo plan?
Did you skip high school classes
as well? Didn't they teach you..
.. necessity is
the mother of invention!
But how did know
the exact quotation?
l read it! How else would l know?
On that notice board?
Sharma!
But Mr. Sharma didn't
show us any quotation
No one shows you a quotation kid!
You have to see it.
That's what he was reading!
You can read upside down too?
You know what they call a salesman
who can't read upside down?
What?
A Blind salesman.
lf Jogeshwari is
on the Goregaon link road then,
it is in Jogeshwari. lsn't it?
No it's not.
Everyone knows it's in Goregaon.
He is my prospect Mr.,
and l have already spoken to him.
Madam, when you'd called l was there.
Besides, l've already spoken
with Nitin.
Nitin!
Oh hello.. got your target?
No, where do you get it from?
lt falls on your head.
Look l am warning you,
if you even look at my clients,
l'll kill you.
Hello
- Put Giri on.
Who? - lt's Koena,
who else would call you here.
Pass the phone to Giri.
- Giri who?
Get up, look over the partition.
The Service manager.
Hurry up now,
his client is getting impatient.
Hi
What? - How much longer?
Your client's been waiting an hour.
l don't know.
Give me an estimate? Or will you
make him wait till evening?
Told you, l don't know. lt's
a technical problem, will take time.
What's the problem? - The Monitor
is not showing anything.
Needs a new mother board.
Why don't you open it
and take a look Giri sir?
Maybe it can be fixed.
Open it. Open it.
Whack it in!
Not that! The third one!
ls it in? Reboot.
lt's working.
lt was a loose connection.
Pack it up.
Dial Koena, number 9
Tell the client his mother board
was fried-Rs. 5000. Less?
lt's his fault, he didn't use a UPS.
That's another Rs. 3,250.
Will take a week to fix it all.
lf you want a client's blood
why don't you ask him?
Why are you asking for money?
Experience!
He's the one getting
a week's experience.
lf l fixed your computer in 5 minutes
would you pay me 1 0,000?
Should l tell Nitin sir?
Go tell him! How do you think
his London trip is funded?
From here. Now leave me alone.
Chotelal yesterday's CD..
where is it?
lt's here. Sir please don't leave it
lying around.
You watched it last night?
No, no, l left.
You watched "The wild Queen"?
Go get me a cup of tea.
Should l pack this?
What.. leave it. Get me tea first.
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
At least l'm a salesman.
What's going on?
l have an announcement.
Jai Hind Motors is in!
Party time in the evening,
booze is on the company,
Women are not, so bring your own
Yes, yeah, l'm calling from office.
Will l be calling you
from college again?
Please eat dinner, l'll be late.
l have an office get-together.
Oh! We can discuss fixing
the flush later. Ok, bye.
Sorry Mr. Mishra..
- What.. ?
You are Chotelal Mishra?
lt's on the intercom list
What's this.. the man who failed
is the most educated.
Chotelal, what are you doing?
lt's spilling.
Don't worry madam. Everyone
in a line please. l'll serve you
Move it Grandpa,
move it or l'll put in a quotation.
Nitin? Have you spoken
to Mr. Puri about me?
Oh shit..
Please Nitin,
the office manager's position..
..has been open for a longtime.
They will get someone eventually..
.. and anyways, l have been
looking over the work.
Hope you've been looking out
for the phone calls?
The credit card collector has been
trying to get to you for two months.
Has he reached you yet?
So attendance shortage, how are you?
l'm good sir, thank you,
how are you
How ambitious are you exactly?
Do you think you can
take over his job?
No sir
You think l would have fired him
if you said yes?
No, no sir
l like you,
you didn't get emotional.
You have a quality to go up,
but you also have a quality
to go down.
Eventually the quality that
wins will define your life.
So where you want to go?
Up or down?
Up sir
To climb up, you'll have to walk
over many people..
.. and they will bite you hard.
And tomorrow if you're late for work,
your pay will be cut. Welcome to AYS!
Booo!
Shit man! They say after 70,
a man's age restarts from zero.
Dude, close your eyes.
One minute..
l don't have two minutes..
don't you understand!
l waited for you for three hours,
you don't have 2 minutes for me
Ok fine, it's your carpet.
Don't blame me later.
New pinch!
What's this?
Our brand new scooter
- What?
Yes.. one with a button start.
No more kicking or pushing,
just gently press the button
and fly like a bird.
You want to ride a scooter
at this age?
Why should l ride it?
l'll sit behind like a prime
minister. You'll drive right?
Me?
- Yes
Ride a scooter?
- What's the problem?
lt's your favorite colour too.
Maroon.
Grandpa l have told you earlier,
jokes after 9:30 am only!
lt's no joke! l put my life's
savings into buying it.
But l never asked for a scooter.
You go finish your toilet, and
then we'll talk.. more comfortably
What comfortably?
You put your entire savings
into buying me a scooter..
.. without telling me!
How much advance did you pay?
The scooter is outside.
- You paid the entire amount?
You don't get a scooter
for half the price!
Come on sardar, check it out.
Bloody hell.
Why are you being so difficult?
Can't gifts given with love,
be received with love?
Did l ask you for it? - lt's very
modern. Ride it once and see.
Did l ask you for it?
Have l only given you things when you
asked for them? Who are you to ask?!
Go to hell!
Target Rs.6,00,000.
25000/-. lf 1 computer
is for Rs. 25000/-
and 24 PCs quarterly, means 24
computers in three months, monthly,
You have 8 PCs to sell and it's
already the 20th of this month.
But l started last week on the 1 4th
and l got my target today..
.. so ideally my month starts today?
Really? You're learning fast!
Just do what you're told boss,
You're a trainee not
a Managing Director.
Right sir
- That's the spirit
Listen..
On your way drop this quotation off
to Mr. Chaudhary
at National Chemicals.
National Chemicals is
in the wrong direction.
So, did we hire you
to go in the right direction!
Best of luck
for your first client visit.
Stop by a temple for blessings.
Emotions are under control,
My scooter has petrol.
That's all l need.
Good morning sir
Fine.. and the rest?
The rest sir, if you have
any further requirements,
let me know. l'll arrange it.
What's there to arrange?
l'll give you an address,
have it sent there.
Sure sir, do you have another branch?
That's a good one.
l do, my sister's house.
How much has been decided?
Whatever is in the quotation.
Plus taxes.
Government gets taxes.
What do we get?
You get the machines sir..
Nice sense of humour you have huh?
1 0 percent ok?
Sir please
why are you pulling my leg?
No l am not.. are you?
Sir, please don't embarrass me sir
Your attitude is very unprofessional.
Work will be difficult.. for you.
Sir please speak to Nitin directly.
l am leaving.
Leaving without anything?
On an empty stomach?
Some tea or coffee. Sardarji?
..connecting sir At your service,
Good afternoon..
l will get it sent across.
- Where is Mr. Nitin?
Right.. sir, Back so quick.
ls it raining outside?
Where is Mr. Nitin?
lnside the Taj Mahal.
He's already had 4 cold drinks,
waiting for you.
These days
there's a lot of Global warming.
Good afternoon sir
Hello sir
What happened at NCC?
What didn't happen?
Something is terribly wrong there.
Why? What happened?
Sir, he asked for a bribe
and to my face.
What are you saying?
- l swear!
So what was your reply?
l didn't say anything at the time,
l carefully tried to explain it.
But on my way out
l saw a complaint box,
l wrote down all the details
and dropped it in,
properly on our company letterhead.
Signature, date.. everything.
Here's a copy.
What happened sir?
Aren't you being over smart?
Why, what happened?
You think without authorization
you can use the company letterhead..
.. and make false allegations
against our clients?
And get away it? Sir it's a clear
case of company letterhead forgery.
One second boss.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you place allegations
against the General Manager of NCC?
You are barely born
and already trying to fly high?
Sir it was your decision
in the interview. - Shut up Nitin
We can charge him
with fraud to begin with..
Let's consult the lawyers,
there'll be many more charges.
Sir please tell him
to mind his language sir
You bastard.. You think you can go
and spoil our relations with clients,
and nothing will happen to you.
How dare you speak to our clients
in such a way?
You haven't sold one thing yet, but
you talk as if you've sold millions.
l'll slap you so hard,
you won't know what hit you.
Quietly complete your training period
and get out of here.
One mistake.. One more mistake
and l will throw you out..
Bloody bastard..
Get out!!
Did you have to be so righteous?
You should have quietly gone back
to work, and let them resolve it.
Did you have to become a "hero"?
Did someone tell me when l started,
that the company was corrupt
and l'd have to do all this.
Every company is like this, and
you have to do this in every company.
This is common sense
- Leave this job.
Leave and do what? l haven't even
finished one month yet.
lt'll look bad on my resume.
Hello.. yes l am in office.
No, you eat dinner, uh,
l have another get together.
l won't ride the scooter drunk.
You've bought me a MlG 29
it might end up crashing!
Ok bye
To top it off, this scooter
has tapped into his savings.
Why don't you join a call center?
They'll employ anyone.
l didn't mean it like that!
You will need a relieving certificate
from the previous employer.
Tell them it's your first job.
What have l done?
Why should l lie to anyone?
Should l go beat up Mr. Puri?
That's all that's needed.
You should have made at least
one sale in all these days..
How long has it been
since you joined the job?
Listen to me.. don't worry,
go to office tomorrow.
Your Puri will have
forgotten everything.
Who remembers a trainee
in such a big company
Exactly
- Right?
Watch me, l'll leave
for my field-rounds early tomorrow.
Notice! What happened? Trouble?
Did you have a fight with Nitin?
What happened bro?
What happened?
- They're praising you
A lot
- Read it out to him
"Mr. Harpreet Singh is henceforth
stopped from visiting any clients..
He will only make cold calls
from his desk..
.. and pass on leads to other
colleagues.. " - Colleagues
They have stopped you
from entering the field.
Your targets have been thrown away.
Not just targets,
your entire career is over.
Ok people, sales target meeting,
in the conference room.
Oh man what now?
There are limits to targets.
Let's go drop our pants
and stand in a row.
Don't know what's going to happen?
Boss, not you
What will you do if you came?
Yours have already been dropped!
What did you do boss?
Beat up a client?
Bloody idiot!! You'll get us killed,
which idiot hired you?
You call my clients,
l'll beat the crap out of you.
You look so normal on the outside,
but on the inside you're completely
mad. Why don't you get admitted?
Oh anti-corruption branch,
from now on your territory is mine..
.. lf you have any
leads give them to me.
l'd give them to you,
if there were any.
Look at this idiots' attitude.
Why don't you shut up.
Because of you all our targets have
been doubled. Watch what you say.
Don't come near me. l'll kill you.
No use talking to him. ldiot.
What are you doing?
The Ramayan is on.
Ramayan has been on for ten years
now. Has anyone learned anything?
How many times will you watch
the same thing over and over?
You're letting things get to you.
This job has stressed you out.
Don't work too hard.
You are a hard worker anyway.
Do your co-workers realize this?
Jobs today are too stressful.
They make good men into coconuts.
Hello Harpreet
- Good morning
Hey Harpreet..
What happened?
Hello
- Good morning ma'am,
l'm calling from
"At your Service computers",
we sell and support all kinds
of PCs and also undertake..
Please don't bother me!
- No problem ma'am, l-l'll try later.
Hello - Good morning sir, l'm calling
from At your Service Computers..
Call later!
No-no problem sir, l'll try later.
Somebody's just died.. will you
let people die in peace at least?!
Oh! l'm extremely sorry sir,
l'll try you later. Yes sir
What is it?!
Why do you keep calling?
uh hello.. sir
- Please don't irritate me!
Hello.. Sir am l speaking to Jai hind
Joshi. - What number have you dialed?
Give me your business card?
All of them. Nitin wants them.
You are not going on field,
we'll cut them and give them to taxi.
Nitin said so.
This seat is cursed..
Hello sir, A 21 inch monitor
is perfect for entertainment.
ok see you, bye
Can you drop me to the station
my husband isn't coming.
l had an inquiry from your territory,
for 2 PCs
Give it to Rajesh,
l have to give it to him anyway.
lf you don't give him one or two
you won't catch malaria.
Quietly go get an order.
Tell them after a couple of days.
lf you don't get an order,
you'll get into trouble;
Get an order,
and get into trouble.. or not.
Ok.. Don't take it.
My husband's here, Ok bye
So what l'm saying is ma'am that, the
kind of technical expertise we have,
the kind of experience we have,
and the kind of service we give,
we don't really have any competition.
But your company is so big,
so your prices..
Why? Just because the company
is big that doesn't mean,
the prices should be high.
They have to be based
on the customer's pocket,
not the company's.
And that's exactly what we do!
And you want a bet..
That is really impressive..
but.. ummm..
Discount.. ?
Ma'am at least place an order first.
Pentium processor
with this graphic card..
Ma'am l'm going to give you
the best price.. - Okay
Ma'am we.. uh, we don't sell Pc's
with this graphic card.
But no problem,
l'll check with the office.
Boss are you a trainee or something?
No.. but everyone has a boss.
l am sure you do too?
No.
He doesn't even know what kind
of product he has, forget it,
those who can't do anything,
become salesmen.
Okay, please find out
from somewhere else.
From where.. ?
- l don't know ma'am
Look.. l'm really sorry..
For the last two days we're
meeting salesmen after salesmen..
lt's okay
- at least find out for us..
What?
Which company assembles this
configuration with this graphic card?
Ma'am l told you, l don't know.
Noodles?
- Huh?
Maggi noodles.. come eat..
please eat.. it's ready..
please eat.
Please join us.
Ayesha, come eat. Come on
They are plain glasses.
We started a new business
but no one takes us seriously.
Neither parents,
nor clients nor salesmen.
l'll uh.. find out
about your graphic cards
Hello
Yes, how can l help?
Sir, do you keep this graphic card?
HD 4350.. keep them, l sell them.
What's the Price?
- Here it is.
What's the price?
- Rs. 4,400
And for two?
Why don't you take it for Rs. 8,000..
..l'll throw in the condiments
for free.
Can't it be less?
That is the wholesale rate.
How much will you reduce?
With rest of the parts,
you'll have a new PC for Rs. 20,000,
and you'll at least
sell it for Rs. 30,000?
One can assemble a PC
with this card for Rs. 20,000?
Then? We make one for Rs. 25,000..
want one?
But companies don't sell it
to the customers
for less than 35-40,000 rupees.
lf it's made for so little,
why sell it for so much?
The thing is, the word customer
has "mer" (die) in it.
Forgive me lord Ganesh.
See, if l had an A/C room, a big
store, l would also sell it for more.
This is quite a con!
You're buying two,
who are you conning?
No, l am not conning anyone.
Can l keep this price-list?
l want it for a client.
Keep it. l was going
to recycle it anyway.
And listen, get your
stuff today or tomorrow.
Here the world changes like this..
like this.. like this.
There's no guarantee of anything.
l know..
Ok.. bye.. that, that will cost you
Rs. 350, do you want it?
Hello, Miss Sherena please..
Hi it's me.. Uh, Harpreet..
You asked me to find
out about the PC's.
How are you? Good. We'll supply it
Oh.. okay..
Uh.. Rs. 27,500 per PC
with one year guarantee
Are you sure? ls there a sale on?
No, uh, because this
is your first order.
Ok.. Who should l make the cheque
out to?.. That.. uh- hello
Hello.. ?
Rocket..
Rocket Sales Corporation
Mr. Lalwani?
l was about to close.
Do you want the card?
Yes, 2 graphic cards, and everything
that goes in for 2 PCs.
Pack everything.
Who are you conning?
You. l'll take it on credit.
Payment next week.
Do you see that
- "Cash today, credit tomorrow"
When you started your business,
how much money did you have?
Someone must have trusted
you and given you credit.
Yes, that was a relative.
So consider me your relative too
and keep my scooter as a guarantee.
lt's more valuable
than this purchase.
What kind of business
deal are you making?
Will you give it to me?
Ok go ahead. As it is, l've never
seen a Sardar cheat someone, take it.
But when you get
what you want don't forget me,
you've made me your relative.
lf l forget everything, l wont
forget this Mr. Lalwani.. thanks
What are you doing
in office at this hour?
You can barely bring
in orders during the day,
what will happen in the night?
l have some work for me..
l mean you..
You've managed to mess up
work with this company,
now what work do you have?
There's.. Uh.. there's an order
Aren't you supposed
to pass your orders to others?
No, l'm not giving
this order to anyone.
Who is the client?
- A friend of mine.
You mean it's a personal order,
not the company's?
Profit is also personal.
What you seem, you are not.
What you are, l don't know.
Do you have petrol in your scooter?
- Why?
l don't waste fuel on friend's work.
lt's a rule, from my engineering
college days. Shall we leave?
Yes
- let's go
What?
Nothing.
ls all this yours or AYS's?
Did l ask you if the order
was yours or AYS's
See, for 50 years,
government has been encouraging us..
Become entrepreneurs,
become entrepreneurs.
Shouldn't we do something or
will the government do everything?
Did you ever apply
for a government job?
No why?
Nothing, the country was spared.
Does Puri know?
No boss, keep it quiet. Why drop
an ant in an elephant's trunk?
What if he finds out?
Who'll tell him, you?
This is the configuration..
will you get it ready by 1 0am?
Why 1 0 am? lt'll be ready by 8 am
When do you sleep?
ln office!
Any advance cash?
No, it's ok.
Thanks. Shall l leave?
See you.
Oh, l forgot.. the software.
Were you born today?
When there's a free copy, why buy it
legally? PC will become expensive..
l'll reduce my profit.
But l won't reduce my fees..
lnstead of fees,
l'll share the profit with you.. ok?
l don't mind,
but if you use legal software..
.. and give me profit sharing,
what will you earn? Peanuts?
lt's okay
What?
All okay ma'am?
We'll know in time.
l hope your service etc..
See our service.
Well, l hope
l don't have to see it..
Of course.. any problems call me,
on my mobile phone..
No need to call my office..
Why? ls it unavailable?
Uh, no. And another thing
Yes?
This was my first order.
So it's not that 'those who don't
know anything become salesmen'.
Right
- Right
Well, thanks
Well you're most welcome
Hurry up.. dinosaurs are
jumping around in my stomach..
l'm coming..
l'm very hungry dadaji,
what's for dinner?
Lentils and spicy fried potatoes .
Oh forget the lentils, let's order
a pizza.. what do you say?
What's going on?
Have you received a big order?
Don't ask, just tell me..
you want it or not?
Yeah sure treat me,
But first let's thank the lord,
you've barely begun
and you are successful.
Thank you, God.
My child has worked diligently..
.. and you have blessed him
with success.
So please guide him
through a righteous path..
..and protect him from evil.
Let his mind be free from deceit
and let his head be held high.
"l belong to God,
and God is victorious"
Call for pizza.
No, let's have the lentils instead.
Why? What's happened now?
No let's have the lentils.
What are you doing..
l'm "downloading"
l'm confessing everything to Puri.
Whatever money l get,
l will return it to him.
And l will clear your payment
in time.
What?! What's gotten
into you this morning?
Calm down and let me explain.
lf you mention me,
l'll deny everything.
ls Mr. Puri free?
He has lunch at the club.
Where's the club?
Our offer is value proposition.
See the price, see the quality
and make a decision.
Drink? 2 More please..
come come..
Sit.
- Sorry sir,
l'll come back later.
Sit.. sit.. Please sit.
Remember him? Your old friend?
Say hello.
Hello
- Hello.
How are your..
.. complaints etc.?
Sir, l'll come back later.
- No, sit.. sit..
We were just praising you.
Sit.. sit.
Do you know this man?
Oh! of course you know..
but you must have thought..
ls this the company's
most idiotic employee?
No he is. He's an idiot.
Zero! Total zero!
But even a zero has value.. we were
talking about value. Ask how? Simple.
Just like the value of zero,
he also has value.
ldiot, doesn't have a basic brain.
Doesn't know how to talk, nor does
he understand things. A donkey, zero!
But even a zero can be useful sir,
if the person who uses
it understands it's value.
Put it in the right place,
and you can keep putting
it till it becomes of use.
Zero is quite amazing.
lt was invented in lndia!
Where else?
Today this idiot,
this zero was helpful..
.. to my company more than
the salesmen.. ask me how?
Him?
lt's a fact sir, a fact. You see,
this donkey misbehaved with you.
But he is a donkey,
he will kick you.
But because of his "donkey ness",
l found what an opportunity.
Like a 9/1 1 attack on the company.
l decreased the sales commissions,
doubled the targets.
And you wont believe it,
l'm sitting on the most profitable
quarter of my career.
Accountants are in a haze.
And all this
because of this big zero.
But what happened
with you was very wrong..
.. we'll ask him
to beg for forgiveness.
Come on say sorry to sir.
Say sorry sir, l won't do it again.
Shall l make him do a hand stand?
- please..
Should he.
Sorry
Forgive him. He is a small man.
Not our level.
So when should we expect
clearance on our order?
lt has gone to the higher ups.
By tomorrow you'll get it.
Just give us good service.
Aren't we giving you
good service now?
Let's go confront him.
You did your best, now just quit.
Right, you are not meant
to be a salesman. Leave it.
l'll leave it, but wherever l go
l'll be the same.
Was it your mistake?
lt's the company's fault.
And if the next company is the same?
And the next one?
- Meaning?
Meaning l always quit boss.
You two studied hard
night after night..
..while l played cricket, know why?
Because l'd failed on the inside
from the beginning.
That's why whatever numbers
l earned were enough.
Passing MBA exams is one thing,
l failed the moment
l thought of taking them.
l was kidding..
No listen.. do you know
why Puri insults me over and over?
Because l let him, because
l'm satisfied that l have a job.
You know what l just realized,
it's not his fault,
it's mine because l'm taking it.
- You're nice..
Nice! Nothing happens
with being nice. Mice are nice.
l had to pay the price
for being nice.
The people who are not
so nice should pay the price.
Have a seat.. have a seat
lf like every time,
l live with being nice,
it'll be the biggest
mistake of my life.
l'm going to teach
that Puri a lesson.
Forget it,
you were going to quit right?
l was.. but now l won't let go.
l wont let go off the job..
l was interviewed and selected.
l'm suitable for this job.
l haven't done anything wrong.
But if the whole company is wrong,
then..
Company is wrong
but company will be right.
l won't do wrong
and l won't leave this job.
So what will you do?
l don't know..
but whatever l do,
for the rest of his life,
Puri won't call anyone a zero.
Whatever happened till
today was a mistake.
But l'll make that mistake big,
so big, that AYS will look
like a mistake in front of it.
Calm down,
your career's just started.
Why are you taking such a risk?
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
at least l'm a salesman.
You should use the key, Sakku..
Where were you since yesterday?
Did Puri fire you?
No, he offered me beer.
Oh come on, Puri is the king..
.. in the computer assembly business
for 20 years.
He has 2,500 clients in his pocket.
He's so shrewd, branded
companies steer clear of him,
and you want to compete with him?
There's a big difference
in making a computer for a friend
and starting a company.
You haven't hatched out
of the egg yet
and you want to be a roast chicken?
What do you know about making a PC?
You know, that's enough.
Fifty-fifty, every order,
every month
Lift. Lift.
Congrats.. put a sexy girl's photo
on that, it'll attract clients..
Sorry
These are A4 sheets, right?
What's their price?
Why?
How much does
the printer cartridge cost?
You want one?
l'll give them to you..
How many?
Also the electricity, we are
the only ones using it.. right?
How much will all of this be?
Whatever it is, Puri will pay.
What is it to you?
All this, printer paper
electricity phone calls ink,
l'll return their cost to Puri
one day, with bank interest.
Why? He wants to ruin your career
and you're looking out for him!
Not him, l'm looking out for us..
There has to be some difference..
..between AYS and
Rocket Sales Corporation.
Yes l can see the difference..
while he's making a profit,
on our first day,
we're talking about losses.
.Make some room..
these are old files..
There's a lot of space on your desk..
Bablu, get more.
Everyone! Please meet Mr. Shah,
our new office manager..
Mr. Shah, this is the sales team,
that is customer support,
and over there accounts..
Narayan
- Hello.. Hello
Nitin.. Nitin.. one minute.
This manager, meaning new..
Yes, so?
Ohh.. happens.. let it go.
But you said,
Puri sir was giving me..
So? lf someday that "cup-plate"
wants to be the MD..
..will we make him one?
There is a system! Not everyone
is suited for every post.
There's ability.. - But Nitin,
l am handling all the work,
and that ability..
ls that ability? The ability
that you have, is it less?
You should stay
where we can see you looking pretty.
You increase sales by 2-4%
when clients come in.
Now, l'm a little busy.. ok?
Koena..
One minute
- What?
No, not here
- What is it?
The next time l'll slap you,
there are times for pranks.
l am not joking
- Neither am l.. now leave.
What's your problem?
Why don't you do your work,
instead of talking nonsense.
Will you be our office
manager Koena? Join us.
Join what? First get out of here..
have you lost your brains.
Haven't you had enough of a beating,
that now you're looking for more?!
lf anyone inside hears of this,
they'll make mince meat out of you
and distribute it to
all the companies.
Will you join us? Yes or no?
Why are you doing this?
Because, we work in an office
where no one sees our potential.
And things that are the most useless,
things that are most unrelated,
they notice the most.
And we have become
only one thing- me a joker Sardar..
..and you an "item girl".
Have you lost your mind?
You told Koena everything! - Relax
Why relax?!
She will tell Puri everything,
then we'll be kicked out and then we
can relax for the rest of our lives.
No she wont, she's not the type.
Why won't she talk?
How do you know how people are?
ln this company,
everyone is a master of politics.
They'll sell your underwear..
..and you'll keep saying
"thank you thank you".
She won't tell anyone.
Why wouldn't she?
ls she related to you?
Koena is not that way.
Don't fall into her trap.
She's married.
Ok, listen to me, do you trust me?
Until now l did, now l don't.
You do, l trust Koena
in the same way.
Now please don't open your mouth
for two minutes.
Don't open your mouth..
Come in partner
- Oh god!!
Welcome to Rocket Sales Corporation.
From today, everything our company
earns will have three shares..
Yours, mine and Koena's.
l see, until morning it was 50-50,
by afternoon it's 33-33.
This is how you do business.
You talk about expanding
and you keep cutting shares.
ls this how you'll expand?!
Koena will help us expand. Because
of her we'll be able to get business.
How? On the phone?
Correct.
- What if something goes wrong?
Nothing will go wrong partner.
l am with you.
Don't be so frustrated
that you get castrated!
Harpreet, what if
something goes wrong?
What could be more wrong
than what's happening here..
Maybe we'll do something right!
Ok l better run..
Good idea?
Giri l have a request for you..
Tell me..
lf you ever look at Koena
in that way..
How?
The way you look at your web sites,
l'll kill you man.. seriously!
Look down.. double A
We will soon need an office, or
at least a conference room, for sure.
Tell me quickly,
office is about to close.
My husband will be here any minute.
What's so funny?
You spend all day long glued
to those photographs,
rest of us have to live
with human beings.
Ok listen.
From today no Rocket Sales Corporation
work will be discussed in AYS.
l think it's too risky.
Hmm.. here's a list
of "dead" clients.
Thanks
They left because of
AYS's bad service.
3 were Nitin's clients.
2 vibha's 2 Rajesh's,
2 Rumaan's and 3 Taxi's..
They've been sold PC's..
so they'll need good service. Right?
Yes
We'll offer them service
for half the price.
How much is AYS's
service contract for?
lt's whatever price
they can sell for.
Meaning.. 4-5,000 for one year,
for one PC.
We'll offer for 2,500..
plus 1 month's extra service free.
lt's a good idea,
but who'll service them?
l can't, l have work
in the office all day.
ln daytime.. you can service them
in the night.
You don't sleep anyhow.
The idea is good.
But l haven't heard it before.
That's why it's good.
Maintenance and repair
will be done in the night,
clients will never get
an opportunity to see a bad PC.
What if a client recognizes me?
No one will recognize me.
Until now,
even l didn't recognize you.
Me neither
Do you know, he keeps an account
of everything from AYS.
Seriously?
- Yeah.. and one day he said..
.. "we'll pay back everything
we've used from the office!"
l hope he doesn't keep accounts
of your downloads,
you'll have to sell your house.
Yello..
- Hello sir, it's Harpreet.
What now?
Uh.. Nothing sir, l have a fever.
lf l get day a off..
Oh, His Highness can't make it
to work!
The company will have to shut down.
All the work was happening
because of you.
Teaching me what happens
during notice period!
Where are you going
for an interview?
No sir, l really have a fever.
Yes everyone has it
during notice period.
Do what you want,
don't waste my time.
Good morning.. Good morning sir,
Good Morning sir
l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi..
from Rocket Sales Corporation.
Hello sir.. l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi
l'm Harpreet Singh Bedi
from Rocket Sales Corporation.
Come in..
Hello sir, l am Harpreet Singh
from Rocket Sales Corporation.. sir..
Oh meaning you provide services
at night and during holidays?
Yes sir at night, during holidays,
Diwali, Dusshehra, Eid, New Year..
Any day. Any time.
One phone call and zero down time
for any PCs we sell.
Otherwise don't pay us,
we'll pay you double the
service contract amount.
This is the unique
Rocket Sales Corporation 24 hour
guarantee, only for this
month's customers sir.
Can you give it in writing? Signed?
l have seen many companies before..
..but have never seen this
much confidence.
Do you have money to refund?
That will never happen sir, but
if l need to, l'll sell my scooter.
l called "your"
Mr. Wajahat's contact..
his friend said to come
by after 7 pm.
He's not free before that,
neither are we free!
AYS.. Good afternoon..
Mr. Wajahat recommended you highly.
That's all ok, however, aren't you
a small company for such a big order?
lt's a small company sir..
That's why we are hungry.
We know and you know that
you don't need us but we need you.
And if we both know,
then there's no chance of mistakes.
lf something goes wrong, how will
you return double the amount?
Ok, l'll do a double contract
with you sir.
Every month,
l'll give you the right to
the payments Mr. Wajahat
makes to us.
lf you're happy with us
then you can transfer the payment,
otherwise your company can keep it.
You are taking a big risk
Even Spiderman has to take risks.
At least l'm a salesman.
very well.. 30 PCs, single order..
You can fill out the amount.
l'll say it again..
Only honesty works with me.
That's the only thing l have sir..
Nothing else.
How long will 30 PC's take?
30, is too many.
lt'll take at least 20 days.
We have to deliver in a week.
- What?!!
l said yes to them.
Don't you know any other word?
He said yes!
l told them a week..
we can't fall behind.
We'll need another person..
who can assemble a PC.
l knew that..
- Do you know anyone?
Of all the trustworthy people,
there's only one..
who can assemble a PC quickly..
Who?
- Chotelal..
But he doesn't even know
how to work on one.
He knows how to assemble one..
He can do it in his sleep!
lf that's the case then,
it's time we
get another partner
into Rocket Sales Corporation.
Are you crazy..
You'll make a peon a partner?
Why not? lf someone can do
the work of a director..
.. then why can't they be
a director?
l knew something would go wrong.
lf you already knew everything
then why did you join the company?
l didn't know it would go so wrong!
Me? Partner in a company?
No it can't be
Why not.. Can you assemble a PC?
- Yes
Then you can be a partner
in this company.
But.. my job is to make tea.
lf you miss it so much
then you can make tea as well.
Then it's fine..
Will l need to speak in English?
No.. You don't need to speak
to anyone about anything.
Just assemble PC's with Giri.
Say ok?
Yes. Does it involve going to jail?
We are running a business,
why will we go to jail?
The big businessmen always
go to jail.
lt's not that big a business!
What if Mr. Puri gets to know?
Who'll tell him?
Only the four of us know about this..
Sir, l could never have received
such respect anywhere.
The day you called me Mr. Mishra,
instead of Chotelal,
is the day you made me feel big.
Good, good.. that means you don't
want a share in the company?
No, when did l say that?
Partner..
l said Partner..
Are you tired?
You are doing it, right?
- l am, but you are not.
You are also a partner,
you will also get a share.
You bastard..
Do it.. do it
Good morning AYS..
yes sir.. connecting
Good morning partner
Oh Cup-plate!
What's going on? Where's my coffee?
Yes sir, l'll pass on your message.
Good afternoon AYS, can l help you..
connecting sir.
Good afternoon..
yes one minute sir connecting..
Yello! Rocket Who?
Rocket Sales Corporation?
l think you have the wrong number.
Yeah right, the number is right
but this is AYS computers.
Good afternoon.. Can l help you?
Yes Rumaan.. What is to you
if l didn't say AYS?
Who do you want to speak to?
One minute.
Good afternoon.. Wrong number.
Too many wrong numbers these days?
- What?
You just put one through.
Rocket Sales Corporation?
The credit card collectors
make up any name to get through.
Yes.
And you would definitely
transfer them now..
l want to speak to everyone
right now.
Now.. no it can't wait till evening.
No right now. Didn't l say now!
l don't know how it reached Nitin.
Must have been in a hurry..
There must be some way our clients
can call us and we don't get caught.
Umm.. there are 2 connections
that were bought but never used.
Mr. Puri probably doesn't remember.
lf those numbers are used,
we may not have a problem.
lf it flashes on the board,
l'll know.
Fantastic! - lf you ever cheat
on your husband, he's had it.
Will our phone bills be separate?
l'll have to write it
down in the accounts.
He's started again.. - l have to
run.. Someone might get suspicious.
Me too.
Are you coming?
- No no you carry on..
Ok.. l'll see you tomorrow.
HP.. !!!! Long time..
HP.. Where have you been?
l don't even get to see you..
you bloody big salesman..
Office..
- Office!! Go get a drink!
Let me relax a minute..
Take your time
but what will you drink?
Uh, juice..
Juice? What's happened to you?
Sai..
- Yeah.. what happened?
Why aren't you dancing?
Oh-.. HP meet Sherena..
Sherena, meet HP
HP.. ?
Come on guys dance please..
How are you?
What?
How are the.. uh, computers
l'm good..
How are you?
What?!
Nothing..
Huh?!
Forget it.. Nothing!
What?!
Shall we go in?
Juice?
No.. no.. inside!
lnside. Shall we go in?
Ok
Oh so you know Appy?
Yeah, how do you know her?
College.. and you?
School.. hostel.. you know,
l never thanked you..
you sold those computers
to us at such a low price,
it really helped us you know.
Setting up a new business
is quite difficult.
Well you're welcome..
By the way, how's your business?
Planning to close it down.
Why?
Life is not as easy as
it seems in college.
Salaries for 2, rent,
electricity bills,
and clients don't even take
phone calls from new companies.
Anyway, they say it takes 2 to 3
years to set up a new business,
unless you are doing something wrong.
Anyway how's it going with you?
Uh, okay.. l mean ok-ok
ls your training period over?
Yes, it was over then.
- When?
Then.. after your order.
lt was not that big an order ok.
You've no idea how big it was.
Meaning?
l'll tell you some other time.
- No, tell me now.
No, some other time.
You know, you're really nice..
other wise salesmen
can be really pushy.
l feel l can really talk to you..
Right..
Hey do you want catch a film..
Sunday?
l mean, if it's okay with you..
l don't want to sound like
a pushy salesman and all
No no, actually.. you're my client..
l'm sorry.. l shouldn't
Why? Don't clients watch films?
No, of course they do
7 PCs were assembled in 2 days..
target is 30 PCs. We are going slow.
We are trying.. You refuse
to buy parts from another place.
"Your" Lalwani Electronics
is a very small supplier.
lf you want to increase work
leave him.
l won't leave him Giri.
When l didn't have money,
he gave me credit.
And today when l have a big order,
l should leave him?
Business doesn't run like this.
You're the only one who understands,
your way of running a business.
Why are you trying to be
a "saint" in a "jungle"?
You'll be ruined
and you'll ruin us as well.
Eat a sandwich,
nothing will go wrong. Trust me.
ldli(Steamed cakes)
l didn't order any, who did?
Maybe the guy on the other table.
- Correct..
l suspected something the moment..
.. this kid started acting
like a smart alec..
And that phone call..
Where's the complaint box?
l have a complaint about corruption.
Forget it.. lets make a phone call..
Everyone will have Mr. Puri's
number on their cell phone..
Whose shall l use?
Look, say the word, we'll make
a quiet arrangement between us.
What do you say?
lf l say something
then you'll say l talk a lot.
And for not talking,
it'll cost you.. a lot.
How much?
- 1 0%, of every sale.
Look, if you want a share
in our company..
.. then like all the partners,
you'll have to work for it.
Ok kid.. time to wake up,
Good morning.
From now on, the situation is such
that you can't dictate terms to me.
But l can dictate any terms l want.
No, we can also dictate terms
and the terms are these..
lf you ever put
on this shameless smirk then,
those bogus conveyance vouchers..
..that you have me fill out
for the last two years,
l'll decorate them on a plate
and serve them to..
.. Mr. Puri along
with his morning coffee,.
And.. if you call me
"cup-plate" one more time..
then if this company
remains or doesn't,
my share remains or doesn't,
l will take this very idli
and shove it down your throat!
Thanking you, yours faithfully,
Mr. Chotelal Mishra.
ln front of Rocket Sales
Corporation's partners,
l repeat my offer once again..
Work with us,
and share the profits equally
with the other partners.
Now there are five of us,
so each one will get 20% .
Besides we needed another person
in sales.
Why should we give this snake
an equal share?
Because he's an experienced
salesman Giri..
He'll bring in so many orders that
20% won't seem a lot. Right partner?
Welcome to Rocket Sales
Number 1 . We never lie to a client.
- Even if we lose the order?
We can lose the order
but not the client's trust.
Number 2. We believe
in service more than sales.
Because the company that
provides service, sells more.
What are you talking about?
Number 3. Even if the client asks,
we never offer a bribe.
Then how do you get an order?
We don't want such orders.
Number 4. Whatever date we promise..
on that date, at whatever cost,
we make the delivery.
Number 5. We are always available
for the client day or night
He'll drive us crazy
with his phone calls.
That's the rule.
- So what do think?
This is what happens in asylums,
where patients wear white coats
and become doctors.
So wear a coat.. Best of luck
for your first client meeting.
There's something wrong,
but it feels right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but it feels right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
Turning night into day
pinned up by stars
Embedding the twilight
with a hundred moons
We have no time to offer apologies..
for now!
There's something wrong,
but everything's right..
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but it feels right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
Holding our breath forever
We were searching
for something true
We caught a light..
.. and held on to it
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
Spinning like glistening tops
in a race against sanity
We travel along untravelled paths
leaving no trail behind
The faster we run,
the faster desire catches up
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finally in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finally in sight
M&T's order has also gone
to Rocket Sales Corporation.
And this is not the first order
that was going to be ours..
.. and ended up with them. Good huh?
And all of you, the so called
"best sales team" has lost out..
.. for the second time in two months,
against this insignificant company.
What's going on? What does
this Rocket, or whatever it is,
do to whisk away the clients
from right under your..
.. commission filled noses?
Any ideas?
What the shit is happening here?!
What is this bloody company?
What are they doing?
How much are they bribing that,
at the very last moment
the order ends up with them?
Who can tell me here?
You must have already applied
with them..
Who are these people?
When M&T was giving them the order,
were you sleeping?
How did your order go to them?
Sir, we don't know a lot but at..
.. the last moment they offered
the client a terrific scheme.
What scheme? Which scheme?
This is lndia,
when did orders come from schemes?
Sir, my clients are always giving
examples of their services.
These guys service
computers even at night!
What rubbish!
Sir, they keep their
quotes so low that,
one of my clients called me
a thief to my face.
How low?
Sir the simple PC that we sell
for 32,000 they offer it for..
.. 26,000 with two years free
service, including nights services.
So, if they have priced their PC
at this rate it means,
they are only earning 2,200
while we make 6,000.
What are they doing?
Don't know sir..
Where is their office?
How's it possible that
they are taking away orders..
.. from right under your noses,
and besides this pamphlet..
.. and phone number,
no one knows anything about them.
Something is very wrong.
Nitin One week.. get the history..
.. and geography of this
Rocket Sales Corporation! Get out!
You stay!
The post for
the vice President Sales is vacant.
l want a very useful person there.
Show me in a week how useful
you are, and move in.
Otherwise, leave.
There are other useful people here.
Growth will not cease,
whether a person stays or leaves.
Enough. l think it's over.
Before Puri catches us,
we should go apologize.
One minute, let me think.
Don't panic,
Panic? Do you know
what kind of person Puri is?
lf he catches us,
he will ruin our careers.
No other company will hire us.
No Giri, at the moment,
he's only suspicious.
lf my husband finds out..
lf none of us tell him,
how will he find out?
Don't under estimate him.
Didn't you see how quickly
he calculated the profit?
Yeah and all the client bills
have our address printed on them.
So what? lt's just an address.
Mine.. l told you we should
have used a post box number.
Sure.. those who are not suspicious
also become suspicious.
He will know it eventually,
one of us will tell him.
Who?
The snake has woken up.
What happened?
Look boss, whatever happened between
us, please don't take it personally.
l talk nonsense most of the time,
l had nothing against you.
We are ok boss, right?
lt's strange, for the first time
in my career people are..
.. scared of me and l am not happy.
When l first started in this
business, l was just like you.
The first few times,
l also didn't take any bribes.
But then l lost my first promotion,
soon followed by a second one.
Everyone around me kept receiving
commissions. Eventually, l also..
Thanks to you, after many years
l felt the need to be my own boss.
But today, Puri put me in my place,
in a minute.
lf you sell out once, everyone
thinks you have sold out, forever..
whether it's your boss or partners.
l will never tell Puri,
l've said what l had to.
The rest.. you think about it.
Thought about it.. Giri
Yes
- Move somewhere else for a few days.
But where will we
keep all the stuff?
When the customers call,
someone has to pick up.. Right?
Yes, someone has to do it..
l have a friend
- She knows too?
What kind of a secret is this,
the entire world knows?!
She doesn't know yet,
but l'll have to tell her someday.
You could also be intelligent,
frankly, l didn't think so..
Thanks huh..
- very smart.. huh?
'l will have to ask the company.'
l had taken your order
for the company..
But supplied it yourself instead?
They were throwing rockets at me!
Wow! What an excuse..
'they were throwing rockets at me!'
What would you do in my place?
lf l were in your place..
your boss would be dead.
What a jerk! Kiss me quickly
before l get angry.
So, are we on?
Yeah, obviously.
l love you so use me. What can l do..
When do you want to start?
Uh, Actually they
are waiting out side..
the supplies are in the van,
and the van needs to be returned..
ls the company named after you
or you're named after the company?
Can't you do things slowly?
Rocket Sales Corporation..
Bas say Rocket Sales Corporation..
May l help you?
Rocket Sales corporation,
may l help you?
Rocket Sales corpo-!
Rocket Sales here, yup?
Will you talk to clients like that?
Just say "Rocket Sales Corporation,
may l help you?"
Oh so what! See how nice this is..
"Rocket Sales, Hi!"
Clients will think
they've called a slimming center!
Ok? You want to make it formal?
Ok no problem
- Sure?
What?!
Nothing..
Then why are you
giving me these stares?
Well at least we have
a separate number now.
ln a few days, we will give these
new numbers out to the clients.
Thank god! l was on pins and needles.
Not bad huh..
Rocket Sales Corporation,
may l help you?
Ah.. yes.. yes l want
to order some PCs..
Transferring sir
- Where is your offi..
Sherena, take this call.
lt's Puri, speak to him.
What do l know? Talk about anything..
Rocket Sales Corporation,
may l help you?
Ah yes, this is Sunil Puri,
MD of AYS Computers.
l would like to speak
to your MD please
Shit!
- Hello.. ?
He is not in office sir.
l will give him your message.
Okay.. ok. By the way,
where exactly is your office?
Second floor sir,
thank you for calling
For now, it's only a phone call,
next time he'll go for our throat.
He knows. l'm telling
he knows everything.
lf he'd known, we wouldn't be here
chatting, we would be in jail.
ln jail?
lt's not that easy to go to jail.
You can't make a booking
on the internet, and send someone.
Nothing will happen.
What if he calls again?
Just say.. the CEO is out sick.
No No, tell him, he's out of town.
Why town?
Say he's out of the country!
lf he wants to meet me,
then l'll meet him.
Do you think it's a joke?
Think it's a joke?
You told me this didn't involve
going to jail.. didn't you?
You've gotten everyone in a fix..
talking like a big shot.
Look. He wants to meet the MD
of Rocket Sales Corporation.
There must be something on his mind.
And until l meet him,
we won't know what it is.
What will we gain by finding out
what's on his mind? Worry about us.
l am worried about us.
His business is failing,
and he'll do anything to save it.
Before he does something,
we should know what he'll do.
But how will you meet him?
The same way Porus met Alexander.
A king meets another king.
Face to face.
Call him.
Sir, Rocket Sales Corporation's MD
is on the line for you.
He was bound to call. Transfer it..
Transferring sir
Ok all set? 1 .. 2..
You should have counted till 3.
l wouldn't have stayed alive till 3!
Hello, Mr.
- Singh
Mr. Singh, thank you for calling
back, this is Sunil Puri here.
We haven't met but l'm sure
you must have heard my name.
No, not really..
Uh, l'm the MD of AYS Computers
Oh yes, of course of course,
sorry boss, How are you?
Good, very good, very good..
uh, congratulations boss,
your business is doing well..
very well, for a small company.
Thank you
So, what are your future plans?
The future has all the plans,
the past has only.. "empty cans"
You have a nice sense of humour.
My sense of honour is not bad either.
Of course, of course..
so tell me, what are your plans?
Just keep watching..
l have been watching..
but forget about the present,
and let's look far into the future.
- Meaning?
Meaning boss.. you know and l know..
.. that this computer assembly
business is a jungle.
That it is.
And since the multinationals
have arrived,
the jungle has only become smaller,
and in one small jungle
2 lions can't survive.
Are you leaving this business?
You can joke well..
But can we talk seriously?
lnstead of competing with each other,
let's work together.
How?
l'll buy out your company.
This is what you
call working together?
See, why talk like you're a wet
noodle, when your name is Rocket.
What's your little company's value?
value is in the name, sell the name.
30, 40 lakh? 50 lakh?
Ok take 55 lakh and enjoy yourself.
Leave your business
with people with experience.
Yes, what you're saying is correct.
Let's work together..
l'll buy you out.
You, will buy my company?
Why not..
You.. you will buy me out?
Why? Don't you want
to work together anymore?
Look boss, every person has two basic
qualities, to go up and to go down.
And whichever quality wins will
determine how he'll win life, right?
Ok take 60 lakh, you won't
get another chance like this.
Ok, l'll ask my colleagues
and let you know.
What happened?
Everyone likes to keep servants,
he may also love and care for them.
But you're the first person l've
met who consults business with them.
Look, you won't get
this offer a second time.
l'm giving you
an offer of a lifetime.
Oh, so you sell phone cards as well?
Look, understand this now.
You won't be in a position
to understand things later.
Mr. Puri, in business the one
who calls the other first,
is not in position to threaten.
Look.. even my father
never spoke to me like this.
For the last time,
sell me the company,
take the money
or you will regret later!
Ok do one thing..
- What?
Put the phone down, l am very busy.
Besides you have phone
cards to sell. Right?
Bastard.. l'll see you!
lf you could see,
you would have seen by now.
What have you done?
What?
This is our company
not used furniture!
We are owners, not employees.
This company is not for sale and no
one can buy it. Whoever it may be!
We sent you to the lion's den
to negotiate..
.. and you shoved your hand
down the lion's mouth.
l wasn't afraid to put my hand
into the lion's pocket,
then why would l be afraid
to put it into his mouth!
Look boss,
before Puri goes in deeper..
..let's take his money and leave.
You go deeper! lf he buys
the company won't he know,
who he's buying from.
Even if Puri wants the company,
we can't sell it.
But we can leave his company.
We have hands, brains,
clients. What else do we need?
l think it's time to
sacrifice our monthly pay,
and concentrate
on our business full time.
Besides it's becoming difficult
to manage two jobs!
l'm okay..
So tomorrow morning, resignations?
Hello?
Hello,
is this Rocket Sales corporation?
Yes sir, can l help you?
Yes you can..
l wanted to buy a few PCs,
l hope l didn't call to late.
No, no sir, you're not late at all..
we are open 24 hours sir
Ok.. the number l have called on,
is it yours?
Right sir
ls this your office number?
Right sir, in 2 days we'll have
a new 24 hours helpline. Just 2 days.
Really? You.. you sell PCs right?
Not just sell,
we service them as well.
We build relationships sir,
We have the best service in lndia.
Ok.. so how big is your company?
How many people?
We are a small sir,
but very dedicated team sir.
Sir please meet us
personally some day.
Yes l really want to meet you,
who is the owner of this company?
Sir, we are all owners.
We have no employees, only partners.
Really?
So sir, when do you want
to meet executives.. personally?
Right now
So.. let's meet then.
What were you thinking?
You "chickens" can fool Sunil Puri..
.. and that too with this zero brain!
You were going to become
the vice-President anyway.
You could have told me everything?
What was the problem?
You won't understand.
So explain it to me.. explain it!
l can understand things..
Before l send you to jail,
try and explain it to me.
Look, everything that's happened..
l started it.
So whatever you have to say,
speak to me.
Oh so Mr. Zero has
leadership qualities!
Fine l'll only speak to you.
How long has this been going on?
And how many orders
have you stolen from here?
We have not touched
any of your clients.
And all the facilities that
we've used in your company,
this is the account, which we
were going to reimburse anyway.
Here is the cheque.
You want to give me a cheque! Things
are going to go badly for you..
and so that others don't
face the same bad fate,
l will have to make it worse for you.
Take a bath.
No, it's ok.
Take a bath, maybe
your sins will wash away.
Mine will never!
Whatever happens, l'll deal with it.
You don't need to worry about it.
You should have left
the job right away..
l have looked after you for 21 years,
l would have done it for more..
Why did you have to
do a thief's work?!
You never taught me to how to do
a thief's work, if you'd taught me..
l wouldn't have
to become a thief today.
You accept and acknowledge that
after signing this agreement..
.. the trademark 'Rocket'
and 'Rocket Sales Corporation',
are now a property of AYS computers
in perpetuity worldwide.
Till you keep to this and the other
commitments in this contract,
AYS Computers will not file a legal
case to prosecute you for forgery,
cheating, fraud and embezzlement.
ln addition, you accept and
acknowledge that you will not..
.. engage in the computer business
formally or informally either as..
.. a company or as an employee
for a period of three years..
One sec, what is this rubbish?!
You want him to sign that
he won't work in the computer sales..
.. business for three years!
No business, nor a job?
Yes, that's good, isn't it?
Let's go, we'll think of something.
What are you doing? l told you
we'll think of something.
lt's not just me Sai, there are
4 other people. They trusted me.
They can, at least,
start their careers again.
So the Rocket's fallen?
Ok then.. from 4 o' clock today your
Rocket Sales Corporation is mine..
.. and all your clients..
are also mine!
Congratulations.
You have sold your company!
See, everyone has a quality
to go up and to go down.
Once l humbly requested you
for this name.
And today, you're on
your knees like a beggar..
selling me this very brand name.
What have you learned?
What have you learned kid?.. that a
man should stay in his place. Right?
Otherwise the fool will
never belong anywhere.
You don't have it in you..
You are a zero! Get out!
Oh.. at least take your
full and final compensation.
Don't ever become a businessman,
you'll fail again!
Yes sir.. the big news..
is here sir.. yes.
Now that two big brands have merged,
the investors will definitely come.
Let me wrap up
and hide away my dreams
Let me fold up
and bury my desires deep
The heart cannot be a slave
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
Let it soar, let it soar
Let it feel the breeze,
let it wake up to possibilities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
What is this l am hearing boss,
you sold your company?
Yes sir..
l didn't think
you were the type Harpreet..
Are you sure you have
made the right decision?
Yes sir..
Like a kite, the heart's spinning
through a million wants
Let it go, l'll show what
l'm destined for
Let me fall, l'll dust myself up
lf you don't fade,
how will you shine
Let me soar! Let me soar!
Let it feel the breeze,
Let it wake up to possibilities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
Sir my name is Rajess Das,
new Sales Manager of AYS-
Rocket Sales Corporation..
As you know Rocket Sales Corporation
is now part of AYS,
so l dropped by for an introduction.
Sir, why don't we continue this,
somewhere else.. over lunch?
Let me soar!
Let it feel the breeze,
Let it wake up to possibilities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
What's going on?
Nothing sir.. We are meeting
their clients one by one.
Meetings are ok, but when are you
getting their orders?
These clients have..
strange expectations sir!
They ask for all sorts of things..
These Rocket's clients are used
to some other type of service..
But we'll handle it sir..
This is Kumar, Giri's replacement.
Service will happen but help the
sales team! That's the real job.
Of course sir
Hi
- Hi..
Sir brands keep coming and going..
But please listen to me sir..
Sir, Wajahat's order
is not going to come..
Some of Rocket's other clients
are not looking too hopeful either!
Sir, we haven't really benefited
from Rocket Corporation's clients.
We haven't gained anything
from this buy out.
ln fact,
the liabilities have gone up..
Salaries of new engineers apart.
Sir, Rajesh said that
Rocket Sales was about
to receive a big order
from lnamdar's company.
lf we get that, then l can
manage the remaining accounts.
Look lnamdar, you are one of us.
l need this order.
Whatever has to be done, l'll do it.
Will you give us service?
Service is my guarantee,
You've known me for a long time.
lt's a new team
but the company is the same.
Yes, the company is the same.
You still don't understand.
You've bought
Rocket Sales Corporation's name,
but you've let it's people go..
you've been foolish..
Look, let bygones be bygones.
Let's start a new relationship.
l'm canceling all future orders.
And as far as l'm aware, rest of
the Rocket Sales' clients have
either done the same,
or are about to.
Mr. Puri there was a day
when your ways had changed
the geography of this business.
Don't take it badly,
but your way is now history.
Good Day!
Who are you.. Who are you!!
Who are you?!!
- Sir
What are you made of?
What is it with which you're
fooling everyone? What is it?
Who do you think you are
to sell for so little?
One's back breaks,
but still one doesn't make profit.
Sold your company.. who won?
You're on the street!
l've been selling computers for
1 0 years, 1 0 years before that fax
and 5 years before that,
electronic typewriters.
l have this business
running in my blood.
But l made one mistake..
The person l should have
made salesman of the year,
l kicked him out
and made him a competitor.
No problem, l made a mistake..
l had fun.
Now l'll straighten it out.
Come, l'll give you your job back.
vice-President's position
is still open.. come back.
You used to tell me that every
person has a quality to go up
and also to go down. And the road..
l took the road going down
because you never left me a choice.
l didn't know anything sir.
But l learnt by doing,
in business there are no tricks,
no schemes, and no magic.
Just one thing
- people!
The one's that work with you,
one's that your customers.
But you never saw them as people,
you saw them as numbers.
Who achieved which number,
who broke a target by how much..
But l never really understood
numbers. l always saw people.
Who's happy.. Who's sad.. Who does
good work.. Who enjoys what work..
do you know what the amazing
this is, when people are happy,
numbers increase on their own.
Because business is not numbers,
business is people. Only people.
You took my company.. no problem.
lt came from your company
and it went back into your company.
No problem. But what l have learned,
you can't take.
And with that l can build 1 0 more
companies, and l will one day.
But what will you do sir?
All that you know has become zero.
Who will you put
a zero "next" to sir?
All l wanted was a chance
in your company.
You didn't give me that..
And the way you're giving it to me..
l don't want it.
Wish me best of luck sir.
l couldn't be like you,
but l became a man.
l'll see you on the field!
l have never seen
a bigger zero than you.
And "it" ended up in such a place
that the company changed.
And when l removed "it",
the customers changed.
My people couldn't
handle your customers,
l have brains to understand that.
And a young kid has defeated me,
l can accept that too.
Do you have one rupee?
Do you have.. one rupee?
Here, l'm returning your company.
l couldn't digest it.
You want me to spell it out..
You won, l lost.
When blood and sweat are
printed on paper together,
table becomes a bed,
and office a home,
hunger and thirst are forgotten
and children are neglected..
only then a company is made.
And that is not given away as alms,
especially not to a man like me.
And a man like me never takes it.
l'm leaving you
with your life's biggest lesson.
And l've never even given
my father anything for free.
The thing you're doing..
l don't know if it's business or not
but never become a businessman,
you'll fail again.
l'll see you on the field.
l'll see you on the field
Giri, the delivery is in 4 days.
Mr. Mishra can you please
follow up on that delivery
Yes.. Can l speak
to Mr. Saxena please?
Yes, l'll hold ma'am..
Good job Nitin!
Yes sir.. this is Nitin
from Rocket Sales..
Hi Rocket Sales Corporation,
yes sir..