DDR -=KaMaL=-
Cheers...
Ready? Go...
Woo...I'm on top of
the worId!! Enough!
No, no, no, baby one more
one more one more pIease...
Harpreet! You passed!!
Bunty, you bum, congrats!
Come...I'II get you a drink.
Sai...Sai do something...
It's your party dude
and the DJ is Ieaving.
What's happening?
Nonsense! Give him some more money.
He can't stop now, the
party is just warming up.
I just did that, he
wont take my money,
says it's past 2 am and
he has to wake up earIy.
WeII it is past 2 am
- Wake up earIy...why become a DJ?
Let me taIk to him...
HP if he doesn't want money it
must be something serious. Leave it.
HeIIo Prince CharIes, not
everyone is motivated by money.
So how eIse are they motivated?
Have you ever heard of the word
- Persuasion?
You can't get anywhere
with B.com 39 percent.
I keep teIIing him to appIy
for an MBA, doesn't Iisten to me.
Life is not aII fun and games no...
Ok grandpa
Wow, what did you do?
A IittIe conversation, a IittIe
persuasion, a IittIe negotiation...
Done with your negotiation, can we
taIk about something worthwhiIe?
Do you taIk about anything eIse?
Not my work, I'm taIking about yours.
I'm starting with my dad's Iaw firm,
I don't care...what about you?
Why? What about me?
He graduated, isn't that enough?
You won't take the MBA exam?
If my grandfather was rich as your
father, I wouId have taken the exam...
So what wiII you do?
S-a-I-e-s
What...you'II be a saIesman?
Why? Aren't saIesmen human beings?
They are...of course they
are...but not very rich human beings.
My son, do you remember
Randy Bahadur, from arts?
He is a saIesman...
He gets 40,000
rupees without bIinking.
HaIf of that is commission, which
he gets onIy after he gets an order.
And do you even know
what aII a saIesman has...
...to go through to get an order?!
Why do you find
fauIt in everything I do?
BIoody negative bastard you are!
Dude he has a habit of Iecturing
peopIe...come on, Iet's dance.
No, once and for aII
Iet's get this straight,
these management exams
are not my cup of tea,
and my famiIy doesn't have
money for a private MBA.
SaIes is the onIy fieId where
common sense matters more than grades.
And now you'II say that I
don't even have common sense.
What'II I say...
Come...come...come...Let's dance.
I don't want to.
Oh come on
I toId you I don't want to.
I don't do things that
don't have power or money.
Just try it once. PeopIe wiII
pay just to watch you dance.
Good morning...morning...morning,
morning...morning...Good morning
Good morning...morning...Good morning
Good morning...Good morning sir.
This is Harpreet Singh Bedi,
Harpreet Singh. Harpreet Singh..
Good morning sir I'm Harpreet
Singh Bedi...Can I have a seat?
Good morning sir I'm
Harpreet Singh Bedi...ca..ca
Morning gentIemen, morning ma'am.
I'm Harpreet Singh Bedi...
I can't teII you how much I admire
this unique company and...Unique?
Good morning unique-
Come on son, come have
some sweet curd for Iuck.
Have aII your certificates?
EspeciaIIy your
character certificate? - Yes
Brushed up on your generaI knowIedge?
- Yes
Have you memorized an essay?
It's an interview, not an exam.
Have you memorized today's newspaper?
- Ya.
Put in money on your phone card?
- Ya
Emptied your boweIs?
Oh man, on one side you're
feeding me sweet curd and
on the other...ok I'm Ieaving.
If you'd used your brains studying,
you wouIdn't need sweet curd for Iuck
If Einstein studied with your snoring,
he'd aIso have to eat sweet curd.
Had I taken to snoring again?
You weren't taking, you were giving
it to the worId...for free. Ok bye
At Ieast straighten your turban.
What does the company make?
Don't know, wiII find out on the way
They make computers grandpa.
My grades are Iow not my IQ.
Oh Iord, aII is up to you now.
However he is, he is
your son. Watch over him.
Good morning AYS...transferring sir
Good morning AYS...Iine 2 sir
Excuse me ma'am...
Good morning
AYS...Transferring you to saIes sir,
Nitin, enquiry! - He's inside
the Taj MahaI, I'II speak to them.
I may Iook it, but I am not...
You'II burn your fingers...
...if you take a peek at
other peopIe's cIients or wives.
Everyone's suspicious here!
I'm going to Ieave this pIace.
I've heard it for 3 years.
Those who do things
don't taIk about it.
HeIIo...I haven't received a singIe
caII since morning. I am not fasting.
CouId you hoId sir? What can I
do if your territory's dead?
When you get your territory,
you don't say anything.
If you say something in the
Taj MahaI, you hear an echo.
This month's commission is gone.
I had narrowed in on an
LCD...wife wiII be upset.
Just try to get back home on
time everyday, she'II be happy.
Who troubIes you more,
your motorcycIe or your wife?
Connecting sir
Go pick up, it's your cIient.
He's been trying you for four days.
CaII them once in a whiIe,
cIients don't die after saIe.
Even the cIients wonder, what
happens to a saIesman after a saIe?
Excuse me ma'am
- At Your Service good morning
Sir pIease try and reboot.
No Mr. Puri is not in India...
ChoteIaI, have you
served Mr. Puri his coffee?
He has had four since morning.
Nitin is inside with
the saIes figures.
It's a wonder he
doesn't want a drink instead.
What are you Iooking at?
Nothing
You want to get kiIIed?!
HeIIo...Can I heIp you?
Oh I'm sorry ma'am, I'm Harpreet
Singh Bedi, for the saIes interview
One minute...Sir a
caII for you on Iine two.
You shouId have toId me earIier.
You Iooked busy so I
did not want to disturb.
Afraid of disturbing peopIe...
How wiII you become a saIesman?
Harpreet Singh?
- Yeah...I mean Yes
Nitin sir has caIIed you
to the conference room.
Where is the conference room pIease?
Up, in the sky. FoIIow me
HeIIo sir, I'm Harpreet Singh Bedi,
uh-it's an honour to be
in this fantastic company-
Why, what is so
fantastic about this company?
SaIes sir, your saIes
team's reputation is...
Good...but it can be better.
12th 35 percent...B.com 39 percent
no experience nothing,
'put together coIIege magazine'
You want to be a saIesman?
- Yes Sir...
Ok, seII yourseIf, come on.
Sir, uh...I think I
am a hard worker and-
You think, or you are...
I mean I-I am sir...and I want to
Iearn everything about products,
markets, customer reIations and
- Enough! Enough!
Do you know seIIing?
- Uh, of course sir
SeII this penciI to me,
for 100 rupees.
Sir this eraser
I took it off, but you
convince me that it's stiII there.
Sir, how can I convince
you if it's not there?
If you can't seII, how
can we give you a job?
AppIy eIsewhere.
HeIIo sir, I'm Harpreet
Singh from Singh PenciIs,
this is our new penciI, HS-1016
Sorry we have aIready
stocked up penciIs for the year
No probIem sir, Iet me give
you a quick two-minute demo.
Why watch a demo of a
penciI with no eraser?
This is not a penciI
without an eraser.
It's a penciI with a
detachabIe eraser.
Come up with something new!
Sir, the Iead on this
penciI is unbreakabIe.
Sir, if you appIy that much pressure,
anything wiII break.
But see, this penciI this
can be sharpened easiIy too.
TeIIing Iies doesn't make a saIe.
But perfume can make a saIe.
Sir, this eraser sir, it is a
speciaIIy imported perfumed eraser.
ShouId we put the penciI up our noses?
No sir, in the AC vent...See?
There are many other uses for this.
It's an ear bud for cIeaning ears.
A Tooth pick for cIeaning teeth.
Hair...I mean comb.
Reboot your mobiIe.
You can make a 3 pin
socket into a pin socket.
In case, you're stiII not satisfied,
you can kiII time with it.
Like you are...
What's going on?
- Sir
Puri sir
HeIIo sir
Sir, those saIes interviews.
Nothing speciaI sir.
Take him
- Sir?
You did not give up, I Iike that
Thank you, sir
- Okay you can go now
Your mark sheets
He faiIed a year, sir!
Not faiIed exactIy,
feII short on attendance.
SaIes' doesn't run on mark sheets,
it runs on baIance sheets.
SeIIing a two rupee
penciI Iike a Mercedes...
He must be something.
Thank you sir,
I won't disappoint you
Don't.
15,000...per month...no medicaI,
no gratuity, no provident fund...
six months training, no
commitment from our side...yes, or no-
Yes!
Everyone, this is...uh,
Singh...saIes trainee
WeIcome to wonderIand
- DisneyIand
Koena
- Sexy
His mother's name!
- Rajess
Rumaan, doubIe A
- Narayan
Tanmay
- Taxi
Bastard... - ChoteIaI give the new kid
the product brochure, rate Iist, etc.
Tomorrow is Sunday,
memorize everything. - Yes sir
Now go settIe down...over there...
Go on
- Yes sir
This way...
Okay Monday morning's meeting,
everyone's gonna get it.
So everyone pIease keep
your saIes figures ready.
We stiII have eight
months to go and we know...
One who seIIs the most wiII
be the saIesman of the year,
wiII receive a commission
of 5 Iakh and a Goa vacation
And you'II get a London vacation,
after adding up everyone's saIes.
I heard that...
- Where are you going this year boss?
We beat around in the sun
and he gets a London trip.
You know, you guys need to improve...
personaI attack is a
beIow the beIt game.
Let us be professionaI here, okay?
Yesterday, he coined a new sIogan
those who seII...come by,
and those who don't...goodbye
Shut up, cup-pIate.
Sit down
Those who seII...come by
And those who don't...goodbye.
What does that mean?
That's what happens in saIes. Those
who can't perform they have to go.
Where wiII he go?
He can go anywhere, join
another company if he Iikes.
What if that company
turns out to be the same?
Of course, it'II be the same.
Today's companies have
become so unethicaI.
ProfessionaI...ProfessionaI grandpa.
Not Iike in your times,
go to office everyday,
sign in, eat Iunch and come home.
As if we didn't work aII our Iives,
companies ran by themseIves?
I am not taIking about
you...you beIieve work is worship.
These professionaIs...
what does work mean to them?
Nothing, just work.
How does it matter? As Iong as
my grandson worships his work.
Rest, Ieave it to god.
Yes.
HoId him, hoId the Sardar
Oh...No no pIease,
Iet go of me Sardar...
He faiIed.
Mr. Inamdar. Honest man.
He got his due!
Meaning?
- Nitin sir wants to see you.
They want 56 computers
So, put in a quote for 16...we'II see.
Yes sir
Read it aII? AII set?
- Of course
Anyone want to voIunteer
for his fieId induction?
Haven't been on a
fieId visit in aIong time,
Iet's see what's going
on in whose territory.
Yeah! As if a manager becomes a
saIesman again by riding a motorcycIe.
The Wife must have taken the car...
Letterheads...Visiting cards.
10 in pocket, 10 in waIIet. 20 in bag.
Let's go.
350 huh? Now that's a motorcycIe, sir.
Zip it up.
You are wearing it the wrong way sir.
Does your dad run a Iaundry?
By evening the shirt wiII
get dirtier than your tongue.
From this signaI to the
next is your territory.
No other AYS saIes executive
wiII venture into the offices here.
Any inquiries from here,
Koena wiII Iet you know...
But this is a residentiaI area, sir!
Where wiII I find an office here?
Even if you did, what
wouId you do? SeII penciIs?
Sign in.
What are you doing?
FiIIing in our names
and our company's name.
You want to become a saIesman?
First ruIe of the fieId,
never write your or your
company's correct detaiIs anywhere.
Why?
- Put an ad in the paper instead!
No one Iooks at the
register in the company.
But a competing
saIesman aIways scans...
...the entries for
names of fooIs, Iike you.
Are aII these names incorrect then?
Of course! The saIesmen names are
incorrect, Iike this James Bond.
He is from Monovo. He is marking his
territory here. He is teasing us...
He thinks he's aIready got the order.
So then?
I have a trump card. Let
me see, if I can use it now.
Mr. Pandey!
Sir! It's been a whiIe...
Thanks!
What news?
The guy from Monovo has been
hovering here since morning.
Saw him photocopying
some documents in a hurry.
Server quotation
Thanks.
Sorry boss
What is it?
Nothing boss, he's crazy.
Oh Iook, your fIoor!
Boss...
Ha! He got off on the wrong fIoor.
New kid from WinteI.
By the time he reaches
the cIient he'II grow up.
Ok sir...yeah...6.30? Ok sir.
I'II just convey it to him.
Have a nice day.
Yes?
Are you going to say something
or keep smiIing Iike a fooI?
How are you?
- Sharma sir is busy.
CouIdn't I have come to meet you?
You wouIdn't meet your
wife without a reason.
First become the wife, then we'II see.
Sit down, Iet me see, idiot.
Is she your girI friend?
I am not that desperate.
What if she'd taken offense?
You were taking a big risk, sir!
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
At Ieast you're a saIesman.
Ok...go ahead!
Idiot.
Mr. Sharma's AustraIia trip canceIed.
Bonuses announced.
Mr. MavaIankar promoted. Ha!
My next trump card.
You go in first. He's in bad a mood.
- Why?
Because MavaIankar has
been promoted. Go in!
Good morning sir, I am
Harpreet Singh, this is my coIIeague-
Nitin, how are you? Now that you're a
saIes manager, we don't exist anymore?
No sir, nothing Iike that. Tanmay
must be dropping by now and then!
You must be busy
pIanning your AustraIia trip?
No I canceIed it. There's
a Iot of work in office.
I thought this company
has other peopIe as weII?
Yes I have heard that there are,
but tiII date I haven't seen any...
Anyway, teII me more... - Tanmay
must have maiIed you the quotation?
Is that a quotation?
This...you peopIe maiI anything.
He is a kid. StiII Iearning the ropes.
So what range are you Iooking at?
I wiII send you a fresh one.
Ok, I'II Iet you know.
By the way the Monovo
peopIe were saying that...
...Mr. MavIankar asked to
keep it Iess than 10 Iakh
MavIankar? What has he
got to do with this quote?
This is not even his department!
No sir they said that
he has been promoted,
and now heads the purchase department.
One minute. Do me a favour!
Send in a new quote of
10 Iakh, 10 thousand.
Throw in a year of
free service and warranty.
Then Iet's see who gives,
I mean, who gets the order?
Right sir
But I must say these Monovo
peopIe are very unprofessionaI,
I never expected this from them.
Now what can I say sir!
We have a poIicy of not
taIking about Competition
Yes I know, sorry you?
HeIIo sir I'm... - My cousin sir,
I was dropping him off to coIIege.
You're too good boss
Weren't you getting too
famiIiar with Tanmay's cIient?
No, no sir, I was introducing myseIf.
Started aIready? SaIes freak!
Good good.
But sir, how did you
know of the Monovo pIan?
Did you skip high schooI cIasses
as weII? Didn't they teach you...
...necessity is the
mother of invention!
But how did know the exact quotation?
I read it! How eIse wouId I know?
On that notice board?
Sharma!
But Mr. Sharma didn't
show us any quotation
No one shows you a
quotation kid! You have to see it.
That's what he was reading!
You can read upside down too?
You know what they caII a
saIesman who can't read upside down?
What?
A BIind saIesman.
If Jogeshwari is on the
Goregaon Iink road then,
it is in Jogeshwari. Isn't it?
No it's not. Everyone
knows it's in Goregaon.
He is my prospect Mr., and I
have aIready spoken to him.
Madam, when you'd caIIed I was there.
Besides, I've
aIready spoken with Nitin.
Nitin!
Oh heIIo...got your target?
No, where do you get it from?
It faIIs on your head.
Look I am warning you, if
you even Iook at my cIients,
I'II kiII you.
HeIIo
- Put Giri on.
Who? - It's Koena, who
eIse wouId caII you here.
Pass the phone to Giri.
- Giri who?
Get up, Iook over the partition.
The Service manager.
Hurry up now, his
cIient is getting impatient.
Hi
What? - How much Ionger? Your cIient's
been waiting an hour. - I don't know.
Give me an estimate? Or wiII
you make him wait tiII evening?
ToId you, I don't know. It's a
technicaI probIem, wiII take time.
What's the probIem?
- The Monitor is not showing anything.
Needs a new mother board.
Why don't you open it
and take a Iook Giri sir?
Maybe it can be fixed.
Open it. Open it.
Whack it in!
Not that! The third one!
Is it in? Reboot.
It's working.
It was a Ioose connection. Pack it up.
DiaI Koena, number 9
TeII the cIient his mother
board was fried-Rs. 5000. Less?
It's his fauIt, he didn't use a UPS.
That's another Rs. 3,250.
WiII take a week to fix it aII.
If you want a cIient's
bIood why don't you ask him?
Why are you asking for money?
Experience!
He's the one getting
a week's experience.
If I fixed your computer in 5
minutes wouId you pay me 10,000?
ShouId I teII Nitin sir?
Go teII him! How do you
think his London trip is funded?
From here. Now Ieave me aIone.
ChoteIaI yesterday's CD...where is it?
It's here. Sir pIease
don't Ieave it Iying around.
You watched it Iast night?
No, no, I Ieft.
You watched The wiId Queen?
Go get me a cup of tea.
ShouId I pack this?
What...Ieave it. Get me tea first.
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
At Ieast I'm a saIesman.
What's going on? I
have an announcement.
Jai Hind Motors is in!
Party time in the evening,
booze is on the company,
Women are not, so bring your own
Yes, yeah, I'm caIIing from office.
WiII I be caIIing
you from coIIege again?
PIease eat dinner, I'II be Iate.
I have an office get-together.
Oh! We can discuss fixing
the fIush Iater. Ok, bye.
Sorry Mr. Mishra...
- What...?
You are ChoteIaI Mishra?
It's on the intercom Iist
What's this...the man who
faiIed is the most educated.
ChoteIaI, what are you doing?
It's spiIIing.
Don't worry madam. Everyone in
a Iine pIease. I'II serve you
Move it Grandpa, move it
or I'II put in a quotation.
Nitin? Have you spoken
to Mr. Puri about me?
Oh shit...
PIease Nitin, the office manager's
position has been open for a Iongtime.
They wiII get someone eventuaIIy...
...and anyways, I have
been Iooking over the work.
Hope you've been Iooking
out for the phone caIIs?
The credit card coIIector has been
trying to get to you for two months.
Has he reached you yet?
So attendance shortage, how are you?
I'm good sir, thank you, how are you
How ambitious are you exactIy?
Do you think you can
take over his job?
No sir
You think I wouId have
fired him if you said yes?
No, no sir
I Iike you, you didn't get emotionaI.
You have a quaIity to go up,
but you aIso have a
quaIity to go down.
EventuaIIy the quaIity that
wins wiII define your Iife.
So where you want to go? Up or down?
Up sir
To cIimb up, you'II have
to waIk over many peopIe...
...and they wiII bite you hard.
And tomorrow if you're Iate for work,
your pay wiII be cut. WeIcome to AYS!
Booo!
Shit man! They say after 70, a
man's age restarts from zero.
Dude, cIose your eyes.
One minute...
I don't have two
minutes...don't you understand!
I waited for you for three hours,
you don't have 2 minutes for me
Ok fine, it's your carpet.
Don't bIame me Iater.
New pinch!
What's this?
Our brand new scooter
- What?
Yes...one with a button start.
No more kicking or pushing,
just gentIy press the
button and fIy Iike a bird.
You want to ride a
scooter at this age?
Why shouId I ride it?
I'II sit behind Iike a prime
minister. You'II drive right?
Me?
- Yes
Ride a scooter?
- What's the probIem?
It's your favorite coIour too. Maroon.
Grandpa I have toId you earIier,
jokes after 9:30 am onIy!
It's no joke! I put my
Iife's savings into buying it.
But I never asked for a scooter.
You go finish your toiIet, and
then we'II taIk...more comfortabIy
What comfortabIy?
You put your entire savings
into buying me a scooter...
...without teIIing me!
How much advance did you pay?
The scooter is outside.
- You paid the entire amount?
You don't get a
scooter for haIf the price!
Come on sardar, check it out.
BIoody heII.
Why are you being so difficuIt?
Can't gifts given with Iove,
be received with Iove?
Did I ask you for it? - It's
very modern. Ride it once and see.
Did I ask you for it?
Have I onIy given you things when you
asked for them? Who are you to ask?!
Go to heII!
Target Rs.6,00,000.
25000/-. If 1
computer is for Rs. 25000/-
and 24 PCs quarterIy, means 24
computers in three months, monthIy,
You have 8 PCs to seII and it's
aIready the 20th of this month.
But I started Iast week on the
14th and I got my target today...
...so ideaIIy my month starts today?
ReaIIy? You're Iearning fast!
Just do what you're toId boss,
You're a trainee not
a Managing Director.
Right sir
- That's the spirit
Listen...
On your way drop this quotation off
to Mr. Chaudhary at
NationaI ChemicaIs.
NationaI ChemicaIs is
in the wrong direction.
So, did we hire you to
go in the right direction!
Best of Iuck for
your first cIient visit.
Stop by a tempIe for bIessings.
Emotions are under controI,
My scooter has petroI.
That's aII I need.
Good morning sir
Fine...and the rest?
The rest sir, if you have
any further requirements,
Iet me know. I'II arrange it.
What's there to arrange?
I'II give you an address,
have it sent there.
Sure sir, do you have another branch?
That's a good one. I do,
my sister's house.
How much has been decided?
Whatever is in the quotation.
PIus taxes.
Government gets taxes. What do we get?
You get the machines sir...
Nice sense of humour you
have huh? 10 percent ok?
Sir pIease why are you puIIing my Ieg?
No I am not...are you?
Sir, pIease don't embarrass me sir
Your attitude is very unprofessionaI.
Work wiII be difficuIt...for you.
Sir pIease speak to
Nitin directIy. I am Ieaving.
Leaving without anything?
On an empty stomach?
Some tea or coffee. Sardarji?
..connecting sir At your service,
Good afternoon...
I wiII get it sent across.
- Where is Mr. Nitin?
Right...sir, Back so quick.
Is it raining outside?
Where is Mr. Nitin?
Inside the Taj MahaI.
He's aIready had 4 coId drinks,
waiting for you.
These days there's a
Iot of GIobaI warming.
Good afternoon sir
HeIIo sir
What happened at NCC?
What didn't happen?
Something is terribIy wrong there.
Why? What happened?
Sir, he asked for a
bribe and to my face.
What are you saying?
- I swear!
So what was your repIy?
I didn't say anything at the time,
I carefuIIy tried to expIain it.
But on my way out I
saw a compIaint box,
I wrote down aII the
detaiIs and dropped it in,
properIy on our company Ietterhead.
Signature, date...everything.
Here's a copy.
What happened sir?
Aren't you being over smart?
Why, what happened?
You think without authorization
you can use the company Ietterhead...
...and make faIse
aIIegations against our cIients?
And get away it? Sir it's a cIear
case of company Ietterhead forgery.
One second boss.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you pIace aIIegations
against the managing director of NCC?
You are bareIy born and
aIready trying to fIy high?
Sir it was your decision in
the interview. - Shut up Nitin
We can charge him with
fraud to begin with...
Let's consuIt the Iawyers,
there'II be many more charges.
Sir pIease teII him to
mind his Ianguage sir
You bastard...You think you can go
and spoiI our reIations with cIients,
and nothing wiII happen to you.
How dare you speak to
our cIients in such a way?
You haven't soId one thing yet, but
you taIk as if you've soId miIIions.
I'II sIap you so hard,
you wont know what hit you.
QuietIy compIete your
training period and get out of here.
One mistake...One more
mistake and I wiII throw you out...
BIoody bastard...
Get out!!
Did you have to be so righteous?
You shouId have quietIy gone back
to work, and Iet them resoIve it.
Did you have to become a hero?
Did someone teII me when I started,
that the company was corrupt
and I'd have to do aII this.
Every company is Iike this, and
you have to do this in every company.
This is common sense
- Leave this job.
Leave and do what? I haven't
even finished one month yet.
It'II Iook bad on my resume.
HeIIo...yes I am in office.
No, you eat dinner, uh, I
have another get together.
I won't ride the scooter drunk.
You've bought me a MIG 29
it might end up crashing!
Ok bye
To top it off, this scooter
has tapped into his savings.
Why don't you join a caII center?
They'II empIoy anyone.
I didn't mean it Iike that!
You wiII need a reIieving
certificate from the previous empIoyer.
TeII them it's your first job.
What have I done? Why
shouId I Iie to anyone?
ShouId I go beat up Mr. Puri?
That's aII that's needed.
You shouId have made at Ieast
one saIe in aII these days...
How Iong has it been
since you joined the job?
Listen to me...don't worry,
go to office tomorrow.
Your Puri wiII have
forgotten everything.
Who remembers a
trainee in such a big company
ExactIy
- Right?
Watch me, I'II Ieave for my
fieId-rounds earIy tomorrow.
Notice! What happened? TroubIe?
Did you have a fight with Nitin?
What happened bro?
What happened?
- They're praising you
A Iot
- Read it out to him
Mr. Harpreet Singh is henceforth
stopped from visiting any cIients...
He wiII onIy make coId
caIIs from his desk..
...and pass on Ieads to
other coIIeagues... - CoIIeagues
They have stopped you
from entering the fieId.
Your targets have been thrown away.
Not just targets, your
entire career is over.
Ok peopIe, saIes target meeting,
in the conference room.
Oh man what now? There
are Iimits to targets.
Let's go drop our
pants and stand in a row.
Don't know what's going to happen?
Boss, not you
What wiII you do if you came?
Yours have aIready been dropped!
What did you do boss?
Beat up a cIient?
BIoody idiot!! You'II get us kiIIed,
which idiot hired you?
You caII my cIients, I'II
beat the crap out of you.
You Iook so normaI on the outside,
but on the inside you're compIeteIy
mad. Why don't you get admitted?
Oh anti-corruption branch, from
now on your territory is mine...
...If you have any
Ieads give them to me.
I'd give them to you,
if there were any.
Look at this idiots' attitude.
Why don't you shut up.
Because of you aII our targets
have been doubIed. Watch what you say.
Don't come near me. I'II kiII you.
No use taIking to him. Idiot.
What are you doing? The Ramayan is on.
Ramayan has been on for ten years
now. Has anyone Iearned anything?
How many times wiII you watch
the same thing over and over?
You're Ietting things get to you.
This job has stressed you out.
Don't work too hard.
You are a hard worker anyway.
Do your co-workers reaIize this?
Jobs today are too stressfuI.
They make good men into coconuts.
HeIIo Harpreet
- Good morning
Hey Harpreet...
What happened?
HeIIo
- Good morning ma'am,
I'm caIIing from At
your Service computers,
we seII and support aII kinds
of PCs and aIso undertake...
PIease don't bother me!
- No probIem ma'am, I-I'II try Iater.
HeIIo - Good morning sir, I'm caIIing
from At your Service Computers...
CaII Iater!
No-no probIem sir, I'II try Iater.
Somebody's just died...wiII you
Iet peopIe die in peace at Ieast?!
Oh! I'm extremeIy sorry sir,
I'II try you Iater. Yes sir
What is it?! Why do you keep caIIing?
uh heIIo...sir
- PIease don't irritate me!
HeIIo...Sir am I speaking to Jai hind
Joshi. - What number have you diaIed?
Give me your business card?
AII of them. Nitin wants them.
You are not going on fieId,
we'II cut them and give
them to taxi. Nitin said so.
This seat is cursed...
HeIIo sir, A 21 inch monitor
is perfect for entertainment.
ok see you, bye
Can you drop me to the
station my husband isn't coming.
I had an inquiry from
your territory, for 2 PCs
Give it to Rajesh, I have
to give it to him anyway.
If you don't give him one or
two you won't catch maIaria.
QuietIy go get an order. TeII
them after a coupIe of days.
If you don't get an order,
you'II get into troubIe;
Get an order, and get
into troubIe...or not.
Ok...Don't take it.
My husband's here, Ok bye
So what I'm saying is ma'am that, the
kind of technicaI expertise we have,
the kind of experience we have,
and the kind of service we give,
we don't reaIIy have any competition.
But your company is so big,
so your prices...
Why? Just because the
company is big that doesn't mean,
the prices shouId be high.
They have to be based on
the customer's pocket,
not the company's. And
that's exactIy what we do!
And you want a bet...
That is reaIIy impressive...
but...ummm...
Discount...?
Ma'am at Ieast pIace an order first.
Pentium processor with
this graphic card...
Ma'am I'm going to give
you the best price... - Okay
Ma'am we...uh, we don't seII
Pc's with this graphic card.
But no probIem, I'II
check with the office.
Boss are you a trainee or something?
No...but everyone has a boss.
I am sure you do too?
No.
He doesn't even know what kind
of product he has, forget it,
those who can't do anything,
become saIesmen.
Okay, pIease find out
from somewhere eIse.
From where...?
- I don't know ma'am
Look...I'm reaIIy sorry...
For the Iast two days we're
meeting saIesmen after saIesmen...
It's okay
- at Ieast find out for us...
What?
Which company assembIes this
configuration with this graphic card?
Ma'am I toId you, I don't know.
NoodIes?
- Huh?
Maggi noodIes...come eat...
pIease eat...it's ready...pIease eat.
PIease join us.
Ayesha, come eat. Come on
They are pIain gIasses.
We started a new business
but no one takes us seriousIy.
Neither parents, nor
cIients nor saIesmen.
I'II uh...find out
about your graphic cards
HeIIo
Yes, how can I heIp?
Sir, do you keep this graphic card?
HD 4350...keep them, I seII them.
What's the Price?
- Here it is.
What's the price?
- Rs. 4,400
And for two?
Why don't you take it for Rs. 8,000,
I'II throw in the condiments for free.
Can't it be Iess?
That is the whoIesaIe rate.
How much wiII you reduce?
With rest of the parts, you'II
have a new PC for Rs. 20,000,
and you'II at Ieast
seII it for Rs. 30,000?
One can assembIe a PC with
this card for Rs. 20,000?
Then? We make one for Rs.
25,000...want one?
But companies don't seII it to
the customers
for Iess than 35-40,000 rupees.
If it's made for so IittIe,
why seII it for so much?
The thing is, the word
customer has mer (die) in it.
Forgive me Iord Ganesh.
See, if I had an A/C room, a big
store, I wouId aIso seII it for more.
This is quite a con!
You're buying two,
who are you conning?
No, I am not conning anyone.
Can I keep this price-Iist?
I want it for a cIient.
Keep it. I was going
to recycIe it anyway.
And Iisten, get your
stuff today or tomorrow.
Here the worId changes Iike
this...Iike this...Iike this.
There's no guarantee of anything.
I know...
Ok...bye...that, that wiII
cost you Rs. 350, do you want it?
HeIIo, Miss Sherena
pIease...Hi it's me...Uh, Harpreet...
You asked me to find
out about the PC's.
How are you? Good. We'II suppIy it
Oh...okay...
Uh...Rs. 27,500 per PC
with one year guarantee
Are you sure? Is there a saIe on?
No, uh, because this
is your first order.
Ok...Who shouId I make the
cheque out to?...That...uh- heIIo
HeIIo...?
Rocket...
Rocket SaIes Corporation
Mr. LaIwani?
I was about to cIose.
Do you want the card?
Yes, 2 graphic cards, and
everything that goes in for 2 PCs.
Pack everything.
Who are you conning?
You. I'II take it on credit.
Payment next week.
Do you see that
- Cash today, credit tomorrow
When you started your business,
how much money did you have?
Someone must have trusted
you and given you credit.
Yes, that was a reIative.
So consider me your reIative too
and keep my scooter as a guarantee.
It's more vaIuabIe than this purchase.
What kind of business
deaI are you making?
WiII you give it to me?
Ok go ahead. As it is, I've never
seen a Sardar cheat someone, take it.
But when you get what
you want don't forget me,
you've made me your reIative.
If I forget everything, I wont
forget this Mr. LaIwani...thanks
What are you doing in
office at this hour?
You can bareIy bring in
orders during the day,
what wiII happen in the night?
I have some work for
me...I mean you...
You've managed to mess
up work with this company,
now what work do you have?
There's...Uh...there's an order
Aren't you supposed to
pass your orders to others?
No, I'm not giving
this order to anyone.
Who is the cIient?
- A friend of mine.
You mean it's a personaI order,
not the company's?
Profit is aIso personaI.
What you seem, you are not.
What you are, I don't know.
Do you have petroI in your scooter?
- Why?
I don't waste fueI on friend's work.
It's a ruIe, from my engineering
coIIege days. ShaII we Ieave?
Yes
- Iet's go
What?
Nothing.
Is aII this yours or AYS's?
Did I ask you if the
order was yours or AYS's
See, for 50 years,
government has been encouraging us...
Become entrepreneurs,
become entrepreneurs.
ShouIdn't we do something or
wiII the government do everything?
Did you ever appIy
for a government job?
No why?
Nothing, the country was spared.
Does Puri know?
No boss, keep it quiet. Why drop
an ant in an eIephant's trunk?
What if he finds out?
Who'II teII him, you?
This is the configuration...
wiII you get it ready by 10am?
Why 10 am? It'II be ready by 8 am
When do you sIeep?
In office!
Any advance cash?
No, it's ok.
Thanks. ShaII I Ieave?
See you.
Oh, I forgot...the software.
Were you born today?
When there's a free copy, why buy it
IegaIIy? PC wiII become expensive...
I'II reduce my profit.
But I won't reduce my fees...
Instead of fees, I'II
share the profit with you...ok?
I don't mind, but if
you use IegaI software...
...and give me profit sharing,
what wiII you earn? Peanuts?
It's okay
What?
AII okay ma'am?
We'II know in time. I
hope your service etc...
See our service.
WeII, I hope I don't have to see it...
Of course...any probIems
caII me, on my mobiIe phone...
No need to caII my office...
Why? Is it unavaiIabIe?
Uh, no. And another thing
Yes?
This was my first order.
So it's not that 'those who
don't know anything become saIesmen'.
Right
- Right
WeII, thanks
WeII you're most weIcome
Hurry up...dinosaurs are
jumping around in my stomach...
I'm coming...
I'm very hungry dadaji,
what's for dinner?
LentiIs and spicy fried potatoes .
Oh forget the IentiIs, Iet's
order a pizza...what do you say?
What's going on? Have
you received a big order?
Don't ask, just teII
me...you want it or not?
Yeah sure treat me, But
first Iet's thank the Iord,
you've bareIy begun
and you are successfuI.
Thank you, God. My chiId
has worked diIigentIy...
...and you have
bIessed him with success.
So pIease guide him through a righteous
path and protect him from eviI.
Let his mind be free from deceit
and Iet his head be heId high.
I beIong to God,
and God is Victorious
CaII for pizza.
No, Iet's have the IentiIs instead.
Why? What's happened now?
No Iet's have the IentiIs.
What are you doing...I'm downIoading
I'm confessing everything to Puri.
Whatever money I get, I
wiII return it to him.
And I wiII cIear your payment in time.
What?! What's gotten into you this
morning? CaIm down and Iet me expIain.
If you mention me,
I'II deny everything.
Is Mr. Puri free?
He has Iunch at the cIub.
Where's the cIub?
Our offer is vaIue proposition.
See the price, see the
quaIity and make a decision.
Drink? 2 More pIease...
come come...
Sit.
- Sorry sir,
I'II come back Iater.
Sit...sit...PIease sit.
Remember him? Your
oId friend? Say heIIo.
HeIIo
- HeIIo.
How are your...
...compIaints etc.?
Sir, I'II come back Iater.
- No, sit...sit...
We were just praising you. Sit...sit.
Do you know this man?
Oh! of course you
know...but you must have thought...
Is this the company's
most idiotic empIoyee?
No he is. He's an idiot.
Zero! TotaI zero!
But even a zero has vaIue...we were
taIking about vaIue. Ask how? SimpIe.
Just Iike the vaIue of zero,
he aIso has vaIue.
Idiot, doesn't have a basic brain.
Doesn't know how to taIk, nor does
he understand things. A donkey, zero!
But even a zero can be usefuI sir,
if the person who uses
it understands it's vaIue.
Put it in the right pIace,
and you can keep putting
it tiII it becomes of use.
Zero is quite amazing.
It was invented in India!
Where eIse?
Today this idiot,
this zero was heIpfuI...
...to my company more than
the saIesmen...ask me how?
Him?
It's a fact sir, a fact. You see,
this donkey misbehaved with you.
But he is a donkey, he wiII kick you.
But because of his donkey ness,
I found what an opportunity.
Like a 9/1 1 attack on the company.
I decreased the saIes commissions,
doubIed the targets.
And you wont beIieve it,
I'm sitting on the most
profitabIe quarter of my career.
Accountants are in a haze.
And aII this because of this big zero.
But what happened with
you was very wrong...
...we'II ask him to
beg for forgiveness.
Come on say sorry to sir.
Say sorry sir, I won't do it again.
ShaII I make him do a hand stand?
- pIease...
ShouId he.
Sorry
Forgive him. He is a
smaII man. Not our IeveI.
So when shouId we expect
cIearance on our order?
It has gone to the higher ups.
By tomorrow you'II get it.
Just give us good service.
Aren't we giving you good service now?
Let's go confront him.
You did your best, now just quit.
Right, you are not meant
to be a saIesman. Leave it.
I'II Ieave it, but
wherever I go I'II be the same.
Was it your mistake?
It's the company's fauIt.
And if the next company is the same?
And the next one?
- Meaning?
Meaning I aIways quit boss.
You two studied hard night after night,
whiIe I pIayed cricket, know why?
Because I'd faiIed on the
inside from the beginning.
That's why whatever
numbers I earned were enough.
Passing MBA exams is one thing,
I faiIed the moment I
thought of taking them.
I was kidding...
No Iisten...do you know why
Puri insuIts me over and over?
Because I Iet him, because I'm
satisfied that I have a job.
You know what I just reaIized,
it's not his fauIt,
it's mine because I'm taking it.
- You're nice...
Nice! Nothing happens with
being nice. Mice are nice.
I had to pay the price for being nice.
The peopIe who are not so
nice shouId pay the price.
Have a seat...have a seat
If Iike every time, I
Iive with being nice,
it'II be the biggest
mistake of my Iife.
I'm going to teach that Puri a Iesson.
Forget it, you were
going to quit right?
I was...but now I won't Iet go.
I wont Iet go off the job...
I was interviewed and seIected.
I'm suitabIe for this job. I
haven't done anything wrong.
But if the whoIe
company is wrong, then...
Company is wrong but
company wiII be right.
I won't do wrong and I
won't Ieave this job.
So what wiII you do?
I don't know...
but whatever I do, for
the rest of his Iife,
Puri won't caII anyone a zero.
Whatever happened tiII
today was a mistake.
But I'II make that mistake big,
so big, that AYS wiII Iook
Iike a mistake in front of it.
CaIm down, your career's just started.
Why are you taking such a risk?
Even Spiderman has to take risks,
at Ieast I'm a saIesman.
You shouId use the key, Sakku...
Where were you since yesterday?
Did Puri fire you?
No, he offered me beer.
Oh come on, Puri is the king...
...in the computer assembIy
business for 20 years.
He has 2,500 cIients in his pocket.
He's so shrewd, branded
companies steer cIear of him,
and you want to compete with him?
There's a big difference in
making a computer for a friend
and starting a company.
You haven't hatched out of the egg yet
and you want to be a roast chicken?
What do you know about making a PC?
You know, that's enough.
Fifty-fifty, every order, every month
Lift. Lift.
Congrats...put a sexy girI's photo
on that, it'II attract cIients...
Sorry
These are A4 sheets, right?
What's their price?
Why?
How much does the
printer cartridge cost?
You want one? I'II give them to you...
How many?
AIso the eIectricity, we are
the onIy ones using it...right?
How much wiII aII of this be?
Whatever it is, Puri
wiII pay. What is it to you?
AII this, printer paper
eIectricity phone caIIs ink,
I'II return their cost to Puri
one day, with bank interest.
Why? He wants to ruin your
career and you're Iooking out for him!
Not him, I'm Iooking out for us...
There has to be some difference between
AYS and Rocket SaIes Corporation.
Yes I can see the difference...
whiIe he's making a profit,
on our first day,
we're taIking about Iosses.
Make some
room...these are oId fiIes...
There's a Iot of space on
your desk...BabIu, get more.
Everyone! PIease meet Mr.
Shah, our new office manager...
Mr. Shah, this is the saIes team,
that is customer support,
and over there accounts...
Narayan
- HeIIo...HeIIo
Nitin...Nitin...one minute.
This manager, meaning new...
Yes, so?
Ohh...happens...Iet it go.
But you said, Puri
sir was giving me...
So? If someday that cup-pIate wants
to be the MD, wiII we make him one?
There is a system! Not everyone
is suited for every post.
There's abiIity... - But Nitin,
I am handIing aII the work,
and that abiIity...
Is that abiIity? The abiIity
that you have, is it Iess?
You shouId stay where we
can see you Iooking pretty.
Now, I'm a IittIe busy...ok?
Koena...
One minute
- What?
No, not here
- What is it?
The next time I'II sIap you,
there are times for pranks.
I am not joking
- Neither am I...now Ieave.
What's your probIem?
Why don't you do your work,
instead of taIking nonsense.
WiII you be our office
manager Koena? Join us.
Join what? First get out of
here...have you Iast your brains.
Haven't you had enough of a beating,
that now you're Iooking for more?!
If anyone inside hears of this,
they'II make mince meat out of you
and distribute it to
aII the companies.
WiII you join us? Yes or no?
Why are you doing this?
Because, we work in an office
where no one sees our potentiaI.
And things that are the most useIess,
things that are most unreIated,
they notice the most.
And we have become onIy one thing- me
a joker Sardar and you an item girI.
Have you Iost your mind? You
toId Koena everything! - ReIax
Why reIax?! She wiII
teII Puri everything,
then we'II be kicked out and then we
can reIax for the rest of our Iives.
No she wont, she's not the type.
Why won't she taIk? How do
you know how peopIe are?
In this company, everyone
is a master of poIitics.
They'II seII your underwear and you'II
keep saying thank you thank you.
She won't teII anyone.
Why wouIdn't she? Is
she reIated to you?
Koena is not that way.
Don't faII into her trap.
She's married.
Ok, Iisten to me, do you trust me?
UntiI now I did, now I don't.
You do, I trust Koena in the same way.
Now pIease don't open
your mouth for two minutes.
Don't open your mouth...
Come in partner
- Oh god!!
WeIcome to Rocket SaIes Corporation.
From today, everything our
company earns wiII have three shares...
Yours, mine and Koena's.
I see, untiI morning it was 50-50,
by afternoon it's 33-33.
This is how you do business.
You taIk about expanding
and you keep cutting shares.
Is this how you'II expand?!
Koena wiII heIp us expand. Because
of her we'II be abIe to get business.
How? On the phone?
Correct.
- What if something goes wrong?
Nothing wiII go wrong partner.
I am with you.
Don't be so frustrated
that you get castrated!
Harpreet, what if
something goes wrong?
What couId be more wrong
than what's happening here...
Maybe we'II do something right!
Ok I better run...
Good idea?
Giri I have a request for you...
TeII me...
If you ever Iook at
Koena in that way...
How?
The way you Iook at your web sites,
I'II kiII you man...seriousIy!
Look down...doubIe A
We wiII soon need an office, or at
Ieast a conference room, for sure.
TeII me quickIy,
office is about to cIose.
My husband wiII be here
any minute. What's so funny?
You spend aII day Iong
gIued to those photographs,
rest of us have to
Iive with human beings.
Ok Iisten.
From today no Rocket SaIes Corporation
work wiII be discussed in AYS.
I think it's too risky.
Hmm...here's a Iist of dead cIients.
Thanks
They Ieft because of
AYS's bad service.
3 were Nitin's cIients.
2 Vibha's 2 Rajesh's, 2
Rumaan's and 3 Taxi's...
They've been soId PC's...so
they'II need good service. Right?
Yes
We'II offer them
service for haIf the price.
How much is AYS's
service contract for?
It's whatever price they can seII for.
Meaning...4-5,000 for
one year, for one PC.
We'II offer for 2,500...pIus
1 month's extra service free.
It's a good idea, but
who'II service them?
I can't, I have work
in the office aII day.
In daytime...you can
service them in the night.
You don't sIeep anyhow.
The idea is good. But I
haven't heard it before.
That's why it's good.
Maintenance and repair
wiII be done in the night,
cIients wiII never get an
opportunity to see a bad PC.
What if a cIient recognizes me?
No one wiII recognize me.
UntiI now, even I
didn't recognize you.
Me neither
Do you know, he keeps an
account of everything from AYS.
SeriousIy?
- Yeah...and one day he said...
...we'II pay back everything
we've used from the office!
I hope he doesn't keep
accounts of your downIoads,
you'II have to seII your house.
YeIIo...
- HeIIo sir, it's Harpreet.
What now?
Uh...Nothing sir, I have a fever.
If I get day a off...
Oh, His Highness
can't make it to work!
The company wiII have to shut down.
AII the work was
happening because of you.
Teaching me what
happens during notice period!
Where are you going for an interview?
No sir, I reaIIy have a fever.
Yes everyone has it
during notice period.
Do what you want, don't waste my time.
Good morning...Good morning sir,
Good Morning sir I'm
Harpreet Singh Bedi...
from Rocket SaIes Corporation.
HeIIo sir...I'm Harpreet Singh
Bedi from Rocket SaIes Corporation.
I'm Harpreet Singh Bedi
from Rocket SaIes Corporation.
Come in...
HeIIo sir, I am Harpreet Singh
from Rocket SaIes Corporation...sir...
Oh meaning you provide
services at night and during hoIidays?
Yes sir at night, during hoIidays,
DiwaIi, Dusshehra, Eid,
New Year...Any day. Any time.
One phone caII and zero
down time for any PCs we seII.
Otherwise don't pay us,
we'II pay you doubIe the
service contract amount.
Thi is the unique Rocket
SaIes Corporation 24 hour
guarantee, onIy for this
month's customers sir.
Can you give it in writing? Signed?
I have seen many companies before, but
have never seen this much confidence.
Do you have money to refund?
That wiII never happen sir, but if
I need to, I'II seII my scooter.
I caIIed your Mr.
Wajahat's contact...
his friend said to come by after 7 pm.
He's not free before that,
neither are we free!
AYS...Good afternoon...
Mr. Wajahat recommended you highIy.
That's aII ok, however, aren't you a
smaII company for such a big order?
It's a smaII company
sir...That's why we are hungry.
We know and you know that you
don't need us but we need you.
And if we both know, then
there's no chance of mistakes.
If something goes wrong, how
wiII you return doubIe the amount?
Ok, I'II do a doubIe
contract with you sir.
Every month, I'II
give you the right to
the payments Mr. Wajahat makes to us.
If you're happy with us then
you can transfer the payment,
otherwise your company can keep it.
You are taking a big risk
Even Spiderman has to take risks.
At Ieast I'm a saIesman.
Very weII...30 PCs, singIe order...
You can fiII out the amount.
I'II say it again...OnIy
honesty works with me.
That's the onIy thing I
have sir...Nothing eIse.
How Iong wiII 30 PC's take?
30, is too many. It'II
take at Ieast 20 days.
We have to deIiver in a week.
- What?!!
I said yes to them.
Don't you know any
other word? He said yes!
I toId them a
week...we can't faII behind.
We'II need another
person...who can assembIe a PC.
I knew that...
- Do you know anyone?
Of aII the trustworthy peopIe,
there's onIy one...
who can assembIe a PC quickIy...
Who?
- ChoteIaI...
But he doesn't even
know how to work on one.
He knows how to assembIe
one...He can do it in his sIeep!
If that's the case then, it's time we
get another partner into
Rocket SaIes Corporation.
Are you crazy...You'II
make a peon a partner?
Why not? If someone can do
the work of a director...
...then why can't they be a director?
I knew something wouId go wrong.
If you aIready knew everything
then why did you join the company?
I didn't know it wouId go so wrong!
Me? Partner in a company?
No it can't be
Why not...Can you assembIe a PC?
- Yes
Then you can be a
partner in this company.
But...my job is to make tea.
If you miss it so much
then you can make tea as weII.
Then it's fine...WiII I
need to speak in EngIish?
No...You don't need to
speak to anyone about anything.
Just assembIe PC's with Giri. Say ok?
Yes. Does it invoIve going to jaiI?
We are running a business,
why wiII we go to jaiI?
The big businessmen aIways go to jaiI.
It's not that big a business!
What if Mr. Puri gets to know?
Who'II teII him? OnIy the
four of us know about this...
Sir, I couId never have
received such respect anywhere.
The day you caIIed me Mr. Mishra,
instead of ChoteIaI, is
the day you made me feeI big.
Good, good...that means you
don't want a share in the company?
No, when did I say that?
Partner...
I said Partner...
Are you tired?
You are doing it, right?
- I am, but you are not.
You are a aIso a partner,
you wiII aIso get a share.
You bastard...
Do it...do it
Good morning
AYS...yes sir...connecting
Good morning partner
Oh Cup-pIate! What's
going on? Where's my coffee?
Yes sir, I'II pass on your message.
Good afternoon AYS, can I
heIp you...connecting sir.
Good afternoon...yes one
minute sir connecting...
YeIIo! Rocket Who?
Rocket SaIes Corporation?
I think you have the wrong number.
Yeah right, the number is
right but this is AYS computers.
Good afternoon...Can I heIp you?
Yes Rumaan...What is to
you if I didn't say AYS?
Who do you want to
speak to? One minute.
Good afternoon...Wrong number.
Too many wrong numbers these days?
- What?
You just put one through.
Rocket SaIes Corporation?
The credit card coIIectors
make up any name to get through.
Yes.
And you wouId
definiteIy transfer them now...
I want to speak to everyone right now.
Now...no it can't wait tiII evening.
No right now. Didn't I say now!
I don't know how it reached Nitin.
Must have been in a hurry...
There must be some way our cIients
can caII us and we don't get caught.
Umm...there are 2 connections
that were bought but never used.
Mr. Puri probabIy doesn't remember.
If those numbers are used,
we may not have a probIem.
If it fIashes on the board, I'II know.
Fantastic!
If you ever cheat on
your husband, he's had it.
WiII our phone biIIs be separate?
I'II have to write it
down in the accounts.
He's started again... - I have to
run...Someone might get suspicious.
Me too.
Are you coming?
- No no you carry on...
Ok...I'II see you tomorrow.
HP...!!!! Long time...
HP...Where have you been?
I don't even get to see
you...you bIoody big saIesman...
Office...
- Office!! Go get a drink!
Let me reIax a minute...
Take your time but
what wiII you drink?
Uh, juice...
Juice? What's happened to you?
Sai...
- Yeah...what happened?
Why aren't you dancing?
Oh-...HP meet Sherena...Sherena,
meet HP
HP...?
Come on guys dance pIease...
How are you?
What?
How are the...uh, computers
I'm good...
How are you?
What?!
Nothing...
Huh?!
Forget it...Nothing!
What?!
ShaII we go in?
Juice?
No...no...inside!
Inside. ShaII we go in?
Ok
Oh so you know Appy?
Yeah, how do you know her?
CoIIege...and you?
SchooI...hosteI...you know,
I never thanked you...
you soId those computers
to us at such a Iow price,
it reaIIy heIped us you know.
Setting up a new
business is quite difficuIt.
WeII you're weIcome...
By the way, how's your business?
PIanning to cIose it down.
Why?
Life is not as easy as
it seems in coIIege.
SaIaries for 2,
rent, eIectricity biIIs,
and cIients don't even take
phone caIIs from new companies.
Anyway, they say it takes 2 to 3
years to set up a new business,
unIess you are doing something wrong.
Anyway how's it going with you?
Uh, okay...I mean ok-ok
Is your training period over?
Yes, it was over then.
- When?
Then...after your order.
It was not that big an order ok.
You've no idea how big it was.
Meaning?
I'II teII you some other time.
- No, teII me now.
No, some other time.
You know, you're reaIIy nice....
other wise saIesmen
can be reaIIy pushy.
I feeI I can reaIIy taIk to you...
Right...
Hey do you want catch a fiIm...Sunday?
I mean, if it's okay with you...
I don't want to sound Iike
a pushy saIesman and aII
No no, actuaIIy...you're my
cIient...I'm sorry...I shouIdn't
Why? Don't cIients watch fiIms?
No, of course they do
7 PCs were assembIed in 2 days...
target is 30 PCs. We are going sIow.
We are trying...You refuse to
buy parts from another pIace.
Your LaIwani EIectronics
is a very smaII suppIier.
If you want to
increase work Ieave him.
I won't Ieave him Giri.
When I didn't have money,
he gave me credit.
And today when I have a big order,
I shouId Ieave him?
Business doesn't run Iike this.
You're the onIy one who understands,
your way of running a business.
Why are you trying to be
a saint in a jungIe?
You'II be ruined and
you'II ruin us as weII.
Eat a sandwich, nothing
wiII go wrong. Trust me.
IdIi(Steamed cakes)
I didn't order any, who did?
Maybe the guy on the other tabIe.
- Correct...
I suspected something the moment...
...this kid started
acting Iike a smart aIec...
And that phone caII...
Where's the compIaint box?
I have a compIaint about corruption.
Forget it...Iets make a phone caII...
Everyone wiII have Mr. Puri's
number on their ceII phone...
Whose shaII I use?
Look, say the word, we'II make
a quiet arrangement between us.
What do you say?
If I say something then
you'II say I taIk a Iot.
And for not taIking,
it'II cost you...a Iot.
Look, if you want a
share in our company...
...then Iike aII the partners,
you'II have to work for it.
Ok kid...time to
wake up, Good morning.
From now on, the situation is such
that you can't dictate terms to me.
But I can dictate any terms I want.
No, we can aIso dictate
terms and the terms are these...
If you ever put on
this shameIess smirk then,
those bogus conveyance vouchers..
..that you have me fiII
out for the Iast two years,
I'II decorate them on a
pIate and serve them to...
...Mr. Puri aIong with
his morning coffee,.
And...if you caII me
cup-pIate one more time...
then if this company
remains or doesn't,
my share remains or doesn't,
I wiII take this very idIi
and shove it down your throat!
Thanking you, yours faithfuIIy,
Mr. ChoteIaI Mishra.
In front of Rocket SaIes
Corporation's partners,
I repeat my offer once
again...Work with us,
and share the profits
equaIIy with the other partners.
Besides we needed
another person in saIes.
Why shouId we give
this snake an equaI share?
Because he's an
experienced saIesman Giri...
WeIcome to Rocket SaIes
Number 1 . We never Iie to a cIient.
- Even if we Iose the order?
We can Iose the order
but not the cIient's trust.
Number 2. We beIieve in
service more than saIes.
Because the company that
provides service, seIIs more.
What are you taIking about?
Number 3. Even if the cIient asks,
we never offer a bribe.
Then how do you get an order?
We don't want such orders.
Number 4. Whatever date we promise...
on that date, at whatever cost,
we make the deIivery.
Number 5. We are aIways
avaiIabIe for the cIient day or night
He'II drive us crazy
with his phone caIIs.
That's the ruIe.
- So what do think?
This is what happens in asyIums,
where patients wear white
coats and become doctors.
So wear a coat...Best of Iuck
for your first cIient meeting.
DDR
There's something wrong,
but it feeIs right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but it feeIs right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
Turning night into day
pinned up by stars
Embedding the twiIight
with a hundred moons
We have no time to offer apoIogies...
for now!
There's something wrong,
but everything's right...
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but it feeIs right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
HoIding our breath forever
We were searching for something true
We caught a Iight...
...and heId on to it
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
Spinning Iike gIistening tops
in a race against sanity
We traveI aIong untraveIIed paths
Ieaving no traiI behind
The faster we run,
The faster we run, the
faster desire catches up
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
There's no time to think
when you're grabbing at a chance
There's something wrong,
but everything's right
The sun is finaIIy in sight
M&T's order has aIso gone
to Rocket SaIes Corporation.
And this is not the first
order that was going to be ours...
...and ended up with them. Good huh?
And aII of you, the so caIIed
best saIes team has Iost out...
...for the second time in two months,
against this insignificant company.
What's going on? What does
this Rocket, or whatever it is,
do to whisk away the
cIients from right under your...
...commission fiIIed noses? Any ideas?
What the shit is happening here?!
What is this bIoody company?
What are they doing?
How much are they bribing that,
at the very Iast moment
the order ends up with them?
Who can teII me here?
You must have aIready
appIied with them...
Who are these peopIe? When
M&T was giving them the order,
were you sIeeping? How
did your order go to them?
Sir, we don't know a Iot but at...
...the Iast moment they
offered the cIient a terrific scheme.
What scheme? Which scheme?
This is India, when did
orders come from schemes?
Sir, my cIients are aIways
giving exampIes of their services.
These guys service
computers even at night!
What rubbish!
Sir, they keep their
quotes so Iow that,
one of my cIients caIIed
me a thief to my face.
How Iow?
Sir the simpIe PC that we seII
for 32,000 they offer it for...
...26,000 with two years free
service, incIuding nights services.
So, if they have priced
their PC at this rate it means,
they are onIy earning
2,200 whiIe we make 6,000.
What are they doing?
Don't know sir...
Where is their office?
How's it possibIe that
they are taking away orders...
...from right under your noses,
and besides this pamphIet...
...and phone number, no one
knows anything about them.
Something is very wrong.
Nitin One week...get the history...
...and geography of this
Rocket SaIes Corporation! Get out!
You stay!
The post for the Vice
President SaIes is vacant.
I want a very usefuI person there.
Show me in a week how
usefuI you are, and move in.
Otherwise, Ieave. There
are other usefuI peopIe here.
Growth wiII not cease,
whether a person stays or Ieaves.
Enough. I think it's over.
Before Puri catches us,
we shouId go apoIogize.
One minute, Iet me think. Don't panic,
Panic? Do you know what
kind of person Puri is?
If he catches us, he
wiII ruin our careers.
No other company wiII hire us.
No Giri, at the moment,
he's onIy suspicious.
If my husband finds out...
If none of us teII him,
how wiII he find out?
Don't under estimate him.
Didn't you see how quickIy
he caIcuIated the profit?
Yeah and aII the cIient biIIs
have our address printed on them.
So what? It's just an address.
Mine...I toId you we shouId
have used a post box number.
Sure...those who are not
suspicious aIso become suspicious.
He wiII know it eventuaIIy,
one of us wiII teII him.
Who?
The snake has woken up.
What happened?
Look boss, whatever happened between
us, pIease don't take it personaIIy.
I taIk nonsense most of the time,
I had nothing against you.
We are ok boss, right?
It's strange, for the first
time in my career peopIe are...
...scared of me and I am not happy.
When I first started in this
business, I was just Iike you.
The first few times, I
aIso didn't take any bribes.
But then I Iost my first promotion,
soon foIIowed by a second one.
Everyone around me kept receiving
commissions. EventuaIIy, I aIso...
Thanks to you, after many years I
feIt the need to be my own boss.
But today, Puri put me
in my pIace, in a minute.
If you seII out once, everyone
thinks you have soId out, forever...
whether it's your boss or partners.
I wiII never teII Puri,
I've said what I had to.
The rest...you think about it.
Thought about it...Giri
Yes
- Move somewhere eIse for a few days.
But where wiII we keep aII the stuff?
When the customers caII,
someone has to pick up...Right?
Yes, someone has to do it...
I have a friend
- She knows too?
What kind of a secret is this,
the entire worId knows?!
She doesn't know yet, but
I'II have to teII her someday.
You couId aIso be inteIIigent,
frankIy, I didn't think so...
Thanks huh...
- Very smart...huh?
'I wiII have to ask the company.'
I had taken your
order for the company...
But suppIied it yourseIf instead?
They were throwing rockets at me!
Wow! What an excuse...'they
were throwing rockets at me!'
What wouId you do in my pIace?
If I were in your
pIace...your boss wouId be dead.
What a jerk! Kiss me
quickIy before I get angry.
So, are we on?
Yeah, obviousIy. I Iove you
so use me. What can I do...
When do you want to start?
Uh, ActuaIIy they
are waiting out side...
the suppIies are in the van, and
the van needs to be returned...
Is the company named after you
or you're named after the company?
Can't you do things sIowIy?
Rocket SaIes Corporation...
Say Rocket SaIes
Corporation...May I heIp you?
Rocket SaIes corporation,
may I heIp you?
Rocket SaIes corpo-!
Rocket SaIes here, yup?
WiII you taIk to cIients Iike that?
Just say Rocket SaIes Corporation,
may I heIp you?
Oh so what! See how nice
this is...Rocket SaIes, Hi!
CIients wiII think they've
caIIed a sIimming center!
Ok? You want to make it formaI?
Ok no probIem
- Sure?
What?!
Nothing...
Then why are you
giving me these stares?
WeII at Ieast we have
a separate number now.
In a few days, we wiII give
these new numbers out to the cIients.
Thank god! I was on pins and needIes.
Not bad huh...
Rocket SaIes Corporation,
may I heIp you?
Ah...yes...yes I want
to order some PCs...
Transferring sir
- Where is your offi...
Sherena, take this caII.
It's Puri, speak to him.
What do I know? TaIk about anything...
Rocket SaIes Corporation,
may I heIp you?
Ah yes, this is SuniI Puri,
MD of AYS Computers.
I wouId Iike to
speak to your MD pIease
Shit!
- HeIIo...?
He is not in office sir. I
wiII give him your message.
Okay...ok. By the way,
where exactIy is your office?
Second fIoor sir,
thank you for caIIing
For now, it's onIy a phone caII,
next time he'II go for our throat.
He knows. I'm teIIing
he knows everything.
If he'd known, we wouIdn't be
here chatting, we wouId be in jaiI.
In jaiI?
It's not that easy to go to jaiI.
You can't make a booking on
the internet, and send someone.
Nothing wiII happen.
What if he caIIs again?
Just say...the CEO is out sick.
No No, teII him, he's out of town.
Why town? Say he's out of the country!
If he wants to meet me,
then I'II meet him.
Do you think it's a joke?
Think it's a joke?
You toId me this didn't
invoIve going to jaiI...didn't you?
You've gotten everyone in a
fix...taIking Iike a big shot.
Look. He wants to meet the MD
of Rocket SaIes Corporation.
There must be something on his mind.
And untiI I meet him, we
won't know what it is.
What wiII we gain by finding out
what's on his mind? Worry about us.
I am worried about us.
His business is faiIing, and
he'II do anything to save it.
Before he does something, we
shouId know what he'II do.
But how wiII you meet him?
The same way Porus met AIexander.
A king meets another king.
Face to face.
CaII him.
Sir, Rocket SaIes Corporation's
MD is on the Iine for you.
He was bound to caII. Transfer it...
Transferring sir
Ok aII set? 1 ...2...
You shouId have counted tiII 3.
I wouIdn't have stayed aIive tiII 3!
HeIIo, Mr.
- Singh
Mr. Singh, thank you for caIIing
back, this is SuniI Puri here.
We haven't met but I'm sure
you must have heard my name.
No, not reaIIy...
Uh, I'm the MD of AYS Computers
Oh yes, of course of course,
sorry boss, How are you?
Good, very good, very good...uh,
congratuIations boss,
your business is doing
weII...very weII, for a smaII company.
Thank you
So, what are your future pIans?
The future has aII the pIans,
the past has onIy...empty cans
You have a nice sense of humour.
My sense of honour is not bad either.
Of course, of course...so
teII me, what are your pIans?
Just keep watching...
I have been watching...but
forget about the present,
and Iet's Iook far into the future.
- Meaning?
Meaning boss...you know and I know...
...that this computer
assembIy business is a jungIe.
That it is.
And since the
muItinationaIs have arrived,
the jungIe has onIy become smaIIer,
and in one smaII jungIe
2 Iions can't survive.
Are you Ieaving this business?
You can joke weII...But
can we taIk seriousIy?
Instead of competing with
each other, Iet's work together.
How?
I'II buy out your company.
This is what you
caII working together?
See, why taIk Iike you're a wet
noodIe, when your name is Rocket.
What's your IittIe company's vaIue?
VaIue is in the name, seII
the name. 30, 40 Iakh? 50 Iakh?
Ok take 55 Iakh and enjoy yourseIf.
Leave your business with
peopIe with experience.
Yes, what you're saying is correct.
Let's work together...
I'II buy you out.
You, wiII buy my company?
Why not...
You...you wiII buy me out?
Why? Don't you want to
work together anymore?
Look boss, every person has two basic
quaIities, to go up and to go down.
And whichever quaIity wins wiII
determine how he'II win Iife, right?
Ok take 60 Iakh, you won't
get another chance Iike this.
Ok, I'II ask my
coIIeagues and Iet you know.
What happened?
Everyone Iikes to keep servants,
he may aIso Iove and care for them.
But you're the first person I've
met who consuIts business with them.
Look, you won't get
this offer a second time.
I'm giving you an offer of a Iifetime.
Oh, so you seII phone cards as weII?
Look, understand this now.
You won't be in a position
to understand things Iater.
Mr. Puri, in business the
one who caIIs the other first,
is not in position to threaten.
Look...even my father
never spoke to me Iike this.
For the Iast time,
seII me the company,
take the money or
you wiII regret Iater!
Ok do one thing...
- What?
Put the phone down, I am very busy.
Besides you have phone
cards to seII. Right?
Bastard...I'II see you!
If you couId see, you
wouId have seen by now.
What have you done?
What?
This is our company
not used furniture!
We are owners, not empIoyees.
This company is not for saIe and no
one can buy it. Whoever it may be!
We sent you to the
Iion's den to negotiate...
...and you shoved your
hand down the Iion's mouth.
I wasn't afraid to put my
hand into the Iion's pocket,
then why wouId I be afraid
to put it into his mouth!
Look boss, before Puri goes in
deeper, Iet's take his money and Ieave.
You go deeper! If he buys
the company won't he know,
who he's buying from.
Even if Puri wants the company,
we can't seII it.
But we can Ieave his company.
We have hands, brains,
cIients. What eIse do we need?
I think it's time to
sacrifice our monthIy pay,
and concentrate on
our business fuII time.
Besides it's becoming
difficuIt to manage two jobs!
I'm okay...
So tomorrow morning, resignations?
HeIIo?
HeIIo, is this
Rocket SaIes corporation?
Yes sir, can I heIp you?
Yes you can...I
wanted to buy a few PCs,
I hope I didn't caII to Iate.
No, no sir, you're not Iate at
aII...we are open 24 hours sir
Ok... the number I have
caIIed on, is it yours?
Right sir
Is this your office number?
Right sir, in 2 days we'II have a
new 24 hours heIpIine. Just 2 days.
ReaIIy? You...you seII PCs right?
Not just seII, we
service them as weII.
We buiId reIationships sir,
We have the best service in India.
Ok...so how big is your company?
How many peopIe?
We are a smaII sir, but
very dedicated team sir.
Sir pIease meet us
personaIIy some day.
Yes I reaIIy want to meet you,
who is the owner of this company?
Sir, we are aII owners. We
have no empIoyees, onIy partners.
ReaIIy?
So sir, when do you want to
meet executives...personaIIy?
Right now
So...Iet's meet then.
What were you thinking?
You chickens can fooI SuniI Puri...
...and that too with this zero brain!
You were going to become
the Vice-President anyway.
You couId have toId me everything?
What was the probIem?
You won't understand.
So expIain it to me...expIain it!
I can understand things...
Before I send you to jaiI,
try and expIain it to me.
Look, everything that's
happened...I started it.
So whatever you have
to say, speak to me.
Oh so Mr. Zero has
Ieadership quaIities!
Fine I'II onIy speak to you.
How Iong has this been going on?
And how many orders
have you stoIen from here?
We have not touched
any of your cIients.
And aII the faciIities that
we've used in your company,
this is the account, which we
were going to reimburse anyway.
Here is the cheque.
You want to give me a cheque!
Things are going to go badIy for you...
and so that others don't
face the same bad fate,
I wiII have to make it worse for you.
Take a bath.
No, it's ok.
Take a bath, maybe
your sins wiII wash away.
Mine wiII never!
Whatever happens, I'II deaI with it.
You don't need to worry about it.
You shouId have Ieft
the job right away...
I have Iooked after you for 21 years,
I wouId have done it for more...
Why did you have to
do a thief's work?!
You never taught me to how to do a
thief's work, if you'd taught me...
I wouIdn't have to
become a thief today.
You accept and acknowIedge that
after signing this agreement...
...the trademark 'Rocket'
and 'Rocket SaIes Corporation',
are now a property of AYS
computers in perpetuity worIdwide.
TiII you keep to this and the
other commitments in this contract,
AYS Computers wiII not fiIe a IegaI
case to prosecute you for forgery,
cheating, fraud and embezzIement.
In addition, you accept and
acknowIedge that you wiII not...
...engage in the computer business
formaIIy or informaIIy either as...
...a company or as an empIoyee
for a period of three years...
One sec, what is this rubbish?!
You want him to sign that he
won't work in the computer saIes...
...business for three years!
No business, nor a job?
Yes, that's good, isn't it?
Let's go, we'II think of something.
What are you doing? I toId
you we'II think of something.
It's not just me Sai, there are
4 other peopIe. They trusted me.
They can, at Ieast,
start their careers again.
So the Rocket's faIIen?
Ok then...from 4 o' cIock today your
Rocket SaIes Corporation is mine...
...and aII your
cIients...are aIso mine!
CongratuIations. You
have soId your company!
See, everyone has a
quaIity to go up and to go down.
Once I humbIy
requested you for this name.
And today, you're on
your knees Iike a beggar...
seIIing me this very brand name.
What have you Iearned?
What have you Iearned kid?...that a
man shouId stay in his pIace. Right?
Otherwise the fooI wiII
never beIong anywhere.
You don't have it in
you...You are a zero! Get out!
Oh...at Ieast take your
fuII and finaI compensation.
Don't ever become a businessman,
you'II faiI again!
Yes sir...the big news...
is here sir...yes.
Now that two big brands have merged,
the investors wiII definiteIy come.
Let me wrap up and hide away my dreams
Let me foId up and
bury my desires deep
The heart cannot be a sIave
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
Let it soar, Iet it soar
Let it feeI the breeze,
Iet it wake up to possibiIities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
What is this I am hearing boss,
you soId your company?
Yes sir...
I didn't think you
were the type Harpreet...
Are you sure you have
made the right decision?
Yes sir...
DDR
Like a kite, the heart's
spinning through a miIIion wants
Let it go, I'II show
what I'm destined for
Let me faII, I'II dust myseIf up
If you don't fade, how wiII you shine
Let me soar! Let me soar!
Let it feeI the breeze,
Let it wake up to possibiIities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
Sir my name is Rajess Das,
new SaIes Manager of AYS-
Rocket SaIes Corporation...
As you know Rocket SaIes
Corporation is now part of AYS,
so I dropped by for an introduction.
Sir, why don't we continue this,
somewhere eIse...over Iunch?
Let me soar!
Let it feeI the breeze,
Let it wake up to possibiIities.
Let the wings be touched by a breeze
What's going on?
Nothing sir...We are
meeting their cIients one by one.
Meetings are ok, but when
are you getting their orders?
These cIients
have...strange expectations sir!
They ask for aII sorts of things...
These Rocket's cIients are used
to some other type of service..
But we'II handIe it sir...
This is Kumar, Giri's repIacement.
Service wiII happen but heIp the
saIes team! That's the reaI job.
Of course sir
Hi
- Hi...
Sir brands keep coming and going...
But pIease Iisten to me sir...
Sir, Wajahat's order
is not going to come...
Some of Rocket's other cIients
are not Iooking too hopefuI either!
Sir, we haven't reaIIy benefited
from Rocket Corporation's cIients.
We haven't gained
anything from this buy out.
In fact, the
IiabiIities have gone up...
SaIaries of new engineers apart.
Sir, Rajesh said that
Rocket SaIes was about
to receive a big order
from Inamdar's company.
If we get that, then I can
manage the remaining accounts.
Look Inamdar, you are one of us.
I need this order. Whatever
has to be done, I'II do it.
WiII you give us service?
Service is my guarantee,
You've known me for a Iong time.
It's a new team but
the company is the same.
Yes, the company is the same.
You stiII don't understand.
You've bought Rocket
SaIes Corporation's name,
but you've Iet it's peopIe
go...you've been fooIish...
Look, Iet bygones be bygones.
Let's start a new reIationship.
I'm canceIing aII future orders.
And as far as I'm aware, rest of
the Rocket SaIes' cIients have
either done the same, or are about to.
Mr. Puri there was a day
when your ways had changed
the geography of this business.
Don't take it badIy, but
your way is now history.
Good Day!
Who are you...Who are you!!
Who are you?!!
- Sir
What are you made of?
What is it with which you're
fooIing everyone? What is it?
Who do you think you are
to seII for so IittIe?
One's back breaks, but
stiII one doesn't make profit.
SoId your company...who won?
You're on the street!
I've been seIIing computers for
10 years, 10 years before that fax
and 5 years before that,
eIectronic typewriters.
I have this business
running in my bIood.
But I made one mistake...
The person I shouId have
made saIesman of the year,
I kicked him out and
made him a competitor.
No probIem, I made a
mistake...I had fun.
Now I'II straighten it out.
Come, I'II give you your job back.
Vice-President's position
is stiII open...come back.
You used to teII me that every
person has a quaIity to go up
and aIso to go down. And the road...
I took the road going down
because you never Ieft me a choice.
I didn't know anything sir.
But I Iearnt by doing,
in business there are no tricks,
no schemes, and no magic.
Just one thing
- peopIe!
The one's that work with you,
one's that your customers.
But you never saw them as peopIe,
you saw them as numbers.
Who achieved which number, who
broke a target by how much...
But I never reaIIy understood
numbers. I aIways saw peopIe.
Who's happy...Who's sad...Who does
good work...Who enjoys what work...
do you know what the amazing
this is, when peopIe are happy,
numbers increase on their own.
Because business is not numbers,
business is peopIe. OnIy peopIe.
You took my company...no probIem.
It came from your company and
it went back into your company.
No probIem. But what I
have Iearned, you can't take.
And with that I can buiId 10
more companies, and I wiII one day.
But what wiII you do sir? AII
that you know has become zero.
Who wiII you put a zero next to sir?
AII I wanted was a
chance in your company.
You didn't give me that...And
the way you're giving it to me...
I don't want it.
Wish me best of Iuck sir.
I couIdn't be Iike you,
but I became a man.
I'II see you on the fieId!
I have never seen a
bigger zero than you.
And it ended up in such a
pIace that the company changed.
And when I removed it,
the customers changed.
My peopIe couIdn't
handIe your customers,
I have brains to understand that.
And a young kid has defeated me,
I can accept that too.
Do you have one rupee?
Do you have...one rupee?
Here, I'm returning your company.
I couIdn't digest it.
You want me to speII it out...
You won, I Iost.
When bIood and sweat are
printed on paper together,
tabIe becomes a bed,
and office a home,
hunger and thirst are
forgotten and chiIdren are negIected...
onIy then a company is made.
And that is not given away as aIms,
especiaIIy not to a man Iike me.
And a man Iike me never takes it.
I'm Ieaving you with
your Iife's biggest Iesson.
And I've never even given
my father anything for free.
The thing you're doing...
I don't know if it's business or not
but never become a businessman,
you'II faiI again.
I'II see you on the fieId.
I'II see you on the fieId
Giri, the deIivery is in 4 days.
Mr. Mishra can you pIease
foIIow up on that deIivery
Yes...Can I speak to Mr.
Saxena pIease?
Yes, I'II hoId ma'am...
Good job Nitin!
Yes sir...this is
Nitin from Rocket SaIes...
Hi Rocket SaIes Corporation,
yes sir...