Harpeet you also has been passed
Lets have a drink
lts your house and DJ is saying Thank You
Give him some more money
He's not giving the money...
its 2 o clock I want to wake up early
If you want to wake up early
so why you became DJ?
I'll see later
If he's dont understand with money
so I'd be a serious matter.
Everyone dont understand with money.
So how can he understand?
Have you heard the name persue?
Nothing can be happen with 39% B.COM
I told him to apply for CAT,
but he is not listening to me
What yod did?
Your negotiation is finished?
Lets talk about work
I'm talking about your work
What happen to me?
Means you are notjoing CAT?
If my grandpa would've be a rich
like your father, so he'd give it.
What he'll do?
Want to become salesman?
Why salesman aren't human being?
They are...
definetly.
But they're not more rich people
remember that bahadur?
Now he's a salesman.
He earns 40 thousands a month.
And for having commision, have
to get a order, and for getting order
you dont know what have to done.
Whatever I'm going so you're against it
He's habitual to give lectures.
Lets dance
Now you'll say I have no brain.
What do I say?
I dont want to dance.
Eat some yogurt and sugar.
Did you took all certificates?
Specially Charactor certificates.
I'm eating the yougurt and other side...
If you'd have spend your wit in
education So I'd not eat you yogurt
What your company makes?
I'll get know in the way.
The makes computer...
they have less number no brain.
However he is but he's yours...
bless him.
Give me, I'll talk.
Never poop over others wife and clients
You'll not get burnt your hand.
All are...
You dont say when you got territory...
what we say?
If we says...
so our voice echo's there.
I lost the commision of this month
I just kept the LCD...
She'll yell at me
Go attend your client...
he's calling since 4 days.
Ask to them after selling them
Cliends must be thinking to where
the salesman goes after selling?
I told you thatjust reboot it once
He's not in india now
Did you give him coffee?
Yes he've drunk 4 till now.
Sir, a call for you on line 2
Cant you say it earlier?
You were busy.
How can you become salesman
Where is a confrence room?
In the sky.
Follow me
your salesman's reputation is good.
You can make it good more.
Want to become salesman?
Yes sir
Do you know how to sale.
Yes sir.
Sale me this pencil in 100 rupees.
You convince me to buy it.
Its worth is not 100 rupees. If you
cant sale me so how can I give you job
Sorry we've taken the stock pencil this year
Just let me give you demo.
Why to give demo about eraserless pencil
lts not eraserless pencil...
its a detachement pencil
The coin is unbreakable in the pencil
If you push it hardly so it'll broke
You cant sale it by lying
This eraser is a specially imported
perfumed eraser
Do I've to put this in my nose?
No sir
You can hitch by it.
And also can use it like tooth pick
You can dress you hair...
and can reboot your mobile
even then if you're not fullfilled?
So you can pass your time...
As you're doing now.
Sir the salesmans's interview...
he's useless
Sales works by balance sheet not
by mark sheet
He was selling the 2 rupee's
pencil like 20 lacs mercedes.
He's must be talented
Give him address and everything
tomorrow is sunday let him roam.
Whoever will sale more will become
salesman of the year.
Will get the commision and will
go to goa...
He was making a new slogan
yesterday
Whoever sales can come...
and who dont sales so bye...
What's that mean
It happens in sales
who cant perform...
so he've to leave
Where the person will go.
Wherever he go
he can join some other company...
if that company will be like them so?
This generation is not like yours...
go to office 9 to 5 daily
lts something else about your genration
what the professionals thinks
about that work
nothing...
just thinks its a work
just do your work like veneration
And leave it all to God.
He was honest
Adjust his fee...
who will go
Didn't audit since many years.
I want to see territory accounts
You are wearing it front side back.
Your father ows a laundry...
do your work
Here's all inquiry will go
to directories...
But its a residencial area...
If it would be so what will you do
What're you doing...
writting the company's name
Sales first rule...
never write correct name of your and compnay's
no one sees the register of company.
But competitor will scan it.
Is that a name?
I'm entered here...
do whatever you want to do
lts mean the order is in his pocket
boss you?
Since long time
What's the matter?
That monao had come many times
what happend?
Nothing.
You'll grew up when
you'll reach to client
Will you say something
or smile like a fool?
Sharma is busy!
Why?
Can't you come to meet you... without
any reason you dont meet with your wife
sit down there.
Its not a misery days now.
The spider man have to take risk...
eventhen you're salesman
go
really...
I got second one
You go first...
he's mood is off
How are you... you dont remind
me when you became sales manager
there's nothing like it...
I used to come to you always
Is there a training going on with you.
I've canceled the trip
There's load of work in office.
But there's others for working in office
I heared it but didn't seen yet
I've sent you quotation...
Is that a quatation?
You do mails anything...
He's a kid...
he need time to learn
You tell me what quoation
do you want to make
What is concern about him with
that order?
Lts not his department...
no sir
they're saying that they are promoted
and purchshing is in his under
do one work
Send a fresh qoute 10 lacs 10 thousands.
Along with put warranty and
free service.
They're non professional.
He's my cousin
I was just introducing myself
How come you know the trick about manno...
But how come you know their quotation
by reading...
but sharma didn't show us quotation
No one shows quotation...
we've to poop in
You can read it upside down?
The salesman cant read upside down,
do you know what we call to him
blind
What are you saying...
its my prospect...
Did you got the target
no...
where from can I get it
I'm warning you not to see
my clients or I'll fix you
I'm koina...
who'll call you.
Stand up and see
how much time will you take...
client is waiting for an hour
Tell me the estimate
Dont know...
there's a problem
Just open it...
push it
reboot it
It has started...
tell the client that his
mother board has been burnt
Have to put new one
It will cost 5000 for fix it
Compressor has been burnt...
you didn't put the ups...
It will take one day for fix it.
Why are you taking money for?
For experiens
he'll be expericend for one week
It will be fix in 5 minute...
will he give me 10000?
If we send it to london so
can company can earn
will you give me at night.
Should i pack it up...
to whom?
Spider man has to take risk
Is your name mishara?
Take this intership
what are you doing
go ahead
this post was vacant since many days.
He'd make some atleast
even then I'm handling all work
He was after me since 2months
do you think you can do his job
If you says yes so will I fire him?
You're not emotional in situation
You've quality to go high
also have quality to going down
in the end which quality will survive
will get you winner
where do you want to go
Up or down?
Up
to going up, you've to
step up on everbody's head
After 70's person life will
start from zero.
I ve'nt two minutes...
I want to pee
I'm wating for you and
you've no two minutes for me
lts your carpet...
dont blaim me if something happens
Will you ride the scooter in this age.
Why should I ride
I was sitting pillion like king
Will you ride?
Do I ride the scooter
I told you do joke after 9:30 o clock.
When did i said I need scooter
just go to bathroom...
then we'll talk
What do you want to talk.
You're booking the scooter...
What is the advance...
I've paid fully payment
is someone gives scooter
in half money
just ride once
you have taken the money in advance
I justjoined last week
And I got the target today
so my work starts now
Really...
you're learning so fast
Drop this quatation in the way.
National chemicals is not in my way
first stop and client then on God
I've control on emotions...
and got petrol on scooter
remaining? Tell me your requirement>?
I'll fullfill it
I'll tell you the address...
I'll send it there
lts my sister's house
how much did you decided?
Whatever is in quatation
and taxes will goes to government
You'll get machines
Why are you joking?
I'm not doing
aren't you?
You're not professional!
The work will be hard like that
for you
you should talk with nitin sir...
I've to go
Just take something with you...
Want to have some tea?
We'll send it...
but sir tomorrow
you came so early...
Is rain is falling outside
where is boss...
Inside
what happend there?
Ask what has'nt happend?
What are you saying...
So you dont want it...
he didn't say.
I got his complaint box when coming
I putted on box
you're becoming smart enough?
Why... what happend?
What are you to blaiming on
general manager?
I was rejecting him in interview...
and you kept him
He's convict of case number 420
sit with lawyer...
you'll found anything else
how dare you
to messing with clients
you even didn't sold out anything...
and uttering everytime
You'll be silence for forever
finish your training period
and get out from here
What do you need to become hero.
They'll settle whatever they want
Was is important to become hero.
Did they told me while joining
That you have to do all this
The companies are all same...
you've to do it in all
so leave thatjob...
and what I do after leave it
I even didn't complete my month...
my all bio data will spoiled
I'm speaking from office
you eat it...
I'll come late
I'll not ride bike after drinking
Scooter busted my futere
Why dont you join another one
I should atleast have the
certificate for it
is that important to tell them?
Tell them its your firstjob
what I did wrong?
Why should I say lie?
It was remaining
Listen to me... go to office tomorrow
He'll forget everything...
who'll remember a trainee
I'll see it tomorrow
What happend?
Changed the beared
Targets gone in well...
And carrier also
called in confrence room...
its a meeting
Will you kill us...
there's a limit of target
what will you do by coming...
you are all ready busted
you'll sink everyone...
who hired you
you looks noble person...
but you're mad from inside
Go to asylum
I got my territory...
give me lead
I'd give you if I have it
because of you... our targets gone
double
what are you saying.
Remand is going on?
Its going since 10 years
you was very fondy ofjob...
You're allready hard worker...
Office colleagues recognize you
has something happend?
Dont disturb me
Will you let us die peacefully?
I got a call from your territory
lts a inquiry about two PC...
Give to rajesh
It will be mine after two months
Go...
and show it after few days
Die after getting orders
but if its your big company so
your prices is high too
If company is big so its
does'nt mean price high
price should not be accordint
to company but clients pocket
just give order first
We dont sale the pc on debit card
are a trainee?
No.
Who dont know becomes salesman
where?
Because while meeting
with so many salesman...
Which company made it
Will you eat maggie?
Eat it
no one is taking us serious,
because I've started new business
Speak up
sir
what the mean of graphic
We just sale it...
what is the price
and what about two?
Take it both in 8000
cant you discount it...
its whole sale rates
If you put other parts in it...
so you'll make full pc in 20000
you'll sale it on 30000 atleast?
The full pc could assemble in 20000
thousand with graphic card
We can make it in 25000
But company dont give clients
less than 35-40...
If its worths so cheap so why
do you sold out it on high rates?
Because cutomers meant be fool
If I'd have big show room,
so I'd sale it on high rates
To whom will you rob?
I'll not to anyone
There's no guarantee about
anything.
Its costs 350...
do you want it?
You told me to get know
about pc...
We'll supply it...
Is first order by you...
At whom name should I make
the check?
I just was sutting off my shop
yes both graphic cards...
pack it up whatever is compatible with pc
To whom you're robbing
I'll take it on credit...
pay you next week
what is written there...
pay today borrowing tomorrow.
When you started the bussiness
so how you had money??
Someone must have believes
you and borrow you
Yes, they was my relatives
So consider me your relative
How do you do your business...
are you giving me?
Okay take it
even then I ve'nt ever heared
that sardar is thief
when you done your work...
dont tell me you made me your relative
I'll not forget you.
You dont get orders In day tiem
What will you do in night
you ruined the entire company
I've a order...
you've to give order to others
dont want to give this order
to anyone
lts not company's order
Profit is personal too
You're not what you looks
have you petrol in your
scooter? Why?
I dont burns my petrol for others
lts indian policy
what
lts all yours or of your lovers
Government is annoucing since
many years do self employement
We have to do something
Did he know...
no
When he come to know so?
Who will tell him? You?
Will you keep it ready till
10 o clock on morning? Why
When do you take sleep?
In the office
any advance etc
no...
it will work
shall we leave
If you drink coffee so why its legal
Can I give you profit rathan a fee
lts allright?
Yes
If you install legal software and
gives me profit and what will you earn
It will known later...
You just see our service
lts dont got connected?
Lts my first order...
And I'm proud of it
Who dont know anything...
who becomes salesman
I'm starving
I was hungry...
what've you made
I made a peas and fried bread
leave the pease...
order the pizza...
what do you think
what's the matter.
Do you got big order today?
Dont ask... tell me do you want or not
yes
the kid did his hard work...
and you blessed him
Just always feed us food
like that with honesty
forbid us from lying and betraying
so we can runs with honor
As zero has its value...
so he has own value
neither manners for talking...
nor wit for understand the world
But zero is very usefull sir...
If a user knows its value
You reached at right place
at many times you'll put it...
you'll gain by it...
zero is very amazing thing
Today that zero gave me profit
more than entire salesman
ask how?
That fool was mis behaving with you...
But he's a fooll...
he was shocked
But by his fool act...
I got a chance
It had attacked like 9/11 on company
Salesman's commisons got removed...
and targets reached double
Now I'm on the top portal
of my life
and lts all beacause of this zero
But he did very bad with you sir.
We'll make him apolozise to you
speak up...
I'll not do it again
okay forgive him
He's minor man...
he's not on our level
shall we go
leave all this about salesman
I will leave it
But wherever I'll go...
will be salesman
What is your fault in it...
its company's fault
If next company will be like that so?
Means?
You used to do preparing for exame
whole night...
And I used to play cricket...
do you know why?
Because I was failed inside
So whatever Numbers used to got...
I just was...
no listen...
Do you know why Puri is continously
insulting me, because I'm letting him do,
But I am happy with that I
got ajob,
I just realise that it's not his
mistake but mine,
I have to pay the price to being nice,
If I would be sitting as a nice, then
it would be the biggest mistake of my life,
You supposed to quit this job,
I was...
but now I won't quit,
I won't quit this job,
I gave my interview,
and I have been selected,
I'm suitable for this job,
I ain't do nothing wrong,
When entire company is wrong...
If company is wrong then
it will be right.
I won't be wrong,
neither I will quit this job,
What will you do?
Whatever I will do...
after that puri will never said to
any employee that he is zero.
Whatever happened till today,
it happened by mistake,
but if mistake has been commited,
Now I will grow up that mistake,
You have just started your carrier,
why you are taking a big risk,
Even Spiderman have to take
the risk,
and I am just a salesman,
Will you be our office manager?
Join us,
First you leave this job,
Have you lost your mind,
You are already doomed,
now what are you doing?
If somebody will know about that,
they will chop your carrier and
distribute to entire staff,
Will you join us or not?
Why you are doing this?
We work in some office where nobody
cares our efficiencies,
and what is really not important,
everyone cares about that,
and we are just become that,
I was just ajoker,
and you are some item girl.
Have you gone mad?
You told her everything,
What relax?
She will tell puri everything,
then we both will lose ourjobs,
She won't tell him,
She is not like that,
Why she won't tell him, how
do you know about everyone,
Everyone in this company is
politician master,
They will sold you and you
will keep saying them thanks,
She won't tell anyone,
Why?
Is she belongs to your village,
She is not like that,
Don't interact with her,
Listen to me,
Do you trust me?
It was yet but not anymore,
Do you?
Like I trust Koena,
and please you shut your mouth,
From today whatever our company will
earn that will be divided in 3 shares,
Yours, Mine and Koena,
You're talking about to rise up the
business, and no profit,
How would you rise up your business?
We will get large business because
of her, How?
If something will happen wrong?
Nothing will happen, I am here.
If something will happen wrong,
What more will happen wrong,
If you will look over koena like...
How?
Like you look at your web sites.
We need our own office,
At least we will be needed our
own conference room,
Tell me what happened,
My husband has suppose to come,
You are busy with your photos
all day long,
We have to deal the people.
After today...
We won't discuss anything regarding
Rocket Singh Corporation in this office,
Take these dead client's list.
They all quit our company to
fed up from our bad services.
And I hope they all needed
a good service.
Let's offer them
services in half rates.
I mean it will cost 4-5 thousand
per computer,
We will offer them 2500.
And who will provide services.
I am busy in office all day long,
but we can service in nights,
idea is good,
but I never heard before.
He will ask about his computer's
services and maintenance,
client will never have a chance
to see the broken computer.
Nobody will recognize me,
What?
Nobody will recognize me either.
You don't know air voice company
keeps the record of everything.
Whatever office equipments you used,
you have to repay for all of them,
Hello! It's me.
Now what?
Nothing, I am suffering from viral.
If I got holiday today then...
You can't come on job,
then our company will be closed,
In fact you handle the entire jobs,
No,
It's just a fever,
Do what do you want?
Don't waste my time,
You mean you provide services
in nights and holidays,
Yes, in nights, holiday, eid,
new year.
Anytime, any day,
just a phone call away.
Would you give me in written
with your signature,
I have seen many companies before,
but never seen confidence like you,
You won't need it,
and if it will be any,
then I will sell my bike.
I have called to Mr. Wajahat
on his UAN number,
He called us in office after 7.
Client is not free before that,
We are also not free,
Mr. Wajahat has recommended you.
It's all fine,
but don't you think you are small
company for this huge order,
We are small but our hunger
is bigger,
We both know that we both
need each other,
and when we both know then we
don't have chance for mistake.
If there will be something wrong then
how would you pay double from contract,
It will be your right on first cheque
what will come from Mr. Wajahat.
If you will be happy from us, then
you will transfer that money to us,
otherwise your company can keep it,
You're taking a big risk,
Even Spiderman have to take risk,
and I am just a salesman,
I am telling you one more time,
Only honesty will work with me,
that's the only thing I have,
what else?
How many days it will take
for 30 computers.
30 are enough it will take 20 days.
We have to deliver in one week,
What?
And I said them yes,
don't you know another word,
You didn't hear that,
He said yes to them,
Now I have said one week,
Now I can't take my words back.
Who could assemble computer.
I knew that,
Do you know someone,
There is only trustable man,
who can quickly assemble computers.
Who?
Shukla!
He doesn't know how to run it,
But he know how to assemble it.
If it's like that then...
I think we can bring one more
partner in our company,
Have you gone mad, you will make
a peon your partner,
Why not? If he know the job of
director then why he can't be one,
I knew that something will
happen wrong,
If you already knew that why did
you join us,
I didn't know that it will happen
much wrong,
Me?
A partner in company,
No!
It's not possible.
Why?
You can assemble the computer.
Yes!
Then you can become a partner,
but my job is to make tea,
if you're missing alot then
you can make tea too.
May I have to talk in english.
You don't have to talk to anyone,
All you have to assemble computers
with Giri.
I hope there will be no issue ofjail,
We are doing business,
Why we will go to jail.
Many big businessman goes to jail,
We're not doing a big business,
If Mr. Puri will knew about that,
who will tell him,
Only we four knew about that.
I can only get this respect in
your company,
Which day first time you called me
Mr. Mishra instead of Chotay Lal.
If you don't need a partner share
in our company,
No!
I didn't said it.
He won't do it,
but why you are not working,
You are also a partner,
you will also get your share,
We are getting many wrong numbers,
What?
You just gave me,
Rocket Sales Corporations.
Credit card companies change their
names to call us,
I have to talk all of you.
Right now,
How do I know how nitin get it.
It must be gone in urgent,
There must be a solution,
with who our clients can call us,
and we did not get caught.
We have two numbers.
What we got but didn't used,
and puri might be doesn't remember,
If someone call us on that number,
then we won't have problem,
If some day you will cheat your
husband, he will be doomed,
Our phone bills will be submitted,
We have to write down in accounts,
He is started again,
somebody will be doubt on us.
You gave us computers in cheap prices,
Really impressive.
It's hard to setup in new office,
By the way how is your office,
I'm thinking to close it,
Why?
Life is not so easy what we
assume in college,
Salaries, Utility bills, Rent,
And for new companies client
doesn't come on phone,
Everyone says that you need few
years to start your new business,
Anyway how's your going?
Training period is over,
It was over that time,
When?
After your order,
It wasn't a big order,
How do you know how bigger it was,
what do you mean?
I will tell you later.
Tell me right now,
Clients doesn't watch movies,
Ofcouse they watch,
Seven computers in 2 days,
We are going too slow,
You are not taking parts from
other shop,
Your lalwani electronics is just
a small part supplier,
If you want to do big job
then leave him,
I won't leave lalwani,
When I didn't have money so
he gave me credit,
Now when I got big order
so we should leave him,
Business doesn't happen like this,
Which kind of business you're doing,
You will get loss and give us too.
I was doubted from that day when
this child was behaving like elders,
and that phone call.
Let's call him directly,
I hope you all have Mr. Puri's number,
If I will speak then you will
say that I speak much,
and if I won't speak...
it will cost big amount
for not to speak,
How much?
10 percent,
on your every sale.
If you need share in our company,
so you have to work like all partners,
Come in senses,
Good Morning,
Situation is like that you can't
put me on any condition,
but I can put any condition,
We can also put condition,
and we are putting,
If you will misbehave with us
one more time,
then since past 2 years what
counterfiet conveyance vouchers you
are making from me, I will give all
of them to Mr. Puri with morning tea.
I am giving you the same offer on
the front of all partners,
Join us,
and take your share like others,
Now we are five people.
Why should we give him equal share.
Because he is experienced.
He will bring many orders...
We never lied to clients,
No matter you lost your order,
Let the order go but never lose
the client's faith.
We believe in services more
than sales.
Because which company offers services,
he got the big sales.
We don't give bribe if client
ask for it,
then how do you get order,
We don't get such orders.
We don't promise in false delivery.
And what date we promised,
we deliver on the same date.
We are always available for client,
days and nights.
He will drive us crazy to call us,
that's the rule.
When patients become doctor
to wear doctor's coat.
Same thing happened there.
And it's not the first order.
What goes to them besided
it was coming to us,
and you...
You lost twice from this company,
What happened? What this so
called rocket company does,
that he takes clients under your noses,
How much they are giving bribes,
that every order goes to
them on last moment,
You must have applied there yet,
who are they people?
When Amenti was giving them order,
you were sleeping,
How order goes to them,
Sir, I don't know much they offered a
nice sheme on last phone call,
What scheme?
This is India,
Since when people are getting
orders on service scheme,
Sir, they reached to service in night,
Rubbish!
Sir, their quotations are cheap like
one client called me thief,
How cheap?
Which computer we are selling on
32000, they are offering on 26000.
And they are also offering
2 years free service.
If he is selling computers in this
rates it means...
on which computer we were earning
6000, he is earning 2200.
What are they doing?
I don't know sir,
Where is the office?
They are taking orders under your nose,
and nobody knows anything
except phone number,
There is something fishy.
Find out every detail of Rocket
Singh within a week,
Vice President Sale's post is empty.
I need an efficient man for it,
Show me in a week that
how efficient you're.
And next week,
shift on it or find anotherjob,
We have many efficient people here.
Do you know which kind of
human puri is,
He is just getting doubt...
If he will know...
If we won't tell then how do he know,
don't under estimate him,
You didn't see how did he
calculate the profit.
And our address is printed
on all client's bills.
I told you let's have post box number.
Really?
Then everyone will doubt on us.
He will must know.
What happen?
Whatever happened between us,
don't take is personal.
I was never against you.
First time in my carrier many people
are scared from me,
what do you think?
I am not feeling happy.
When I came to this business,
I was like you.
I didn't take bribe in begininng.
But when I start losing my promotions,
and others get promoted on my
front then I also...
Because of you after many years I felt
to become owner of myself,
but Puri showed my limits today.
If you sold yourself once, then others
always thinks you're for sale.
No matter what he is his boss
or his partners,
I won't tell anything to puri.
Now you decide what to do.
You shift the place for few days,
but where we will keep the material.
If customers will call then we
will need it,
Yes,
someone must have to do it.
I have a friend,
I took your order for company,
but you supplied by your self.
If you would be on my place,
then what would you do.
If I would be on your place then
your boss will be in grave.
They are waiting outside,
They have stuff in tempo,
Rocket Sales here,
Will you speak to client like this,
Client will think he called up
in slimming centre,
Finally we got our seperate number,
and within few days we will give this
number to our all clients.
Take this call.
It's Puri on phone,
Talk to him,
He is not in office,
I'll give your message to him,
Where is your office?
On Second floor.
Thankyou for calling,
This time he just called,
Next time he will catch our throats.
He know everything,
I am telling you,
If he would know then we won't
keep talking here,
we would be in jail...
Jail?
Jail is not a concern,
that book on internet and send people,
Nothing will happen,
What if he will call again,
tell him that boss is sick,
No!
He is out of station,
tell him he is out of country,
If he wants to meet me then I'll
meet him, Are you kidding?
You told me there will no
issue ofjail.
He wants to meet the M.D.
Of Rocket Sales.
Something is running in his mind,
and until I won't meet him,
We will never figure it out,
but what we have to do what's
running in his mind,
Just look after your self,
His business is going down,
and he can do anything to save
his business,
Before he do something we should
know what he will do.
But how would you meet him,
Like...
A king met another king,
Sir, there is phone call for you from
Rocket Singh's MD.
I have to purchase few computers.
I hope I didn't call late,
No, no!
Is it your office where I called up,
Is it your office number,
Right sir,
and within we will get
24 hours helpline.
You people sell computers,
Notjust sell we also provide services,
then how bigger company you have,
how many people,
It's such a small team,
Sir, meet some day personally,
Who is the owner of your company,
We all are owners,
when you will meet personally
to our executive.
What did you think?
You junior people will fool
around Sunil Puri.
And with this zero mind,
You were already become Vice President,
you should have tell me everything,
What was wrong with you?
You will never understand?
Then explain me,
I am an intelligent man,
before jail just try to
explain me once,
Look!
Whatever happened, I have started,
so you better talk to me,
Leadership qualities come out
from Mr. Zero.
I'll talk to you.
Since when it's running,
and how many orders you took
from here.
We didn't touched single client
of this company.
And what facilities of your company
we have used here is the account,
and it's payment we are already
going to pay you.
You will give me a cheque,
You are supposed to be
in bad condition.
And others shouldn't follow you,
that's why...
Go and take bath,
It might be wash your sins,
I will see whatever it will take,
You don't need to worry.
I have nurtured you many years,
I can nuture more years,
what was the need to become thief,
You didn't teach me stealing,
If you would have teach me stealing,
then I shouldn't become a thief,
At least they can start their
carrier again,
from 04:00 your Rocket Singh Corp
has become mine,
and your all customers are
become mine,
Congratulation,
Every man have qualities to rise up,
and rise down,
Before I was requesting you for
the same job,
but today...
...you are giving me the
same brand name.
What did you learn?
That man should be stay in his limits.
You don't have those guts.
After all you are a zero.
At least take your full and
final compensation,
Never become a business man,
You will be sold,
we didn't get profit to buy it,
In fact our liabilities are increased,
Sir, Rajesh was saying that...
...Rocket company is going to get a
huge order from Inamdar,
If we get that order,
then I will handle other accounts,
Look!
You are my own man,
I need this order,
I will take care of rest.
Would you service,
Service is my guarantee.
Since when you know me,
Team is new but company is same,
You didn't understand yet,
You have bought
rocket corporation's name...
...but you lose it's men,
You have become fool.
Let's start new relationship.
I am cancelling all future orders,
and as well I know all other
rocket clients have...
...either cancelled or
they're going to cancel.
Don't mind your business ways
are become history now,
Who you are?
With what you fooled everyone,
What was your limit to sell stuff
in cheap rates.
You lost your life but
never get profit,
your company is sold,
Who won?
Now you are on streets,
I am selling computers since 10 years.
Before that fax,
and before that electronic typewriter.
I am old business man,
But I made a mistake.
Who I have to keep in company and to
pronounce salesman of the year.
I though him out and made him
competetor.
No problem,
I made a mistake,
I had fun,
Now I will correct it.
I am giving you yourjob back.
Vice President post is empty.
Every man have qualities to rise
up and down,
I chose the way to go down,
but you didn't left any way for me,
I didn't know anything,
but to keep doing that I know
there is no scheme in business,
there is only one thing,
People!
Did you ever see people.
And you just saw numbers.
Who achieved how many numbers.
But I never understand score numbers.
I always seen people.
Who is happy and who is sad?
Who can do what,
and who enjoyed what?
When people become happy numbers
are getting increased by itself.
You snatched my company,
I don't care.
It came out from your company,
and it went back to your company,
but what I learned,
you can snatch it.
And with that I can build
ten more companies.
But what will you do?
Everything is become zero
whatever you knew,
like you are giving me today...
...I don't need it,
I couldn't become like you.
But I have become a man,
I have never seen such a
big zero like him,
He just changed my company,
and when I remove it,
my customers are changed,
Your customers won't be handle
from my people.
And I have mind to understand it.
And such a new comer defeat me,
I have a limit to accept it.
Do you have a rupee.
I am giving your company back.
I couldn't handle it.
You won,
I lose.
When blood and sweat printed on paper.
Then table become bed,
and office become home,
People forget hunger and thirst,
then a company build up.
A man like me you will never found,
I am giving you the biggest lesson
of your life.
And I didn't give anything free
to my own father.
What you do?
Either that's business or not,
I don't know,
but never become a businessman.
---created n Uploaded by SwaroopJain---