Psagmeno.com
Subtitles / Screenshots / Trailers
In the Name of God
In memory of Yadollah Najafi
Shahab Hosseini
Taraneh Alidoosti
Babak Karimi
Farid Sajjadi Hosseini
Featuring
Mina Sadati
First Assistant to Director of Photography
Morteza Sobhani
Photos
Habib Majidi
Assistant Director and Coordinator
Kaveh Sajjadi Hosseini
Script Supervisor
Parisa Gorgin
Decor
Keyvan Moqaddam
Customs
Sara Sami'ei
Make Up Designer
Mehrdad Mir Kiani
Music
Sattar Ooraki
Executive Producer
Hasan Mostafavi
Camera Operator
Peyman Shadmanfar
Sound Recordists The late
Yadollah Najafi Hossein Bashash
Sound Design & Mix
Mohammadreza Delpak
Sound Editor
Reza Narimizadeh
Editor
Hayedeh Safi Yari
Director of Photography
Hossein Jafarian
Producers Alexandre
Mallet-guy Asghar Farhadi
Hey, Mr. Etesami!
Rana, Missy!
Come on out!
The building's about to collapse.
Woman: The building's falling apart.
Get out of there!
What's going on?!
What are you doing here, honey?
Come here, honey.
Why? What's going on?
Mr. Etesami evacuate the building.
It's collapsing. Hurry up!
- Let's go, everyone!
- Rana!.. Rana!
- What's going on, Emad?
- Come here, Rana! Hurry up!
Let's go, man!
- What's going on, Mr. Fallah?
- I don't know. Just evacuate, man!
Rana!.. Hurry up!
Come on!
- What is it?
- Go down! Go, go!
Nasim!..
Chop, chop, Nasim!
Mr. Amiri, let's go!
Evacuate!
Emad, son!..
For God's sake someone help my baby.
I'm coming, wait.
Here, here, put this on.
What?..
Let me come with you.
No, you can't.
Just go down to the alley.
Go tell everyone to go to the alley.
Mrs. Samimi!..
Mrs. Samimi!
- Where's Hossein?
- I can't get him out of there.
Hossein get up, my boy!
The house is coming down.
Get up, Hossein!.. Get up!
- Emad, come on, everyone's gone.
- Go down to the alley. Go tell everyone.
Mr. Fallah, get everyone down to the alley.
Come on, Hossein!..
what are they doing?!
- Glasses... my glasses...
- I'll bring your glasses.
The Salesman Written and
Directed by Asghar Farhadi
Guys!..
There's no need to
bring all your stuff.
- We've got everything down in our place.
- Okay.
- I can't find it.
- I don't know, just look around.
- You want me to take these?
- Yeah, thanks a lot.
I thought you were supposed to just
bring your towel and toothbrushes?
The towel and the brushes
are in there too.
- Did you lock the car?
- Yeah.
Ah, keys, keys!..
Gimme the keys.
Here.
Guys!
Hey
Hey Kati.
Hi.
What's up, Kati?
You're alive?!
The way Sia said the
house has collapsed,
I thought we'd have to drag
you from under the ruins.
Oh, whoa!..
What's going on here?!
There's smell of gas...
It's from last night.
Well, then, get your stuff.
Let's get out of here.
Hey.
Why did you come up?
Cut off the electricity,
this is dripping.
I can't find the card, man.
Well, see if it's between your
documents and stuff.
Kati, dear, don't go there,
it's dangerous.
Oh, my God...
You could only hear the sobbing
of Mashti Hassan's wife,
... sitting alone with her lit lantern
on the stable's roof
and the desperate moans of a cow
from inside the stable.
Sir! is it a true story?
True? No, but you could say that
in a way, in Saedi's stories
the scenery, the type of characters,
and relationships are real. Very real.
Sir, how can someone turn into a cow?
Try looking in the mirror.
You think you're funny, huh?
But seriously, Sir,
how does a person turn into a cow?
Gradually...
Sir, are we gonna watch the film
of this story too?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Maybe I bring it next time and
we can watch it together.
Yes?
Sir, when can we see your play?
The performance begins next week.
Once we've had a few days to settle in,
I'll definitely invite you all to come.
- Thank you, Sir!
- What's it called, Sir?
"Death of a Salesman",
who's read it?
"The enemy"!
Jokes aside,
have any of you read it?
Sir, who's the author?
Arthur Miller
Hmm... no, I've not.
Very good.
Excuse me, boys.
Yes?
Hello.
Yes.
Sorry, I can't talk right now,
I'm in class.
If you call back in 10
minutes, I'll be free.
Yeah, with stick shifts... Silver...
Sure... that's fine.
Sir, what's your role?
The Salesman.
- What are you selling, Sir?
- Potatoes!
When you come,
you'll see for yourselves.
What's it's model, Sir?
- What?
- Your Peugeot 206, you know.
- Why do you wanna know?
- Aren't you selling, Sir?
Sir, his dad's a parking officer,
just tell him to scrap your fines for you.
Do you even commit driving offenses, Sir?
Sir, why do Iranians call BMWs
"Bee-Em-Veh"s?
I didn't hear you.
Why do Iranians call BMWs
"Bee-Em-Veh"s?
- Get outa here!
- Dude, just zip it!
That's alright. He doesn't know,
so he's asking.
I don't know either.
Guys... eh, for your next session...
I want a summary of this story.
I don't want any excuses, like...
"I fell asleep, we had guests",
and... stuff like that.
Mister, could you please
scooch over a bit?
Sir, can I sit in front and
this young man sits back here?
Father...
Somebody in there?
No, I think the noise was
from the next door.
- No, no, somebody got in your bathroom!
- No, there's no one there.
It’s the next room, there’s a party.
These kind of noises are normal...
Can I come out?
There’s something moving
in the bathtub, Willy!
Ah, Miss Francis,
you better go back to your room.
They must be finished
painting by now.
But I can't, I’ve got to get dressed first!
Yes, you can, you can!
Please!
Biff, this is Miss Francis,
my next-door neighbor.
They were painting her room.
And she asked to come and use the bath.
And I said, that's alright,
So, I let her take a shower here.
You can go back to your room now.
But Willy, I don't have any clothes on!
Please, get out of here!
Go back to your room.
You promised me stockings, Willy!
I have no stockings here!
Why?! You had two boxes of size 9s for me,
and I want them, Willy!
Alright, take one and go.
For God’s sake, will you get outa here!
Please!
Go!
I just hope there’s nobody in the hall.
I can't go out without any clothes!
By the way, are you
football or...
Dammit!
Siavash!
What happened, mom?
I do my best to ignore it but he
keeps getting worse every night!
Sadra, dear, come down, let's go!
Sanam, dear, just ignore him.
He thinks just because I'm playing a whore,
he can do whatever he wants.
What's that got to do with it?
Why don't you laugh at the others then, huh?
- I was laughing at your clothes, not you...
- Shut up! Shut the hell up!
Siavash, come here!
Sanam, don't be childish on
this final night. Sanam...
Alright, I'm freaking sorry...
I'm sorry.
In this cold, rehearsing every night,
with this child.
Let's go, honey.
You just had to fuck it up,
didn't you?
What's that got to do with us?
It's your own husband.
Let me take the k...
Let go!
Sanam don't...
I said get off!
I was kidding...
- I was messing with you.
- Where are you going?
Comes out of the shower with a raincoat,
and says,
"How can I go out
without any clothes?"
I can't, man,
it makes me laugh.
Go after her or she'll get annoyed
and won't come tomorrow.
Don't make me go out without clothes!
I'm shy!
Come on, how can I go out
without any cloth...
Sanam!
The guy's totally nuts!
Did you find a place?
60 sq. metres, 3rd floor, no elevator.
40 mils in front, 600k tomans per month.
- Where?
- Amiratabak
- What sort of a place are you looking for?
- Something temporary...
...If we can't find anywhere,
We have to bring our stuff,
and live right in the middle of the stage.
You free tomorrow afternoon?
How come?
I'm taking you somewhere.
Come on guys...
once more from the top, no interruptions.
You tired?
Nope
Oh, you're here too!
Aww kitty!
Who's this?
Come here, you!
He's tame... What's up, kitty?
This place is cool!
Babak
Is that the storage room?
- Which one?
- This
No! It's the second bedroom
- Really?!
- Well, yeah.
- Isn't it too small?
- It's a two-bedroom!
So it's good?
You're just two people,
what do you need all this space for anyways?
Watch your mouth, "two people"!
Who knows,
maybe we end up being three people...
Rana, is he serious?
No, come on!
- He doesn't look like it.
- Why is that?
Is this door locked?
Is it locked?
The previous tenant's stuff is in there;
they're supposed to be collecting it.
Don't be scared kitty, it's just me.
- How long's it been vacant?
- Three weeks.
What are they doing to this city?
I wish we could tear it
all down and start again
They've already destroyed and rebuilt it,
and look how it's turned out...
Babak?
Yes dear
God have mercy on us.
When do you think they'll
clear their stuff out?
They promised they'll be
here in the next day or two
There's no parking, you'll have to
leave your car on the street.
We don't need parking anyways.
We're selling our car to pay
your mortgage down payment.
Who mentioned money?
Well, either way...
Hello
Hello Mr Salimi.
One of the good things about this
place are Mr. Shanazari and his wife.
- Hello.
- Hello, how're you doing?
- Hello, hello. how do you do Ma'am?
Babak, which one's the storage?
It's here, come, take a look.
- Mr Salimi?
- Yes?
The door's open, take a look.
Please make sure it doesn't
turn out like the last one.
- No, come on, I know these guys.
- You said you knew the last ones too.
Don't worry about it.
- Babak, what do they do?
- They're my friends, they're into arts.
I hope so
It's okay for a few months.
Just make sure he lets us pay him for it.
No favors.
Looks like we've finally caught a break.
Careful, don't rush
- You need help, Sir?
- No, you go ahead and bring the rest.
Just be careful not to hit the light-bulb.
Sorry sir, thanks for the help.
- Are the keys here too?
- They took that one room's with 'em.
Where's Ali?
Ali...
Yep?
For God's sake, leave that alone,
I'll call an electrician tomorrow.
It'll only take a second
Leave it, man!
If she'd said, we wouldn't have hired
the truck and the movers.
How was I supposed to know?
She sounded so sure that I
didn't think she'd bail on us.
So, what's she saying now?
Hasn't answered
ever since this morning.
Why don't you try from a different number?
Bring your phone Nana.
We really need that room,
we've brought a pickup full our things.
Yes
Okay
He's here if you like to speak to him,
Thanks
Says, she's said all
she has to say to you.
Well, what did she say?
She signed the contract on
a new place two days ago,
but the landlord bucked
at the last moment,
She's looking for a place, but can't come
for her stuff until she finds somewhere.
She said to tell you not to
let anyone touch her stuff. Please.
Oh, yeah, and she doesn't want
to talk to you again.
Any news? What happened?
I don't know, nothing for now.
Let me take it, Kati.
Ali
- Yes?
- You got a screwdriver in your car?
This is enough stuff for a bride's dowry!
I thought it was just
a few bits and pieces.
- Maybe we should leave it...
- It's fine, I'll take responsibility for it
Alright, boys,
let's move those things over there.
Rana...
mumbling
These are people's belongings
What do you want me to do? It's been
3 days now. She keeps saying...
... "I'm coming today, I'll come tomorrow."
What if she shows up?
Well she should've kept her word then.
Never mind. Come on!
Guys, I can't carry anything heavy!
Mr?
Come on, let's eat.
Rana, dear!
Yes dear?
Honey... the charger.
I'll turn into words,
run through your ears...
I'll turn into thoughts,
stick in your head...
I'll be a Benz,
race under your feet...
I'll be poverty
in your purse...
I'll be a wolf,
raid your herd.
You two, go to the door and
bring over one of those boxes.
Hi guys
Are these your 206's car parts, Sir?
Put these in front of
the principal's office,
tell the librarian to come see me.
Put these in front of
the principal's office,
tell the librarian to come see me.
Very good guys, I want the poem
memorized for next time.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bye, Sir.
Bye.
- Bye, Sir!
- So, long.
Thanks Sir
Goodbye
- Sir, can I say something?
- What?
Sir, I was really pissed off the other day.
Which day?
The day that woman insulted you
in the Taxi.
Was it an insult?
You know, that she said,
she wants to sit in the front seat.
Sir, after you got out of the car,
I told them that you were my teacher.
And that we all love you so much.
Like, all the guys.
What was your first name again?
Amin..
Amin, you can be sure, some guy had
done something to her in a taxi before...
...to make her think
that way about everyone.
Don't worry about it, it's just
the first 100 years that are tough.
See you
Bye
Okay
Of all the time...
I don't know what to do with her.
Who?
This woman
I called to ask when she'll
clear her stuff out.
She got angry, started threatening...
Over what?
"Why did you touch my personal things?
those were my private stuff...
... I'll sue you.."
Last night I was running around, saving
her stuff from the rain, up until morning.
Her problem's something else...
- Who Babak, the woman?
- Yeah.
When's she coming to get her stuff?
Says, whenever she finds a place.
Sadra darling, come here with me.
Hurry up.
Hurry up guys, the audience will
be in in five minutes.
Emad... Emad, they're coming here
again after the performance.
They've approved 3 of the 6 revisions,
there's another three left.
if you stay around after the performance,
you can talk to them.
Tonight after the performance?
Yes
If it helps, I'll stay.
Sure, or else there's a chance they
might cancel the whole show tomorrow.
How many did they say?
Three... Guys will you please hurry up!
I'll go, then.
Won't you wait around?
No, you'll be stuck here
until around midnight.
Take the car, then.
Where are the house keys?
In my coat's pocket.
Have a good performance
You too!
Say, on your way back, if
the supermarket's open...
... buy something, we've got
nothing for breakfast.
Yes, I said if it's open. If it's open!
Also, pick up some hand sanitizer.
Maybe I take a shower
until you get here.
No not at all, I'm a mess. I haven't
even wiped off my stage makeup.
I'll be out soon... soon.
Yup... love you, bye.
Anything else?
That's all, thanks.
Be my guest.
Are you paying by card?
No, cash.
Hello Ma'am
Hello?
Good evening, I'm your upstairs neighbor.
We've just moved in,
could you open the door please?
Thank you.
Rana?
Rana!
What happened to you?
Please step outside, Sir.
You can't be in here, Sir.
We'll call you when for the CT scan.
Wait outside, please.
Look at me Rana...
Everything's fine,
I'll call you for the CT scan... Please.
Make sure you change the locks
first thing tomorrow.
Why? Did someone get into the house?
I thought she'd fainted,
was dizzy or...
We don't know what happened yet
All of a sudden we heard shouting
and screaming from upstairs.
Not like, normal, not once,
scream after scream...
I told him go upstairs and check,
he said,
couples get into fights all the time.
Then we heard some heavy
bangs in the stairs,
I told him "Muhammad,
God knows, something's up."
Who was it?
By the time we reached the stairs,
we just saw someone fleeing up the street.
I don't know what happened to his foot,
but it had bled all over the stairs.
If I'd caught him, he'd be dead now.
Then we went upstairs and
found your wife unconscious...
there was blood all over the bathroom floor.
I dressed her and brought her here.
Never mind that, thank God
something worse didn't happen.
Woman, do us a favour, go to the ER,
and check if there's any news or something.
Sorry about putting you to all this trouble.
Have a seat, sit down, son.
Was anything missing from the house?
I don't know.
I didn't notice anything.
I don't think it was a robbery.
What would a thief be doing in the bathroom?
Then who was it?
The guy was one of
that woman's customers.
Who? What woman?
The woman who lived there
before you moving in.
Tell you the truth, she
was kind of messed up...
... and I think, the guy came here
on account of her still being there.
Don't shut the door, Ali's coming up
Don't shut the door, Ali's coming up.
Sure
Come on, lie down.
Take my sleeve, hold this bit.
Thanks
Wait, let me take off your scarf.
You want me to put
two pillows for you?
No.
Turn off the light, so she can sleep.
Don't turn it off.
Can I get you anything?
No, thanks.
Where are you going, Emad?
Darling?
I said, where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere,
I'll be here. Do you need anything?
Nope. Leave the door open.
Okay, thanks
Look, her blood pressure's low,
be careful when she's walking around.
Thanks for everything.
Sit down guys,
I'll make you some breakfast.
No thanks, I'm fine.
Come on, you haven't eaten
since last night.
Kati, you wanna stay here, and
make soup or something for them?
- You want me to stay?
- You want Kati to stay?
No, no.
Are you sure?
You must be tired.
Go, get some rest.
Call if you need anything.
Really, man, just let us know.
- Thanks again for everything, guys.
- Bye
... scrap metal... Iron doors...
Aluminium doors...
Fences... Metal dishes...
buying...
... scrap metal... lamps...Samovars...
anything, bring it over...
Come on, stand here
while I use the bathroom.
What are you doing?
Leave it, I'll wash it myself,
Rana, dear. Leave it.
Come and wash it then.
Alright, turn off the water
and come out.
Then, come and clean it
before I use it.
The police might need to see it.
Yes?
Of course, sorry
Who was it?
A neighbor
What did they say?
I'll be right back.
Sorry
I'm really sorry for all the trouble
you've been put through, ma'am.
Now, come on, don't say that.
I think you should call 110, they'll be
able to track him down through the car.
Yeah, I'll definitely do that.
Anyways, I'll try to find some place...
Here I was thinking, when that woman left
she's taken all her troubles with her.
Have you ever seen
this car's owner around here?
Well, it wasn't like, just
a couple guys visiting her.
I might have to trouble you again
when the police comes...
...if they have any questions
about exactly what you saw.
Of course, it's our duty. Would you
like to take my mobile number?
Yes, please.
I'll get going.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
They should put an ewer
around these guys necks,
and parade them around the city,
shaming them.
0912...
Why are you out here? Come in
I'm scared of being
alone in the house.
Where did you go?
I went to thank the neighbors
for last night.
What did they say?
Nothing.
They asked how you were.
You didn't tell Kati and the guys
what happened, did you?
No.
Okay, I'm going to
the police station.
We have to file a complaint
for them to start looking for the guy.
How will they find him?
He left his pickup behind.
His mobile too,
but it's disconnected.
Who was he, Emad?
The neighbors are saying the woman
who lived here before us was shady.
The scumbag must've been
one of her customers.
Came here on account of her.
Do you remember what he looked like?
No
Didn't you get a look at him?
It's cold.
Come inside, you'll catch a cold.
Gimme that.
Who helped me out of the bathroom?
One of the neighbors.
Which one?
I don't know, just forget it.
Eat your breakfast.
and then go get some rest.
I can't. As soon as I close my eyes
that scene comes to my mind.
How did he get in?
I opened the door,
I thought it was you.
I came out of the bathroom,
buzzed him in, and then went back.
I was shampooing my hair when
I realised someone had come in.
He put his hand in my hair from behind
and I thought it was you.
But then I saw his hands
and after that it's blank.
Rana...
Darling, have some breakfast.
Rana, dear...
Sweetie...
What about tonight's performance?
I called and told them to cancel it.
No, call and say I'm coming.
How? In this condition of yours?
It's harder for me to stay at home.
Put this on,
let's go to the police station.
We might get held up there
for a while anyways.
No, leave it.
Let's not go to the station.
We can't just do nothing!
I don't want to have
to go there and tell
a bunch of officers or
whoever what happened.
Did something happen
that you can't tell?
No.
Then, you don't have to say anything.
I'll tell 'em myself.
I can't, it'll be too much.
No, this isn't foolish talk, Linda.
When I'm walking in the street,
I clearly feel these things...
...They pass me by, but it's as if they're
laughing at me with their eyes.
Why? Why would they laugh at you?
Don't talk that way about yourself, Willy.
Sometimes they pass me by
as if I don't even exist.
As though nobody sees me.
Nobody notices me. Nothing.
Linda?
How long are you going to spend
repairing those socks, huh?
You know it makes me angry.
At least don't do it while I'm home,
talking to you. Okay?
Okay, we'll talk about something else,
for example my income.
My never-changing income.
God, this is really ridiculous.
What's wrong with you?..
why aren't you saying your lines?
Willy, darling, you're the most
handsome man in the world to me.
You always say this to me, Linda, always,
but it doesn't help me at all.
I'll never be able to make you happy,
do you know why?
Because I'm just a salesman.
I'm nothing! I'm nothing, Linda!
But I always tried...
why are you crying, anyways?
Wait, where are you going?
Linda, come back...
Sorry, I have to stop the play.
I apologize to you all.
My wife, the other actor,
isn't feeling well.
Please give us a ten minute intermission.
Sorry.
Can you carry on?
What do you mean, Kati?
Can't you see she's not well?
Go on, cancel it.
Do you wanna go to the other room
and lie down a little?
Alright, guys, let's just clear the room.
She's not well.
Sanam, dear.
I'm coming.
Can I get you anything?
Kati darling...
Go and cancel the show
What happened there?
The way someone in the audience
was staring at me bothered me.
The audience've come to watch the play,
of course they'll be looking at you.
Looked at me just like that guy.
I thought you said you didn't see him.
I'm really unwell, I just
don't know what to do.
Babak, come here a minute.
Coming...
Is she feeling better?
Goddamit, man,
what can I say to you...?
Don't you think you had
to let me know about
the kind of people who
used to live in there?
- What's happened?
- You're supposed to be my friend
Seriously, what's happened?
What is it to you who lived there before?
That apartment's infamous
in the whole neighborhood.
Who's said such a thing?
Let's say nobody's said anything,
why isn't this woman coming
to collect her stuff?
I just wanted to help.
Remember the state you were in, last week?
Ready to sleep on the set?
Regardless, should you have hidden
that woman's line of work from me?
What hiding?
Well, yeah. Did you tell me or not?
Was I supposed to pass on to you some
unfounded gossip? To upset you?
Well, what's going, anyways?
What's this all about?
Babak, I'm going
I'm coming.
Go take a look at Rana,
you'll see what this is all about.
They said she slipped
in the bathroom.
We said right in front of you
we might be having a kid in that place.
And you didn't say a word, what kind of...
You were joking!
If we weren't joking,
would you have told us?
Told you what?!
Put yourself in my shoes,
the same room we sleep in, each night...
...how many strange men
have been with that woman.
Don't take it so hard on yourself.
I haven't cashed your check yet.
Whenever you find another
place whose previous tenants
had your approval,
you can move out.
Hello
How are you doing
Be careful not to slip on the
stairs Mrs Shahnazari, they're wet.
I was actually going to ask the cleaner
to come early and sort these out.
But, I thought you'd want to report it,
the police might want to see them.
Well, it wasn't such a big deal.
You wouldn't say that,
if you'd been there and seen
the state your wife was in,
on the bathroom floor.
When Mr. Alimoradi opened the bathroom door,
he thought, God forbid, your wife was dead.
Say hello from me.
Get up, I've made some breakfast for you.
I'm heading out.
Wait.
Wait, I'll get ready and come with you.
Where to? I have class.
I know, I'll wait in the car.
It's not just an hour or two,
you'll get tired.
Then don't go today.
What?
I said, don't go today.
Let's say I don't,
what about tomorrow then?
The day after tomorrow?
It's not gonna work.
I can't stay here alone.
I said, I don't want
to be here alone.
What can I do?
You want me to get you
a ticket to visit your
parents for a few days?
Looking like this?
I've made up my mind...
... we either have to go to the police,
or forget this altogether.
Okay forget it,but let's look for
a new apartment right from today.
Okay, we'll start looking.
But until we find somewhere,
you need to try and pick yourself up.
What do you mean?
It's not something I can control.
You taking your pills and
not staying up all night
getting worked up about it,
is up to you, isn't it?
Go take a shower, I'll wait here.
I don't want to go in that bathroom.
I'll drop you off at a friend's place.
Use theirs.
Go and tell them we've
come to take a shower?
What do you want me to do?
You keep changing your mind.
At night you tell me
not to come near you,
then in the morning you
tell me not to leave you.
Tell me what to do and I'll do it.
Just go, you're late
It'll take a couple weeks to find a place.
What?
You're not gonna wash up
with that wound of yours?
I love you.
Just think, it could've been worse.
What if a piece of glass
had gone in your eye,
or your head had been hit harder?
Then...
...then what the hell would I have done?
I wish my head had been hit harder.
God forbid! Honey,
don't say things like that.
Hello, Mr. Etesami.
Hello Sir, how are you doing?
Mr. Yeganeh gave me these books
to give them to you.
Be quiet. What's so funny?
Why?
He said they're not suitable for kids.
Quiet!
Mr. Yeganeh decided these
weren't suitable for the kids?!
Go, throw them in the bin.
Why the bin?
Just throw them away.
Give me your phone.
I don't have a phone, Sir.
Give it to me.
I don't have a cell.
Sir, wait a minute.
Give it to me.
Sir, there's nothing in it about you.
I want to see what you have
I've deleted it
Let me see it
Sir please, I've deleted it
Sir, I have private photos in there
Put your hand down
That's not fair
Mr Etesami?
Sir?
I have personal things on there.
I deleted the video.
On my mother's life, I deleted it
Sir, send it on Telegram,
so that everyone can see.
It's much better than this movie.
I'll kick you out of the class,
if you say another word.
Mr. Etesami!
Sorry, Sir
You stay out of this!
Mr Etesami?
I mean all of you.
I'm talking to him.
I deleted it
Please
Call your father to
come to the school
and see the kind of photos
you have on your cell.
His dad's dead, Sir.
Hi, sorry about that
Hi, no problem.
If it's a hassle for you to keep moving it,
then you can leave it in the corner.
Next to the boiler room.
When my husband gets back
he'll move it to a better place.
I don't want you to have to keep
going up and down the stairs.
I'm going out for a couple of hours
you can take my spot.
Don't worry,
I'll find a better place for it.
Suit yourself.
Sorry
If you give me the keys, I can do it
Thanks
My wife said, you're not going to report it.
No.
You're doing the right thing,
they won't do anything,
even if they catch him.
And you'll have to explain over and over
why you opened the door
... plus trekking back
and forth to the court.
Endless hassle for nothing
But he'll probably be back for his car.
Please, call me if he shows up.
I'll sort out that bastard.
I'll take mine out and
then come and park yours.
There's no need,
I'll do it myself.
Okay, then, goodbye.
Thanks.
Goodbye
How's it going?
Hey, you okay?
Is Rana here?
No, wasn't she with you?
She's coming on her own
Any news about the guy?
Who?
Babak had heard some things
from your neighbors.
Where is he?
Is he here?
Babak?
Yep, he's back there.
Hi
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
What should I have told you?
About the man turning up
the other night.
How's Rana?
The neighbors told you
They're also worried...
Tell 'em nothing happened,
the guy just barged in.
Then why are you keeping his pickup?
Shahnazari said it's in the parking lot.
Tell them we'll be gone soon
we're looking for a new place.
Where will you go?
I won't let you
Can you find that previous tenant
and arrange a meeting for me?
Why?
I wanna talk to her.
Ask her why she did this
Did what?
Sent this thug to our house
Why would she do that?
You said yourself, she made threats
about us touching her stuff.
She's nothing like that.
She hasn't taken her stuff
because she still
hasn't found a place.
She was just annoyed
with me that day.
Hello
Feeling better?
Yep, I'm fine thanks
Did you tell the guys?
No
Then how do they know?
One of the neighbor had called Babak.
I'm not sure what they said
Emad, get dressed and
come for the make up.
My outfit's not here
Kati's going to take your place tonight.
And you accepted, just like that?
What can I do?
It's not up to me.
The director wanted her
to replace you tonight.
If you're alright, and you can do it,
I'll go talk to her.
No, I don't want to
Have you started house-hunting?
No, I will do
As soon as I get time
When you get time! Like it doesn't
matter how I feel in that place!
You haven't done anything
Huh?
I want us to go to the police,
but you won't let me. What do you mean?
You said you'd drop by the school,
find a substitute teacher, and pick me up.
I couldn't find anyone
to cover my class.
Auntie?
Yes Baby?
Why aren't you acting tonight?
I'm not feeling well tonight, darling.
Why did you come here then?
I get bored at home
What?
Well, I get bored here.
Would you like to come
to our house this evening?
Do you have Spongebob?
No, but we can go buy it on the way home.
From tomorrow you really
need to perform again.
Everything's Topsy turvy.
Everybody's making mistakes.
Why?
I don't know, everyone's upset
You're better now,
you should act again tomorrow.
Mum?
Darling?
Can I go to Auntie's house?
No, baby.
Let him stay with me tonight, I'm alone.
I'll bring him with me tomorrow.
He can't, his dad's coming to pick him up
to go to his house tomorrow.
Well, his Dad can pick him up
from our place.
You wanna go?
Yes!
You won't be a nuisance for Auntie Rana?
He won't.
Tell Emad we're taking the car.
I'll bring his things over.
I need to pee, auntie.
I know, go on, go inside
Whose bike is this?
That... belongs to some kid.
Where's the kid?
The kid's not here anymore.
Where did he go?
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Moved to a new house.
Don't you need to pee?
Oh, yes!
Go on then
Not that one, over here
Well...
...it's dark!
I'm coming...
It's scary in there
Come on
No, I don't need to go anymore.
Let me help
No, you go... I... I'll do it
Are you feeling shy in front of me?
Nope!
Can you do it yourself?
I'm drawing his mustache
Yes?
Come up, dear.
Who was it?
Uncle Emad
If it's my dad,
then tell him Sadra's not here.
Why?
Because I love my Mom
Okay
Rana?
Hey
The pickup isn't in the parking.
I parked it outside this morning.
Why?
I didn't fancy moving
it every ten minutes
Hello!
Helloooo, how are you kid?
Where are the keys?
Where you'd left them.
How are things with my favorite?
Welcome to our house, all good?
Welcome!
Leave it where it is Emad
I'll be right back
Emad... Emad...
Let's forget all that for tonight,
just leave it.
I've made dinner,
go wash your hands and change.
Go on, darling
Ready for takeoff
ladies and gentleman!
Sadra!
Yes!
Emad it's ready,
come before it gets cold.
Coming
Let's go wash those hands of yours.
My hands are clean!
Let's wash them again anyways.
Wow, wow, wow, look at this!
Thanks so much
Get your hands off it!
Rana, where are you?
Sadra, come and eat!
Helllllo
Hello trouble, have you two been
having fun without me?
We went shopping
and then hung out
Well done!
We went shopping and then hung out
But we didn't find Spongebob
Yes, unfortunately.
Don't worry, Patrick,
eventually a good day will come
when you and I will find someone.
Look at this, Spongebob!
Look what Auntie Rana made, macaroni!
More?
No no, that's enough
Okay, just let me know
Thank you
Wow, what a nice macaroni!
Bon appetit!
Let's eat it all
Look what she's made.
Yeah, I know!
How was tonight's performance?
Very...
not that great.
It was terrible
You're lying
That's how it is without you
Did you find the credit card?
No
How did you go shopping?
With the money you'd left
What money?
In the drawer.
Why aren't you eating?
Do you not like it?
Is it not tasty?
Don't eat it
What's up?
That scumbag had left it behind
the other night.
Sadra?
I've got an idea
Do you like pizza?
Yep
Then let's order some pizza.
Don't eat that, it's not good
Do you like fries?
And after that Ice Cream?
Hi there.
Gimme a call when you can.
Hello? Mum? Mummy?
Hello? Uncle?
Are you there?
It's the 3rd time I'm calling.
Ahoo darling, it's Babak
Ahoo... Ahoo...
Are you there?
Gimme a call when you get home,
I'll be up late.
What are you doing?
Nothing
Come on, go sleep.
You haven't slept for two nights
I can't sleep.
Why did you open her letters?
It's her private stuff.
I wanna find out
who the hell that scumbag was.
Let's say you find out how it was...
He'll say it was a mistake
He came inside by mistake?
He rang the bell
and I opened the door.
He must've thought it's that woman
since I opened the door so easily.
He came here by mistake?
Any when he realized his mistake...
...Why didn't he leave?
Because he saw the bathroom light's on
and there's a woman in there?
How would he know it's a...
From your clothes on the bed.
If I'd just used the damn intercom...
If I'd just asked who it was...
None of this would've happened
If you think it's that simple...
You can just tell all the neighbors
about the intercom...
Why are you getting
the neighbors into this?
They knew what was
going on in this house.
So it'd be fine with you,
if they didn't know?
What are you on about?
Leave me alone.
The pickup wasn't there
What?
Sorry
Where was it?
There
Sorry
Where did you leave it?
I left it there
Where?
Over there, where the Peugeot is
He's taken it
I have to find that asshole
Jackass!
Okay, slow down!
It's freezing in there.
Never mind.
What do you mean, never mind?
You'll get sick.
Let's go to a public bath.
No, I'll be out quick.
Just wait here.
Hasanpoor, come here a sec.
Hello
What can I do for you, Sir?
Hi
How's it going?
Your dad was a traffic cop, right?
He's retired now, why?
A car hit my wife and drove off.
Hope it's nothing serious, Sir!
No, thank God
It was a pickup, if I give you
the number plate...
Can your Dad find the guy's address?
If it's not too much trouble, that is.
Sure,
he has contacts in the department.
If you gimme the license plate,
he can find out.
But, I think you should report it.
It wasn't anything serious, so
I don't wanna get the police mixed up.
Okay, gimme the registration
and I'll call my Dad.
- Get a pen and a paper, then.
- Okay.
Why don’t you want to work for me?
Have you lost your mind, Charlie?
I've got a job.
Then what’re you walkin’
in here every week for?
Well, if you don’t want me to
walk in here...
I'm offering you a job.
I don't want your goddam job!
I've got one already. Get outa my way!
When the hell are you
going to grow up, huh?
Goddam you, Charlie!
You big ignoramus!
Big ignoramus!
How dare you talk to me like that?
If you say that to me again,
I’II rap you one!
I don’t care how big you are!
You degenerate!
What's wrong with you tonight?
What did I do?
Why are you adding dialogues?
What did I add?
If you've got a problem with me,
let's sit and talk.
Not on the stage, calling me,
"You degenerate!"
It's neither improvisation, nor acting,
you're insulting me.
What?
Did I hurt your feeling?
Yeah.
And if you do that one more time,
I'll answer you right in front of everyone.
Degenerate is the one who speaks his mind
through swearing.
Didn't know that.
I'm really sorry.
Bakery
Hello, how're you doing?
Speaking Azeri
What can I do for you?
Two baguettes, please.
You want 'em cut?
Thanks a lot.
That pickup is yours?
Why?
There's an officer writing tickets,
from the top of the street.
Majid, come here, go move the car.
...before the officer slaps a ticket on it.
Soheil, bring the keys.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Later.
Bye.
Here you go, Sir.
Thanks.
Thanks, dude.
I'll take a water.
Hello, mister, sorry
is that your pickup?
Yeah.
I had some load, I wanted to
ask you to move it for me.
Nah, that pickup is for a store.
Well, not now, whenever you're free.
No, it's just that, I do something else.
I don't do that.
Not even Friday?
Nah.
You can find pickups at
the top of Haft-e-Tir.
No, it's just that,
my stuff are books and paintings
and things like that,
I was looking for a softopper.
You know, on account of rain
or things like that.
I'm really busy.
I don't have time.
I don't care about the fee. I'll pay.
I just want my stuff to get there safe.
It's just that, I'm busy.
I can't.
Majid, come on, man.
Help the guy. Late night or something.
Well, how about you gimme your number?
I'll call you whenever you say.
And if you come yourself,
even better.
Bro, find some time between
your schedule for him.
Careful not to hit the walls.
Ah! what're you doing here?
Come here... kitty...
Careful with that not to scratch it.
Babak, tell 'em to come
have a cup of tea.
- There's no need for that.
- It's getting cold.
Where are you taking these?
I'm taking'em to my parent's parking lot.
We'll see what happens.
Won't she come to take 'em?
She's got problems of her own.
She hasn't found a place yet.
Get up, Babak wants to
take away that woman's stuff.
What do you want me to do?
What's going on
between you two?
Nothing, let him take 'em.
That's okay with me.
Hello? Majid?
It's me, Etesami, couple days ago.
You free today?
How about Friday?
Yeah?
You?
Yeah, come on up.
Hello, can I help you?
Hello, Sir. You okay?
Have I come to the right place?
Majid said, there's some stuff
you need to move.
That's right, come on in.
Why didn't he come himself?
Well, he was busy,
so he sent me instead.
- After you.
- You first.
But he didn't say anything
about all these stairs.
With this heart of mine.
Well, if I knew you're coming,
I would've told him about the stairs,
and the broken elevator.
Well, I can't use elevators anyways, Sir.
Would you gimme a glass of water?
Have you hired movers?
No, I thought he's coming.
And, we'd take the boxes ourselves.
Well, the poor guy
was kinda busy today.
- Is he your son?
- Nah, my son-in-law.
Doesn't make a difference though.
He's like my own son.
Sorry, old man, we just moved out.
There's no glasses or anything.
That's alright, mister.
I'll drink from the tap.
Where are the boxes?
In that room.
We'll see. If there's too many,
we'll call movers.
Give him a call. Maybe he's around
here somewhere. I can pick him up.
Who?
Your son-in-law.
Nah, the poor souls just went shopping
for the "exchange of the vows" ceremony.
Isn't the janitor
allowed to help here?
Nah, the building's empty.
The walls caved,
the residents have all moved out.
Wow, wow! what if it collapses
on us or something?
Nah.
Let's take a look and see
if it's worth hiring movers.
Grandpa!
What?
Would you come sit here for a sec?
I wanna tell you something.
Look here, mister,
this isn't my line of work.
Majid, said, "there's this guy,
who's called a couple times...
...would you do it?"
I said, okay, why not?
Now, you paying depends on
how generous you're feeling.
Nah, it's not about... wages,
fees, and stuff like that.
Just sit down. There's something
I have to tell you.
Good news, I hope.
How long do you know this guy?
- My son-in-law?
- Yeah.
What for?
I wanna know
if you know him well.
Well, it's about two years they've
asked for my daughter's hand.
Have you asked around
about him?
Do you know Majid?
If there's anything you know,
just tell me.
When my wife and I moved out of here,
we went to a place that...
...it's previous tenant was... you know,
a woman of the street.
One night, when I got home a little late.
My wife was alone in the house.
One of these lowlifes on account of
that woman still being there...
...enters my house.
When my wife was
in the bathroom.
The jerk goes
into the bathroom.
Who?
That filthy
son-in-law of yours.
Now, how do you know
it was Majid?
When my wife starts screaming,
the guys makes a run for it, but...
He was in such a hurry that,
he leaves his pickup behind.
I found him from his pickup.
I went down to where he works.
I wanted to go there,
grab hold of him...
...and dishonor him in front
of all his co-workers, but...
I couldn't bring myself to do it.
This pickup changes hands
a lot in that store.
That's why I asked him to come here.
To talk to him, and ask him...
... if it was him or someone else.
Majid's not like that...
if I find out it's been him,
I'll call off everything.
The wedding and all.
How's your wife, now?
I don't know what to say.
Let me talk to him tonight.
Give him a call and tell him
I wanna talk to him.
Tell him to come here,
I wanna ask him who's done it.
Well, it's just,
they've gone with my wife and daughter
for "the exchange of vows" shopping.
Well, at least give him a call.
Ask him who had his pickup
that night.
When did this happen?
About two weeks ago.
Okay, so you just let me
talk to him tonight... Oh my...
But, I wanna talk to him,
old man.
Wait a second, I wanna talk to him.
Call him.
I don't have his number
in my phone.
I have it.
When I say call him to come here,
it's because I don't want to...
...go down to the store,
make a scene in front of his co-workers.
You just let me
make sure it's him.
I have to talk to him in such a way
that I'll get an answer...
How about I call him myself, huh?
You want me to do it?
Okay, let me just
dial his number.
Hello, Majid? Hi, son...
where are you guys?
Yeah, I'm here with him.
Who's with you?
Listen, when you're alone, gimme a call.
I wanna tell you something.
Call my cell.
I don't have it memorized.
Ask Moj'gan.
Okay... it's nothing...
Bye.
He said, he'll call when he's alone.
Say, what do you do yourself?
I work with this car of Majid's.
His pickup.
I sell clothes from the
back of the pickup, at nights.
and I don't come out during the day,
on account of my heart.
And, how come you don't have
your son-in-law's number?
Well, I just don't.
Not just him, a lot of people.
Have you just bought
this number of yours?
No.
How come... your son-in-law
doesn't have your number?
You just told him to
get it from someone else, huh?
I don't know, man, I don't know.
I'm so messed up right now that,
I don't even remember my own name.
Wait a second, old man.
- It won't open.
- Not so fast. Wait a minute.
If it's okay, I want you
to take off your shoes.
What for?
I wanna see your foot.
Mister, I'm as old as your father,
you telling me to take off my shoes?
Open the door, let me go!
I didn't do anything to you.
Why are you talking like that?
Take it easy.
Just take off your shoes for a sec.
Then, I'll open the door for you to leave.
Why should I take off my shoes?
Open the door!
Hush! Come here.
Let's go over there.
Sit on the stair, for a sec,
take off your shoes.
Sit!
Sit down!
Just sit, okay?
Take off your shoes, please.
I'm not feeling well, just don't!
Well, let me help you.
I'll take it off, okay.
whispering: I'll take it off.
The other one,
take off the other one too.
Your socks too.
Mister, what do you want from me?
Take 'em off!
I said, take off your socks.
Let me do it myself.
- No!
- Let me!.. just let me!
Hello, Siavash!
No, I'm a little busy right now.
What time is it, anyways?
No I'll be there.
Don't worry.
She'll come herself...
She's a little busy.
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm fine.
Okay, bye.
Swear on my life, I didn't
want to hurt anyone.
Did that woman tell
you to go there that night?
That woman had been messaging me
for at least a month.
She said, "If you still have the pickup,
come over, I wanna see you."
And I messaged back,
"Ahoo, dear, sorry...
I'm not feeling well.
I can't come.
She took it to herself.
No matter how many times I called...
She never answered.
Didn't want to talk to me.
That night, I thought I'd drop by
and make it up to her.
Didn't you know she's moved out?
God knows, I had no idea.
Swear on my kids' life...
You opened the door, and went in.
You saw the furniture is different...
How come you're saying
you didn't know?
I went in, I saw a bunch of stuff,
the bicycle I had bought myself...
I thought maybe she's moving.
You're not going out of that door,
until you tell the truth.
If I had the slightest idea that
you guys have moved in,
I would've thought, maybe
there's a man in the bathroom.
- My wife's clothes were on the bed.
- I didn't saw those.
You saw those and figured
there must be a woman in the bath.
...all alone, she even
opened the door for you.
I didn't see any clothes.
It didn't take even five minutes.
I came in, there was no one there.
Just a minute ago, your wife
had opened the door for me.
Why did your wife
open the door for me?
Well, she thought it's me.
Let me tell you
what really happened.
I went by the bathroom door,
called the kid, as soon as I did...
...there starts the screaming.
Then, I ran away.
You went into the bathroom.
I didn't go in the bathroom.
Then, where was your foot cut like that?
I have no idea.
By the time I was downstairs...
I felt a sting in my foot. I thought I've
stepped on something running down stairs.
Then, my wife's lying?
Your wife says I went into the bathroom?
My wife was scared and
bumped into the glass,
otherwise God knows what you
would've done, dirty scumbag!
I swear on my life or
whatever's dear to you...
as soon as I found out I'm
in the wrong place, I ran away.
Well, just tell your wife to come here.
Here, I'll wait right here. Ask her.
What's my wife supposed to say?
My wife's said all she had to say.
It's your wife's turn to come here.
Call her, and tell her to
come here, right now.
What for?
What you said, I want you to repeat
in front of your wife.
Mister, why don't you get it?
I didn't go in that bath...
Okay, you didn't!
I want you to tell your wife
what you were doing in that house.
Call her, right now!
Get it out, and call her!
Nope! Get out your cell!
Don't make me look bad
in front of my wife and kids.
Call her, right now.
My daughter's about to get married.
Your daughter has to know
her real father.
I'm gonna tell your son-in-law everything,
just so he knows his father-in-law.
I don't have have to keep you here.
Go on, get out! Go!
I'm gonna call your son-in-law,
tell him to bring your wife here...
Leave me alone, mister! Ah!
Someone help me!
Help!
Don't make noises!
Quiet!
Open the door! Open up!
I'll die!
I'm about to have a stroke.
Open the door!
Mister! open the door!
I'm afraid of closed spaces.
Open the door, my boy.
At least turn on the lights.
Forgive me...
... my dear!
I can’t cry.
Why did you ever do that to yourself?
I don’t understand it.
Help me, Willy!
It seems to me that you’re
just on another trip.
I keep expecting you.
I made the last payment
on the house today.
Right today.
And there’II
be nobody home.
We’re free and clear.
We’re free.
Rana, lock the door,
and take the keys.
Get up, on your feet.
Here, wait.
Sit here.
You go in that room.
Look how mentally and
emotionally shattered she is.
There's my wife. Are you gonna keep saying
you haven't gone into the bathroom?
I'm sorry.
Answer me.
I made a mistake.
Tell me, why did you
go into the bathroom?
I gave into temptation.
What are you gonna do to him?
His family are on their way,
I want his wife to know what he's done.
You're taking your revenge.
Let him go, let him leave.
I know what I'm doing.
You sit here, there's no need
for you to come out.
Where are you going?
I'm not feeling right at all.
Let me go.
They're coming after you.
Your son-in-law called,
he asked about you.
I told him to come over.
And to bring your wife too.
They're on their way.
Sit down.
I'm begging you, please
let me go.
When your family get here.
Tell them everything you told me.
Then you can leave.
I'm begging you.
Miss!
Forgive me.
Let me go, before they get here.
That woman lived with me for
35 years.
Mister! get up!
Get up, go!
You, sit down!
Leave him alone, let him go.
He'll go, he will. When his family get here,
they can leave together.
Sit down.
For the love of God!
Here, mister, go.
- Just, sit down.
- Let him go!
My girl!..
My boy!
- Leave him alone, Emad!
- You stay out of this!
- Sit down!
- Please.
I said sit down! Ah!
SIT... DOWN!
Here.
What?..
What do you want?
Oh, my God!
Emad!
Does he, by any chance,
take any under-the-tongue pills?
I searched. There's nothing
in his pockets.
- What happened?
- Where are you now?
No, no, get here as soon as you can.
Okay, okay.
- Was it the Emergency?
- His family. They're coming.
- Oh, my God!
- Mister! can you hear me?
Does he have a pulse?
Emad, can you hear his heartbeat?
Rana, for God's sake, keep quiet.
Let me see what I'm doing.
Where are you going?
He said he's got pills.
Maybe they're in the car.
Can you hear me?..
Open your mouth. Open!
Mister! get up!
Can you hear me?
Oh, God!..
Oh, God!
You better now?
You feeling better?
Breathe! Breathe!
You better, now?
Don't worry,
he's better.
You didn't call the Emergency?
No, I was afraid he might be dead.
Wait a minute!
If you say anything to his family,
I don't wanna have anything to do with you.
Yes?
- Hello.
- The elevator's broken, use the stairs.
Come on, ma!
You go ahead,
I can't run with this pain in my legs.
Ya Ali!
My dear.
Come on in.
Come in.
Ya Allah! Dad!
Dad!
How are you dad?
- Majid!
- What? Come in.
- Dad! Daddy!
- Thank God, he's fine.
You okay, dad?
I'm fine.
You're okay.
That was such a scare, dad.
Where's you mother?
She's in the stairs.
Let me call her.
Majid, don't call her.
- Let's go!
- We'll go, dad, just wait a little.
Majid! if mother doesn't see him,
she'd think something
must've happened to him.
Let her see he's fine.
Hello, sorry. We were in such a hurry
that we didn't notice you.
That's alright.
Sit down, dad. What
are you getting up for?
I thought mother better come up and see you,
and then we'll leave. Sit.
We're in no hurry.
Let him sit down until he gets better.
We're really sorry, mister.
Dad, just sit down.
Can you?
Yeah, I'm alright.
Majid!
What is it, ma?
We're here.
Come. Thank God, dad's sitting here.
He's all right.
What is, dad?..
Huh?
- It's nothing, ma.
- What happened?
What happened to you?
Sweetheart, didn't I tell you not to go?
See what you're doing to me and yourself?
Oh, God.
Thank you so much, God!
God knows, on our way here
I vowed to give away a hundred
different charities, just to
hear his voice one more time.
Thank God.
How many times did
I tell you not to go?
My dear! I don't want you to work.
I don't.
Darling, you said, "Majid called,
I have to go, I'll be back soon."
Soon, you call this "soon"?
Mom, we have to thank these guys,
they stayed with him all this time.
or else, we don't know
what would've happened to dad.
We really don't know how to thank you.
That was so kind of you.
May God give you back, miss.
He's my whole life, mister.
Thank you so much.
You gave me my life back.
He's all I've got.
Come on, mom, stop it.
Get up, let's go.
Did you take all your stuff, dad?
Where's your cellphone?
Car keys.
Where's his glasses?
Don't leave without his glasses.
I've got it...
Come here, I'll give it to you.
- You go, I'll get it
- Majid, the glasses...
This way.
What business?
You just saved his life, son.
No, mister, we've put you through
enough trouble already.
It's nothing fancy, you know.
Come on, this way.
Well, if there's anything to do,
just let me...
No, let him come himself.
Come on, this way.
You guys go.
Majid. let me...
How much money did you
leave in the room, that night?
Huh?
How much money did you
leave in the room?
I didn't count.
What happened, dad?
What happened to you?
Oh, my God!
He's sick again.
What are these?..
Where were these?
- Come on, sit down a little.
- Is it your heart, dad?
Let him sit for a while.
Come on, this way.
We can't take him like this. Majid!
Majid, hurry up!
- We're almost there, dad.
- Esmat!
I'm hear, dear.
Come on, mom.
Watch it, don't drop him.
- Esmat! Esmat!
- What? Darling, I'm here.
What happened to you?
Ya Abalfazl!
Stretch his legs.
- God! Dad! you hear me? Dad!
- Where are his pills?
Where are his pills?
Search his pockets.
Stretch his legs! Hurry up!
- God help us!
- Dad, breathe!
See if his pills are upstairs.
Miss! Miss! are my dad's pills here?
He's got sick again,
he's lying in the stairs.
Mister, for God's sake, will you
get on the way right away?
Yes, miss, just give some time
for my colleagues to get there.
Just follow my instructions.
His legs must be straight, not bent.
He's lying face up.
Mister, he's all blue in the face.
Just keep doing what I told you.
If you get tired, let someone else do it.
Mister, he's not moving...
No, no, nothing. He's not moving at all.
Mister,
can we put his pill under his tongue?
No, no, miss, don't give him anything,
just do what I told you.
Just make sure his legs,
are stretched, not bent.
Yeah, yeah.
Guys, please hurry up!
- Hello, where's the patient?
- He's inside.
Psagmeno.com
Subtitles / Screenshots / Trailers
Subtitles: Amir Shumal