Everyone...
Everyone!
Wait!
Wait! Everyone!
A dream...
Good morning!
Morning!
Kourin isn't here?
Even though she's always here before I am...
Don't tell me...
What about everyone else?
Mornin'!
Good morning!
Naoki! Shingo!
Somethin' wrong?
No. It's nothing.
First, the Australopithecus
was born in Africa...
So Kourin never did show up, huh?
I wonder if something came up?
Shall we try calling her?
Well?
No good. Nobody's answering.
Well, she is an idol.
She's probably just busy with work.
To be sure, Ultra-rare is
an ultra-popular idol group.
Did you know they've got another
new song coming out soon?
Still, to not even let us know...
But that reminds me, what are
we doing for the club today?
Right!
Apparently Misaki is busy
helping out at the shop.
And it's been a while, so I thought
we could gather at Card Capital.
Great idea! We can try our skills
against students from other schools
without the interference
of that Student Council!
The guys from Hitsue High hang
out at Card Capital, don't they?
Yeah. They could be there.
All right! This is my chance at revenge!
I'm fired up!
...Ah. I'd like to stop by a
bookstore on the way over...
Sure.
Shoot! I left my bag inside.
You guys go on ahead. I'll catch right up.
In that case, why don't we
just reconvene at the shop?
Sure, that'd be fine.
Okay! See ya in a bit!
Mystery Dragon
Still, it's hard to concentrate on the club with
the Student Council breathin' down our necks.
I don't even know why they're in the picture.
Jeez...
Ain't she the Student Council secretary?
All right. Maybe I'll go an'
give her a piece of my mind!
Man, she walks fast...
She's not goin' to the
Student Council office?!
There...
What kinda room is this?
How do you open this door?
Yes. Understood.
No. Everything's fine here.
Yes. I will continue to
monitor the Cardfight Club.
Whoa!
You!
I heard that!
Under whose orders are you
spyin' on our Cardfight Club?!
I revise my report. An unforeseen
development has occurred.
W-What the...?!
Yes. I am going to resolve
the problem immediately.
Kourin was absent?
Yes. She didn't come to
school at all today...
Sendou is too worried about it.
She's just busy with her
work as an idol, I tell you.
Takuto could be calling the school
right now to let them know.
I remember she did seem really busy
when we had the school festival.
That's true, but...
Aichi.
What's bothering you?
Kai...
Before now, Kourin's always contacted us
to let us know when she couldn't make it.
So her absence today without any
warning kind of made me worry.
Is that all?
Well... and, also, this morning,
I had sort of a nightmare...
A nightmare?
Yeah. I mean, it's not a big deal...
Naoki! That took a while, huh?
It took way too long, you
would-be juvenile delinquent!
What's wrong?
Listen, it's pointless to
designate a place to meet
if you're just going to show
up whenever you feel like it!
You're no good.
How am I no good?!
That's an outrageous thing for
you of all people to say, Ishida!
I wouldn't be satisfied with you.
I'm looking for a strong opponent.
What's with him?
You.
Fight me.
Huh? Me?
That's right. I gotta
fight a strong opponent.
"Strong opponent"?
What the heck? That's pretty
overbearing for a practice match.
What's wrong, Aichi Sendou?!
Are you gonna fight me?
Sure. Let's do it.
That's what I wanna hear.
Be careful, Aichi.
I sense something's not right about him.
Yeah, got it.
Thank you, Kai.
Certainly, Naoki isn't his usual self.
But I don't want to run away from any fight.
Naoki, picture it...
I don't need that stuff.
It's pointless.
Right now, I'm gonna
crush you and your image.
Naoki?!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Eradicator, Blade Hang Dracokid.
Cheer Up Trumpeter!
Blade Hang Dracokid?
Naoki, you've changed
your first Vanguard, huh?
I ride Demolition Dragon.
I ride Llew!
I call Marron!
I ride Vowing Sword Dragon.
Ride!
Call!
Alfred!
I guard with Guld, a perfect guard!
What's that about?! Ishida's
acting oddly high and mighty,
even though it took no time at
all for him to get 5 damage!
In the end, he went off half-cocked.
Ishida is still Ishida.
Kid with the glasses, I know how you
feel, but you gotta watch without bias.
Sure, he's got 5 damage, but the match
doesn't look one-sided from where I'm sitting.
True. And Ishida hasn't
made any mistakes so far.
In fact, I'd say it's
an evenly-matched fight.
But it can't be!
Ishida...?!
What is it?
Certainly, I'm fighting Naoki,
but it doesn't seem like him.
You're disappointin' me, Aichi Sendou!
I was lookin' for the strongest Vanguard
fighter, and is this his ability?
Well, whatever. I'll take
down the strongest fighter.
That's my...
That's what I... was ordered to do.
What? What'd he just say?!
"Ordered"?
That's right. Here I go!
Final Turn!
Final Turn?!
"Final Turn," he says?!
That voice echoes in the darkness,
whispering for me to beat Aichi Sendou!
Observe!
The ebony flames that burn
in the pitch-black darkness!
Crossbreak ride!
Eradicator, Vowing Saber Dragon "Reverse"!
"Crossbreak ride"?!
Crossbreak ride?!
What is that? I've never heard of it!
A crossride... on top of a break ride?
That unit has an ominous aura!
Eradicator, Vowing Saber Dragon "Reverse"...
A unit like this exists?
Kai... How about you?
It's the first time I've seen it.
A unit that neither of you know...
Break ride skill!
My Vanguard gets +10000 power!
And I retire one of your
front rear-guard units!
On top of that... Limit Break activated!
I retire two units and get +10000 power!
Suddenly, three of his
rear-guards are retired?!
It isn't over yet.
Hey, ya know, this isn't my limit.
Another Limit Break!
I don't believe it! The five rear-guards
that were on Sendou's field...
...were all retired in an instant?!
And now I get another +10000 power.
But I still ain't done.
When Vowing Sword Dragon is in the Soul,
Eradicator, Vowing Saber Dragon
"Reverse" gets +2000 power!
That's a total of 43000!
Did you see my crossbreak ride?
That's the power of Eradicator,
Vowing Saber Dragon "Reverse"!
Crossbreak ride...
What overwhelming power...
That's 43000 with just one unit!
Uh oh. Aichi doesn't have a perfect guard!
And that's not all. Look at his rear-guard.
Th-That's... Homing Eradicator, Rochishin!
You noticed? Every time a rear-guard
is retired, Rochishin gets +5000 power.
In other words, with five rear-guards
retired, he gets +25000 power!
Even the rear-guard has 33000...
Sendou...!
W-What is that power coming off of Naoki?
Naoki Ishida...
True, at the VF High School
Championship preliminaries,
I saw how he'd made tremendous strides.
But his strength here is clearly
different from that time.
What in the world happened?!
What do you think of the power of
a crossbreak ride, Aichi Sendou?
Aichi... Can you fight him?
Aichi!
Naoki, this is amazing.
With your strength here, it feels like I'm
fighting a completely different person.
But somehow,
I sense that something is
off with your strength.
Like it's not true strength,
but something sinister...
That's why I don't want to lose against you!
Eradicator, Vowing Saber
Dragon "Reverse" attacks!
No guard!
Drive trigger check!
Rochishin attacks!
Guard!
Awesome, Aichi! He successfully
guarded against that attack!
His Final Turn failed.
Even if he acts differently
than usual, Ishida is Ishida.
But Aichi isn't in good shape either.
He successfully guarded against the attack,
but now he has zero cards in his hand.
Moreover, he has zero rear-guards.
Will he be able to win it this turn?
Too bad, Aichi Sendou.
You managed to protect against my
attack, but now you can't do anything.
What do you think about my strength?
Well, you are definitely strong...
...but I can't afford to lose to
you when you're like this, Naoki!
Naoki! When you joined the Cardfight
Club, what did you say to me?
That you wanted to play Vanguard together!
And you wanted to find something that you
could really get passionate about, remember?!
But I don't sense that
passionate soul in you now.
What?!
Naoki, your soul has always overflowed
with passion for Vanguard and
fondness for your friends!
That enthusiasm has always encouraged me.
Your strong support helped
to found the Cardfight Club!
Friends... Friends...
I'm going to make you remember
the true power of friendship!
Even in solitude, only your strong soul,
unafraid of any fight, knows true friendship!
I ride...
...Wolf Fang Liberator, Garmore!
And now, my gathered champions,
go to that lonely soul!
Limit Break!
I superior call from my deck!
You called Gancelot?!
Another card!
What?!
I call Geraint!
One more!
I call Marron!
And then Mark!
I don't believe it! What is this?!
I call Epona!
Your rear-guards...
The rear-guards that I retired...
...are all back!
That's right. That's Garmore's Limit Break!
Fellowship Circle!
I'm not acceptin' it!
I'm not acceptin' that image!
Just by riding, he was able to
put five rear-guards into play...
It's incredible... It's too incredible!
From the abyss of despair, he
calls together his comrades
and sends up the signal flare of a comeback.
Yep. That's just like Aichi.
Gancelot attacks with a boost from Epona!
Intercept!
Garmore's skill is activated!
Epona!
Marron boosts!
Let's go!
Darn it! No guard!
I won...
He did it...
Sendou wins!
Naoki?!
What the...?!
I-Ishida!
Naoki!
Ishida!
Is he okay? He didn't hit his head, did he?
Are you all right? Naoki!
Naoki?
Aichi... Where are we?
Card Capital!
How...? When did I get here?
You don't remember?
You just had a Cardfight with Aichi.
No... I don't remember.
But we were talking about going to
Card Capital after school, right?
And then I went back to the
classroom to get my bag...
After that...
Darn it! I can't remember!
Naoki Ishida has been released from Reverse.
It's unfortunate. I thought
we could use him as a pawn.
Still, let's continue with the plan.
Naoki, are you really okay?
Yeah. I'm fine now.
What do you mean, you're "fine now"?!
I don't forgive you for your insults before!
Insults...? I don't remember.
Excuse me?! Are you saying you
were possessed or something?!
I'm sayin' I dunno!
If you can't remember...
maybe you bumped your head?
Eh?! In that case, this is serious!
You should go to the hospital...
Y-Yeah. Maybe...
His memories from earlier... are gone...
This is Eradicator, Vowing
Saber Dragon "Reverse"...
The card... disappeared?!
Naoki, are you all right?
I don't know why you're
worried, but yeah, no problem.
You weren't yourself, Ishida.
Maybe, but I just don't remember...
You were acting strange, somehow.
Huh? I wonder where Kai went.
He was right next to me before.
Next time: Lock!
Lock!
What's wrong, Aichi? You look anxious.
Oh, I just had a bad feeling about
something. But it's nothing.