Morning, Emi!
Morning, Mai!
Listen to this! Listen to this!
The Cardfight Club that Aichi formed
was recognized as an official club!
Really?! Good for them!
Yep. Oh, and it made our mom happy, too.
Cardfight Club Now Official
Congratulations on getting official
approval for your Cardfight Club, Aichi.
Now dig in. It's a special Shizuka dinner.
Th-Thank you...
Uh... uh... Shizuka... right...
She didn't have to make so much
that we couldn't eat it all...
Your mom must be proud of your
brother for working so hard.
Yeah. For the shy Aichi to change this much...
I think he owes it to Vanguard.
Yep, must be!
Come to think of it, she's...
She did say she was going to be late.
That girl is amazing, you know?
I really admire her.
Me too.
Let's do our best, too!
Yeah!
Miyaji Academy, Middle School Division
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
Cardfight Circle?
According to the Komoi Information Network,
which is spread throughout the academy,
a "Cardfight Circle" has formed
in the middle school division.
No doubt they came together
after being influenced by the
formation of our own Cardfight Club.
Huh, influenced by us...
That kinda makes me happy, but
also a little uncomfortable...
This is an instance where we should
provide guidance as upperclassmen.
Guidance?
That's right.
Cross over from the high school
to middle school division
and learn from each other through
a little friendly competition.
Not a bad idea, eh?
Learn from each other
through competition!
I got nothin' against
that passionate feeling!
All right! Let's give these
kids some guidance!
As a Vanguard beginner, silly
Ishida, you totally fell for it.
You don't realize it, but this
is part of my grand plan.
If I show off my prowess
as an upperclassman now,
the underclassmen who join
our club starting next year
will look upon me with respect.
That's right!
Ishida stole the position
of Cardfight Vice-captain,
but I'm the one who possesses
the real power of influence.
I respect Sendou and Misaki,
and Kourin is strong,
but I can't abide this hierarchy
that puts me at the bottom
while a Vanguard noob like
Ishida looks down on me!
Cardfight Club
I'm going to use the power of the Komoi
Corps to stand higher than Ishida.
What are you laughin' at?
Gulp! N-Nothing! Well, shall we go?
Shouldn't we go with Aichi?
Our opponents are middle school students.
Just the two of us is plenty.
I guess you're right...
If Sendou were to go with us, all of
the respect would go his way. Right?
Come on, let's go!
O-Okay...
Come on, come on!
Cardfight Circle
Looks like this is the place.
Puttin' out a wimpy sign like that
tells me they don't got enough passion.
I'll get 'em back on track!
Let's help these guys!
What the heck is this?!
I don't believe it.
Is this really the Cardfight Circle clubroom?
I feel itchy all over...
I can't relax here...
Um, can I help you with something?
Are you two members of the Cardfight Circle?
Yes!
So what's with this room?
Me, Mai over there, and one more
are the founding members.
We three started the Cardfight Circle.
She's the one who had the idea
to make the room all cute.
I'm surprised the school allowed it.
Yeah...
Anyway, what are you two from the high
school division's Cardfight Club doing here?
When I heard that you formed
the Cardfight Circle,
I thought we could fight so
you could learn a few things.
Thank you very much!
Since there are still only three
of us, I'm delighted by your offer!
I'm sure we can learn a lot
from you upperclassmen!
Upperclassmen, upperclassmen,
upperclassmen...
Sure, I'll teach you.
For the future of the Komoi Corps...
Komoi Corps?
Y-You misheard me...
I meant K-Komoi and I-Ishida Corps...
Oh, like a project name?
"Komoi and Ishida Corps."
It sounds cool, doesn't it?
Y-Yeah!
Are you ready?
Yes, please go easy on me.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Costume Change, Alk!
Ambush Dragon Eradicator, Linchu!
Here I go!
You're gettin' a serious passionate
fight with me, the vice-captain!
Huh? Nobody's here...
I thought Naoki was already here...
Kourin said she might not be able to
come to school today, but Shingo too?
That was Naoki Ishida
who went to the middle
school division, wasn't it?
Isn't that Ishida guy kind of scary?
No kidding!
And I hear that Cardfight Club he's in
is frowned on by the Student Council!
Maybe it's a hangout for
juvenile delinquents...
H-How do you say "juvenile
delinquent" in English again?
M-Maybe "bad boy"...?
No good... I got nothing...
Misaki!
It looks like Naoki and Shingo are
at the middle school division.
I move my rear-guard Fundy to the Soul!
Eternal Idol, Pacifica gets +3000 power!
With a boost from Felucca... Eternal Idol,
Pacifica attacks Vowing Sword Dragon!
Dance, waves! Sparkle! The drop
of a soul that gives birth to life!
Glow with the seven colors of the rainbow!
Prism Splash!
I return my two rear-guard Celtics to my hand...
and call a new Bermuda Triangle from my deck!
PR❤ISM-Image, Rosa!
And then another ability of my Celtics!
When they return to my
hand, I do a Soulblast,
and Eternal Idol, Pacifica gets +8000 power!
That's a total of 31000 power!
Shining Prism Make-up!
I can't guard...
No guard!
I lost!
Me, the vice-captain of Miyaji Academy
High School Division's Cardfight Club...
I did it!
Mai, that was great!
I wish she'd been here to see it, too...
She's late. Even though she said
she'd be here today for sure...
What the heck, Ishida?
The vice-captain of the Cardfight Club,
and you lose to a middle-school student?
You're unfit to be vice-captain.
Unfit?!
I couldn't ask for a better turn of events!
If I win the next match...
Cardfight Club
The big shot is the one who wins!
You beat me, Master Komoi!
This way, the Cardfight Club will be mine!
I can't just go home like this!
Why are you so strong?!
Mai!
Cut it out! Ishida, what are you doing?!
Tell me!
I swore by this fist that
I'd get strong. So...
Aichi?
Boss Lady!
What are you doing to that little kid?!
We're not little kids!
We're middle school students now, so...
Th-That's right. My bad...
Okay, back to you!
Th-This isn't what you think!
She hit him with her fist...
Yeah. Yeah.
Oww! Let a guy finish talking, Boss Lady!
I just wanted to get her advice!
Oh...? It's still your fault for
making the wrong impression.
R-Right!
So let me rephrase that.
Please! Teach me how to fight!
I don't think I can teach you.
But we're always willing
to fight you... right?
Sure!
That's okay with me!
I'm lookin' forward to it!
Me too!
Give guidance to the Cardight Circle?
That's right.
These are the Cardfight
Circle's members, Emi and Mai.
We know each other...
So you formed the Cardfight Circle?
Yep, Aichi!
Emi, I note a certain lack of respect
in the way you address Sendou here.
Uh... okay...
Look! Th-This person is one of the champions
of the Vanguard Fight Asia Circuit,
Team Q4's Aichi Sendou!
He's someone who deserves a little more
respect than what you're giving him!
Well, after all, Aichi is Aichi...
Silence! I demand you give him more respect!
Uh, Shingo, the thing is...
Sendou, please leave this to me.
She needs to be told in no uncertain terms.
Uh... but... you know...
Emi, it seems you need to be
taught to respect your elders.
And I'll be the one to teach you.
I didn't do anything wrong!
Uh, come on, you two...
Stand up, Vanguard!
Prism Smile, Coro!
Deity Sealing Kid, Soh Koh!
Shingo is using a Narukami deck.
That guy switches decks a lot.
Everyone's got their own
preferred style of play.
Good luck, Emi!
I pretty ride PR❤ISM-Romance, Mercure!
Bermuda Triangle really is cute!
I know, right?
You're going to lose, Emi!
Caring about cute cards
proves you're a beginner.
There's no way I'm going to lose.
I ride Red River Dragoon!
Soh Koh moves!
Red River attacks!
I lovely ride PR❤ISM-Smile, Ligurian!
Ligurian attacks!
3 damage. Emi has turned it around! Wow!
Sendou, I'm going to win this for your honor!
What admiration, huh?
I ride Thunderstorm Dragoon!
Soh Koh boosts!
Thunderstorm, attack!
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks
with a boost from Red River!
I guard with PR❤ISM-Miracle, Canary!
3 to 3! Emi, get him all at once!
Twinkle! Sparkling splash!
I super-cute ride PR❤ISM-Image, Vert!
Call!
Vert's skill!
Since I have four or more
rear-guards, she gets +2000 power!
PR❤ISM-Image, Rosa attacks!
Rosa's skill!
When the Vanguard has a Limit Break ability,
she gets +3000 power!
I guard with Eradicator, Dragon Mage!
Vert attacks with a boost from Coro!
Drive trigger check!
Damage trigger check!
PR❤ISM-Romance, Lumiere attacks with
a boost from PR❤ISM-Image, Clear!
Lumiere's skill!
When the Vanguard has "PR❤ISM" in
its name, Lumiere gets +3000 power!
I guard with Worm Toxin Eradicator, Seiobo!
3 to 4...
If Emi can just hold out
after taking 1 damage...
Komoi can do 1 more damage...
It was a tie up until now...
Yep. I'm still hanging in there somehow...
You're better than I thought.
But it's time to close that loop.
Your military power rends the earth,
cleaves the sea, and shakes the sky!
I ride Martial Arts General, Daim!
Daim's skill!
Every time my turn comes
around, I can Soulcharge!
Then Daim gets +2000 power!
A Soulcharge every time it's your turn?!
That's right.
In other words, I'll eventually
be able to do a Megablast!
All I have to do is bide my time...
There's a deck with that skill?!
Emi...
I call Riot General, Gyras!
Gyras attacks Lumiere!
Rosa intercepts!
Daim attacks Vert with a boost from Soh Koh!
Drive trigger check!
Second check...
Critical trigger!
I add +5000 to the power of
Eradicator, Thunder Boom Dragon
and give the extra critical to Daim!
5 damage...
It looks like I don't even
have to wait for a Megablast.
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks with
a boost from Red River Dragoon!
I guard with Mermaid Idol, Elly!
Perfect guard...
Okay, that's fine.
I don't have to do anything, and
victory will come around to me.
That's right. Everything up to now
has just been a warm-up, so to speak.
Now it's going to get serious.
And you're going to apologize to Sendou!
What's wrong with the way I talk to Aichi?!
Emi, do your best!
Yeah. Mai, I'm not gonna lose!
Give rise to a cute storm! A young maiden's
twinkling! Sparkling! Heart-pounding!
Break ride!
PR❤ISM-Promise, Labrador!
I add +10000 to the power of
Labrador! And then I draw a card.
I return two rear-guards to my hand.
+10000 power... I can
still guard against that.
By returning Clear to hand, Clear's Soulblast!
I add +4000 to the power of Labrador!
I'm still okay...
On top of that, Coro's skill!
When a Bermuda Triangle
unit returns to the hand,
Coro can return to the hand, too!
A combination skill with two units...
Emi's doing well.
Yep.
Huh? Do you know her?
I call Sedna!
Labrador attacks with a boost from Sedna!
Cute!
Sweet!
Charming! Envelop the world with love!
Labrador's Limit Break!
Love Love Break!
When Labrador attacks the Vanguard,
I can call three rear-guards!
PR❤ISM-Promise, Celtic... Clear... Lumiere!
Then Labrador gets +10000
power and an extra critical!
A total of 43000 power and two criticals?!
I can't guard...
No guard!
But if I draw a heal trigger,
I'll still have a chance...
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give +5000 power to Lumiere and
the extra critical to Labrador!
Three criticals?!
But if I draw two heal triggers,
I'll still have a chance...
Damage trigger check!
Second check...
No... trigger...
I... I lost...
Cardfight Club
My Cardfight Club!
I won, Mai!
Yeah! Good thing you put together
a new deck with cute cards!
I lost to an opponent whose
priority is cuteness...
I'm sorry, Sendou...
Uh, you don't need to apologize...
That's two losses in a row for
the high school division, huh?
Sendou!
At this rate, the dignity of us
upperclassmen won't be maintained!
Please show them something
worthy of an upperclassman!
Are you telling me to fight, too?
Yes! Please!
Then it's settled! I'm going
to show you Sendou's power!
Be very afraid!
Sorry to make you wait.
Classy ladies are fashionably late.
Rekka?!
Too bad, but it looks like the formation
of the Komoi Corps has been pushed back.
Yes. You're right.
That Emi treats Sendou too casually,
but we should've been on guard
against her and her classmate, Mai.
Yeah.
Who's that munchkin with the rhythmic
gymnastic ribbon pigtails?!
You mean Rekka?
Next time: Idol Fight!
Idol ride, then idol attack?
But you won't beat my
idol, Sendou, with that!
Um... Shingo...