Permission denied.
Oh, no... Isn't there
anything that can be done?!
It is possible.
Fight against a powerful high school
team of my choice and achieve victory.
We'll do it. Please let us do it!
Ehhhh?!
We're fighting against Hitsue High,
where Kai and the others go?!
Do you have a problem with that?
N-No...
In short, if we beat this Vanguard Club,
you'll recognize us as
an official club, right?
Correct. Although if you lose,
you'll have to disband immediately.
Let's go, Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club!
T-Tentatively! This is our first match!
First Match! Miyaji
Academy vs. Hitsue High School!
Vanguard Club
U-Um, we've come from Miyaji Academy.
Welcome to Hitsue High's Vanguard Club!
Huh?! Mr. Mark? What are you doing here?
Job change!
And I'm also the faculty
advisor of this Vanguard Club.
You're the faculty advisor, Mr. Mark?
Yes! Advisor... or perhaps
you could say "instructor"...
Who is he?
H-He was my teacher in middle
school. A very mysterious man...
Oh, here they are!
Kai, Miwa, Izaki!
We're Hitsue High School's select team!
Just the three of you?
Kourin!
I've been waiting for you, my angel!
Safe...
That was too close.
What do you think? We've got a funky,
happy little club here, right?
R-Right...
Oh yeah, start with a proper greeting,
people. This is an away match.
Go ahead, Aichi.
Ah... um... right.
Um, we appreciate your club
accepting our invitation to...
Yeah, yeah. This bunch doesn't
need any stiff salutations, right?
That's Toshiki Kai, isn't it?!
So where are we gonna fight?
Shingo, Naoki, give a proper greeting.
Oh, Aichi! I hardly recognize you!
Oh...
Excellent!
Toshiki Kai, the fighter who was
in both Team Q4 and Team New AL4!
It's such a thrill to be able to meet you!
Kai, looks like you've got a fan.
Say something.
Nice to meet you.
He suddenly keeled over...
Hey, are you okay?
Shingo...
Kourin!
Hey! Everyone!
It's me.
The match with Hitsue High is about to start.
I'll call you back later
with news of their loss.
That's why I set up the match.
Be there at their finish and report it to me.
As vice president, that's your duty.
Please leave it to me.
It's almost too easy.
Whoa! We're gonna do it here?!
Shhhh! It's embarrassing if
you make a scene about it.
All right, Miyaji Academy
versus Hitsue High School.
Let this intramural Cardfight match begin!
I was hoping we'd be able to have an
intramural match like this sometime, but...
Aichi Sendou.
We know about your club's circumstances,
as well as your friendships here.
But, Hitsue team, there'll be
no holding back, you hear?
Of course!
Yeah!
Okay. Then, Miyaji Academy team...
Right. Holding back won't...
No, thank you!
Good!
If I go up against Kai by
the luck of the draw...
All right! I'm gettin' psyched up!
In our own way, we've been
working really hard, too!
If we win and Aichi's club folds...
Hitsue High School Division
What the heck?!
Miyaji is boring without
Morikawa or a Cardfight club!
I'm transferring to Hitsue!
Here I am! I wanted to see you, Morikawa!
Me too... Kourin!
And so begins a school love story!
I don't think you're on the right track,
but I can see you've got enthusiasm.
It'll be five against five,
with victory going to the
team that has the most wins.
Vanguard Club
Let's start the roulette!
The first match is between...
Stop!
From Miyaji Academy.... Naoki Ishida!
All right!
I've been amped up since we got here!
Hurry up and let me fight!
Naoki Ishida... The boy
that Aichi was mentoring...
...versus, from Hitsue High School...
Stop!
Toshiki Kai!
Kai and Naoki?!
It'll absolutely, positively, 100%
be over in a matter of moments!
What's that?!
What? It's not even worth discussing.
Look, Toshiki Kai is a solitary,
legendary-class fighter
who's roamed all over the world.
Even dandelions are afraid
to sprout in his wake.
There isn't even a remote chance you
could beat a fighter like that...
Shut up! Whether he's a great
fighter or not, I'm gonna win this!
Hey, where's the table... That's far!
No problem!
So what's with this glove?
You need it for this fight.
W-What the...?!
What is this?!
A Motion Figure System.
With it, the world you picture
will expand significantly!
Motion F-Figure System?
A know-nothing noob.
And he suddenly has to
take on Kai? Unlucky guy.
Turn down my first Vanguard...
Set down my deck... Draw five cards...
All right. Not a bad hand...
Stand up...
...the...
...Vanguard!
Wha...?!
"The," he says?!
Why, you...
You're...
...pretty cool.
But where are we?!
W-Wow...
This is the space between
the planet Cray and Earth.
The units battle on Cray as we fight here.
So that's what a Motion
Figure System is about!
That's right. It seems you're picturing it.
Then let's start.
Y-Yeah!
Ambush Dragon Eradicator, Linchu!
Eradicator, Strike-dagger Dragon!
Awesome! I don't even need to
picture it to see the unit over there!
Funny guy!
That's why he's a noob.
I think you were the same way
when you first started out.
What was that?!
Interesting...
I'm gonna give it my best shot!
Narukami versus Narukami...
Kai... Naoki...
Strike, Thunder Boom Dragon!
No guard.
Drive check!
Turn end!
You're just lucky that you drew a critical.
But Naoki's doing great! He
isn't afraid of Kai at all!
Ride!
Counterblast! Spark Rain retires.
Call.
Dragonic Deathscythe attacks
with a boost from Hisen!
Strike-dagger boosts! Spark Rain Dragon!
Kai is wasting effort, huh?
Oh, I wouldn't say that. To Kai,
no fights are a waste of effort.
He plays seriously, no matter
who the opponent is.
Are you shocked?
Is your first time seeing
images too strong for you?
Naoki...
A-Awesome! Dragonic Deathscythe
and Spark Rain Dragon!
I never imagined I'd get to
have a live showdown with 'em!
Too cool...
This fight is awesome!
I stand and draw!
All right, how about this one?!
Strike, my avatar!
I ride Eradicator, Vowing Sword Dragon!
One more of the same!
How 'bout that?!
Ride the Vanguard!
Hot-blooded, scarlet dragon...
Eradicator, Vowing Sword Dragon!
That's...
Amazing, huh, Shingo?
It sure is a spectacle!
Great!
Dragons really are impressive, y'know?
It's a grade 3 festival!
That's all?
This guy...
Even though we've got the same dragon,
he's cool every step of the way!
Call!
Supreme Army Eradicator,
Zuitan and Red River Dragoon!
Zuitan attacks with a boost from Red River!
I guard with Spy-eye!
Vowing Sword Dragon!
If the opponent has three or more damage,
Vowing Sword Dragon gets +2000 power!
No guard!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
5 damage...
Spark Rain Dragon attacks.
Naoki!
Guard!
He withstood it?!
Nice guts!
The fate of the Cardfight
Club is on the line here...
Like I'm gonna make myself
look bad by losin'?!
Naoki...
I stand and draw!
Watch this! Now it's my Break Time!
"Break Time"?
He's gonna take a break?
I told him that's wrong!
Maybe that guy belongs right over here...
What does that mean?
My heart is on fire!
It's screaming for me to
protect the Cardfight Club!
Watch this! My invincible...
surefire... miraculous...
...Break Ride!
Eradicator, Gauntlet Buster Dragon!
Vowing Sword Dragon's break ride skill...
When another Narukami rides, I can
retire one of your rear-guards!
Gauntlet Buster Dragon gets +10000 power!
And then... Limit Break!
One of your rear-guards
went into the Drop Zone,
so this gets +3000 power
and an extra critical!
And I'm not done yet!
On top of that, an Especial Counterblast?!
I choose one rear-guard unit and retire it.
One more time!
Power-up, critical, and
retiring rear-guards to boot?!
Give me that grade 3, too!
It isn't just the power of the cards.
That newbie is pretty good.
Naoki, to be able to get
that far against Kai...
What are you saying?
Compared to you and everyone else here,
he's got a long, long, long way to go.
Shingo, when I first started Vanguard,
I was so weak that I was
scared to have a match.
I don't believe it!
Sendou, you of all people...?
It's true.
Naoki is doing great!
I call Thunder Boom Dragon
and Red River Dragoon!
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks Zuitan!
Here I go! Gauntlet Buster
Dragon, Dynamite Counter!
Strike!
I guard with Pollux, Seiobo,
Yellow Gem, and Hisen!
Twin drive check!
First check...
I give the power to Gauntlet and
the extra critical to Vowing!
Second check!
Yes! He blocked it!
I'm still goin'! Vowing
Sword Dragon! Linchu boosts!
No guard.
That makes it 5 to 5!
I'm gonna break you in the next turn!
Well, he's in high spirits.
He's a real character.
I can see why Aichi mentored you.
You're a Vanguard fighter
with real potential.
But your deck isn't Narukami yet.
What?!
I'll show you a true Narukami!
I stand and draw!
Powerful, ancient dragon, trace the
ancestry of your form and strength
and swoop down to the Earth again!
Break Ride!
Eradicator, Dragonic Descendant!
Vowing Sword Dragon's Break Ride skill!
Uh oh!
I give +10000 power to Dragonic Descendant.
Especial Counterblast!
It gets +5000 power this turn.
Watch, Naoki Ishida. This
is the true Narukami!
Dragonic Descendant attacks
with a boost from Hisen!
And another +5000 power
with Hisen's Soulblast!
Perfect guard with Guld!
Twin drive, first check.
Second check.
Dragonic Descendant's Limit Break!
When its attack doesn't hit,
Descendant stands again!
Stand?!
And then on to even greater heights!
An extra critical!
This is... This is Narukami?!
Victory! Hitsue High School's Toshiki Kai!
Hey!
Will you... fight me again?
You know where to find me.
Yeah!
Sorry, Aichi. I lost.
That's okay. It was a good fight.
It was your first time with
a Motion Figure System,
and you didn't freeze up under his
attacks. That alone is impressive.
That guy is amazing.
Yep!
That's what I was trying to tell you!
What are you talking about?! This
is your first intramural match.
There are a lot more like
him all over the world.
Seriously?! Whoa!
Vanguard is awesome!
I'm even more fired up than before!
One loss to begin with...
Hitsue High School        Miyaji Academy
One win to start! Just two more, and
Kourin will transfer to my school!
What's he doing?
G-Good question...
And now, roulette! Our
second match is between...
Miyaji Academy
Kourin Tatsunagi
Miyaji Academy's Kourin Tatsunagi!
What?! Kourin?!
What is this?! What twist of fate?!
What mixed emotions!
I want to be with the one I love, but
I have to battle and defeat her?!
The gods are putting me to the test!
Hitsue High School
Yuuta Izaki
...and Yuuta Izaki of Hitsue High School!
Okay!
What?!
You're lucky, Morikawa. Now
you don't have to fight her.
You need 100 years more experience
before battling Kourin!
Let me do it, Izaki!
Which is it?! You are such a pain in the...
Okay, okay.
The great and powerful Morikawa
will get his chance later.
It's like in sumo and go, where the
grand champion always goes last.
O-Oh yeah?
Can we get on with this?!
Yuuta Izaki is on the way!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Kourin!
Toshiki Kai... I'll remember your name!
What are you babbling about?!
Even a baby can remember names!
Oh, shut up! At least
let me try to look cool!
Next time, I'm definitely gonna win!
So Hitsue High's next fighter is Izaki, huh?
But what I'm curious about is their
fighter that we haven't seen yet...
Next Time: The Ringer is
a Middle School Student!
The Ringer is a Middle School Student!
Ringer? Don't tell me...
That's...!
I get to see a fight like that here?!
Yep. This one's with Misaki.
A passionate fight is about to start!