Kai...
I didn't believe that you were
Reversed... but it's true, huh?
Kai!
Now that's the kind of look
I wanna see on your face, Aichi.
Miwa...
I'm gonna test you to see if you're
really good enough to fight Kai.
It's not just Kai... I have to
get Miwa back to normal, too.
Therefore... I have to fight.
Misaki?
I'm going to fight Miwa.
Huh?
Let me fight him.
But...
Aichi, your fight is with Kai.
Misaki...
Let's fight, Miwa.
Sorry, Tokura, but I'm not interested in you.
Are you afraid of losing to me again?
Ouch! You know how to hurt a guy.
All right, Tokura. A fight it is...
Ishida... By showing Aichi your fighting
form, you got him back on track.
And you brought the Reversed Kamui back
to normal with a desperate fight, Aichi.
So now...
It's my turn!
It's like the last time.
You representing Miyaji...
And you responsible for Hitsue.
Maybe the only thing that's different is that
now the fate of the world is on the line?
Stand up, Vanguard!
The Form of Friendship
Lizard Soldier, Conroe!
Battle Maiden, Amenohoakari!
A new first Vanguard!
Does this mean she's powered up even
more from her previous Genesis deck?
Misaki...
I ride Dragon Monk, Gojo!
Conroe moves back. And it's your turn.
Draw.
I ride Witch of Cats, Cumin!
Attack!
Next!
I ride Dragon Knight, Nehalem!
Call!
Attack!
I ride Battle Maiden, Sahohime!
Cider moves back.
I call Goddess of Trees, Jupiter!
3 to 2...
They were tied up to now.
Misaki...
Miwa... Your offhanded consideration...
You watched the store for me,
knowing I wanted to practice fighting.
And that's not all.
When I was troubled over
being on a losing streak...
No good... I can't win like this.
I can't drag Aichi and the others down.
What should I do?
Would you fight me?
Miwa...
Kai went off somewhere. I'm waiting
and waiting, but he's a no-show.
Help me kill some time?
Sorry. I'm really not fit to...
Okay! Here I go!
I'm telling you, right now is...
Look, fear is often worse
than the danger itself.
Too much discretion
becomes stupidity.
When I think too much,
I get a headache.
At a time like that, I try
to do some physical activity.
Give it a shot.
You were right.
I figured more things out through actual
fighting than just thinking about it.
You're late, Kai!
Sorry. We gotta stop here.
U-Um...
Thank you.
That's my line. Thanks
for hanging out with me.
You can always offhandedly pick
up on what somebody is feeling.
Indomitable emperor dragon,
with the unwavering fighting spirit
that resides in your fangs,
turn despair into light!
I ride Dauntless Drive Dragon!
Call! Berserk Dragon! Counterblast!
You're retired, Jupiter!
I call Seal Dragon, Kersey!
Conroe's Counterblast!
Conroe goes to the Drop Zone.
I add this guy to my hand.
Barri... A perfect guard.
Perfect guard...
It ain't all bad.
Now that she knows he's got one,
she can come up with a strategy.
You're actually smart.
You didn't have to say "actually"!
You're always offhanded about everything.
But just once, I've seen you serious.
It was during the local preliminaries...
Usually, you act like you're not
really interested, but the truth is,
you're passionate when
it comes to your friends.
In that fight, I saw how serious
you could be for their sakes.
But you're different now!
I haven't changed at all.
Kai chose Link Joker,
and now you guys are enemies.
I decided to become Kai's ally.
I'm helping him do what he wants to do.
That's what are friends are for.
As I suspected, you don't see it.
I'm going to take you down, Miwa!
Whoa! That's a scary look.
I stand and draw.
With the heavenly power
that resides within you,
seek out intelligence, courage, and justice,
then connect them with the future!
I ride Regalia of Wisdom, Angelica!
Call!
Grappa attacks!
Guard!
Angelica! Soulcharge.
On top of that, I Soulcharge
with Amenohoakari!
No guard.
Drive trigger check.
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Ordain,
and heal 1 damage point.
Rats!
Healing damage is a big deal here!
And it's 4 to 2 now! She can do this!
Don't you think so, Brother Aichi?
Ha!
If you think you can beat me playing
at this level, you're sorely mistaken.
I still have a trump card.
Stand and draw!
Cursed power! Fangs thirsting for madness!
Mete out despair deeper than any other!
Break ride!
Dauntless Dominate Dragon "Reverse"!
The break ride gives it +10000 power.
And it gains a skill!
I call Calamity Tower Wyvern!
Soulblast.
Draw!
And now the real game begins!
Ruler of darkness, return everything
to nothingness with your accursed roar!
Dauntless "Reverse's" Limit Break!
I Lock Calamity Tower!
On top of that, it gains a skill.
Two skills?!
Are you ready?
Dauntless "Reverse" attacks!
Drive trigger check!
Limit Break activated!
I can retire one of your
grade 1 or lower rear-guards!
Amenohoakari!
Dauntless "Reverse" gets +3000 power!
That ain't no ordinary retiring.
He just decreased the number of
Soulcharges she can do next turn.
What?!
This is the power of Miwa's Reverse deck...
Second check.
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects
to Dauntless "Reverse"!
Damage trigger check.
Plus, break ride skill activated!
By putting three cards from my hand into
the Drop Zone, Dauntless "Reverse" stands!
This is my trump card...
Death Spiral Darkness!
The spiral of death doesn't stop.
Dauntless "Reverse" attacks!
Misaki!
Five elements created
by the almighty goddess.
Your soul acts as a catalyst
for ultimate change!
Descend in all your radiance!
Shield Goddess, Aegis!
Quintet Wall!
Quintet Wall?!
Guarding alone, the total is 25000...
Wow...
And also...
...I guard with a shield!
I give the skill to my Vanguard!
Shoot. But whatever.
Drive trigger check.
Limit Break activated!
Cider, get lost!
Second check!
Critical trigger! I give
all the effects to Berserk!
Cider's skill activated!
When I move a unit from the
guardian circle to the Drop Zone,
I get to move it again to the Soul!
Her Soul increased to
seven cards all at once!
She charged up her Soul with a
lot of cards while defending!
That Quintet Wall combo is formidable!
Berserk attacks with a boost
from Seal Dragon, Kersey!
Guard! And intercept!
Rats. Then I've got no choice...
Dominate Drive attacks Ordain!
When it attacks, it gains +3000 power!
Guard!
Whoa!
She protected herself against that attack!
Well done!
Misaki...
Final Turn, huh...?
Your feelings for your friend haven't
changed. That's what you said, right?
Yeah!
You're wrong.
The way you are now, you're just following
your friend, because you're Reversed!
You didn't do it because you wanted to.
You did it to try to keep him from
going in the wrong direction.
That's what a true friend does, right?
Before being Reversed, you acted
as Kai's beneficial brakes.
That's the person I'm going to bring back!
After all... I'm your friend, too!
Stand and draw.
Goddess who appears in response to
the call of the regalia of wisdom!
Use your sword of intelligence and foresight
to cut through the tangled skein of fate!
Break ride!
Omniscience Regalia, Minerva!
I use three cards for the Soulblast,
and draw two cards.
On top of that, it gets +10000 power!
Ordain moves. I call Jupiter!
Watch the miracle of a goddess!
Ordain's skill.
I take one unit with "Regalia" in the name from my
Drop Zone, and move it to the bottom of my deck.
Then Minerva gets +5000 power!
Angelica!
And one more unit!
A combo with fellow Regalia units!
Minerva attacks!
Not so fast! Guard!
Intercept!
Drive trigger check.
All right! The attack doesn't go through!
After I'm done attacking, Minerva's
true worth comes into play.
What?!
Intelligence is stronger than the sword!
God of intelligence, gather here! Guide me!
Limit Break!
Minerva, stand! +5000 power!
Minerva attacks!
I won't let you get in
Kai's way! Perfect guard!
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give both the power and the
extra critical to Jupiter!
So a perfect guard here...
But Misaki took that into account.
Yeah.
Jupiter attacks with a boost from Ordain!
No guard!
If I lose, Kai will...
...be alone again!
I'll gamble everything on a trigger!
Damage trigger... check!
Second check...
Kai!
Miwa...
She did it! Boss Lady won!
Yeah!
She did it!
She made the most of Genesis's
special characteristics.
It's a deck that she obviously
put a lot of thought into.
It's not only Naoki. When I wasn't paying
attention, Misaki was preparing for this war.
Aichi...
You're not alone. We're here with you.
Miwa?!
I...
Misaki...
Aichi...
Miwa...
Kamui and... the guys from Miyaji...
Sorry, Kai.
It looks like I've left you alone.
Miwa!
I can walk on my own!
What is this... discouragement?
It just means you thought a little
too much about your friend.
You'll get better soon.
Thought too much... about my friend?
That's an embarrassing expression
if I've ever heard one...
So even while Reversed,
you thought about your friend...
Yeah. That's a man for you!
A man who's honorable and loyal!
Look, guys, I don't remember anything,
but don't try to snow job me with cheap praise!
Fight me, Kai!
Miwa... You know, you're really...
Save your breath. I know the rest.
Miwa...
I thought it right before I was Reversed...
That I had to be there for him.
So that's why!
Kai... Is it because of Ren and me?
Is that even possible?!
Kai, you were my goal and Ren's rival...
Next time: The Two Leaders!
The Two Leaders
But I'm going to do everything
in my power to stop Kai!
That's my duty!