Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
You're going at it, eh?
Hello, Mr. Nakamurabashi!
Hello.
The captain and vice-captain
are having a match?
That's interesting.
Look at that!
Which side is winning?
They're still just getting started,
so neither has the upper hand yet.
Is that right?
Mr. Nakamurabashi...
...why don't you learn a
little more about Vanguard?
I do apologize.
That aside, it's unusual for you
to put an appearance in here.
Oh, that's right. Actually,
this was delivered to the school.
High School Championship
Miyaji Academy, High School Division
Advisor: Mr. Nakamurabashi
Could this be...?
Indeed. An application to
Vanguard Fight High School Championship.
Um... The registered fighters are...
Aichi, me, Kourin, Boss Lady...
And while I'm at it, Komoi...
Why am I an afterthought?
Oh, shut up! I wrote your
name down, so don't complain!
...Writing?
Kourin Tatsunagi
Misaki Tokura
Shingo
Your handwriting is lousy.
Never mind!
It doesn't matter if my writing's a
little messy or I make mistakes...
The important thing here is enthusiasm!
As long as I do it with
passion, it'll get by!
The rest is up to you!
All right.
Well, it should be okay...
I'll send it out for you.
See you later.
All right!
VF High School Championship
at last! I'm fired up!
You're free to get fired up,
but be careful the flames
don't fry your brain.
Did you say something, Granny Glasses?
Couldn't you hear me?!
I guess your hearing is as bad as
your handwriting, Porcupine Head!
What's that?!
You have a problem?!
Come on, you two!
VF High School Championship
is a team competition,
so club members need to get along!
That's an order from the captain!
Hmph!
Good grief...
I'm worried about this club's future.
Reunion with the Wind
About Vanguard Fight High
School Championship!!
Okay, I'll explain about VF
High School Championship.
It's a tournament where more than 4,000
high schools from all over Japan participate.
4,000 schools?!
Yes. As Vanguard has spread,
participating schools have
increased year by year,
so that figure is a given.
I didn't know...
The first obstacle we have to surmount
is the regional tournament,
which is held for every bloc.
If we win the regional tournament, we'll
be able to participate in the finals.
Regional tournament first, huh?
Don't sound like such a wuss!
Regionals oughta be a piece of cake for us.
You're naive!
The bloc we're in, Kanto #3 Bloc,
includes top contenders for the
title, so it'll be a fierce battle!
Then... what?
You're sayin' we suddenly gotta
fight against schools
that got a good chance of bein' in
the finals at nationals?
That's right.
Strong schools like that are in our region?
Unfortunately...
That makes us hecka lucky!
When I fight, I wanna start
off by crushin' strong guys.
That's my surefire way to win!
Hey, Granny Glasses!
Where are those schools that
are supposed to be contenders?
According to my research,
one is two train stops away...
I mean, my name is Komoi!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
It's decided!
What's decided?
Reconnaissance, of course!
Reconnaissance.
Reconnaissance?
We'll gather as much info
as we can on our opponents.
That's my second surefire way to win!
Reconnaissance, eh?
Analyzing the strength of
the enemy is basic strategy.
I'm surprised to find myself in
agreement with Porcupine Head.
So... what's it called?
The school that dares to stand in our way...?
It's an elite private school by
the name of Fukuhara High School.
Fukuhara?
Kourin? Do you know it?
Well... You'll understand when we go there.
This is... Team Asteroid's headquarters?!
Sendou!
Fukuhara High is over here!
Oh! I was shocked for a second there...
But still, I never noticed a school
next to Team Asteroid's HQ...
I see. This is what Kourin meant when she
said I'd understand when we came here.
Well, the captain is here,
so let's start our recon.
W-What the...?!
Smart-alecks!
They must've figured we'd check 'em out
and made the first move!
There's no way.
So you need an ID card to
get into this school, huh?
Maybe we should just ask if we
can do an official observation...
Or if any of us know someone who goes here...
Well, if it isn't Aichi Sendou!
Tetsu!
Tetsu Shinjou!
What, you know him?
Tetsu Shinjou... You mean,
from Team Asteroid?!
What are you doing here?
That ought to be my line.
I see. Reconnaissance, huh?
Fine. Wait here a second.
You can come in.
Team Asteroid runs this school?
More properly, an educational corporation
affiliated with Team Asteroid runs this school.
I don't really get it, but we're talkin'
about somethin' on a huge scale, yeah?
Team Asteroid gathers fighters
from all over the country,
so a school is needed for them.
I myself was a student here until last year.
Until last year?
Then why are you here now?
I'm the coach of
Fukuhara High's Vanguard Club.
Then you're totally the enemy!
Jerk!
Figured you'd put us at ease
in order to fish for information!
You're too worked up.
As always, you've got
interesting friends, Sendou.
Boss Lady...
I have nothing in particular to hide.
Actually, my school's
Vanguard Club is scheduled
to have a friendly fight
with another school today.
You should stay and watch.
This is a school?!
I wouldn't be surprised if they
sold brand goods over there.
What I'd like to know is how far
this elevator is taking us...
Maybe it's the underground
base of a secret society...
But this is...
Yeah. We're using Team Asteroid HQ equipment.
You remember it, don't you, Sendou?
Uh... Yes...
That room!
I told them to wait until I got here...
These people have no patience.
Then that's the friendly match?
That's Asaka Narumi!
Who's she fighting?
Leon?!
Aichi Sendou...
Huh? There's a familiar face.
But what's he doing here?
Come to think of it, I'm pretty
sure he's not a student here...
Hey! When we're fighting,
could you stop looking away?
Pardon me. Let's continue.
Team Dreadnought and AL4!
This is one match we can't miss!
My turn. Stand and draw.
Be enthralled by the score that's playing!
I ride Starlight Melody Tamer, Farah!
Girl Who Crossed the Gap's Counterblast!
I superior call Mirror Demon!
Hear the melody preceding
a curtain's rise on the battle.
Farah's Persona Blast!
I superior call Midnight Bunny.
She gets +3000 power.
When Farah attacks now,
her power will be 21000...
Her rear-guards on either side
have plenty of power, too.
Does she mean to end it this turn?
Maybe.
That guy has 4 damage and
two cards in his hand.
It'll probably be tough
for him to weather it out.
First, Barking Cerberus
attacks Tear Knight, Lazarus!
No guard.
He's down one unit that can intercept!
Bunny boosts.
Farah attacks Blue Flight
Dragon, Trans-core Dragon!
No guard!
Twin drive!
Rainbow Magician, a draw trigger!
I give the power to Mirror Demon.
Damage check.
Stand trigger!
I stand Titan of the Beam Cannon Tower!
I give the power to Trans-core Dragon!
+5000 power...
However...
The attack that Bunny boosted was
successful, so her skill activates!
I put Bunny in the Soul
and do a Counterblast!
I superior call Purple Trapezist!
Cerberus moves to the Soul.
Superior call!
I get it!
By movin' it to the Soul once
and then doin' a superior call,
she can make it stand!
You're being unusually quick on the uptake.
Although you're just saying what you see...
What was that?!
Now I can attack with Cerberus one more time.
Worthy of a fighter who's
called "AL4's Assassin"...
This makes it worth coming
all the way to Japan.
I wonder how long that
confidence of yours can last...
Purple Trapezist boosts.
Cerberus attacks Trans-core Dragon!
I intercept with Titan!
Dark Metal Bicorn boosts.
Mirror Demon attacks.
Guard!
Turn end.
Wow...
She has total mastery
over the chain of attacks
that the Pale Moon deck specializes in.
But...
...Leon Souryu still
manages to deal with them.
But he hasn't escaped the danger yet.
What do you mean?
He only has one card in his hand
and no rear-guard units in the front row.
I don't know if he'll be able to
do 2 damage in the next turn...
I see... And if he can't,
with her next attack, that girl will...
Exactly.
But...
...I have the feeling that something
is going to happen this turn.
Stand and draw.
Level every hurdle to the ground!
Bring forth the glory of victory!
That is your mission!
I break ride Last Card, Revonn!
Revonn gets +10000 added to his power.
I call Light Signals Penguin Soldier
and Soulblast.
I draw one card.
I call Pyroxene Communications
Sea Otter Soldier.
Tear Knight, Theo moves,
and I Counterblast.
I add +2000 to the power of Revonn.
I use this skill four times!
29000 power!
I attack Mirror Demon!
Penguin Soldier attacks Cerberus
with a boost from Twin Strike Brave Shooter!
With that, she can't intercept anymore, huh?
But she still has five cards in her hand.
Even if she can't intercept,
just guarding alone here...
Revonn attacks Farah with a
boost from Sea Otter Soldier!
When he attacks a Vanguard,
his skill activates!
And due to the break ride's
effect, during this battle,
you can't guard with cards from your hand!
What?! That skill sounds like
it'd be against the rules!
Don't jump to conclusions.
That skill isn't set in stone yet.
The only thing you can do to avoid this
effect is throw away one card from your hand.
Of course I'm going to
put one in the drop zone.
I hope she doesn't think
Leon's attack ends here.
Me too!
What?!
After Revonn attacked, the three
units in the front row are at rest.
The conditions to activate it are met!
A champion always comes in at the end!
Accompanied by a trump card,
he destroys the limit!
Revonn's Limit Break!
+3000 and an extra critical!
With just one Counterblast,
he got not only power,
but an extra critical?!
Asaka has to guard against that attack
with only the cards in her hand.
Beat her, Leon!
Go!
I guard with two Candy
Clowns, Bunny, and Rainbow!
She used up her whole hand.
That makes a 41000 shield.
His power is 37000...
...so as long as he doesn't draw a trigger...
Fine.
Twin drive...
First check.
Second check...
Heal trigger.
I heal 1 damage
and give the power to Revonn!
Along with Sea Otter's 5000, that
makes the total power 42000!
Attack Farah, Revonn!
Dude...
I'm impressed.
No, the trigger made all the
difference. I was just lucky.
Besides, that deck...
You don't use it for fights
that count, do you?
That's for me to know...
You were wonderful, Leon!
You did it!
It's been a long time, Aichi Sendou.
Long time no see. You're as strong as ever.
You tell me that?
You helped me back then.
Not really...
What the heck? He not only knows the coach,
but this guy, too?
What are you talking about?!
You don't know about Dreadnought, the team
that had a heated battle with Team Q4
at the VF Circuit?!
Dread Note?
That's cool!
But I never heard of 'em.
For crying out loud! Read Monthly
Vanguard every once in a while!
What are you mad about?
But why are you in Japan?
Right now, we go to high school in Hong Kong.
A high school in Hong Kong?
That's right!
Like Singapore's SIT,
it's a school that's famous throughout
the world for its Vanguard studies.
I'm the Souryu child.
I have to devote myself
to my studies every day
in order to make the name
of Aqua Force famous.
However, I'm not misreading the wind anymore.
Great!
The high school sent us
here to Japan this time.
VF High School Championship
is a Japanese tournament,
but the world will be watching because
of the high level of fighters.
That's right!
And, starting this year, they're
letting a small number of people
from other countries participate.
Then...
Right.
We've come to participate in
VF High School Championship.
Sendou, that means there's a
possibility of us facing off.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too!
But why did you come to Fukuhara High?
I invited them.
I thought it would be a good idea for them to
get used to Japan before the tournament began.
But you really invited us so
you could observe us, right?
Right?
Well, you got me.
Not that we mind. We don't
need to hide anything.
Anyway, it's my turn, right?
Who will fight me?
Sorry, but I'd like to see
what Miyaji Academy can do.
What about my fight?!
Jillian is hot under the collar!
What are you being so lighthearted about?!
You don't get to fight either!
No worries.
There's plenty of time. You can
fight as much as you like later on.
Yeah, but...
All right, who should we have fight?
I'll do it!
It ain't fair if we're the ones
doin' all the reconnaissancin'!
I'll show ya the power of Miyaji
Academy's secret weapon!
Secret weapon?
Well, aren't you the fearless one?
What's your name?
Naoki Ishida.
I'm the man that's gonna be in the spotlight
at the High School Championship!
Fine.
So, your opponent will be...
Let's see...
Tatsunagi! How about you?
Tatsunagi...
I'll do it. Good timing, I was
just starting to get bored.
S-Suiko?!
What?!
You know another one?!
She's a member of Ultra-rare, too!
I never thought the day would come
when I'd get to meet all three!
What's Suiko doing here?
The same as Rekka and me.
Takuto has her going to school here.
Then you knew about Fukuhara
High, Kourin, because...
Right. Because Suiko goes here.
It looks like you're having
a good time, Kourin.
How's that?
Being together with Aichi...
Wh-What are you talking about?!
I had no choice. This is what Takuto decided.
Shoot! I wish I got to be with Aichi, too!
Yes?
You...
...do not belong in a sailor uniform!
Oh, you're a funny kid.
Really, too funny...
I feel like making you my pet!
Both of you are ready?
Yeah.
I'm ready whenever.
Then go ahead.
Stand up, Vanguard!
This Suiko woman is totally strong!
I'm not too sure about that sailor
uniform, but she's got the stuff!
How stupid are you, Ishida?!
Can't you just keep your
mouth shut and fight?!
But this is the perfect opportunity
to see Suiko's ability.
This is a great chance!
Next time: Powerful Fighter at Fukuhara High!
Angel Feather has tricky moves.
How are you going to confront it, Naoki?
This sailor suit is strong!
She's really pushing it, though...
You're still saying that?!