That's why, even if I put
my life on the line...
...I will save you!
You're strong, Aichi.
But this is my...
Kourin!
Thank you for your trouble, Kourin.
You bought me the time I needed.
There's still something that I have to do.
Reinforcements are coming.
You guys are still hurt
from your previous fights.
Aichi, get back.
Misaki?
I'm the only one here who
can still put up a fight.
You can't do it alone.
Let me fight, too!
Me, too.
But... you two are in no condition to...
The time limit is drawing near.
Even as we speak,
Link Joker is swallowing up
the world moment by moment.
There's no choice but to fight.
But, Aichi... you...
Do you like my present?
Takuto!
No. He's Takuto and yet not Takuto.
He's an evil being who stole
everything away from Takuto.
That's right. I'm the ruler
of everything, Link Joker.
If I don't defeat him,
the world won't return to normal.
Fight me!
Yes, certainly.
Is that what you thought I'd say?
Even though all I have to do
for this world to become mine
is wait for time to keep on passing?
If you want to battle me,
you'll have to win against
those Reversed fighters first.
Although in your condition,
you'll lose a fight and wind
up being Reversed yourselves.
We'll take those fights.
Tetsu!
Asaka!
Kyou the Great also came to pitch in!
Stand up...
...the...
...Vanguard!
It looks like we made it in time.
Ren's Wish
Ren!
Ren, leave this to us!
Ren, stay safe!
I'm counting on you, Tetsu and Asaka.
I'm here, too!
Take that!
Well, I'll bring this whole thing to an end.
Me, too!
No, Aichi!
You're in no shape to...
I want to protect you!
You, Kourin, Naoki, Shingo, everyone...
Aichi...
I'm not going there to lose, but to win.
I'm going to take back everyone's futures!
Make sure you come back. Promise me.
I promise.
Please take care of Kourin.
You promised, Aichi.
No one's even getting close to Ren!
That's right. I won't let anyone near Ren!
Your opponent is the all-powerful
Kyou the Great! Be grateful!
Aichi...
I... want to go, too.
Right now, we're not the only ones
battling against Reversed fighters.
Vanguard fighters all over
the world are fighting.
They have faith that we'll beat Takuto.
For the sake of everyone's feelings,
we can't afford to lose!
Everything is now ready
for me to seize the world.
This is the top floor, isn't it?
I see. We're supposed to go even higher.
Whoa...
Link is near.
Things certainly are getting
serious, aren't they?
Look at that, Aichi.
It's so beautiful!
Ren...
The Takuto you know no longer exists.
Takuto, the very symbol of the planet Cray...
His memories, abilities...
everything is now mine.
I see.
So the Reversed fighters back there were
to buy you time to meld with Takuto.
What?!
I've fused with Takuto and
advanced to a new stage.
Do you know understand what this means?
This evil vibe...
Don't tell me...
It means you've gotten even stronger?
That's correct.
Earth and Cray are about to be
reborn thanks to Link Joker.
Right now, that energy is flowing into me.
No one can defeat me.
Just as Takuto has been
stained by my color,
Earth and Cray will be
tainted with Link Joker!
Soon, the gate will open and
everything will come to an end.
I've heard enough prattling.
Let's get started.
Fine. But your opponent is him.
Kai!
Kai! This time for sure,
I'll bring you back...
Kai...
Ren.
Kai.
I'm going to beat you!
It took a little time to track
you down, but I finally arrived.
Just as you want to fight me,
I want to fight you, Kai.
Kai...
Ren...
Well, Aichi Sendou, let's
be spectators for this one.
We don't want to interfere with their fight.
Toshiki Kai.
Show me the Link Joker power
I gave you. Don't hold back!
Kai...
Ren...
Stand up the Vanguard!
Judge Bow Revenger.
Red Pulse Dracokid.
Kagero?
His deck has changed?
I see. Kagero?
This should be even more fun.
Flighty as I am, I actually did
my homework on Link Joker decks.
And yet you've betrayed my
expectations, in a good way.
I finally get to fight you.
I'm sure you understand.
In fact, you're the only one who
can understand this feeling.
In that one fight, you
gave everything you had
to open my eyes when I was
in the grip of darkness.
When I clashed head-on with the
fiercest fighter, Toshiki Kai,
sparks flew, and it's never
happened before or since.
I want to seriously fight and
defeat you one more time.
That's what I've been thinking all this time.
I ride...
Transient Revenger, Masquerade!
Dragon Monk, Gojo!
Call.
Attack!
Next!
Turn end.
I ride...
Blaster Dark Revenger!
Does he sense that I've come
prepared for this fight?
Call.
Blaster Dark's skill activated!
Dorint's skill.
With Dorint's combo,
he retired one rear-guard.
Attack!
Ride!
Turn end.
3 to 1...
That's Toshiki Kai for you.
He's off to a splendid start.
That's right. I've been waiting
anxiously for this fight.
Beginning with Tetsu, fighters all
over the world have been Reversed.
After fighting them, I confirmed it.
This was your doing.
Finding out that you were
getting stronger and stronger
made me want to
fight you all the more.
I'm going to beat you.
There will be no greater pleasure in this world!
Ren?
Join my great ambition with
your blade and create a path!
I ride...
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Call!
Nullity, Masquerade attacks Burning Horn!
Guard!
Judge Bow boosts Mordred!
Phantasmal sword that doesn't
even realize it's been shattered!
Return to nothingness while
you're still half asleep!
Turn end.
Well, Kai, show me your power.
The ultimate power that will make
me fall down to my knees in fear...
I ride the Vanguard!
The apocalyptic flames that reduce
everything in this world to ashes!
Dragonic Overlord!
Overlord...
That's the name that says,
"This is Toshiki Kai."
The unit of his soul!
Switching to the new Overlord was done
to aim for even greater strength.
Red Pulse's skill!
I look at the top five cards in my deck
and move one grade 3 unit to my hand.
Call!
Soulblast.
I call Nehalem...
...and Eternal Bringer Griffin.
Overlord attacks!
No guard.
Check the drive trigger.
I got a draw trigger.
I give the power to Nehalem and draw.
I got a critical trigger.
I attack Nullity, Masquerade!
Intercept.
Nehalem attacks!
Guard!
Turn end.
4 to 2.
Kai is steadily increasing the damage.
I gave him the power of Link Joker.
It's an inevitable development.
This is getting fun, Kai.
The fate of the world rides on this,
but to be honest, I don't care.
I'm only interested in winning against you.
You, who's stronger than anyone...
You, who were once closer
to me than anyone...
You, who I once admired...
You, the strongest of all,
who I'm going to beat here.
Nothing excites me more than
a fight against you!
Fighting you is the greatest
pleasure in my life!
And that's exactly why
I'm going to defeat you.
That's right.
Against the supreme Kai in a fight
that will nearly shorten my life...
This feeling...
It's just like when Ren was
under Psyqualia's spell!
I like that expression.
The mad desire that was lying
dormant in his heart...
It's not for nothing that he was
one of the three chosen candidates
to serve under Link Joker.
Three?
Toshiki Kai...
Ren Suzugamori...
...and Aichi Sendou.
Are you okay? Leave this to us.
My apologies.
You needn't worry.
Ren will get everything under control.
Shoot! Is that jerk Ren making
a play for all the glory?!
Ren... I just hope he doesn't
get into a playful mood.
Well, here I go, Kai.
I'm going to make you kneel
down before me again.
Swoop down from beyond illusion,
cruel blade!
Transient dreams!
Break ride!
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Superior call!
Dorint's skill.
I flip over one card...
...and then do a Counterblast.
Blaster Dark!
I retire Burning Horn!
Attack! Mordred!
Check the drive trigger!
I got a heal trigger.
I give the power to Nullity, Masquerade...
...and heal 1 damage point.
Attack!
Dorint boosts Nullity, Masquerade!
3 to 4!
Ren has turned it around!
Enjoy it while you can.
You're about to learn the
true terror of Link Joker.
Kai, show me your ultimate power.
But I'll show you that I'm even higher.
In that case, I'll meet your expectations.
But when you see my power,
Ren, it'll be the end of you!
What a fight!
I like this kind of fight.
Don't you, Kai?
Yes.
You do possess true strength.
Now, take all of that power
and throw it at me!
Under these circumstances,
they're having fun?!
Just how far will they go?!
Next time: Resurrection of the Dragon!
Resurrection of the Dragon!
Okay, here I come with my strongest unit.
That's fine. I'll meet it with...
...my reborn true form!