Those kids are acting kind of strange. And...
...the same goes for you, Koutei.
Naturally. I've been Reversed.
"Reversed"? What is that?
It means the mighty Link Joker
gave me this glow.
"Link Joker"? What are you
talking about, Koutei?
Those who lose are Reversed.
Yuri, I want you to serve me!
This is wrong. That isn't
the Mitsusada I know.
Mitsusada wouldn't even say
such things as a joke.
What... What's happening?
Come, Yuri. Fight me.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
If you fight, you'll understand
everything. Everything...
Fine. So I just have to win, right?
That's right. If you can win...
Confirm my new justice with your own eyes.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Yuri's Medal
Enigman Flow!
Dimensional Robo, Daimagnum.
His deck hasn't really changed.
That's right.
Dimension Police is your justice.
I go first. Draw!
I ride Enigman Ripple!
With its skill, I put
Enigman Wave in my hand.
I ride...
Dimensional Robo, Dailander!
Daimagnum moves back.
Call.
Attack!
Critical trigger.
Turn end.
I ride Enigman Wave!
Call.
Attack!
Guard.
I ride...
Dimensional Robo, Daifighter!
Call.
Attack!
He fights the same way as the normal Koutei.
I ride Original Savior, Zero!
Call.
Attack!
Turn end.
You've gotten stronger, Mitsusada.
When we first met, I never could've
imagined you'd become this strong.
At the time, my sights were set on winning
the Vanguard National Championship.
I was looking for a second teammate.
We just can't seem to find our third person.
You're so strong, practically
anyone would do, Sis.
Wrong!
Whoever joins our team
needs to bring a certain level of ability
to the table, or we'll be in trouble.
A "certain level"?
Enough to beat me!
Excuse me...
That's when we first met, Mitsusada.
Would you like to fight?
You stepped up and asked for a fight,
which made me wonder how strong you were.
But you were actually exasperatingly weak.
Look, if you have your
Vanguard do the third attack,
you won't be able to use
Commander Laurel's skill.
Ah! I see.
Please fight me one more time.
I feel sorry for him.
Make sure to show him how much
stronger you are, so he'll give up.
R-Right...
My Vanguard attacks!
No guard.
Thanks to Commander Laurel's
skill, my Vanguard stands!
From before!
It looks like you were quick
to take my sister's advice,
but I guard. Too bad.
And that's the game, huh?
You came back the next day, Mitsusada.
Of course, you were extremely
weak, like on the previous day.
But... you weren't exactly the same.
You didn't make the same mistakes
you had the previous day.
That was the clincher.
I've decided! Kenji Mitsusada,
you're our third member!
Sis?
I'm serious.
After all, he sucks!
I'll make him stronger.
But...
You have a problem with that?!
No! Not at all!
Good!
But if I decide it's not working
out, you're off the team.
I'll do my best! I'm looking forward it!
You weren't the type to improve by
leaps and bounds in a short time.
But you kept moving forward one
step at a time, slowly but surely.
You were a master of putting in effort.
Why don't you try using other clans too?
I don't think so.
I want to investigate it thoroughly.
My justice, that is.
Justice?
I learned about this from
my favorite topic, history.
The people who make their marks
in history have all fought for justice.
I figure they must have known about
Dimension Police, which is all about justice.
I want to thoroughly
explore my own justice!
With this Dimension Police.
Then, one day, I'll win the
Vanguard National Championship
and make my own mark on
history, just like they did!
I've just decided! I'm going
to switch to Dimension Police!
Th-That way, you can watch my fights
a-and... you know... study them.
Before we knew it, Mitsusada
was beating Gai and even me.
Then, as our team leader, he pulled us along
until we even accomplished our goal of
winning the Vanguard National Championship.
Yuri... What's this?
A medal... for the emperor.
A medal... The emperor is supposed
to give medals out, not accept them!
I can't accept it. I know how
much it means to you, Yuri...
That's why I'm giving it to you!
L-Look, consider it a reward
for making your mark on history
by winning the Vanguard National Championship!
So... So...
Thank you. I'll take good care of it.
I can never be grateful enough to you
for training hard to the
point of changing your deck.
I really appreciate it.
I was elated by Mitsusada's
success as if it were my own.
It was the first time I realized how joyful
it was to help someone achieve their goal.
He's gotten stronger and
continues to try hard even now.
That's what I respect about you,
from the bottom of my heart.
Draw!
I ride Super Dimensional Robo, Daiyusha!
Call! Dailander's Counterblast!
Attack!
With its skill, it gets an extra critical!
Perfect guard!
Trigger check.
Heal trigger.
I give the power to Daidragon,
and heal 1 damage point.
Second check.
This is my new justice.
You would do well to remember this name.
Dark Dimensional Robo "Reverse," Daiyusha!
"Reverse"... Daiyusha?
Dark Dimensional Robo "Reverse," Daiyusha.
Don't tell me you took
Great Daiyusha out of...?
It's only natural to replace one unit with
another one that's more powerful, isn't it?
What are you saying?!
Great Daiyusha even beat Ren Suzugamori!
I could say that unit is you!
It has special meaning!
It's a symbol of winning through hard work!
Hard work? What nonsense.
What?!
Hard work is meaningless.
At least when compared to a unit
that possesses superior abilities.
You should look back on history.
Power is justice.
Justice belongs to the ruler who holds power.
That's an emperor? You're
saying that's who you are?
Right now, you're not the
emperor that I admire!
I'm going to win!
I'm going to win and wake you up!
I'm looking forward to the next turn.
I won't let you ride a unit like that!
I'm going to win the match this turn!
There it is!
As long as I have this unit...
Even though he's only got
2 damage, I can beat him!
All of the beginning, all of the end!
Take the power of your mother galaxy and...
...break ride!
Enigman Storm!
When Enigman Storm break rides,
it gains +10000 power!
And Daiyusha loses 5000 power!
Daisy moves.
And then I call. Counterblast!
Enigman Storm gets +4000 power.
25000 versus 5000. That's
a difference of 20000.
That's not all!
Enigman Storm attacks
with a boost from Daisy!
Critical 2. I can afford a "no guard" here.
That confidence will be your undoing!
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Enigman Storm!
Draw trigger.
I give the power to Daiyusha.
Draw.
When the Vanguard's attack hits,
Commander Laurel's skill is activated!
I rest four rear-guards,
and stand my Vanguard!
That skill...
It was the first piece of advice you gave me.
He remembers...
That's right.
Look, if you have your
Vanguard do the third attack,
you won't be able to use
Commander Laurel's skill.
Never should have told me that.
If you hadn't done that...
What are you saying?
If you hadn't done that, I wouldn't
have wasted all that time and effort.
That's right. In the face of absolute
power, effort means nothing.
I now understand that fully.
It's not true!
Your effort...
Your effort shone brilliantly!
At least it shone brilliantly to me!
Guard.
I'm not done yet!
Drive trigger check!
You couldn't reach me, huh?
When you naively relied on trying to
draw two triggers in a row to beat me.
You never had a chance.
Yuri, kneel down before me!
Noble soul reborn from the
black dark matter of darkness!
Tremble with the pleasure of destruction!
Crossride!
What?!
Dark Dimensional Robo "Reverse," Daiyusha!
Turn Dimensional Robo, Daiyusha's
light into darkness.
My subjects, Dailander, Daimagnum.
Sacrifice yourselves to end this just war!
Lock!
Lock?!
Enigman Storm loses 10000 power!
I just have 1000 power now?!
This is the Limit Break
of "Reverse" Daiyusha.
Tyrannus Gravity.
Now you understand, don't you?
Effort means nothing in
the face of this power.
Denying effort means denying yourself!
I can't afford to lose against
you the way you are now!
You don't give up, even after being
stripped of all but 1000 power?
Then you can learn the hard way!
Effort prostrates itself before power!
"Reverse" Daiyusha attacks!
No guard!
Drive trigger check.
Draw trigger.
I give the power to Daidragon.
And then I draw!
Thunder Arrow!
My powered-up Daidragon is going to attack.
With its skill, it gets +3000 power.
I won't lose!
Guard!
Then I attack once more with Daidragon.
Guard! And intercept!
Turn end.
I protected myself.
Impressive as ever, Yuri.
But you don't have many
units or cards in your hand.
You don't even have a break
ride in the next turn.
Your attacks won't reach "Reverse" Daiyusha.
Slim chance indeed!
But it's not zero!
If there's even a remote possibility,
I'm not going to give up!
Not on getting you back!
Call!
Justice Cobalt!
Remember all of your hard work!
Remember your justice!
Perfect guard!
Come back! Come back to the real you!
Guard.
Mitsusada!
Daidragon is going to guard too.
No... Mitsusada...
It's like I keep telling you.
Effort is meaningless.
Absolute power is what's necessary!
Now, I'll show you.
This is power.
This is justice!
Limit Break!
Lock!
Attack.
Drive trigger...
Though I really don't even need to check...
Thunder Arrow!
I won't give up. Not as
long as there's a chance!
No trigger. I win.
Mitsusada...
Mitsu...sada...
Well, Yuri... Let's paint the
world in darkness together.
Yes. As you command, Your Imperial Majesty.
Your Imperial Majesty, I've found the
next opponent that should be beaten.
It's Leon Souryu, the man who plays a large
role in the legend of the Souryu Tribe.
So my opponent is Aqua Force, which
preaches absolute justice. What fun!
I had no idea that a Reversed
Daiyusha would be this terrifying!
Next time: Dark Dimensional
Combination! Reversed Daiyusha!
Dark Dimensional Combination!
Reversed Daiyusha!
No one can stop the advance of my army.
Not even if they're a legend!