I won't lose... I won't lose!
I won't lose!!
Here I go! Wake up, friendship!
Special friend fire crush!
Why?! Why is my Angel Feather...
Huh? Emi? Mai?
What am I doing here?
Rekka!
Thank goodness!
Thank you so much for today!
That's right! I have to tell
Brother what happened today!
Kourin?
Boy, we had a heck of a time with Rekka
in the middle school division just before!
Kourin?
I'm done hesitating.
Don't tell me... you're Reversed?!
It looks like I gotta fight one more time.
Sendou?
What's wrong? You look pale.
Yeah. I just had a bad dream...
Why did I have that kind of dream?
You have a message from Takuto.
He said, "I'm satisfied with
the results this time."
Countdown to Despair
Huh... you sure brought me
to an interesting joint.
Now, who the heck are you?
I know the deal with Reverse.
If I win, Kourin goes back to normal.
That's what I'm gonna win this fight for!
I'm going to win.
And you're going to be Reversed.
It's not gonna be that easy for you!
In fact, no way am I gettin' Reversed!
I got Gouki and Rekka back to normal.
Now I'm gonna do the same thing for Kourin!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Beast Deity, Riot Horn!
Desire Jewel Knight, Heloise!
I ride Beast Deity, Blank Marsh!
Riot Horn moves back!
I ride Jewel Knight, Prizmy!
I call Shellie!
Prizmy attacks!
Damned Leo attacks!
Tracie attacks!
Well, I think it's about time
to get down to the get-down!
This is the rumored beast god!
Innumerable opponents have been squashed
by its absolutely invincible fists!
The newest! The greatest! The zenith!
The great Kamui rides Strongest Beast
Deity, Ethics Buster Extreme!
Call! Extreme!
Hatred Chaos! Attack!
Ethics Buster Extreme!
The Hatred that I stood with
the trigger! Once more!
Turn end.
Just 1 more damage, and
I can undo Kourin's Reverse!
My new ace card...
Become a blade that decides fate!
I couldn't use this against Aichi.
Against Brother?
I see!
Rekka was conflicted about
Reversing Miss Emi and Miss Mai.
You must be the same way!
Wrong.
I threw away my indecision.
Say what?!
Use your black wings
to smother all light...
Evil darkness!
I ride...
Broken Heart Jewel Knight,
Ashlei "Reverse"!
I'm going to defeat you
with this unit... and then...
...then I'll beat Aichi Sendou!
Do you really mean that?
That's my destiny.
What the heck is that?!
Brother is your friend, isn't he?!
Are you seriously sayin' you got no
qualms about Reversing your friend?!
Call.
I'm just following my destiny.
Kourin!
Limit Break!
Lock!
I order you, by this jeweled sword!
Hatred Chaos, exit the battlefield!
Next, by this jeweled sword,
I summon a new knight!
Superior call!
It weakens the enemy's strength
while at the same time summoning
comrades to the battlefield.
That's Ashlei "Reverse's"
Jewel Sword Noir!
Kourin...
Here I go, Kamui Katsuragi!
Tracie attacks!
Guard!
Ashlei "Reverse," attack!
No guard!
Twin drive check!
Second check.
Draw trigger!
I give the power to Tilda!
And then I draw!
You're defying destiny.
Have you heard these words before?
"She who follows her destiny rides the tide,
while she who opposes it...
is dragged under."
In the end, you will be dragged under,
and you will lose to me.
Stand against me, and your
agony will only linger.
Tilda!
I don't like this. I don't
like you the way you are now!
No matter what, I'm gonna bring
you to your senses! I swear it!
Resistance is futile.
We're definitely going to make you ours.
What's that?!
I'm sure you don't know this yet,
but something unbelievably
huge is about to begin.
Something huge?
And I want strong fighters like
you for it, Kamui Katsuragi.
What the heck are you talkin' about?!
We're finally movin' again!
For a while there, I didn't know
what was going to happen, you know?
Sendou?
Aichi?
Long time no see.
Yeah.
It has been a while, hasn't it?
You wanted something?
There's this rumor on the Net
about an increasing number
of weird Cardfights happening
here and there around the world.
One day, suddenly, someone's personality
changes, and they're way stronger than before...
And they try to increase the
number of people like them.
This all started around
the time you disappeared.
What a joke!
But it all fits.
Kai. Say something. Tell me I'm wrong.
If I'm one of them, what of it?
I didn't wanna believe it.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you have anything to do with this?!
"Somethin' huge," "destiny"...
I don't know what you
people are goin' on about.
Jeez! What a pain!
The main point is I gotta win, right?!
Draw!
Call!
And I call them too!
Go, Hatred Chaos!
Guard.
Ethics Buster!
Jewel Knight, Hirumi!
Ethics Buster Extreme, attack!
Guard. And intercept.
The attack isn't goin' through... But...
Twin drive check.
Limit Break! Rise, Max Beat!
On top of that, Max Beat's skill!
Hatred Chaos, stand!
Then second check!
Ethics Buster, stand!
And I give it the power!
And finally, Riot Horn!
It stands with its skill!
My Extreme attack didn't go through,
but I can attack two more times!
This is my World Ultra
Mega-Ultra-Super-Destruction!
Just 1 more damage!
Then you'll turn back to normal!
I can't let Brother meet you like this!
Hatred Chaos! Attack again!
Guard!
Intercept!
She's got just one card in her hand.
Even a perfect guard won't save her,
and no way can she mount a decent defense!
This is gonna end it! Ethics Buster!
Attack Ashlei "Reverse"!
Summoning Jewel Knight, Gloria! Quintet Wall!
Counterblast.
I guard with the top five cards of my deck.
What?!
That's right. This is Quintet Wall.
It looks like you underestimated me just
because I had only one card in my hand.
What?!
I told you before, Kamui Katsuragi.
It's useless to oppose destiny.
You're definitely not going to beat me.
Almost there. Our old school...
Miyaji Academy, high school division...
It feels like we haven't been there in ages.
Think!
What should I do to deal with
that Ashlei "Reverse's" skill?
Aichi!
I... I...
Limit Break!
Superior call!
Sybill's skill!
Ashlei "Reverse"...
Attack Ethics Buster Extreme!
Twin drive check.
Second check.
Critical trigger.
I give the power to Sybill and the
extra critical to Ashlei "Reverse."
Sendou!
Aichi?
Kamui?
K-Kamui!
B-Brother...
S-Sorry...
I... wasn't strong enough...
What is this?!
Kourin?
I Reversed him.
The gang's all here.
That girl...
She's the secretary of
the Student Council, right?
This is perfect timing.
Right when it's about to begin.
What's about to begin?!
Something unbelievably huge!
What the?!
Talk to me, Kai. What did you do exactly?
Hello, Cardfighters all over the world.
Takuto Tatsunagi?
I trust you're all enjoying yourselves
as you strive to win a fight today?
It pleases me immensely.
Friends and comrades and frenemies...
Growing as fighters...
I know how fulfilling that can be.
And yet, nothing lasts forever.
No matter how fun your days are,
they'll come to an end eventually.
And that day is right before you.
This may seem sudden, but your world...
...is going to be destroyed.
Kourin... Kamui...
Cardfighters everywhere...
the day of destruction is at hand.
Takuto... What are you saying?
Kamui, does this have
anything to do with
the end of the world that
Takuto's talking about?
In keeping with what I'm about to
explain, please prepare for the end.
Next time: Chaotic Destroyer!
Chaotic Destroyer!
We're shuddering in fear at the coming of
the terrifying world he's talking about.
Aichi Sendou...
Are you strong?