And now, tomorrow's weather...
Hello, Cardfighters all over the world.
I trust you're all enjoying yourselves
as you strive to win a fight today?
It pleases me immensely.
What is this?
What the heck is he talkin' about?
And yet, nothing lasts forever.
No matter how fun your days are,
they'll come to an end eventually.
And that day is right before you.
This may seem sudden, but your world...
...is going to be destroyed.
Kamui!
This is unavoidable.
Link Joker holds sway over the world.
Link Joker?
Link Joker...
A destroyer possessing ultimate power
who has crossed hundreds of millions
of planets and dimensions to get here.
Kourin, what are you saying?
Cardfighters...
I'm sure some of you are aware of
the phenomenon known as "Reverse."
Link Joker is the very one
controlling that phenomenon.
When a Cardfighter loses
to a Reversed fighter,
he becomes Reversed too.
If he's Reversed, his personality
changes, and he becomes very strong...
...but what really happens is that he
becomes a soldier in our Link Joker army.
Is that what happened to...
Darn it! My memory is foggy,
but... I think I might've been...
With an increase in their numbers,
we have become more powerful than ever.
Take a look at this.
This is a gate.
Chaotic Destroyer
If you look up in the sky, you'll see them,
here and there all over the world.
Kamui!
Emi! Gouki!
That's... Takuto?!
Even now, the number of Reversed
fighters is increasing.
The gates will open wider the
more Reversed fighters there are.
And when they eventually cover the Earth...
...this planet will smothered in the
darkness of nothingness in the blink of an eye.
All life will fall into darkness.
No...
What the heck is this?!
What's he talking about?
So Ultra-rare's concert sold out in advance!
Good thing we already got our tickets!
Thank you for buying all our tickets!
I know, right?
What's this?
Don't tell me... we're seeing
something different than they are?
This has all become possible
because of you Earth fighters.
Thank you very much!
By way of gratitude, I'm only telling
you fighters about this today.
I hope you all spend the scant remainder
of your peaceful days in despair.
For a world ruled by Link Joker,
despair is a perfect fit.
What a bunch of hooey!
I never thought you'd be mixed
up in something like that.
So what do you intend to do, Miwa?
If we fight and I win, you'll wake up, right?
I couldn't call myself a buddy
of yours if I just let this go.
Right?
I'll put all of my strength
on the line and beat you!
It's useless.
Darn it! Ruler! Despair! My foot!
That kid's joke ain't funny at all!
Agreed.
It's no joke.
We know about this.
Right now, an enemy called
Link Joker has appeared.
And its soldiers are...
That's right. We're their soldiers...
...and your enemies.
What's happening now is our destiny.
No... Kourin!
In the end, I've always been alone.
I'm being filled with power.
Kamui?
Kamui?!
I'm going to thoroughly crush any
enemies who could overpower me.
That's the only thing of any value.
Kamui...
Are you stronger than me?
Aichi Sendou!
Kamui, you too?!
Why?! Why are you doing this?!
Those words won't reach him.
They're both Reversed, so your only
recourse is to defeat them in a fight.
If you want to help them,
take out your decks. Go ahead!
Fine with me, wench!
Wait! Fighting right now is
exactly what the enemy wants!
What?! What do you mean?
Sendou, I get that you
want to fight. But...
The middle school division
fell into their hands.
Kaoru, Hiroshi, Reiji, and Eiji
said they were gonna get out,
but I don't know what it's like in there.
Got it. Let's make a strategic retreat.
Let's go, Nagisa!
But Kamui is...
Come on! If we stand around
complaining, we'll be surrounded!
Naoki! Shingo!
Let's go!
Aichi!
Well, there's no hurry.
They can't escape forever.
The time to fight will most certainly come.
Let's wait until then.
Hey! Get in, quick!
Shin!
Stand up the Vanguard.
Stand up, Vanguard!
That's right! Kagero.
Toshiki Kai's clan.
I thought this would be the best way
to bring you to your senses.
I ride Dauntless Drive Dragon!
Call!
Conroe's skill!
Go, Nehalem!
Guard!
Dauntless Drive Dragon!
One more time! Nehalem!
Guard!
Look at us...
What do you think, Kai? This is your Kagero.
I'm gonna use it to make you
recall the way you used to feel!
I threw away my old self.
What?!
I was born again with Link Joker.
Slash through everything
with your cursed blade
and cover the world with
the darkness of death!
Break ride!
Star-vader, Chaos Breaker Dragon!
Lock!
What is this?!
I add +10000 to the power of Chaos Breaker.
Call!
Superior call!
Colony Maker attacks Nehalem!
Chaos Breaker Dragon, attack!
Twin drive.
Second check.
Both were triggers?!
Radon!
You're as good as ever, Kai.
But...
...this is your former comrade.
When you see it in battle,
I'm sure your heart will be stirred!
At the end of an endless quest,
this is the pinnacle of its evolution.
Sublimate that savage soul
and show your true form now!
Break ride!
Dragonic Overlord the End!
Break ride skill! The End gets +10000 power!
And then I give it a skill!
Gojo's skill!
Call! This one too!
Here I come, Kai! The End attacks Radon!
Intercept.
Then our Vanguards are going head to head!
Guard!
Twin drive check!
I got a critical trigger!
That attack didn't go through...
But I'm just getting started!
I'm activating its break ride skill here!
I gave the effects of that last
critical trigger to this guy.
Kai! I'm gonna bring you back
with this one attack from The End!
Go, The End!
Attack again!
Twin drive check!
I give the power to Chaos Breaker, and then draw.
All right! Just 1 more damage.
The End's skill!
Counterblast and then persona blast!
The End stands again!
One more time, Kai!
You've done a good job mastering Kagero.
But you're no match for me now!
Will you be able to say that
after this attack hits?
Dragonic Overlord the End!
Guard!
Perfect guard?!
Too optimistic, Miwa.
Limit Break!
Soulblast!
One more Limit Break!
One more...
Miwa, you did well.
Call!
But it looks like you don't understand.
What?!
I became a Reverse fighter
by my own choice.
I threw away my old self
so I could be born anew.
Aichi and Ren...
I had to do it so that
I could fight them!
At the time, I saw a wall
between Aichi and me.
And so... I'm going to overcome that wall!
Are you really that fixated on those two?
Yeesh. Even Reversed, you're
as stubborn as ever.
Trying to walk up the steep path all alone...
But...
I couldn't call myself your buddy
if I kept quiet and ignored it.
We dropped off Emi and Mai, but...
I hope Gouki, Rekka, and
the others are okay...
We got no choice.
We gotta take 'em down one by one,
turn 'em back to normal.
We won't be in time.
There are probably thousands,
even tens of thousands of Reversed
fighters all over the world.
There's a time limit.
Until those gates are big
enough to cover the Earth...
Then what the heck are we supposed to do?!
C-Chewing my head off won't do any good!
Aichi...
What should we do?
If we only knew a way
out of this situation...
That guy...
Takuto...
Takuto Tatsunagi...
But I'm sure he won't tell us.
Still, we've got to get it
out of him, no matter what.
Ow-ow-ow! Your claws are out!
To get to Takuto, you'll have to
fight someone else first.
Miwa...?
What's this all about?!
Who do we gotta fight?!
You don't mean... surely...
Ding-ding-ding!
You can't avoid that fight.
It should be a good one... right, Aichi?
Oh no! Why is Kai caught up in this too?!
You made him do it, Aichi.
I did?
More precisely, both you and Ren.
You two have gotten stronger.
Strong enough that Kai
felt left behind.
So he got power,
through being Reversed...
Aichi... Ren...
He did it to be your equal again.
Kai... It's my fault that he...
Fight Kai with your awesome skill.
That's what he wants.
But don't forget. There's not much time left.
Miwa... You came here to say that?
Even now, I'm his friend.
When I think I can do something
on his behalf, I act.
That's all.
Miwa... and even Kai.
They're Reversed...
Even so, we gotta do it!
Ain't no other way around it! Right, Aichi?!
Huh? Y-Yeah. Naoki's absolutely right!
Let's do it! We'll fight valiantly!
Well said, Aichi!
Or as the saying goes, "If you
try to do, it can be achieved"!
Then mine's that "When there's
no mistake in your heart..." one!
Proverbs from Shingen Takeda
and Kenshin Usesugi...
Miwa...
What the heck?! I don't know who's
our ally and who's our enemy!
Enemy?!
Miwa... Kai...
I know how you feel, but we
can't be laid-back about this!
Anyway, we gotta go see Takuto.
And if talking does no good,
we take him down!
There ain't nothin' else we can do!
Yeah. Let's fight with everything we've got.
Next time: Each One's Determination!
Each One's Determination!
There's nothing else we can do...
With everything we've got...
Right... Me too!