Miyaji Academy High School
Division Student Council Office
Nice aroma...
Earl Grey goes well with mornings
at a well-ordered academy.
However...
...it seems that order is somewhat
lacking here these days.
Ah! My apologies, sir.
Cardfight, eh?
They're not an officially
recognized club yet,
but they've already begun to have a fairly
considerable effect on the students.
Is it necessary to have a club
devoted to mere card games
at an academy that supports
academics and sports?
With all due deference, President,
Cardfight is currently wildly
popular all over the world,
and some universities abroad have even
set up a special department to study it.
Suwabe...
Yes?!
Does this academy need a Cardfight Club?
No, sir, it does not!
In that case...
I want you to visit that Card-whatever
Club and put a stop to it right now.
That's your duty as the vice president.
A-At once, sir!
By the way, how I am supposed to stop them?
You should...
Figure it out for yourself.
B-But I...
What do you think about
this physics prep room?
Out of all the unused rooms
after school, this is the biggest.
The tables are big, too. I think
this would be perfect for Vanguard!
Not bad, Bowl-cut!
Both athletic and culture-related
clubs flourish here at the academy,
so it was tough searching for an open room.
I bet a certain hooligan wouldn't
have been able to accomplish it.
What was that?!
What?!
What'd you say to me?!
E-Excuse me! No fighting!
Come on, you're both members of the
Cardfight Club now, so try to get along!
At any rate, we're allowed to use this room.
Now all we need to do is get one
more member and a faculty adviser,
and then the Cardfight Club
will be officially recognized!
Shut up, would ya?! We already know all that!
Yeah, yeah...
Let's start with finding a fifth member.
I'm already one step ahead of you on that.
I put up posters telling interested parties
to come here from now on.
Then all we gotta do is wait here,
and we'll be swamped by a bunch of rank
amateur fighters like last time...
N-Naoki, they're people who
would like to join the club,
so you shouldn't talk about them like that...
Ishida, you're a rank amateur yourself.
What's that?! Wanna
have it out right here?!
Hey, is this the place?
Yes, Captain!
They're here already!
My fingers are itchin' to start!
Ready? Set! Hut-hut-hut!
W-Who are you?
We're Miyaji Academy's American
Football Club, the Miyaji Vipers!
Aichi Sendou, you're coming with us!
Go with you... where?
Where?!
You'll find out soon enough.
The Football Team's Assassin
This is dangerous!
W-What the...?!
What are you doing?!
The Cardfight Club is causing another stir...
Go! Fight! Win! Go! Fight! Win!
Vipers, go!
Yay!
What the heck is this?! Where are we?!
That's a good question, boy!
This is Miyaji Academy High
School Division's sub-ground.
It's the Vipers' sacred field!
And I'm the captain and quarterback of
the Vipers, Ikki "the Catapult" Kongou!
The Catapult?
Yeah, you know, a catapult.
The device that launches rocks when
you're attacking a fortress...
The passes that I launch tear right
through the enemy's defense line.
That's right, it's just like a catapult!
So what do you want with us, Mr. Catapult?
It's obvious.
Aichi Sendou, I want a showdown!
You're telling me to play football?!
I-It's just not you...
Wrong!
There'd be no sense of pride in
beating you in a game of football!
I'm gonna fight you with this!
A Vanguard deck?
Then, by showdown, you mean...
That's right. A Vanguard fight.
Why a Cardfight?
It takes Vanguard to beat Vanguard.
Think about it.
They're so consumed by Vanguard that
they're trying to build a Cardfight Club.
But if they lose to a committed
member of the Football Club,
someone who chases after
a ball instead of cards...
You're just all talk!
I-It can't be...
Aichi lost?!
Darn it! I've never felt so frustrated!
They'll be immeasurably shocked, right?
Then they'll lose the will
to create a Cardfight Club,
and order can be restored
once more to the academy.
Is that the way it'll go?
It'll go exactly like that!
Um, I don't really
understand this... but fine.
I accept your challenge.
Wait a second, Aichi!
There's somethin' fishy here!
Come on, the Football Club suddenly
challenges you to a fight?!
There must be a catch.
I don't think it's a good idea
to take this guy too lightly...
Yeah. I feel the same way.
Then...
But I want to have this fight.
After all, it shows that there are
Cardfighters at Miyaji Academy besides us.
There's no way I can turn
down this challenge.
I wouldn't be able to call our
group the Cardfight Club if I did.
Besides...
...no matter what they're plotting,
if I win, there'll be no problem, right?
Aichi...
That was cool!
All right. We do it like this, yeah?
Stand up...
Ready, set...
...Vanguard!
Wingal Liberator!
Reign of Terror, Thermidor!
I'm not surprised. Spike Brothers, right?
Of course. Ready! Set!
You're going to experience the
fearsomeness of the Vipers!
This is where the Cardfight
Club gets crushed.
Stand and draw. Gallatin attacks!
Block!
Gancelot!
Trigger check.
Damage check!
With a boost from Wingal Liberator...
Liberator of Royalty, Phallon
attacks Bad End Dragger!
Block! Cheer Girl, Marilyn!
Turn end.
He only has 4 damage...
It's okay!
Aichi's just got 3 damage.
He's still in the lead!
That's true, but...
All right, now it's time
for the Vipers to attack!
You're finally gettin' your
chance, Captain Catapult!
Go! Go! Vipers, go!
Stand and draw!
This will be the last thing to touch my hand
before I launch it straight at the enemy line!
Grateful Catapult!
Break Ride!
+10000 power!
And then... ready, set, hut-hut-hut!
Go, wrapped in the pale flames of youth!
Lightning bolts of the field!
Run like greased lightning and
score a touchdown past the limit!
So during this turn,
all of my rear-guards get +10000
power when they're attacking!
This is the Vipers' Limit Break formation!
Go, Brakki! Kick Gancelot to kingdom come!
On top of that, Brakki's Soulblast!
First down!
What's this "first down" stuff?
In football, you can do four
plays during your turn.
They're called "first down,"
"second down," and so on.
Huh...
And if the goal line is crossed during
those four downs, it's a touchdown.
The team that does it gets points.
You don't say...
Huh. You seem to know an
awful lot about football.
I don't want to boast, but I've got a good
grasp of the rules for every type of game,
from go and shogi to all known sports.
You are boasting...
Following Brakki, Juggernaut!
Soulblast!
First down!
Wait a sec! That was your second time,
so it should be "second down"!
If you advance ten yards or more,
you're given a new first down.
Those two are playing Vanguard, so
football rules don't matter here.
What's more important than that is...
...5 damage...
The goal line is right before our eyes, huh?
I'm gonna win here with one shot!
So, Catapult, prepare to fire!
Go, Grateful Catapult and Wonder Boy!
Drive the ball deep behind enemy lines
and use that impact to destroy
every last bit of the limits!
Limit Break!
Two Juggernaut Maximum
units, get in formation!
Two new units added to the front line!
Then it's possible for him to have
a total of five attacks this turn!
Did you see that?!
This is the Vipers' Ultimate Formation!
The Catapult!
Vipers! Vipers! Vipers!
Ready! Set! Hut-hut-hut!
Your target is Gancelot!
Catapult... fire!
Perfect guard with Halo Liberator, Mark!
You blocked the Catapult's
attack... Impressive.
But now it's finally the second down.
I can still attack twice more!
Juggernaut! Tackle!
Liberator of Hope, Epona!
You've got some gall, blocking me.
But I've still got the third down!
Thermidor boosts! Go, Juggernaut!
I guard with Flogal and Marron!
Liberator of Silence, Gallatin intercepts!
What?!
Turnover?!
Shoot!
It seems the odds are against him...
What's wrong? Everything's
okay on that end, isn't it?
Y-Yes, sir. Of course!
Yes! Interception!
Oh yeah, intercept...
No, no, no! In football, they've
got what's called "interception"!
Oh. That's when the defense catches
the ball thrown by the offense, right?
That's it! And when that
happens, there's a turnover.
The offense and defense switch sides, so
what was the defense gets to attack the enemy!
I don't get all that, but anyway,
it's Aichi's turn to attack, yeah?
Exactly!
All right! Go, Aichi!
You know, this is just a "turn end"...
Stand and draw!
The battle to set the world free from the
nightmare of limitations begins now!
Become a legend!
Break Ride!
Liberator of the Round Table, Alfred!
Alfred gets +10000 power!
Phallon, Wingal, and Llew get +5000 power!
And the limit is already broken.
Limit Break!
Alfred!
As a result, he receives +2000
power for each Liberator unit!
What?!
Right now, he's got three Liberator
units... Phallon, Wingal, and Llew!
That's a total of +6000!
Teamwork isn't found only in football!
Alfred's Especial Counterblast!
I'm going to show you the
power of our friendship!
Superior call... Pomerugal Liberator!
That's another Liberator!
So that means...
That's not all.
There are still two unflipped
Liberators in the Damage Zone.
One more Especial Counterblast!
I superior call Liberator of the Flute, Escrad!
Now Alfred's power is 31000!
I-I don't believe it...
Suddenly he's got five Liberators?!
This is just like a formation!
Yeah... This is definitely an
Especial Counterblast formation!
That formation looks tough...
I can't find a place to break through!
Escrad attacks Grateful Catapult
with a boost from Pomerugal!
Block! Silence Joker!
Alfred attacks with a boost from Llew!
With Llew's skill, Alfred
receives +4000 power!
46000 power?!
Twin drive!
Liberator of Hope, Epona!
I give the power to Phallon and
the extra critical to Alfred!
C-Captain!
I-I lost...
Yes!
Serves ya right!
Lame-o!
Sorry, but we're not interested in weak men!
I'm totally disappointed...
See ya!
Bye bye!
D-Don't be like that...
Come back, my angels!
W-We're no good...
...without you girls!
Jeez. They were of no use...
Hey, dude.
What?
Why did you mess with us?
The Student Council promised to
raise our budget if I won the fight.
Huh. So you were just dazzled by money...
Don't get the wrong idea!
Sure, I want a bigger budget.
But I'm a Cardfighter too,
if not much of one.
I wouldn't challenge anyone
to a fight just for money!
Then what were you after?
Why did you challenge Aichi?
There's a strong fighter around.
That's plenty reason for a
Cardfighter to do battle.
Hey, you guys!
You gonna sit around all day?! Let's go!
Where are we going?
The setting sun!
We're all gonna run for the setting sun!
Yes, Captain!
Run? There's a river in front of you!
Let's cross the bridge over there and go!
Oh, that way...
Your helmet...
Vipers!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Men...
Anyway, why'd the Student Council
send a fighter after us?
To the point of dangling the promise
of a budget increase in front of him...
I don't know...
But it looks like we can't
afford to be careless.
What do you mean?
I mean we should make the Cardfight
Club official as soon as possible,
before anyone challenges us.
Starting tomorrow, the Football Club's
practice area will be Ground Six.
Inform them of it.
Ground Six... You mean, the
other side of the mountain?
Exactly. If they run, it should take
them about two hours to get there...
The exercise will be perfect for them.
Yes, certainly...
The weak are discarded, and the
strong receive favorable treatment.
The law of the jungle is the most
beautiful order that exists.
I'm going to teach you the global standard...
...Cardfight Club.
Why are those Student Council
jerks bein' a thorn in our side?!
Ishida alone is enough of a thorn in
my side! They won't get away with it!
What are you talkin' about?! You're
the one who's the thorn in my side!
I can't let that comment pass!
Both of you, stop fighting!
Next Time: The Birth of the Cardfight Club?!
If only Misaki were here
at a time like this...
Right when the club needs
to "stand up" for real...
Aichi! Who's the bigger thorn in the
side, me or Komoi?! You be the judge!
You know I can't do that!