Stand up, Vanguard!
Flag of Raijin, Corposant!
Hope Child, Turiel!
Huh, Angel Feather, huh?
So your outfit isn't the
only thing that's cute, eh?
You really are an amusing boy...
I'm looking forward to seeing what
kind of fight you'll give me.
She reminds me of you when
you're angry, Sharlene.
I'm like that?
Suiko is laughing, but that's really just...
I don't know if it's that he
can't read a person's mood
or if he's just not afraid of anything...
Naoki Ishida is a formidable man.
Whatever happens, it's not my fault.
Turiel boosts.
Million Ray Pegasus attacks
Dragonic Deathscythe.
Turn end.
That brings Naoki to 3 damage.
Against Suiko's 2 damage.
She pulled a reversal.
Tell me somethin' I don't know.
But this thing's just gettin' started.
With this measly difference
between our damages,
I got plenty of chances to turn it around.
Still...
Her outfit's a little weird,
but she fights totally normal.
Oh, I'm not so sure you can talk...
Your fighting is run-of-the-mill, too.
What was that?! Wait, how'd
you know what I was thinkin'?!
It's because whatever you're thinking
either spills out of your mouth
or is written all over your face.
And it's not just the fight,
but your personality.
I'm not sure if you're honest or just simple.
Personality aside, you dissed my fightin'!
So it's okay to diss his personality...
Draw!
You can decide whether my fightin'
is humdrum after you see this!
Punch through, man's pride!
Victory is on the other side!
I ride Armor Break Dragon!
Huh. Armor Break Dragon...
If he's actually mastered that card,
then maybe what he said before about being
"in the spotlight at the
High School Championship"
wasn't just a lot of hot air...
I call Thunderstorm Dragoon and
attack Core Memory, Armaros!
Guard.
Shoot! In that case...
...Armor Break attacks Armaros!
No guard.
Twin drive...
Draw trigger!
I give the power to Thunderstorm!
Second check!
Go, Thunderstorm!
Attack Armaros!
All right! That makes 4 damage.
Smooth sailin'!
I just gotta ride out the next turn,
then turn the screws on her!
Turn end!
He really thinks he's going to win this...
That's why he's called simple.
Powerful Fighter at Fukuhara High
Blue-winged angel, conquer disease
with your smile and great strength!
I ride Prophecy Celestial, Ramiel!
Call!
Raguel attacks Thunderstorm!
With a boost from Thousand,
Ramiel attacks Armor Break!
Since she's attacking the Vanguard,
Ramiel's skill is activated.
She gets +2000 power.
No guard!
Twin drive check.
Oh? It's a draw trigger.
Let's see... I suppose I'll
give the power to Million.
And then I draw.
That makes 4 damage...
But no prob.
I kinda expected this to happen.
He really does wear his heart on his sleeve.
With a boost from Turiel,
Million attacks Armor Break.
I guard with Eradicator, Dragon Mage!
Thunderstorm intercepts!
Not bad. I take back what I said before.
You're not a run-of-the-mill fighter.
That's why I said I'm gonna be in...
But...
...you're not an interesting fighter either.
What?!
Well, I'm not satisfied at all.
If you don't make me enjoy
myself much more than this,
I'm going to punish you, Naoki Ishida...
My turn is over.
Not satisfied, huh? Good one.
But you're gonna be eatin' those
words by the end of this turn!
If you can do the impossible,
logic goes by the wayside!
If you can get past pride,
the limit backs off!
That's the way a man lives!
Armor Break Dragon's Limit Break!
He does three Counterblasts,
then puts three cards from his
hand into the Drop Zone...
That's reckless. Is that what
you'd call a desperate attack?
Yeah, that's it.
A great sacrifice effects a great outcome.
Armor Break Dragon's Limit Break!
The front-row rear-guards
of both players retire!
On top of that, Armor
Break gets +10000 power...
...and two extra criticals!
He not only eliminated her rear-guards,
but got power and two criticals?!
Armor Break Dragon's skill...
It's a new skill from Sealed
Dragons Unleashed.
He threw away his next defense to
gamble everything on this turn.
I call Dragon Dancer, Julia! And, with her skill,
I take the top card of my deck and show it.
All right! Eradicator Wyvern Guard, Guld.
It's a grade 1, so I can superior call!
And then I call one more Armor Break!
He's filled up his rear-guards in one swoop.
Yep...
He only has one card left in his hand...
I give him props for going full throttle.
Just like a boy.
But...
Attack! Julia!
No guard.
Agnes boosts!
My Armor Break Vanguard attacks Ramiel!
At the same time, Agnes's Counterblast!
I add +3000 to Armor Break's power!
That's a total of 30000 power!
I don't have anything
against spirited boys...
...but at the same time, you
make me want to pick on you.
Wha...?!
Guard.
Guarding with four units for
a total shield of 25000...
Then I'll have to draw two triggers.
Twin drive!
First check!
No trigger...
Second check!
And this is a critical trigger...
Whatever. I'll give the effects
to my rear-guard Armor Break.
And then my other Armor Break attacks!
I'll guard for this one, too.
Shoot! She didn't let me finish it this turn!
He couldn't seal the deal.
Still, she only has one
card left in her hand.
And without any front-row rear-guards,
it'll be difficult for her
to deal 2 damage to Ishida.
If he can hang on 'til the next turn,
Ishida has a good chance of winning!
If he can hang on until the next turn...
Draw.
What's wrong? What are you laughin' at?!
I was thinking that this
fight has become interesting.
But unfortunately...
...it's going to end this turn.
Replacing Ramiel, I break ride
Chief Nurse, Shamsiel!
With its break ride effect...
...I add Million to my
hand from the Damage Zone,
and put the top card of my
deck into the Damage Zone.
Then Shamsiel gets +10000 power.
You scared me for a second there.
+10000 with a break ride, that's normal.
I can handle that.
That's not it!
The problem is she put
Aniel in the Damage Zone.
In the Damage Zone?
Then...
That's right.
Right now, when I put a
card in the Damage Zone,
it activates the skills of two
units, Thousand Ray and Shamsiel.
They bring boundless love by
performing soothing songs for units
that are injured or have
withdrawn from the front line.
That's the true mission of Angel Feather.
Listen to the song of love.
Eternal Song for the Injured!
+2000 power, and for both
units at the same time...
I call Million Ray.
Turiel's Counterblast.
Assault Hospice goes to the Damage Zone.
Let's perform it once more.
Eternal Song for the Injured.
This time it's three units at once?!
Also, I flip over Crimson Mind, Baruch in
the Damage Zone, which activates her skill.
During this turn, my Angel Feather
Vanguard, Shamsiel, gets +3000 power.
In the blink of an eye,
her power became 27000!
With a boost from Thousand,
Shamsiel attacks your Vanguard.
38000 power...
I'm not done yet.
Shamsiel's Limit Break!
I switch a card from my hand
with one from the Damage Zone.
Then... again...
Eternal Song for the Injured.
42000 total...
No good. No matter what
I do, I can't block it!
Twin drive.
Oh?
Don't tell me...
I got one.
Critical trigger.
Let's see. I give the power to Million and
of course the extra critical to Shamsiel.
I-I don't believe it...
I... I lost...
That was more fun than
I thought it'd be, boy.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
It was just a friendly game...
No. This fight made me realize somethin'.
Just bein' around you guys
has made me stronger,
but not to the level where
I can fight other teams.
Naoki...
What was I talkin' about,
"in the spotlight"? What am I, nuts?
This isn't like you.
What was that just now? Whining?
Or wimpy nonsense?
It doesn't sound like the
Porcupine Head I know.
There's no need to confirm that you're
weak at this late date, Ishida.
We all know that's God's honest truth.
You're the baggage of the
Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club.
You drag everyone else down.
S-Shingo...
Jerk...
If you're weak, you should get strong.
Fortunately, there's still time before
the VF High School Championship.
Prepare yourself, because Shingo Komoi
is going to put you through the wringer.
You...
That's right. I think we'll start by taking
another look at your deck...
No, before that, we need to have a
meeting to go over today's fight.
Y-Yeah, I guess we should...
Obedience is good. Confront
your weakness with sincerity
and some self-examination, and
you'll be able to get stronger.
Right now, you're still at the level
of a unicellular euglenid,
but if you can at least get
as far as a water flea,
I suppose I could put your name
on the list of the Komoi Group.
Why, you... Granny Glasses...
Got a problem, Porc...
Make a monkey outta me, huh?
Who're you callin' a ukelele?!
"Euglenid," I said! They move around
with flagellum and capture their food.
In a manner of speaking,
they're carnivorous plants.
Isn't that cool?!
Shut up! Euglenids aside,
water fleas ain't no plants!
That's what bothers you? Then...
Why are they fighting again?
Who knows?
He realized that he's weak...
That's the first step to becoming strong.
I could see that one becoming strong.
Yeah...
Maybe...
...it's good that I am going to
a different school than Aichi.
Tomorrow!
R-Recently, it kind of feels like
I've been gaining strength...
Oh?
Why, if it isn't Aichi.
Ren!
Who the heck is he?
Ren Suzugamori.
Team Asteroid's top reigning fighter!
Then the guy's strong?
That doesn't even deserve an answer!
How mean of you, Tetsu.
Do you mean to just leave me out of this?
It's because you came in late.
See, my cat was sleeping in the sun,
and we ended up taking a nap together.
Then you must be thirsty,
right? I'll get you a drink.
Here you are. Coffee to wake you up.
Oh, alright then...
As always, your coffee is delicious, Suiko.
Really? I use the same beans as everyone...
Ren,
I'd like you to direct your attention to
your duties as the captain of the Vanguard Club.
Tetsu, you're the one who
forced me into the position.
That's alright. You can live as
freely as you always have, Ren.
As the vice-captain, I'll take
care of all the routine matters.
Sorry for making you do all the work, Asaka.
Don't baby Ren, Asaka.
That guy doesn't look strong at all...
Thick-skulled Tetsu...
Well, he is strong... I think...
Sticks and stones...
Then as the captain, I
think I'll request a fight
with the captain of Miyaji
Academy's Cardfight Club.
You know, actually, it's been
a while since I've come across
a deck that clicks with me like this.
Blaster Dark... That's a Shadow Paladin deck!
It seems this trip was well worth it.
Just kidding!
We have to save it for the real deal,
the VF High School Championship, right?
R-Right...
Well, I think that'll do it
for your reconnaissance today.
You can pick up where you left off next time.
Okay, dismissed.
In the end, I'm the only
one who got to fight.
We went through all that
to do surveillance on them,
but weren't able to gather
any important data.
Ultimately, our fights were postponed, too...
I know...
Did you feel it, Sendou?
Yeah...
Sendou...
We were invited to participate in
the VF High School Championship
as fighters from a foreign country.
That's what I heard...
But you don't understand.
We were invited, so we don't have
to go through the preliminary round.
We'll be participating from the VF
High School Championship proper.
In other words, the winner
of the regional tournament,
the one who will be standing in my way,
will be either Fukuhara or Miyaji.
It can only be one of those schools.
That's what we meant.
Of course, Fukuhara is a strong school,
being the home of Team Asteroid.
That's right.
I fought Asaka Narumi today, and she's
not an opponent to be underestimated.
And it looks like they're keeping
some secrets under wraps...
Will it be Ren Suzugamori or you
standing before us at the tournament?
I'm looking forward to finding out.
Aichi...
What's wrong, Aichi?
Oh, nothing...
I'm going back to the club to give
Porcupine Head here a real workout,
but what about you, Sendou?
Of course you're comin', right?
Y-Yeah...
All right, let's practice our butts off and
get to VF High School Championship!
That's the spirit!
...Porcupine Euglenid...
I didn't say anything...
Let's go, too.
Yeah.
This school's going to be in
the regional tournament...
And then, if I don't win against Ren...
...we won't be able to go to
VF High School Championship!
Shoot! I lost!
Well, lose and know thyself. It
was a good experience for you.
What, like you're some authority?!
Be prepared! I'm going to run you ragged!
Let's all get stronger!
A school festival poster...
Is it that season already?
Next time: Exciting School Festival!
Exciting School Festival!
A play? On stage?!
I'm going to be in it, too?!
The day has finally come for
my artistry to be recognized!
The only part I've played before was a tree!