My presence would only hurt you more.
I'm going to disappear...
...from your lives...
...forever.
That's...
That's a mistake!
This is my last ride!
This will bring everything to an end.
Our relationship... and everything else...
Kai...
Please help Kai, Aichi.
Aichi... Your strong feelings
have changed everything.
Believe in yourself.
She's more worried about Aichi
than of losing her memories.
Kai! Don't disappear!
I've already made up my mind, Aichi.
I don't accept that!
It's the only way.
The Connected
With this break ride,
I give +10000 power to Overlord.
Call!
Dragon of explosive fire...
...that has come again, burn down
all order with your scarlet roar!
Overlord "The Re-birth" Limit Break!
I lock all rear-guards!
With five units locked, it gains +10000 power!
Break ride and a Limit Break?
Burn for eternity, roaring flames!
Eternal Flame Re-birth!
No guard!
Check the drive trigger!
I got a draw trigger!
I give the power to Overlord and draw.
The flames of purgatory never extinguish.
Come back from the dead, Overlord!
Stand... and he still has a twin drive!
My next attack! Overlord!
No guard!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
I give all of the effects to Overlord!
Damage trigger check!
I got a draw trigger.
I give the power to Gancelot... and draw!
You have 5 damage.
Flames feed on flames.
Hellfire keeps burning.
Come back from the dead a third time,
Overlord "The Re-birth"!
No matter how many times it
comes back, I'll ride it out!
For the sake of correcting your mistake!
Just 1 more damage...
It ends here!
Attack!
Perfect guard!
Turn end...
Disappearing isn't atonement!
What's lost in a Vanguard fight can
only be regained in a Vanguard fight!
That's...
That's right. What you told me.
Your sins can only be redeemed
in Vanguard fights.
You should atone through fighting!
Even if I lost to temptation
again and hurt you?
Yeah. No matter what happens,
I'll always be with you!
Call!
Star Rain Trumpeter!
Star Rain's skill!
Blaster Blade Liberator in
my Soul returns to the deck.
Blaster Blade...
I superior call one Gold Paladin unit...
Epona!
When you make a mistake, I'll stop you!
I'll put everything I have on the line!
No matter how many times!
Fighting together, hurting each other,
encouraging each other,
competing, building a bond of friendship!
We should join forces now more than ever!
Limit Break!
Guard!
Drive trigger check!
I got a draw trigger!
I give the power to Bruno, and then draw!
Because you're my idol,
my friend, and my rival!
No guard.
Because you mean so much to me!
I can't afford to lose you!
Intercept!
Turn end!
Kai, there's no need for you to disappear!
Picture it!
I'm... I'm with you!
Your friend who always thinks
about you is right here!
Th...
...an...
...k...
...you!
Kai... Just like you were once my leader...
This time, I'll become your leader!
I see... You've always been there for me.
Always with me, spurring me on...
You've been the driving
force that made me stronger.
I'm no match for you.
Kai!
But this fight alone is different.
From here on out, I'm going to
beat you as a fighter, Aichi!
The same for me!
I'm going to beat you, Kai!
I feel it...
As the ring breaks up, the effects of
Reverse inside of me are vanishing.
Along the same lines, Kai's strongest form
is disappearing, along with his deck.
I'll never be able to fight him again.
I want to test how far I can get against him!
Again, I'm going to use
all my might to beat you!
Me too, Kai!
The damage is 5 to 5.
This will end it.
Final Turn!
Kimnara's skill!
I Counterblast...
Zorron retires!
Call!
Burnout's Soulblast!
Star Rain retires!
Limit Break!
By locking five units, it gets +10000 power.
Eternal Flame Re-birth!
Perfect guard!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
I give all the effects to my Vanguard.
Second check.
I got one!
That's even more power and an extra critical.
I'm not done yet.
Flames feed on flames.
Hellfire keeps burning.
Rise from the dead, Overlord "The Re-birth"!
Here I go!
This is the end.
Take this.
The apocalyptic flames that
reduce everything to ashes!
Perfect guard!
Turn end.
That's the stuff, Aichi.
But no matter how much you try to
defend yourself, you can't escape.
I'm going to surpass you, Kai.
You'll see!
If I become stronger,
you'll become stronger, too!
That's right. This fight is a new beginning.
It's the start of a new day,
in which we compete with each other!
Draw!
To release those who are
in the grip of a spell,
come forth, king of all knights!
I ride...
Liberator, Monarch Sanctuary Alfred!
Cheer Up's skill!
Give power to Alfred!
Alfred's Limit Break!
Use your sacred soul to release everything
from what is cursed and evil!
Liberate the lock!
Soothe wounds with your holy light.
Five comrades, gather on the battlefield!
Bruno, Epona, Arum, Gancelot!
And then...
...stand up, my...
...our avatar!
Blaster Blade!
Bruno has 19000 power with its skill.
With Cheer Up Trumpeter's skill,
Alfred has 31000 power!
On top of that...
...Ultimate Break!
With this, Alfred gets +10000 power
and an extra critical!
Kai! This is my soul's Ultimate Break!
His soul's... Ultimate Break...
That one attack crushes everything!
Return to your rightful form!
Sacred light, shine bright!
The sparkle of hope!
Sacred Sparkle!
Perfect guard!
Drive trigger check!
Second check!
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Gancelot,
and heal 1 damage point.
The best opponent, fitting for the end...
Aichi... I'm glad it was you.
Gancelot!
Guard!
Here I come, Kai!
The Blaster Blade that you gave me... attacks!
Anger! Love!
Hatred! Adoration!
Go through all of it, my avatar!
You win, Aichi.
Kai...
I see.
Alfred called on comrades.
Overload "Re-birth" fought alone.
That difference was the
difference between you and me.
Brother Aichi...
It seems he's all right.
Aichi!
Kai!
I was able to win with Blaster Blade
because you introduced me to it, Kai.
I must have sensed something about you then.
Your inner strength...
Your potential...
Your power to believe...
That was a wonderful fight.
The strongest Aichi...
I was able to fight
the strongest Kai...
I won't forget today's fight.
It's a new start with you.
As friends, as rivals...
Competing with each other,
striving for the top...
From now on and evermore...
The ring above the city vanished,
and normal life resumed.
The number of card game players across the world
surged to hundreds of millions of people.
From children to adults, it became a part
of their lives that was taken for granted.
But even after recent events,
the card game that attracts the
most attention remains the same...
...Vanguard.
Don't cry.
Don't cry just because you lost.
But...
I'll give you this.
This is...
You can have it.
Use it to put everybody to shame.
Bro!
And now, what you've been waiting for!
Of course they're going to sing...
Ultra-rare!
Right now, I'm going to fight the person
who freed me from being
Reversed and saved the world.
The strongest fighter...
My best friend.