Fight me!
If you lose, you'll become a pirate too!
This is an offer you can't refuse.
Miss Emi!
And Miss Mai too!
EM, yo!
It's a showdown! I'm gonna beat you,
then save Princess Emi and Princess Mai!
This sorcerer lying dormant in the abyss has
obtained an even more accursed power!
The power to end the life of all beings
on the face of this Earth!
Ice Prison Hades Emperor, Cocytus "Reverse"!
Break ride!
Superior call!
Pirates who have died once, be resurrected!
This is the true value of a Granblue deck.
And its name is...
Eternal Resurrection Final Hell!
That's right. Pirates can keep comin' back!
Where is it? Where'd it go?
I'm gonna beat you!
And then I'll get Miss Emi back!
You won't win against me...
Not when I'm Reversed!
Kamui's Fist
Grovel before the power of Cocytus "Reverse,"
which I gained through that break ride!
Cocytus "Reverse" attacks your Vanguard,
with a boost from Samurai Spirit!
Perfect guard!
Drive trigger check.
Second check.
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Corrupt Dragon!
Without a perfect guard,
I would've been in big trouble.
Thank you, Solar Falcon!
But I'm not through yet!
Like waves, they come roaring to
shore, then pull you out to sea.
That's the terror of pirates!
Ruin Shade attacks Hatred Chaos!
Ruin Shade's skill. +2000 power!
His rear-guard was vaporized.
He doesn't have any rear-guard
units that can intercept.
CI, yo!
And what's waiting for
him in the third attack?
Corrupt Dragon, powered up with
a critical trigger, Brazil!
So, do you know where my deck is?
Look for it, Brazil.
Kamui...
Become scraps of seaweed!
Corrupt Dragon attacks with a
boost from Sea Strolling Banshee!
Perfect guard!
What?!
Turn end!
Unlock Dancing Cutlass!
Two perfect guards?
Lucky twerp!
Wrong!
Guys who don't give up attract luck!
Either way, you're out of luck now.
You got one card in your
hand left, while I got five.
My advantage ain't goin' anywhere!
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm gonna make you remember, Gouki.
It's my turn!
Stand and draw!
Desert Gator moves.
Here I go!
I call a pair of Brainy Papios!
Brainy Papio attacks your Vanguard
with a boost from Desert Gator!
No guard!
Damage trigger check!
Shoot!
5 damage!
5 D, yo!
Rats!
Brainy Papio's Counterblast!
The malignant soul of a beast never sleeps!
I stand Desert Gator!
Brainy Papio attacks your Vanguard
with a boost from Riot Horn!
Intercept!
Gouki!
I'm gonna open your eyes with this
deck that I swore an oath on!
Ethics Buster Extreme attacks your
Vanguard with a boost from Blank Marsh!
Guard!
Drive trigger check!
Stand trigger!
I stand Brainy Papio!
+5000 power!
Beasts awaken fellow beasts.
Riot Horn's skill!
When a unit in the same vertical
line stands, this guy stands too.
So you've filled your front
and back rows again?
Second check.
Grade 1... Beast Deity!
Nuts!
The banquet of beasts ain't over yet!
Ethics Buster Extreme's Limit Break!
When a grade 1 or higher Beast Deity
appears in the drive check,
one rear-guard can stand!
Brainy Papio!
His four left and right rear-guards stand!
GK! Go, Kamui the Great, yo!
This ain't just any fist.
It's a fist of friendship, from me to you!
Brainy Papio attacks your Vanguard
with a boost from Desert Gator!
No guard!
This fist is gonna open your eyes! Gouki!
Kamui won!
Why?! Why did I lose?!
During my training here,
I've tried out various decks,
but of them all, this one fits me the most.
I'll swear this right in front of you, Gouki.
I swear that no matter what rough
waves comes from here on in,
this deck and I will ride 'em out together.
I'm not gonna part with it lightly.
So that's what it was...
Gouki!
Gouki, are you okay?
Kamui the Great!
AYO?
Your fist did the trick, Kamui!
Cool, Kamui the Great!
TMF! That's a man's friendship, yo!
That's nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
Rekka?
Even though he lost, why do I feel so moved?
I don't know, Brazil!
You want something, Brazil?
Rekka?
I wonder what's wrong...
Gouki, what happened?
I don't really remember.
We came to the school with
Nagisa to check it out...
...and the next thing I know...
You were Reversed?
What's goin' on here?
That's right! Nagisa!
Where's Nagisa?!
Miss Emi!
Hurry up, you guys!
That's...
...Rekka from Ultra-rare?!
Don't tell me she's also...
Wait!
Give me back Miss Emi!
I'm goin' too! They may
have taken Nagisa also!
Nagisa!
Kamui, I'm not letting you get past me!
I'm getting the same vibe that
I did with you before, Gouki.
What?! Then...
Nagisa... has been Reversed too.
That's my Kamui!
All it took was one look
for you to figure it out.
You're not my future husband for nothing!
I don't remember promisin'
you anything like that!
You're so cute when you're embarrassed!
Even Reversed, she still doesn't
listen to what a guy says!
Nagisa... Why are you wearing that makeup?!
My sweet, pure little sister is cuter
than cute without any makeup...
I'm talking to Kamui right now!
What do you think, Kamui?
I've changed, haven't I?
Changed how?
Jeez! You don't notice when
a girl's become a woman?!
Last year, I was a fourth-grader.
Whenever I met you, I wanted to
communicate my feelings right away.
Yes, I really was a child.
But now I'm in fifth grade!
As you can see, I've become a
lady who's a perfect fit for you!
I'm tellin' ya, you
haven't changed one bit!
And in the first place,
you're only a year older!
One year for a woman equals
three years for a man.
In other words, even though you're
a first-year middle school student,
I'm older than you emotionally!
"A woman who's older than her
husband," as people say.
What?! I didn't know that!
Yo, Ms. Nagisa!
I've heard that older women
make men successful, Brazil!
Enough, already!
Look, I'll spell it out for you!
I'm in love with...
Me!
No! With Miss Emi!
Bra...
Ah-ah-ah, I'm not falling for that one.
I know all about it.
That is, the tendency of men to eye other
women even when they have no feelings for them.
But, you know, Kamui,
your time to dream is up.
You're going to return to me.
I refuse! Forget it! No, thank you!
I see. Then I have no choice.
I'll open your eyes with a fight!
No two ways about it, she's been Reversed.
The only way to bring her back to normal
is beating her in a fight, like with Gouki.
But...
Kamui, help!
Help!
I have to hurry up and save Miss Emi!
But I can't let Nagisa stay like this either.
I must make my way to
the imprisoned princess.
But will I be able to leave behind
this enchanted forest fairy?
What are you gonna do, brave Kamui?!
Brave Kamui, will you choose Princess Emi?
Or the emotionally older Nagisa?
Brazil?
Princess Emi!
That choice is out of the question.
We'll ask you one more time, Brazil.
Do you choose Princess Emi?
Or the emotionally older Nagisa?
Brazil?
Princess Emi.
Wrong answer!
Enhancement
Period
I'll ask you once more, Brazil!
Do you choose Princess Emi?
Or the emotionally older Nagisa?
There ain't no end to this!
Is fighting Nagisa the only thing I can do?
Leave this to me.
Gouki!
It's only natural for an older brother
to make his sister see the light.
I'll count on you!
That's terrible, big bro!
It's bad enough you're not cheering
me on, but for you to betray me,
your own little sister,
and take Kamui's side...
Big bro, do you hate me?
Nagisa... I'm sorry!
Hey! Oy!
I can't win against those tears!
Sorry, Kamui.
Gouki!
But I'll even become an ogre if it's
for the sake of Nagisa's happiness!
Kamui the Great!
No interference!
Brazil...
All right, we're gonna fight, Kamui!
And when I win, I'll make
you forget all other women.
What is this?!
Brazil!
What the...?!
Kamui?
Are you all right, boy-degozaru?
You're...
...Ninja Master M?!
That mask, that costume... There's no doubt!
The guy that was successful at
the Card Capital shop tournament,
then retired after passing the name
"Ninja" on to the next generation!
LF, a legendary fighter!
Ninja Master M, yo!
I am not Ninja Master M.
Look at this-degozaru.
I am Ninja Master Neo!
Ninja Master
Ninja Master Neo?
Only the name's changed.
ONC, yo.
Anyway, thanks for helpin' me out.
But what are you doing
here, Ninja Master Neo?
Actually, I was here for the open house...
I can say no more-degozaru.
I feel like I've heard that voice before...
That's not important now-degozaru!
I know what's going on-degozaru.
Leave this to me and go
on ahead, boy-degozaru.
But I can't leave Nagisa like this...
Have faith in me-degozaru.
I swear that I'll bring her back to
normal in your stead, boy-degozaru.
Certainly, saving Lady Nagisa is
important, as is saving Lady Emi.
However, you are only one, Lord Kamui.
You can't save both at
the same time-degozaru.
But...
The only way to save them both
is for you to fight the one who
caused this calamity and beat them.
The one who caused it?
Unless you cut it off at the roots,
this disaster won't be contained.
Protect everyone you hold dear, boy-degozaru.
Got it. Then you take care of Nagisa!
Kamui the Great!
Stop him!
I am your opponent-degozaru.
You're just intent on interfering, are you?
It seems I need to show you
just how strong my love is.
Love-degozaru?
It's a beautiful word-degozaru...
Love me too-degozaru!
Now then! You're stuck with me-degozaru.
That's just what I want!
The martial arts training hall?
Brazil?
Meaning we're going to
settle things here, huh?
But I won't let you get one point of love!
Ninpo! Tatami mat flip!
This won't do for a fight table-degozaru.
Ha! I don't need anything like that!
Nagisa!
Enough.
Come back to your old self.
Big bro...
I don't need you anymore.
What?!
Nagisa...
You lash out at your brother like that?
My cute little sister, who I
brought up with my own hands,
says such a cruel thing to me?!
Destruction!
Despair!
The end of the world!
The power of Reverse is
fearsome indeed... degozaru.
Sword
I've always thought that Nagisa
was much manlier than Gouki!
Yes, Brazil!
Owww...
Hiroshi... Kaoru... You too?
Old man ninja?
Pardon?
I'm going to teach you what happens
when you get in the way of my love.
And thus a ninja's duty
is accomplished-degozaru.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Nagisa! Even you've been Reversed!
That doesn't matter.
Whatever happens to the world, my eternal,
indestructible love for Kamui will stand!
Ninja Master Neo! Please take care of her!
Kamui!
During the uproar in the middle school
division, we were still on the bus heading home.
Next time: Ninja Master Returns!
Ninja Master Returns!
Old man ninja who got in
the way of a maiden's love?
You're going to pay!