Be careful, Leon.
Yeah...
I don't know what kind of
trap has been laid here,
but I just have to win.
That's all.
So? Where is he?
My favorite room is the study, but...
The Souryu child...
Even I'm at a disadvantage
when faced with you two.
While you're together, that is...
Leon!
Leon Souryu...
I've prepared a different room for you.
You're a VIP.
I have to give you red-carpet treatment.
Leon!
I told you.
My full-bore reception is waiting for him.
The Two Leons
I've been split up from Takuto?
What the...?!
Who are you?!
The fighter that you'll
never be able to surpass.
I'm asking for your name!
I'm you from the future,
a future ruled by Link Joker.
From the future?!
What is this farce?
A future Leon?!
I won't let you get away with this!
Shut up.
I'd like to dispose of you for good
as soon as possible,
but summoning the future Leon
used up an awful lot of power.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't take up too much of your time.
It's his destiny to lose this fight
and become Reversed.
Even if you are the future me,
I'll still win.
That's logical.
But don't forget that your future is me.
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Advance Party Brave Shooter!
Battle Siren, Katy!
You say I'm Reversed?
As if I would accept that!
I go first. Draw.
I ride Blue Storm Water General, Hermes!
I ride Wheel Assault!
Call!
Attack!
Wheel Assault!
Ride!
And then I call!
What's wrong?
We're still in the opening moves.
Already worried you won't be able
to change your own fate?
I stand and draw.
I ride Tear Knight, Lazarus!
Call!
Basil!
Lazarus!
Drive check...
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Tidal Assault!
Tidal Assault!
Guard!
With its skill,
Tidal Assault stands and attacks.
Guard!
Turn end.
I see.
Aqua Force's combination
attacks are wonderful.
But my Aqua Force is so very superior.
Stand and draw.
Dragon spun into existence from the
warp of the wind and the weft of the sea...
Turn into...
...your destined form!
Don't tell me...
Blue Storm Dragon, Maelstrom "Reverse"!
Maelstrom "Reverse"?!
Enfolded in Link Joker's power,
this dragon will lead to a new land
for the Souryu people.
This is Maelstrom "Reverse"!
What a sinister form.
It's the perfect unit for the Reversed
Leon Souryu, don't you think?
That's right. Despair.
Just like you,
Leon Souryu is sinking
to the depths of despair.
You...
How much do you have to belittle
Aqua Force before you're satisfied?!
Gregorius moves.
I call Diamantes.
It attacks Lazarus!
Intercept!
Diamantes uses its skill to move back.
Tidal Assault attacks!
Guard!
Gregorius!
Maelstrom "Reverse"!
Limit Break!
I lock Katy!
It gets +5000 power and an extra critical.
Twin drive...
First...
Second...
Heal trigger.
What sinister power...
This is the power of the true Maelstrom.
Turn end.
Well?
What do you think of Maelstrom
"Reverse's" power?
Leon...
What's wrong?
Are you intimidated by
Maelstrom "Reverse's" power?
Now, it's your turn.
Advance towards the warped future!
I stand and draw.
Wielder of the Demiurge,
arise from the blue sea!
I ride...
...Blue Flight Dragon, Trans-core Dragon!
Call!
It attacks Gregorius!
Hermes!
Trans-core Dragon!
No guard.
Twin drive...
Tidal Assault!
Guard!
Prepare yourself.
True terror is about to begin.
What do you think?
A fight between two people who share
the same flesh and blood is fun, isn't it?
Particularly in their case,
when it's literally fighting against oneself.
Now, get beaten to a pulp!
Each wound that you sustain
will link to your future...
...Leon Souryu!
Stand and draw!
I move Katy to the Soul.
Gregorias gets +3000 power.
Call!
Diamantes, move forward!
Attack Trans-core!
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Trans-core Dragon.
Vain resistance.
Dorothea boosts.
Maelstrom "Reverse"!
Limit Break!
Emerald Shield, Paschal!
A perfect guard?
If you think that leaves you
in the clear, you're naive!
What?!
Maelstrom "Reverse's" Limit Break!
I draw one card,
and retire one of your rear-guards!
Take this!
Dark Cloud Sacrifice!
My rear-guards are destroyed?!
It's pointless to struggle.
Either you'll be sacrificed,
or you'll have to offer up your
comrades to be sacrificed.
That's Dark Cloud Sacrifice!
I'll tell you just a little
bit about your fated future.
During a match,
this power will make you fall into despair,
lose the will to fight, and be Reversed.
Ludicrous! You speak nonsense!
You get Reversed,
and Aqua Force becomes
subordinate to Link Joker.
Shut your mouth!
Aqua Force equals absolute justice!
They wouldn't give in to anyone!
That line makes me feel nostalgic now.
Fine. Try to fight the certain future.
Stand and draw!
I call Lazarus!
Trans-core Dragon!
Guard!
Twin drive...
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Lazarus!
Intercept!
Is it over already?
Aqua Force, with its
much-prized combo attacks,
is a disgrace.
The wind will blow on you no longer!
Stand and draw.
Diamantes moves.
I call Maelstrom "Reverse"!
Observe.
The Aqua Force taken in by
the power of Link Joker
is the true Aqua Force!
Tidal Assault!
Maelstrom "Reverse"!
This is the end!
Limit Break!
Dark Cloud Sacrifice!
Paschal! Perfect guard!
Twin drive...
Critical trigger.
I give all of the effects
to my rear-guard Maelstrom "Reverse."
Vanish, Lazarus!
Leon!
It's over?
See? Your future is right in front of you!
Quiver in terror!
Guard!
Jet-ski Rider!
Turn end.
You're stripped bare.
You have just one unit,
and no cards in your hand.
Well, your miserable future
is waiting for you...
...Leon Souryu!
I see.
This is where you gave up.
What?!
Stripped of everything, you lost all hope.
You accepted being Reversed.
But I'm different!
How do you have any hope of winning?!
In any case, this is destined to be
over for you during my next turn!
I can't change your past.
But I can change my future!
No, I will change it!
Interesting. Show me, then.
Show me your pathetic resistance!
Stand and draw.
Snowy white, swift wind!
Become a shooting star in the night sky
and come forth!
Tetra-drive Dragon!
Trans-core Dragon's break ride skill!
I add +10000 to Tetra-drive Dragon's power!
As long as my opponent doesn't
discard a unit from his hand,
he can't guard!
And I also gain a critical!
Besides, I'm definitely not alone.
I have friends who entrust
me with the future!
I have comrades who
give me strength!
I also have the hopes
of the Souryu people!
And the sacred wind that
gives me divine protection!
Couldn't you hear it?
Aqua Force's misery...
But that alone can't change the future!
Guard!
Intercept!
Twin drive...
First check...
Second check...
It can't be!
A double critical trigger?!
I'm going to surpass the future!
Together with my comrades!
Farewell, weak self.
This is...
You... Curse you!
If I hadn't given up then...
If I hadn't yielded to
the power of Reverse...
...this future wouldn't have...
Yes.
The wind...
...blew on me...
You... Leon Souryu...
Half of him was used to
bring forth the future Leon.
It seems he took a lot of damage.
Thank you, Leon.
I won't let your fight go to waste.
It's my turn next!
I'm definitely going to beat you!
You little...
You should never have given up.
All paths were closed off,
so I thought only despair was left for me.
Even so, just by believing,
the future opens up.
Faith in friends...
Hope that can't be dashed?
Next time: The One Who Cuts Through Chains!
The One Who Cuts Through Chains
I can't rest here!
But for now, all I can do is entrust
everything to Leon and Takuto...