Miss Emi!
Darn you, Rekka Tatsunagi!
Where did you take Miss Emi?!
Kamui the Great!
No good. We haven't seen her anywhere!
HS, yo!
Sense them... Miss Emi's cries...
Help us, Kamui!
This way!
Kamui the Great!
It's intuition! His animal
instinct has awakened!
AI! I believe in it, yo!
Miss Emi! Miss Mai!
Miss Emi!
Miss Mai!
Kamui the Great!
Kamui the Great, Rekka is friends
with Miss Emi and Miss Mai.
So you don't have to panic.
IBO! It'll be okay, yo!
Idiots!
You guys saw how Gouki
and Nagisa acted while Reversed.
Rekka Tatsunagi...
If she's Reversed,
there's no way she won't do something
terrible to Miss Emi and Miss Mai!
Wait for me, Rekka Tatsunagi!
Miss Emi!
Where am I?
Mai!
Emi?
Mai...
Where are we?
Why are we here?
Emi and Mai, are you two okay?
Rekka?!
Shhh! If you make a fuss, they'll notice.
Did you come to save us?
Hurry up, you guys!
Miss Emi!
Um... Rekka and those
two guys took us away...
Are you awake?
Rekka!
Why are we in here? Let us out!
I can't do that.
You two are precious hostages.
Hostages?
What's wrong, Rekka?!
You got here surprisingly fast.
Did you ditch your friend
for your girlfriend?
G-G-G-Girlfriend?!
Kamui the Great, get a grip!
GG, yo!
Ninja Master Neo is dealing
with Nagisa and the rest!
I mean... We can talk about it later!
Miss Emi!
Yes?
I think she's been Reversed!
Rekka...
...is Reversed?
Rekka Tatsunagi! Let Miss Emi
and Miss Mai go now!
I'll let them go.
That is, if you beat me in a fight.
I was hopin' you'd say that! Let's fight!
Kamui...
Rekka...
Runaway Angel Rekka
Eiji... This could be our
chance to rescue those two.
GI! Good idea, yo!
W-Who the heck are these jerks?
R
We are...
...Rekka's loyal servants!
We love Rekka!
We're Rekka's slaves!
Rekka is our only one!
And our name is...
Rekka
...Rekka Corps!
Rekka Corps?
They're my fans, see, and
they'll do anything for me.
Handy to have around.
Them too?!
I'll let you take care of them!
Leave it to us, Rekka!
Reiji! Eiji!
Kamui the Great! We'll be fine!
KPH! Kamui the Great,
please help Miss Emi and Miss Mai!
I'm countin' on you.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Beast Deity, Riot Horn!
First Aid Celestial, Peniel!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Beast Deity, Riot Horn!
I go first! Draw!
The great Kamui rides Beast Deity, Max Beat!
Riot moves.
Miss Emi... Please hang in there.
I swear I'll save you!
Draw.
Nursing Celestial, Narel!
Rekka's raging fire ride!
Rekka's raging fire ride?
Hey, you! What happened to
your usual "love love ride"?!
"Love love" ride?! What the heck is that?!
That's ultra-lame!
I know!
After you're Reversed, I'm gonna have
you call it your "wild about Rekka ride"!
I'd never say that!
Wild about Rekka ride!
W-What's the deal with these guys?
WD, yo?
Love love for Rekka call!
I'll work you hard until you're just like them:
a lovestruck, moony-eyed mess!
Appreciate their fans...
That's what idols do, don't they?
Is Reversing them and making them your
bodyguards how you show appreciation?
Oh, but they're thrilled to be used by me.
Rekka!
And it's convenient for me...
It's win-win!
I'm sayin' it's a problem
of love... of the heart!
Huh? I thought I was supposed to say that...
O-Okay, then...
Manly spirit!
No, that's not it...
Courage! I'm gonna show you no mercy...
Darn it!
Anyway! I'm gonna show you the
soul of a Vanguard Fighter!
Draw!
The great Kamui rides Beast Deity, Damned Leo!
Call!
Hatred Chaos attacks Narel!
It gets another +3000 power with its skill!
Damned Leo!
No guard.
Trigger check!
Stand trigger.
I give all of the effects to Hatred Chaos!
I use its skill to stand it!
Riot!
Go, Hatred Chaos!
Rise again and again for the sake of justice!
That's a Vanguard fighter's...
...soul!
Have you forgotten something?
With my Angel Feather, even if the
units fall into the Damage Zone,
they're still convenient servants.
Even if they fall into the Damage Zone?
That's right! The Angel Feather
Damage Zone is like a second hand!
Exactly...
Draw.
Emergency Celestial, Daniel.
Rekka's raging fire ride!
Peniel's skill activated.
I put it in the Soul, then superior call
a card that's in the Damage Zone!
Daniel's Counterblast!
Rekka's raging fire superior call!
I call Marking Celestial, Arabhaki!
She's restored her rear-guard
without decreasing her hand!
Rear-guard Daniel attacks!
Guard!
Arabhaki boosts. My Vanguard
Daniel attacks Damned Leo.
No guard!
Ramiel attacks!
Turn end.
This attack is dedicated to Rekka!
I-want-to-see-Rekka-pleased attack!
These guys are strong.
Is it because they're Reversed?
But CAL. We can't afford to lose, yo!
Yeah! If we lose, Kamui the Great
will be on his own in this situation!
We can't let Kamui the Great go it alone!
NGL! We're not gonna lose, yo!
Let's do our best, Eiji.
OC! Of course, yo!
Draw.
Prophecy Celestial, Ramiel.
Rekka's raging fire ride!
I call Sariel.
Counterblast!
I take one card from my deck and put
it in the Angel Feather Damage Zone.
Then I move one face-up card from
my Damage Zone into the Drop Zone.
I call Narel.
With Narel's skill, I move one card
from the Damage Zone to my hand.
She's using the Damage Zone
to set up a combo!
It's far more than a second hand!
Ramiel attacks!
Guard!
Arabhaki boosts! My Vanguard Ramiel attacks!
With her skill, she gets +2000 power!
No guard!
Twin drive...
I got a critical trigger.
I give the power to Sariel and
the extra critical to Ramiel.
Scissors chopper, excellent sharpness!
Darn it!
Hey, who was it that arrogantly said they
were gonna show me a Cardfighter's soul?
Rekka...
Kamui...
Narel boosts. Sariel attacks!
Guard!
Turn end.
I see. It looks like you just
have a fighter's spirit. Right?
Kamui...
If I lose here, Miss Emi and Miss Mai will...
Miss Emi! Miss Mai!
Miss Emi? Miss Mai?
And Reiji and Eiji too...
Reiji! Eiji!
Wait, that's not right...
Kamui the Great...
Reiji! Eiji! Did you win?!
Reiji! Eiji!
It's done, Rekka!
Good job!
We're happy to do anything for you, Rekka!
Reiji...
Eiji...
We're the Rekka Corps!
RC, yo!
No...
Poor baby!
Why, you...!
You're all that's left, Kamui Katsuragi.
And after I beat you, this whole
area is as good as conquered.
Then Emi and Mai will have
to do one more job for me.
With you two as hostages,
Aichi Sendou will undoubtedly come over.
Aichi?!
You mean to Reverse Brother too?!
Oh, please! I wouldn't nearly
be satisfied with that.
After I'm done with Miyaji Academy,
I'm moving on to Hitsue High.
Then all of Japan...
And abroad...
I'll have the whole world
join the Rekka Corps!
Just the idea of the entire world
madly in love with me gives me chills!
The entire world?! She can't be serious...
But with the power of Reversing...
That's right! It'll be a piece of cake.
And it's a wonderful idea, isn't it?
Unforgivable...
It's nonsense. Absolute nonsense!
Excuse me?!
I said it's nonsense!
Using our Vanguard for nonsense like that?!
It's totally unforgivable!
That's being rude to Rekka!
BR, yo!
Shut up!
I apologize!
IA, yo!
How can you have fun doing this?!
This is your school, isn't it?
Everyone here is your friend... your comrade!
Especially Miss Emi and Miss Mai!
That's right! Rekka, wake up!
Stop doing these terrible things!
We're your friends! And so is
everyone else at this school!
Friends?
Friends...
Comrades? School...
Rekka?
What's so funny?!
I'll tell you.
I didn't come to this school
because I wanted to.
Moreover, I have no comrades here.
And I need no friends.
Rekka?
Couldn't you hear me?
I said I don't have any friends.
That's why I'm...
...going to Reverse everyone!
Rekka! Please beat Kamui to a pulp!
BKP, yo!
Y-You guys...
RAR, yo!
Um... I don't know what that means.
Kamui's next opponent is Rekka.
And she's holding Emi and Mai as hostages?!
There must be some explanation for it.
Next time: "Friend"!
Friend
This is unforgivable, Rekka Tatsunagi!
Aren't Miss Emi and Miss Mai your friends?!
Depending on how you answer,
I may wipe the floor with you!