If you can do the impossible,
logic goes by the wayside!
If you can get past pride,
the limit backs off!
That's the way a man lives!
Armor Break Dragon! And
what I'm doin' right now...
Limit Break!
He really is an interesting boy.
The winner of the first match,
from Miyaji Academy, Naoki Ishida!
I did it...
I did it!
I was able to contribute to the team!
Fukuhara High School   Miyaji Academy
It's the final round of the VF High
School Championship, Kanto Block 3.
In the showdown between Fukuhara
High School and Miyaji Academy,
Naoki Ishida had a brilliant win against
Suiko Tatsunagi in the first match.
With this one win, Miyaji Academy
has taken a step toward victory.
Meanwhile, the pressure is
on Fukuhara High School.
Continuing to the second
round, from Miyaji Academy,
we have Vanguard idol and member
of Ultra-rare, Kourin Tatsunagi,
and her opponent from Fukuhara High
School, the Beautiful Assassin of AL4,
the former top team of Team
Asteroid, Asaka Narumi!
Who will win?!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Dreaming Jewel Knight, Tiffany!
Journeying Tone, Willy!
Kourin Love
Do your best, Kourin!
With my support...
...your victory is a trillion
percent guaranteed!
Where do you get that confidence from?
Royal Paladin vs. Pale Moon, huh?
With two strong fighters,
the deciding factor...
...might be the strength of
their feelings for the fight.
Feelings About Victory
I ride Jewel Knight, Prizmy!
Turn end!
I ride Jumping Glenn!
Willy moves back.
Attack!
Turn end.
I ride Dogmatize Jewel Knight, Sybill!
Sybill's Counterblast!
I superior call Stinging
Jewel Knight, Shellie!
I also call Tracie!
I attack Glenn!
2 to 2. Tied up in the
first part of the fight...
Ren... I swear that I'll win this for you.
Good luck, Asaka!
I won't let anyone else have
the honor of serving Ren!
Asaka certainly is fired up, isn't she?
Your greatest misfortune
is having to face me.
Draw.
I ride Nitro Juggler!
Nitro Juggler's skill. Soulcharge...
Dark Metal Bicorn moves back.
I call Mirror Demon and Barking Cerberus.
Cerberus attacks!
Guard!
Nitro Juggler attacks
with a boost from Willy!
No guard!
Drive trigger check.
Heal trigger.
Mirror Demon attacks with
a boost from Bicorn.
Turn end.
4 to 1! How strong is Asaka Narumi?!
There's no way my Kourin
could be this far behind!
It must be a dream! An
illusion! A hallucination!
Aichi...
It'll be okay.
Look.
Are those the eyes of someone who's given up?
Let's have faith and cheer her on.
Yeah!
Cut through the darkness,
light of shining stone!
I ride Pure Heart Jewel Knight, Ashlei!
Call!
My boosted rear-guard Ashlei
attacks Mirror Demon!
My boosted Vanguard Ashlei attacks!
Drive trigger check!
Heal trigger!
She heals 1 damage!
That's what I'm talking about!
Tracie attacks with a boost from Toypugal!
Turn end.
It's 3 to 3! She caught up!
That's the way, Kourin!
She's getting into it...
Heh... I haven't seen
Kourin like this before...
Strange for me to want to win this badly...
I only started my high school
life at Takuto's urging.
I wasn't really interested.
Even with the Cardfight Club, I only
cooperated because Aichi wanted to form it.
Even though that's all there was to it...
...Aichi got me interested
in fighting all over again.
Misaki trusted me to win...
And Naoki, Shingo...
I don't know what a true home is, so I
might get laughed at if I called it "home,"
but this place, where I can be
myself, this is where I want to be.
That's why I can't afford to lose this fight!
That spirit...
You have something you can't give up on.
But I'm the same way. And I'm
going to win... for Ren's sake!
You dance the dance of
corruption and immorality!
I ride Miracle Pop, Ava!
Call! And then Cerberus attacks!
Guard!
In that case, how about this?
Ava attacks with a boost from Willy!
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give +5000 power to my Cerberus
that hasn't attacked yet
and give the extra critical to Ava!
I still have 5 damage...
Willy's skill. He moves to the Soul.
And then I draw one card.
Cerberus attacks your Vanguard with
a boost from Dark Metal Bicorn!
Guard!
She got through it!
Yeah! Now she gets to strike back!
I'm not going to let you win!
Lead me with the steadfast,
unchanging light of determination
that lasts longer than infinity!
Break ride!
Leading Jewel Knight, Salome!
Salome gets +10000 power
and an extra critical!
There it is! Break time!
It's a break ride!
For the Cardfight Club... For everyone...
I'm going to win it right here!
Tiffany's skill. She moves to the Soul,
and I give +3000 power to two rear-guard
units... Ashlei and Shellie!
Salome's Especial Counterblast!
I take one Jewel Knight from
my deck and superior call!
Shellie!
Salome attacks with a boost from Shellie!
Glittering more than gold,
sparkling more than the sun,
silent torrent of fierce light,
now is the time to be unleashed!
Limit Break!
When there are four or more
Jewel Knight rear-guards,
Salome gets +2000 power
and an extra critical!
A break ride, followed by a Limit Break!
Now Kourin will have a great victory!
I guard with Barking Dragon and
Silver Thorn Juggler, Nadia!
Plus, I intercept with two Cerberus units!
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give +5000 power and the
extra critical to Ashlei!
She didn't just guard from her
hand...she also used both intercepts!
Still, this is a chance!
There's still Ashlei with 2 criticals!
Ashlei attacks with a boost from Shellie!
No guard.
It's decided.
5 damage! She's got her on the ropes!
Finish her off, Kourin!
I'm going to put everything
into this one attack.
Tracie attacks with a boost from Toypugal!
Tracie's skill!
When she attacks, if there are three or more
rear-guards with "Jewel Knight" in the name,
she gets +3000 power!
I guard with Nadia and Glenn!
Turn end!
So close!
But her opponent doesn't have
any front-row rear-guards...
And only two cards in her hand...
Yeah. Then next turn...
She may be able to protect herself this turn!
Let's hope!
Kourin...
I'm definitely going to
deliver victory to everyone.
Oh, dear. Do you still think you're winning?
How naive. Your loss is already a done deal.
Draw.
Okay, I'll show you...
...the final act with these two cards.
No matter how hard you struggle, it's
a dream from which you can't wake up.
It's a dance of death that
continues for eternity.
Cry tears of blood and perish in obscurity!
Break ride!
Nightmare Doll, Chelsea!
+10000 is added to Chelsea's
power, and she gets a skill!
Break ride! But...
I call Silver Thorn Barking Dragon!
Here I go.
I'm going to protect myself, no matter what!
Barking Dragon attacks Tracie
with a boost from Bicorn!
Chelsea attacks!
Break ride skill.
I put two rear-guards into the Soul.
Then I superior call two cards from
the Soul, Nitro Juggler and Bicorn!
By switching with units that have already
attacked, she increases the number of attacks!
Perfect guard with Flashing
Jewel Knight, Iseult!
No trigger. If she can just protect
against the next attack...
Our victory...
It's fun watching you struggle in vain.
When you learn the true face behind the
mask, it's the time of destruction!
You should watch this, the last illusion!
Limit Break!
Persona blast!
I superior call two Pale
Moon units from the Soul.
Ava! Glenn!
On top of that, Glenn's skill! +3000 power!
The finale...
Her empty right line has been
filled up with one stroke!
Those two units...
That's right. I held on to
these units in order to win.
The star performers always appear at the end.
Ava attacks with a boost from Glenn.
I don't have enough...
No guard!
I'm not giving up! I can't afford to give up!
For the sake of my teammates,
who believe in my victory...
Everything is riding on...
...this trigger!
The curtain drops.
Please come again.
This victory is proof
of my allegiance to Ren.
Fukuhara High School has
won the second match!
And so, the final round of the VF High
School Championship, Kanto Block 3,
will be decided by a third match!
I'm sorry, Kourin!
My cheering wasn't powerful enough...
Kourin, thank you for moving me!
You've changed, Kourin...
Ren, I won, as promised.
Ren!
I thought she would win. Right, Ren?
Yep.
Thank you, Asaka.
I'm sorry, everyone...
Don't act like such a stiff.
All you did was lose once!
We're all fighting together
here. It's a team competition.
So we'll win it back
together in the next match.
Besides...
...it was a good fight.
Your feelings came through.
If anyone criticized you for a fight
like that, they'd have to answer to me!
Scary... Th-That's right!
I'll win it.
Aichi...
With the feelings that Naoki, Kourin...
...Misaki and Shingo have passed on...
...I'm going to win!
Let's go to the High School Championship.
We're going to fight together.
Aichi...
I'm countin' on you, Aichi!
Aichi!
Sendou!
Kanto Block 3
Final Round
All right, the fateful third match!
From Miyaji Academy, a member of Team Q4,
which won the previous national Vanguard
tournament as well as the Asia Circuit...
Aichi Sendou!
And his opponent, from Fukuhara High School,
the man who led AL4, the
pinnacle of Team Asteroid,
to two national tournament victories
in a row, Ren Suzugamori!
Both of them have triumphed
at the national tournament,
and now they clash here at
the local elimination round!
It's not an overstatement to
call this a duel that'll decide
who the strongest fighter is!
I'm going to win.
And then we'll all go to the High
School Championship together.
What power...
Only we know Ren when he's in that mode.
With apologies to the excited
Aichi and his teammates,
they don't have a chance against him today.
They'll find out about
the true Ren soon enough.
But... I can't lose!
I'm totally tense! I'm even trembling!
But I wanted to see you standing there.
Here it is! Brother Aichi's turn!
Please win, Brother!
Like it or not, this is the final showdown,
and only the winning side gets to
go to the High School Championship!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Stand up the Vanguard!
Wingal Liberator!
Harbinger Revenger, Claudus!
Draw!
I ride Little Liberator, Marron!
Wingal moves back!
I ride Sacrilege Revenger, Berith!
Claudus moves!
We formed this club together from nothing.
Cardfight Club
They all helped me, too.
Kourin... Naoki... Misaki... Shingo...
The way I can express my
gratitude is by winning here.
I started the Cardfight Club, and now
I have to take responsibility and win!
Stand up, my... no, our avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
Aichi, you get stronger at a speed
that stuns everyone around you.
That's exactly why I wanted
to fight seriously with you.
And... I'm going to win!
Envelop everything in darkness, my avatar!
I ride...
...Blaster Dark Revenger!
It's too bad that Kourin didn't win...
Their ability is about the same. After
that, it's just luck of the draw.
That's right! Let's put it behind us and...
Sendou, do your best!
Ren has Shadow Paladin.
I've got to be more careful
than ever before...
Next time: Showdown at the Summit!
I'm going to aim for victory, for the
sake of the friends that fight beside me!
It wouldn't be strange if this fight was the
final one at the High School Championship!
Yeah. Talk about being
on the edge of your seat!