Jillian! Sharlene!
Watch from there.
Yes, Your Imperial Majesty.
As you command.
The loser becomes a subject of the winner.
You see the same thing occurring
in history from time to time.
It's only right. A logical
consequence, don't you agree?
Your power, and Aqua Force too,
are so close to being annihilated.
Won't you become my subject?
Imbecile! Aqua Force
will never be destroyed!
I am the Souryu child!
Leon Souryu's Vanguard is still grade 1.
As opposed to His Imperial Majesty,
with a grade 3 Vanguard.
And Leon's power is 1300.
Even if he rides without any problems,
he still doesn't have a chance.
He should give up hope.
Even his mere two subjects
have abandoned him.
He's like the king of tragedy.
Nah... you can't call one lone
person a king of anything.
I feel sorry for him, but the Souryu
tribe is going to be annihilated...
...by the hand of Mitsusada,
our great Imperial Majesty.
That's right.
I wonder how our two new
members feel about it.
Your expressions are too stiff.
Let yourselves have fun with this!
We pledge our allegiance to you...
...Your Imperial Majesty.
Jillian... Sharlene...
Tight-knit Ship
I stand and draw.
I ride Tear Knight, Lazarus!
Call!
Tidal Assault!
Tear Knight, Lazarus attacks!
No guard.
Check.
I give the power to Tidal Assault
and the extra critical to Lazarus.
Draw trigger.
I give the power to "Reverse" Daiyusha.
Next!
Guard.
Tidal Assault's skill is activated.
Daidriller stands and attacks!
So you're going to ignore
an emperor's mercy?
Aqua Force belongs to the Souryu tribe.
Moreover, I have no intention of
surrendering to your subjects!
Okay. I like it. This makes me
want you as my subject even more.
Why is a fighter who beat
Ren Suzugamori doing this?!
Do you know the expression
"Rome wasn't built in a day"?
What about it?
It took approximately 700 years
for the Roman Empire to be formed.
Makes your head spin, doesn't it?
But with this power, I can
form my empire in a day!
I can force everyone to follow me!
Don't you actually crave it, too?
This power that could rebuild a nation...
I won't misread the wind twice.
I stand and draw.
Assemble, my subjects!
Call!
Limit Break, "Reverse" Daiyusha!
By sacrificing my own subjects,
my opponent loses 10000 power!
Tyrannis Gravity!
Has it hit home just how powerless you are?
But it's not over yet.
It's necessary to punish
those who forget their place.
What do you intend to do?!
These girls are already my faithful subjects.
They'll obey my every order.
That's right. So if I tell
them to give me their decks,
they'll be pleased to hand them over.
You'll be the same way, Leon Souryu!
After you lose this fight,
you'll grovel before me.
I'll relieve you of Aqua Force and
replace it with my Dimension Police.
Wonderful. It's a brilliant idea,
if I do say so myself.
I'm going to destroy Aqua Force!
For eternity!
"Reverse" Daiyusha attacks!
Twin drive check!
Heal trigger!
Glory be to the future of my empire!
"Reverse"... Bow!
Thunder Arrow!
Continue! Daiheart!
Daifighter!
Guard!
Good boy.
I want you to endure for as long as
possible, on the way to meet destruction.
Right, Your Highness?
As befitting a king, even though he's
certain to be annihilated, he's truly tenacious.
Still, he won't be able to put up a fight
against His Imperial Majesty's
"Reverse" Daiyusha's skill.
True, true. And girls don't like
guys who don't know when to quit.
Is that speaking from personal experience?
Talk about getting a dose of reality.
Tch! I'm talking about the
lonely king and his subjects!
I stand and draw!
Wielder of the Demiurge,
arise from the blue sea!
I ride...
Blue Flight Dragon, Trans-core Dragon!
Magnificent! I'm sorry that
I'll have to destroy it. Truly.
Blue Dragon...
Aqua Force...
Give me power!
Call!
Lazarus, attack Daifighter!
Trans-core Dragon, attack!
I'm sorry to put a damper on your history lesson.
But the Souryu tribe's lust for
power nearly destroyed them.
Those who wallow in power
are destroyed by it!
Absurd. The ramblings of
a person who has nothing.
No guard.
Go! Tidal Assault!
Guard.
Huh? Is it over already?
His Imperial Majesty is too strong.
It is hopeless.
I stand and draw.
Even dethroned, you didn't lose your
dignity, but came right at me.
I commend you for that.
But it ends here.
I'm not alone.
Even if I lose this fight,
Jillian and Sharlene are here!
You speak foolishness.
Those two are already my subjects.
The heart of the Souryu clan is the wind.
Wind can't be bound by power!
The wind never stops moving.
Even if thousands of empires crumble!
Even if hundreds of millions of ages pass!
This island has a legend.
It says the Souryu child will take us,
the Souryu tribe, to the free world.
So...
...both of you, smile.
Smile for me, Jillian and Sharlene.
The three of us are Souryu
children. We'll fight together.
Leon!
I'll do my best!
W-What's this wind?!
Is Leon Souryu making this wind blow?!
H-Hey...
I don't believe it!
They're responding to his wind?
Even after we Reversed them?!
This is...
...impossible!
You...
Putting on such an unsightful display in
your final moments befits your hopeless wish!
Call!
Counterblast. Daidragon gets +4000 power!
"Reverse" Daiyusha, Limit Break!
I'll have you taste despair again
and use up all of your power!
Tyrannis Gravity!
Go! "Reverse" Daiyusha!
"Reverse" Bow!
Guard! And I also intercept!
You really don't know when to quit. Check.
Second check...
Double trigger...
Daidragon!
This is painful to watch.
And now for the final blow.
Disappear forever, Aqua Force!
Wind will blow for eternity!
He held on.
It can't be...
That's what you call the "last gasp."
I stand and draw!
Snowy white, swift wind!
Become a shooting star in the night sky!
Break ride!
Blue Wave Dragon, Tetra-drive Dragon!
Because of the break ride
skill, it gets +10000 power!
Also...
...you'll have to put one card in the
Drop Zone before you can guard!
I call Trans-core Dragon.
Counterblast.
One more time.
25000 power without a boost?!
He can't guard.
And on top of that, there's
an extra critical.
His Imperial Majesty will have to
discard a card from his hand!
Trans-core Dragon attacks!
Tetra-drive Dragon!
Twin drive...
I got a critical trigger.
I give all of the effects
to Tetra-drive Dragon!
Tidal Assault!
Its skill lets it stand.
Attack Daiheart!
It's over?
Did he hold out?
No.
It's not over yet...
After four battles are done,
Tetra-drive Dragon stands!
The Souryu child gives an order.
Wind dragon, come back with the wind!
I'll give it to you...
There's no reason to fear
the king of a tiny country!
Twin drive...
I got a critical trigger!
Tetra-drive Dragon, Sacred Storm!
I...
I'm the emperor of a major empire!
The evil power is disappearing...
Wake up from the nightmare
and be reborn again.
Huh? Where am I?
You... You were in the VF Circuit...
Leon Souryu!
That's right! Leon!
Yuri! Chris... Lee... Ali...
What's going on here...?
It seems the only way to turn them back
to normal is to beat them in a fight.
In a fight?
Does that mean... you beat me?
It'll be hard for me alone.
I want to form an alliance with you.
You got it, Souryu guy.
I'm counting on you, Emperor!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Here I go! Super Dimensional Robo...
...Daikaiser!
It's over.
Yeah. I think...
Leon?
Huh?
What in the world were we doing?
Nothing. You just had a bad dream.
Koutei!
Yuri!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Uh... um...
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Mitsusada. You blew it!
It's in there...
Mine was, too!
Thank goodness. Leon gave it to me,
so I'd hate to lose it...
Hey!
Say, Jillian. Let's make a boat for Leon.
Good idea. After all, we're always together.
Right, Leon?
Huh?
Leon!
They're cute!
Hey!
But what are we doing here?
I have no idea either...
I remember coming here to meet you...
Oh, that's right. Where's Gai?
Hey!
Gai!
Sis! Koutei!
Gai! Where have you been all this time?!
Uh... I think that's my line...
Honestly, I can't let you out of my sight!
No, I just wanted to let you two be alone...
Me and Yuri?
W-We weren't! We weren't alone...
You two are hopeless.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Okay, okay. We all got
to meet up in the end...
True.
That's right.
Then let's give a proper welcome.
Welcome home, Your Imperial Majesty!
I came back!
"Welcome home," huh?
Having a place to come
home to is a good thing.
Leon. You have us...
Yeah. That's true.
The wind indicates tomorrow's direction.
Let's walk towards it
together, all three of us.
Right!
Wind courses through forests,
mountains, lakes...
All the students from the high
school division of Miyaji Academy
are on buses, heading for the suburbs!
Next time: Camping Trip!
Camping Trip!
Orienteering, cooking over
a fire... I can't wait!