D-Don't tell me...
They're coming after me directly...
This is the beginning of the end.
I'm going to possess you.
Everything you have will be mine.
Your position, your precious memories...
...and...
Stop it!
I won't let you have them!
Okay, here I go!
Attack!
Vanguard!
The way he looked then...
You're no good.
You.
Fight me.
Me?
Stand up, Vanguard!
You're disappointin' me, Aichi Sendou!
I was lookin' for the strongest Vanguard
fighter, and is this his ability?
Well, whatever. I'll take
down the strongest fighter.
That's my...
That's what I... was ordered to do.
How...? When did I get here?
Darn it! I can't remember!
Is something... something
horrible trying to happen?
If anyone knows the answer to that, it's...
Lock
Please push the room number
that you would like to go to.
We've been waiting for you, Toshiki Kai.
Please go through the door and
into the inner direct elevator.
Welcome.
It's unusual for you to come here.
Where's Takuto?
He's here. This way.
You're not going to ask about it?
This uniform. I like it.
I couldn't care less.
Welcome, Toshiki Kai.
Something wrong?
No.
Anyway, it's been a long time.
What can I do for you today?
There's something I want to ask you.
Please, take your time.
The card he had was...?
A card I'd never seen before.
And right before my eyes...
...it vanished without a trace.
But that's not all.
He lost his memories, too.
And the way he acted during the fight...
Looking at him reminded me of something.
It was...
...similar to the sensation of the
evil force that Leon once displayed.
At the time, he must have
been influenced by Cray.
You know a lot about Cray, don't you?
Do you know anything about this?
Your guess is correct.
The entities called Void are trying to
envelop the planet Cray in darkness.
And they're trying to
begin a new way of battle.
The phenomenon that happened to
Naoki Ishida was only the beginning.
The phenomenon that I call...
...Reverse.
Reverse?!
You lose your own soul, and
your energy becomes Void's.
How does that happen?
It works like this...
One Reverse fighter challenges
a Cardfighter to a battle.
And then, if the fighter
who was challenged loses...
...he too becomes a Reverse fighter.
Where are you going?
To warn Aichi and the others about this.
Please wait a moment.
I'm not done explaining.
Takuto...
It's very convenient that you came to me.
We need strong fighters.
If we succeed here, we'll be able to increase
the number of Reverse fighters even faster.
For example, Aichi Sendou...
Or Ren Suzugamori...
Or even...
...you, Toshiki Kai!
You've been Reversed too?
I...
So annoying.
Please disappear!
You're not just a regular Reverse, are you?
Right now, I'm an ally of Void.
Well, you could also call me a
representative... or an agent...
And Void is searching...
Searching for the first Reverse fighter, the
progenitor from whom everything will begin.
First Reverse fighter...
Toshiki Kai, you're perfect for the role.
Once you're Reversed, you'll understand too.
You'll know how wonderful this
state is, how full of bliss.
I'm not gonna let it happen!
Oh... nothing...
What... What does this
tightness in my chest mean?
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Eradicator, Strike-dagger Dragon!
Star-vader, Dust Tail Unicorn!
What's that unit?!
Surprised, are you? I don't blame you.
This is the first time you've
seen this clan, right?
And you're not the only one.
No one in the world is aware of
the existence of this clan yet.
This entire clan is the avatar of Void.
It's an envoy whose purpose
is to steal the light
from the lives of everything
on Cray and Earth.
A heretic that comes through the
juncture of time and dimension...
The end of an evolution that inherits
a hundred million afternoons and nights,
and casts away imagination...
The destroyer that has
obtained ultimate power...
Its name is...
Link Joker!
A frozen planet that doesn't
know what it means to melt...
A scorching planet that
spews flames for eternity...
A planet with no concept of "moment"
because its time has stopped...
These three planets are the products of
destruction by the hands of Link Joker.
Or perhaps I should say "nothingness"?
A nothingness that brings on destruction.
So targeting Cray and Earth, two planets
that are overflowing with life...
Isn't it only logical?
Link Joker...
The destroyer that has obtained
ultimate power, huh?
Interesting. Just how much power is that?
You'll have to show me!
I ride Red River Dragoon!
Strike-dagger moves!
Call!
Red River!
I ride Star-vader, Mobius Breath Dragon!
Call!
It's like I can pluck the
thoughts right out of your head.
This is what you're thinking.
"Hurry up and show me that
clan's characteristics."
"That way I can get a
good idea of the deck...
...and find a way to beat it."
Isn't that the gist?
I will show you...
The only thing is that... the power they
possess goes beyond what you can imagine.
Now, Mobius Breath Dragon's attack hit!
I'll show you its skill!
Set target on Hisen...
Lock!
What the...?!
What?! My card's turned over?!
What in the world is happening?!
Turn end.
Now it's your turn.
I can't turn it back over?!
This skill continues until
the end of your turn.
What?!
During this time, Hisen stays face down.
It can't boost your Vanguard.
That's "lock."
But a unit that's been locked doesn't
only lose the ability to boost.
Everything is sealed away.
That's right... everything.
Link Joker can use this skill
to bind every possible unit!
I told you it would exceed
what you could imagine.
And Link Joker doesn't only
have an effect on units...
Toshiki Kai!
Before the day is through,
I'm going to bind you!
Talk's cheap. But it's not
gonna be easy for you!
I ride Dragonic Deathscythe!
Counterblast!
Mow down that Star-vader Radon!
Call!
Attack!
No guard.
I got a heal trigger!
I give the power to Zuitan
and heal 1 damage.
Even without having Hisen's boost...
Even with your Lock still in place...
...Dragonic Deathscythe's power...
No... my power won't be bound by that skill!
Continue, Zuitan!
Draw. I give the power to Mobius.
Turn end.
Impressive, Toshiki Kai.
Even while undergoing baptism by "lock,"
you're able to calmly muster power.
Aichi.
Nasty weather... Looks
like it could get rough.
I wonder if it's going to rain.
I just remembered...
that pack you ordered came in.
Oh... thank you very much.
Link Joker...
It doesn't matter who you are.
No one can escape its shackles.
That includes...
...Toshiki Kai. That's right, you.
In the names of the accursed gods,
twine together the monstrous powers
at the end of the universe...
...and push open the door of destruction!
Break ride! Twilight Baron!
Beast of war from another world,
seal the power of all his soldiers!
Break ride skill!
I give +10000 power to Twilight Baron!
And...
Lock!
The target is Hisen...
...and...
Zuitan!
What?!
Two units are locked?!
I'm just getting started.
From here on out, I'm going to subject you
to all of Link Joker's strength and terror!
Link Joker?!
Well, don't you think it's a charming clan?
Yeah. It is interesting.
But I beat any clans that face me!
Unparalleled strength, savage passion...
That's Toshiki Kai, all right.
Until just a little while ago, the
sky was clear, but all of a sudden...
Kai...
Next time: Reverse!
Reverse!
This vague sense of unease is spreading...
"Lock" is going to bind you.
Shut up with that nonsense!