Set target on Hisen...
Lock!
What the...?!
What?!
Two units are locked?!
I'm just getting started.
From here on out, I'm going to subject you
to all of Link Joker's strength and terror!
The lock spell seals all
of a unit's movements.
I told you that already, right?
So your Zuitan can't intercept either.
The only thing you and your units can
do is stand by helplessly as we attack.
Reverse
10000 versus 16000!
The great Kamui guards with
all the cards in his hand!
Yes! As long as he doesn't
draw two triggers...
DDT, yo!
Yep.
Twin drive check...
I got a critical trigger.
SC, yo!
Stay cool. He's still just got one trigger.
Got another.
A draw trigger.
Brother, you've got the magic touch.
It's just luck.
"Luck" is the excuse weak players make.
Brother, you've gotten stronger again, huh?
The way you play now, you'd definitely
beat Ren Suzugamori and that jerk Kai...
More respect for Kai!
MR, yo!
What's this about Kai?
What up?!
Hi, guys.
Miwa, Morikawa, Izaki...
They're upperclassmen!
TU, yo!
Kai isn't here?
He isn't with you?
Nope. I haven't seen him today.
Oh, that's right. Is it true
Kourin didn't go to school today?
Yeah. I think she was probably
busy with work, but...
What the heck?! Why didn't
she text me about it?!
Uh, I don't think she'd even
contact you by mistake...
What was that?
Francium! Attack Dragonic Descendant!
Francium's skill!
How does it feel, not being
able to do anything right now?
When a unit is spellbound, it's as if the
fighter's own hands and legs are tied.
In other words...
"Lock" also has you under its spell.
Twilight Baron! Attack
with a boost from Unicorn!
Toshiki Kai! You're about to get another
taste of pain from Link Joker's spell.
Limit Break!
Perfect guard with Eradicator
Wyvern Guard, Guld!
I sense incredible power
coming from all of his units.
But...
Krypton attacks with a boost from Fermium!
Pollux!
I feel it...
This overwhelming power is coming from there!
You witnessed its strong
presence too, didn't you?
Now that you're locked, you're
connected through the spell...
...directly to Link Joker.
Link... Joker...
What you just saw is an image
of their universal soul.
And... incredible power is released from there.
Have you ever seen anything so powerful?!
I'm sure you haven't.
What if you could wield
such unfathomable power?
It can happen, if you use Link Joker.
I know you.
You're a fighter who seeks strength,
strength greater than any other's.
You value nothing but strength.
You wish to engage in battle with a
fighter who's even stronger than you.
Before Link Joker's power...
...you must be mesmerized!
Nonsense!
True enough, I've been searching for power
and strength that's greater than anyone's.
But you've got one thing wrong!
The kind of power you're
talking about is Link Joker's!
It's not mine!
What I value...
...is the strength that comes from...
...my own power!
I give all of the effects to Twilight Baron.
You already have 5 damage.
With this attack, I'm gonna seal
your and Link Joker's ambitions!
A wasted effort.
You won't be able to obliterate
Link Joker with that level of power.
I got a critical trigger!
Too bad. You don't have enough power.
I'm not done! Descendant, Limit Break!
Counterblast!
With this, it's possible for
Descendant to attack again!
Attack!
I told you. You're just wasting effort.
Twin drive check!
I got a critical trigger!
I give all the effects to Descendant!
One more...
If I get a trigger...
And so your turn ends.
If only your rear-guard Zuitan
or Hisen hadn't been locked,
your total attacking power
would have been much higher.
I might have lost this turn.
In the end, your own power isn't all that.
With what you've got, I doubt you'd fare
well with the kind of fight you're looking for.
What?!
I see everything.
The fight that you desire...
...is one in which you
defeat a strong friend!
For example...
Ren Suzugamori...
Or...
Aichi Sendou...
Shut up!
See? I hit the nail on the head.
Shut up! Shut up!
Ride...
Lock.
Lock!
All of my rear-guards are locked?!
That's right. This is the
limit of your own power.
I'm sure you've actually
known for some time now
that with your current power, Ren Suzugamori
and Aichi Sendou are out of your reach.
Shut your mouth!
Two alternate paths open up for
those who recognize their own limits.
The first path is to do nothing, just
continuing to lose with your weak power.
The other is...
overcoming your current self!
Toshiki Kai!
If you acquire this deck, you'll
be able to surpass yourself.
It will be as if you're reborn.
Which path... do you choose?
Picture it!
Picture yourself using Link Joker
to fight Aichi Sendou!
Kai!
Aichi...
Link Joker!
This is...
...your last chance!
If you let this opportunity slip away,
you'll never beat Aichi Sendou.
But if you ride that unit,
you'll win!
I know.
If I use this, my body
will be filled with power.
The power to be on equal terms...
The power to beat Ren and Aichi!
Strip off your old vestments
and throw them away.
The time to be reborn has come.
To be the one that has surpassed yourself.
Regenerate.
The time to Reverse is here!
This is power.
This is...
Ride!
Lock!
Here I go, Aichi!
Attack!
D-Don't believe it...
Why did I choose power and
strength... that's not mine?!
The only things of value are
your own power and strength.
You had faith in that, huh?
And just now, you murdered that
faith with your own hands.
But that doesn't mean you've fallen.
You've been reborn anew, into an existence
surpassing the previous one.
So, on the contrary, it's...
...something to be celebrated.
Hello.
Welcome.
Aichi!
Yo!
Aichi, do me a favor and
fight Morikawa, willya?
Yeah, this guy hasn't let either
of us relax for a minute!
Hey!
Kai hasn't come today either, huh?
Nope. We haven't seen him at school either.
Maybe he's traveling again,
to train, or so he claims...
Kai's one thing, but the
real issue here is Kourin!
Has she been back to school since that day?
We got a call from Takuto about her.
He said she's really busy with her idol work,
so she'll be on a leave
of absence for a while.
Oh, is that what it is?
It's the same thing with Rekka.
I was worried about her!
That's a relief, huh, Morikawa?
Kourin!
There's nothing to worry about.
I know that...
...but why won't this vague
sense of foreboding disappear?
It's unusual for you to visit here.
But your timing's off.
Ren happens to be out at the moment.
Do you want to wait until he comes back?
I came to battle a strong fighter.
Are you strong?
In other words, I'll do as an opponent?
It's been a long time since we've fought.
I've gotten better, you know.
And I've got new power.
Oh? Did you get a new
Narukami unit or something?
This should be a fun fight.
Ready?
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
With this power, I can
beat Ren, and Aichi too?
That's right. You're the only
one who can master Link Joker.
So you're saying this clan
appeared so it could meet me?
I had no idea that while we were playing
Cardfight, something terrible was happening.
Next time: The Power of the Black Ring!
The Power of the Black Ring!
Link Joker is silently but
surely spreading that power...
I've obtained a mighty power!
Yes. It was inevitable.