Link Joker's ambition has failed.
I'm sure there will be
peace for the time being.
I'm profoundly grateful to you all.
You...
Takuto!
The time has come for us to part.
Let me go!
I won't let go.
We're going together.
No!!
It's over...
To think that the opponent I was
really seeking was right here...
Kai...
Kai and Aichi...
Just those two...
I see... Aichi must've beaten Takuto.
And that set me free from Reverse...
Well, I guess I can't butt in on this fight.
Ren!
Uh oh! This building is dangerous to be in!
Everyone, get outside!
Hurry up! Everybody, withdraw!
Don't leave anyone behind!
Hurry!
The Intersecting Path
Kourin! Leon!
And Misaki too!
What's happening?
Takuto disappeared from this world.
Link Joker's power had spread
across the entire Earth.
He's trying to erase it forever.
He's gone...
Then our memories will vanish too, soon...
...along with that ring.
Hey! Brother and Kai ain't here!
Those two... are still up there.
They're going to fight.
You were freed from being Reversed
after Link Joker's power
disappeared from Earth, right?
Don't tell me Kai is the only one
whose Reverse hasn't been nullified?!
Kai's Reverse is also undone.
Or, to be more precise, it's being undone.
Then why...?
It's not totally undone yet.
As someone who sought to be the strongest,
Kai couldn't bear not
challenging Aichi to a fight.
Before his power disappears,
Kai wants to test it out.
To see whether the path he chose to becoming
the strongest was the real thing or not.
Picture it.
The path you walked on to get here!
After meeting with you again,
I aimed to become the best fighter in Japan.
After splitting away from you, I sought to
become the strongest fighter in the world.
For the sake of my own strength,
I set foot into the darkness.
I obtained the power of Link Joker.
But you overcame the fear of death
and became stronger, strong enough to defeat
the false Takuto, who I intended to beat.
The two separate paths that we've believed in
to progress have now intersected.
The time to fight has come.
Link Joker is vanishing within me.
So this deck will vanish soon.
If I don't fight you now,
when you're the strongest,
accepting this power
will have been for nothing.
Kai...
You said you intended to beat Takuto, right?
Yeah. I never let Link Joker's
reach extend as far as my heart.
I was always myself.
Then you fought me and everyone...
...beat and Reversed us...
of your own free will?!
That's right.
Reversing everyone...
That was absolutely the wrong thing to do!
I'm aware of that.
What I did was unforgivable.
I'll bear the burden of this sin
for the rest of my life.
Why did you accept Link Joker
in the first place?!
You weren't even being controlled...
Why?!
I was seduced by the prospect of becoming
strong... of becoming the strongest...
That's my weakness. My sin.
I sold my soul to Link Joker.
Even as I sensed that it was an evil
entity, I gave in to temptation.
The experience I gained
fighting became my own power.
In order to get stronger,
I didn't care who got Reversed.
Even if they were my former comrades...
Even you...
So in that sense, I was being controlled.
Controlled by my own desire, strength...
Kai!
I know.
Even though Earth has been saved,
my sin hasn't disappeared.
A demon inhabits my heart.
If another such opportunity
happened to come my way,
I'm sure I would
choose the same path.
Even if it hurt you guys
and endangered Earth again...
...I'm pretty sure I would...
Getting stronger, no matter what...
That's the nature of a Vanguard fighter.
The only thing that I can't stop...
...is this desire.
I'll bear the burden of this sin
for the rest of my life.
I have to punish myself.
To seek strength, one must become isolated.
Only one person can stand
at the pinnacle of victory.
To arrive at that point, I have to
beat everyone, no matter who they are.
I will beat everyone around me.
That's the only path that will take me
to what I seek: being the strongest.
My presence would only hurt you more.
I'm going to disappear...
...from your lives...
...forever.
Disappear?!
So you mean for this fight to be our last?
Only a fighter can understand
another fighter.
Stand up...
...the...
...Vanguard!
It's started...
The fight in which their very
existences are on the line.
Red Pulse Dracokid.
Liberator, Cheer Up Trumpeter!
The Gold Paladin deck that beat Takuto...
The Kagero Reverse deck that defeated me...
A clash between the two strongest decks...
Here I go!
I ride...
...Dragon Monk, Gojo!
...Little Liberator, Marron!
I call May Rain Liberator, Bruno!
Attack!
Turn end!
I ride...
...Dragon Knight, Nehalem!
Call!
Burning Horn Dragon and Dragonic Burnout!
Burnout's Soulblast.
Bruno, retire!
Attack!
Turn end.
Kai, you're my idol.
Your strength never wavers.
It's because you pushed your way down
the path that you believe in...
That you carved it out for yourself, without
taking it easy, even in the face of adversity.
In order to become strong...
If I hadn't met you,
I wouldn't be what I am today!
My world expanded because you
introduced me to Vanguard.
Through Vanguard, I've been
able to meet many people.
For the first time, I made friends
I can also call comrades.
You taught us how to picture things
and go beyond our limits.
I was able to change myself...
...because you were there!
I was able to become strong!
The bond that ties us together...
It all started here.
And so it will continue...
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride...
...Blaster Blade!
Counterblast!
Blaster Blade...
Truly, your avatar...
Or the unrivaled existence
that one could say is you.
Blaster Blade attacks Nehalem.
Guard!
Drive trigger check.
Heal trigger!
I give +5000 power to Phallon
and heal 1 damage point.
Phallon attacks with a boost from Zolon!
That's right. Without you,
the current me wouldn't exist, Kai.
Kai, you're the one person I idolize,
want to catch up to, and want to surpass!
You're the one!
I'm a fool who was seduced by strength
and couldn't help but pursue it.
I don't deserve to be idolized by you.
When I saw you and Ren fight, I wanted
to become strong enough to fight you.
And then Link Joker appeared...
I sensed that it was evil,
but that feeling was drowned out
by thoughts of wanting to beat you
and become the strongest.
This fight is my farewell to you.
This is my true form!
The apocalyptic flames that reduce
everything in this world to ashes!
Ride the Vanguard!
Dragonic Overlord!
Phallon attacks your Vanguard!
Guard!
Overlord attacks!
I check the drive trigger!
I got a critical trigger.
I give +5000 power to Nehalem and
the extra critical to Overlord.
Damage trigger check!
Heal trigger!
I give +5000 power to Blaster Blade
and heal 1 damage point!
Nehalem attacks!
Guard!
Turn end.
Overlord, eh? Kai's serious!
Indeed.
Although I've never seen
Kai anything other than serious...
I can't see it from here, but I
suspect Aichi is using Blaster Blade.
Aichi...
Kourin...
Darn it! I hate to say it,
but I wanna see that fight up close!
Agreed.
Were it not for these circumstances,
it would be a perfect opportunity.
It's unfortunate.
Are you going to hurt me?
Is that why you're going to disappear?
That's...
That's a mistake!
I'm not fighting you to say goodbye, Kai.
I want you to understand
that you're not alone!
May your noble power rain down
and become the world's bond!
I ride...
...Liberator of Bonds, Gancelot Zenith!
I swear by this sword that
I'll prove it to you!
Call!
Marron attacks your Vanguard!
Guard!
Gancelot attacks!
Phallon attacks with a boost from Zoron!
Guard!
Turn end!
Aichi...
This is my last ride!
Be resurrected in the flames of purgatory
that reduce everything to ashes!
Be reborn!
Strongest dark dragon of fire!
Crossbreak ride!
Dragonic Overlord the "Reverse"!
This will bring everything to an end.
Our relationship... and everything else...
Kai...
Just watch, Aichi!
The power I was searching for is here!
Overlord "Reverse"...
The embodiment of sinister power...
A unit like that is your avatar, Kai?!
I've gone beyond what's right...
...in order to defeat you!
I understand, Kai.
But I don't accept the end of everything!
Next time: The Connected!
The Connected
I'm going to bring you back
to the right path!
Farewell, Aichi!