Come to think of it,
today's the day, isn't it?
Yeah. The plane should be
getting in any time now.
We haven't seen Mitsusada in a long time.
Are you talking about Kenji Mitsusada?!
Who's that?
Sheesh... this is why you're
like a juvenile delinquent!
'Scuse me?!
Kenji Mitsusada is a legendary fighter
who's even beaten Ren Suzugamori.
He's also called "Emperor" Koutei.
"Emperor"? Sounds like a
guy who's full of himself.
Mitsusada's actually a really nice guy.
Even though they call him the "Emperor"?
I understand your feelings
of doubt, but in the end,
I think it's best to go
with the clan you like.
Really?
You'll be fine. That's a good deck.
Thank you, bro!
"Bro," huh? In Singapore,
I was "the old man."
What... is that?
Pardon me!
A dream?
What was that just now?
We'll be arriving at the
airport in just a moment.
Please fasten your seat belts.
You aren't at the airport yet?
Sorry, Koutei!
We're close, but the traffic
is crazy over here...
It looks like we won't
be arriving anytime soon.
I see. Well, you can't
change the traffic.
Although if we'd left
the house on time,
we probably would've been able
to avoid the traffic jam.
But you took forever to get ready, Sis.
Yuri?
Ow!
Anyway, it won't be too long.
I'm anxious to see what SIT
taught you. Hurry and show me!
So let's fight right away!
That way I can find out what
you learned in one shot, right?
You're as impatient as always.
But sure, I'll show you.
I held fight after fight, doing research
and analysis every single day.
I didn't have a single day off.
So I'll show you the result
of my accumulated efforts.
Cosmo Beak
I think it'll be more difficult for
you to beat me than before.
Oh...?
Eh? What?
You've changed a little, Koutei.
Your voice is full of confidence.
R-Really?
It makes me look forward to
meeting up with you all the more.
Well, see you later.
Yeah.
Kai? Well, if it isn't Kai!
Hey, long time no see!
Huh? Have you come here to meet me, too?
Kai?
Are you strong?
I see. He wants me to show
him what I've learned at SIT.
If we fight, I think you'll
get a good picture.
Daiyusha Falls
Hey, we're not moving at all here.
Even though we can see the airport...
Maybe it'd be faster to walk from here.
You're right. Shall we?
Driver, we're getting off here.
Huh? Uh... sure.
Come on, we're getting out.
Ow! Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
What's wrong?
Urgh! My leg suddenly hurts!
Come to think of it, I bumped my
knee when we got into the taxi.
It must be from that...
It didn't hurt then?
A-Anyway, you should go, Sis!
Are you sure it's okay?
Koutei is waiting. You're eager
to see him, aren't you?
N-Not especially...
Go on, get going!
Y-You're right. It wouldn't
be nice to keep him waiting...
See you later!
Have to give them some time
alone on an occasion like this.
Sounds like you've got it rough, sir.
Yeah, well, those two are exasperating.
This is just like you, Kai.
As before, you fight like a ferocious dragon.
If anything, those claws are even sharper.
Even having changed your clan...
But the emperor who commands many subjects
has also improved with the power of justice!
I'll show you! A righteous
spirit is everlasting!
Burn even brighter!
I ride Ultimate Dimensional
Robo, Great Daiyusha!
Take the great sword of justice!
Special attack!
Burning Justice Heart!
It seems you've learned a
few things studying abroad.
You're stronger than before.
And that strength is what
I've been looking for!
Nebula Lord Dragon!
Moebius Operation!
Whoa! What a cutie!
I'm gonna approach that girl...
Cut it out!
You didn't come here to hit on girls.
We're here to meet Mitsusada.
Don't be such a stiff.
Not bad.
Chris?
Not that. I'm talking about the fight space.
I'm thinking I could
fight Mitsusada right away.
What, right here?
At SIT, our fight grades
were about the same.
So I'm anxious to see who's
stronger once and for all.
Though, of course, he's no match for me!
A decisive fight between Mitsusada and Chris Lo,
who made it to the Asia Circuit finals?
That could be a major event on its own,
but to hold it here, on the down-low...
Yeah!
That makes it sound even more fun.
Excuse me.
You're Chris, Lee, and Ali
from Team Genius, aren't you?
Yeah...
Lounge space?
Yes. He's waiting for you here.
It's hard for civvies to get
into a place like this.
What the heck's a civvy?
I don't really know myself...
He's waiting over there.
A fight table?!
There he is!
What the heck, Mitsusada?! We were
waiting for you in the lobby.
It looks like you and
Chris had the same idea.
Nothing wrong with that.
This is just what I wanted.
Are you... strong?
You must be really confident to ask me that.
This way, I get to see firsthand
how much you've grown at SIT.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Give me all you've got, Mitsusada.
Geograph Giant attacks!
Guard.
Turn end.
Mitsusada has 4 damage.
Chris has 3. It's really heating up.
Mitsusada certainly has gotten stronger.
Still, he doesn't seem like... his usual self.
This is just like you, Chris.
Like a wild beast, you
zero in on my key points.
It's an honor to be complimented by you.
However, before the mighty Emperor,
a beast is no more than prey to be hunted.
Mitsusada!
What are you saying?!
Now, let's start to have some fun.
Fun hunting, that is...
I'll show you the grand power of the Emperor!
What?!
What...
...the heck?!
Everlasting flames of hell!
Burn to ashes all my
enemies who defy justice!
Ride!
Super Dimensional Robo, "Reverse" Daiyusha!
"Reverse" Daiyusha?
Daitiger moves. I call Daifighter.
And then, mighty Limit Break!
My subject, Daitiger!
In order to end this just war
successfully, sacrifice yourself!
Daimagnum, you too!
With this, I'm able to steal the
power of Extraordinary Dr. Noir!
What?!
Now its power is just down to 1000?!
What is that Limit Break?!
By sacrificing my subjects, I can
reduce the enemy's power by 10000.
"Reverse" Daiyusha's Tyrannus Gravity!
You used to be strong.
But with the way I am now, you don't even
have the strength of a common soldier.
The time has come for the mighty Emperor
to rise and render a verdict of justice.
I decree that the weak shall be destroyed!
Go, Daifighter!
Guard!
Then I shall order my hero.
You're about to witness terror, Christopher Lo!
"Reverse" Daiyusha attacks!
Twin drive...
I give the power to my subject,
and the critical to my hero!
I don't believe it...
How can he fight back with only 1000 power?
As I act in the name of justice, I couldn't
care less if I'm called a tyrant.
I shall entrust my deeds
to the judgment of history!
"Reverse" Daiyusha! Consume everything
with your flames of judgment!
Judgment Flame!
Go, Daidragon!
I... I won't let you! Guard!
Turn end.
Chris...
What kind of skill is that?
I've never seen it before!
It's strange.
Mitsusada always used to respect his
opponents, no matter who they were.
But now he's like a self-righteous tyrant.
He didn't get this strength from SIT.
What in the world...?
But wait... that stuff is supposed to be over.
What's wrong, Christopher?
Are you so fearful of my strength that
you've even lost the will to fight back?
Just wait! I'll beat you this turn!
Run through the darkness,
slashing everything!
Break ride!
School Hunter, Leo-pald!
My Great Nature won't become
the prey of your hunt!
Just the opposite! I'll hunt you!
Break ride skill!
By using the skills of these units,
I can turn my rear-guard
into the ultimate beast!
Attack! Leo-pald's skill!
Guard!
Check.
Critical trigger!
I give all the effects to
my rear-guard Leo-pald!
That Leo-pald is building up power!
Attack!
Skill activated!
Yes! Just 1 more damage!
My rear-guard Leo-pald
attacks! Skill activated!
This is the birth of the ultimate beast!
Go, Leo-pald!
You won't be able to withstand
this much power from Leo-pald!
You're the one that's gonna
be hunted down, Mitsusada!
Fool...
Even if a beast sharpens its fangs,
it can't do the slightest damage
to the power of an emperor!
Daishield!
P...
Perfect guard!
Call.
It looks like you're the one
to be hunted down after all.
"Reverse" Daiyusha!
Limit Break!
0 power!
He really isn't the same guy he was before!
I finally realized it.
"Justice" is the strength
to destroy your opponents.
I'm going to thoroughly crush
you with overwhelming power.
Just like a tyrant from ancient Rome.
That is the manifestation of my justice!
And I want to put this justice
into practice more and more.
I want to share it with many people...
Chris...
True justice will invariably win!
Judgment... flame!
Chris!
Stop it!
I won't be possessed again!
I'm not the person I was then!
Lee... Ali... I...
S-Stop it!
It's different...
Similar, but different from last time...
A lovely sight, no matter
how many times I see it.
And I'm going to be able
to see it more and more.
I kept Koutei waiting so long...
Over there, I bet.
The Genius team...
I've been waiting for you, Yuri.
Koutei!
Are you strong?
Koutei...?
Say, how many hours is it to New York?
12 or 13, I believe.
That long?
What happened to Kenji Mitsusada,
the fighter I respect the most in this world?!
Yuri, come with me.
I'll show you a new world.
A world ruled by perfect justice!
Yuri! Please be careful!
Right now, Mitsusada isn't
the Mitsusada that you know!
Next time: Yuri's Medal!
Yuri's Medal!
My justice will defeat your justice!
Yuri... that's enough.
Don't waste the effort.