We finally made it!
Nice scenery!
Welcome to our school's traditional
camping trip, everyone.
Get away from the hustle and bustle
of the city, connect with nature,
take a good, sincere look at yourself, and
raise your global spirit and sensitivity.
The program for the first
day is global orienteering.
After dinner, there will be a lecture on
globalism presented by the Student Council,
so please show up for that.
So? What the heck is this
global orienteering, anyway?
Orienteering is a kind of competitive sport
in which you go through a course, as instructed,
by using a map and compass
within a set time limit.
Apparently, it first started in Sweden
around the middle of the 19th century.
Very impressive, Shingo. You
sure know a lot about it!
Never mind the trivia.
The point is, it's like real,
three-dimensional Parcheesi, right?
Crude as usual...
All of the instructions
are written in English.
So that's how it's "global"!
You think?
Um... The first point is...
It looks like they're having
trouble from the get-go.
For people who spend all of
their time playing card games,
our school's tradition of global
orienteering will be very difficult.
They won't be able to
return in time for dinner,
will become laughingstocks in
front of the entire student body,
and the reputation of the
Cardfight Club will plummet.
I can't wait.
Ah! Kourin!
You're late, Kourin.
Sorry.
That makes all of us.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
Camping Trip
This path!
You're so cool, Sendou!
The next point is 45 degrees
northwest of here: a banyan tree.
This isn't Okinawa, is it?
Huh?
Instead of going down this path, it seems
like taking this fork would be faster...
But how much time did the previous ones take?
This path took us about 15 minutes.
And this one was about 25 minutes.
Just as I'd expect from you, Misaki!
So if we do take the fork,
we'll get there faster, right?
We've got just a little ways to go.
Let's do our best, everyone!
Yeah!
It looks like a spirit might live in this tree...
All right! This makes our second one!
Yeah!
Aichi makes a great leader, huh?
I always thought he was a quiet kid.
Yeah. He used to be like that,
but after participating in
various tournaments, he's grown.
Huh. Both of you seem to
be keeping an eye on Aichi.
That's because we're on the same team,
so we hang around each other.
The next checkpoint is a lake.
Aren't you tired, Granny Glasses?
I've gained stamina thanks to a would-be
delinquent, so this is a piece of cake.
No idea what you mean.
A lake!
It's so big!
It's picturesque!
The breeze coming off the
lake feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah!
Say, this could be that lake!
The one with the legendary tree.
Legendary tree?
It's a story passed down to each
generation at Miyaji Academy.
During the second night of the
camping trip, during the campfire...
If two people will share their feelings for each
other under a large tree next to the lake,
they'll be together forever!
You don't know the legend?!
This is the first I've heard of it.
I wonder if it'll happen to
someone this time...
My heart's pounding already!
Legendary tree...
Together forever... Two people...
Next up is a cave.
Then we get to go spelunking!
They're like a curtain of icicles!
It's totally beautiful!
Incredible!
Romantic!
A little creepy...
Beautiful!
Um... the checkpoint is...
...I guess deeper inside?
Aichi. Um...
Aichi! I found the checkpoint!
Come quickly!
Ah...
Okay!
What's wrong?
Don't you feel well?
No... I'm fine...
Well, don't overexert yourself.
It seems like you've been really
busy with work these days.
Yeah.
That makes all of them!
"Trust in luck, but perform
great deeds yourself!"
No, no. Here, it's more natural to say,
"Where there's a will, there's a way."
All right, all right. Proverbs aside,
the sun is setting!
Let's hurry up and get back to the lodge.
Seconded!
Miyaji Academy
We're back! Please put the final seal here.
You did very well. Your group
is the first to finish.
First?!
Shoot! Another group beat us to it!
Hey! It's the Cardfight Club!
How?
I don't believe it!
They're pretty good...
Really!
I'm seeing them in a new light.
We're first...
It's all thanks to your leadership, Sendou.
You should show a little more pride!
Yay! We're the masters of Miyaji at last!
Cut it out, you delinquent!
That's too arrogant!
Good for you, Aichi.
Th-Thanks...
Hey, Suwabe! What's the meaning of this?
The Cardfight Club's reputation is improving!
B-But after dinner tonight, you're
giving a lecture on globalism.
I think you'll be able to win back the
hearts and minds of the students then.
That's right.
"The people are your castle.
The people are your stone walls."
I'll show them that the people obey
the authority of the Student Council!
I don't think the expression
really means that.
Excuse me?
Nothing, nothing!
I think the students should be finishing
up their supper around now, don't you?
Yes, indeed.
We'll give the students at our academy an
enlightening lecture on just what globalism is.
We passed out a lot of flyers too,
so I'm sure it'll be a full house.
High School Championship
National Tournament Finals
At last, our main event is gonna start!
I can't wait to see what kinda
matches they're gonna be!
Still, to think we're the
only ones who understand
how wonderful the High
School Championship is...
It's as if everybody else at our school
is possessed by the ghost of wastefulness.
That's not true!
W-What do you want?!
We're here to watch it too.
It's an important event.
Let's Vanguard!
Yeah!
We're watching the match from right here.
Formation: Sit down!
Yeah!
What the...
Great! I'm happy to be able
to watch it with a big group.
We're crashing this party too.
S-Sure. You're welcome here.
Um...
Who are those guys?
No clue...
Come to think of it, what happened to Kourin?
It's startin'! Aw, man... I'm all nervous!
Now, all that's left of the finals
is the last match between
the leaders of both teams!
It's starting!
Ren Suzugamori versus Leon Souryu!
We couldn't miss this showdown!
Totally right!
VF High School Championship Stadium
Right now, both schools
have one win and one loss.
Which one will win in the end?!
It's s-o exciting!
Good luck, Leon!
Ren!
Win for Fukuhara High School!
Fukuhara! Fukuhara!
I vow to make this a fight worthy
of the final match.
I'm looking forward to it.
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
The competition in this match is fierce,
with the damage currently at 5 to 5!
Souryu just completed his fourth attack
by using the power of Aqua Force.
Tetra-drive Dragon's skill activates!
Rise again, my Vanguard!
Oh my! Souryu!
The stand ability granted to him by the
Limit Break from earlier is activated!
Experience it again.
Tetra-drive Dragon attacks!
Attack number five!
And because of Trans-core
Dragon's break ride skill,
Suzugamori is forced to choose whether
to discard a card from his hand or not.
Trans-core Dragon...
That's the power that led
us to the correct path.
The real thing...
Yeah. The real thing.
Captain, what is the skill
of that dragon exactly?
If you don't discard a card from your hand,
Tetra-drive Dragon gets an extra critical,
and you can't even guard against it.
Strong!
What is this?
Is there a party?
What's this gathering about?
Baseball?
Gotta be soccer.
The Cardfight Club is watching it, so...
...a Vanguard match?
As expected of you, Leon Souryu.
But I can't afford to lose,
so I discard one card.
And then...
...perfect guard.
Drive check.
Unbelievable!
Suzugamori has held out against Aqua Force's
multi-stage attack, its fifth attack!
Awesome! That's the captain
of Fukuhara's team for ya!
It's a fight that's full of highlights!
Yeah!
My right arm aches.
It wants to borrow power from the wind!
Call!
I think it's about time for
me to move in for the kill.
Skill activated!
Superior call.
And then another skill activates!
Tartu attacks!
Guard!
Raging Form Dragon!
Paschal!
Perfect guard!
Twin drive...
You've used up all the cards in your hand,
and have held out all this time.
As I'd expect.
But I'm going to win it here.
Raging Form Dragon's Limit Break!
On top of that, you should tremble
with fear before its rage!
Superior persona ride!
Victory is ours.
Twin drive...
It's over!
Suzugamori defeated Souryu, and
Fukuhara High School is the winner!
It was a w-o-nderful fight!
My heart's still pounding!
That was the first fight in a long
time that I've sincerely enjoyed.
I'm grateful.
It was fun for me too.
Recently, the wind has been acting strange.
You've noticed the abnormal
phenomenon too, then.
Yes. But I don't intend
to be swallowed up by it.
No matter what kind of storm
comes from here on out...
Yes. We feel the same way.
What are those two talkin' about?
What if they're just shooting
the breeze about the weather?
That ain't funny.
Oh! The awards ceremony!
High school Cardfighters!
Thank you for moving us!
And thank you for those magnificent battles!
That was an awesome match!
It really was.
That was so exciting!
I underestimated Vanguard!
When we get home, let's buy a trial deck!
Yeah! It seems like it
wouldn't take long to start.
What is this?
They've finally recognized
the appeal of Vanguard.
Everyone!
The rules seem pretty simple.
And I get the feeling you can sort of
learn how to do it just by watching!
He lost, but what a marvelous wind.
The real thing...
Yeah. The real thing.
Let's use this moving moment to
inspire us during training!
Yeah!
Hey, you guys must be aiming for that
High School Championship too, right?
Good luck next time!
We'll be there to cheer you on!
Yeah. Thank you!
I'll do my best!
You're always welcome to fight us!
We'll be waiting!
Girls can do it too, right?
Yes. We'd be happy to have you.
What the devil is going on here?
I wondered why no one showed
up for the lecture...
Things can't keep going like this!
Student Council President Naitou
Vice President Suwabe
Suwabe! Get that out!
Yes, sir.
I prepared a global deck
just for you, President.
I never thought it would come to this.
This is training, Suwabe! We're going
to crush them with our own hands!
Yes, President.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Even though we were only watchin',
that took a lot outta me.
I could've seen either one of them
winning. It was a great match.
When we get back home, I'm going to
study by watching it again on DVR.
Nah, let's recreate that fight right now!
Ooh! That's a good idea!
I'll go along with that!
Yeah, me too!
I'm gettin' psyched!
It's not physically possible, but my
blood is tingling with excitement!
Aichi.
Oh... Kourin!
What is it, Kourin? I bet you wanna
get in on the training too, huh?
Training?
We were just talking about how we're
going to hold a passionate fight,
just like Ren Suzugamori
versus Leon Souryu!
Oh. Then never mind.
What's with her?
Is she in a bad mood?
She's probably tired. Not used to
hiking around in the mountains...
Yeah.
2-C Tokura
2-C Yotsue
You're looking outside again.
Is the moon over the lake
really all that romantic?
Yeah. So unbearably romantic!
I hope it's another nice day tomorrow.
I wanna see a campfire, and I keep
thinking about the legend of the lake!
Right, Misaki?
You're back to that again?
Ah... I just can't wait!
Is something wrong?
No, it's fine.
I swear I'll stand on the winners' podium!
I'll win, and become Japan's most
passionate Vanguard fighter!
Yeah. Let's do our best.
I can't see that as any more
than a dream of yours, Ishida...
Well, you're full of dreams and
dreams and dreams.
Wha...?! What do you mean by that?
"Full of dreams"?!
How rude!
Yeesh. I'm going to sleep.
Let's all do our best.
Yeah.
I will.
Let's go there for sure... for sure...
Yeah.
Right.
For sure... for sure... for sure...
Right...
The final match today was truly amazing.
I want to stand up there on
the stage with everyone.
I'll turn this club into an A-1 team,
and win with everyone.
Tomorrow for sure...
The VF High School Championship
final match was awesome!
It sure was! I'm still so
excited that I can't sleep!
Next time, let's go there ourselves!
That reminds me, Aichi. Don't you
think Kourin's been actin' strange?
Yeah. Maybe she's just tired...
Next time: Under the Starry Sky...
Under the Starry Sky...
She's both an idol and a student.
I can't imagine how tough
that must be, you know?
Hey, the delinquent's fast asleep!
Whaz goin' on?! ...Why'd ya wake me...