Good morning.
Kourin...
Morning!
Oh! Good morning, Kourin.
Would you stop being so formal with me?
We're in the same class.
Uh... right...
That Sendou guy is so lucky...
Let's try talking to Kourin, too!
'Sup?! You two are here early!
Morning, Naoki!
Morning!
Ack... Ishida!
How did he get so chummy with them?
Let me borrow your eraser.
Sendou aside, with Ishida around...
Sure.
...Kourin's getting farther and farther away!
Vanguard Monthly
I wanna talk to you, too...
Aichi, I changed my first Vanguard.
And I tried puttin' in
all kinds of cards, too.
I'm sure that, by trying all
kinds of things like that,
you'll eventually hit on the deck
that's perfect for you. Right?
That's right.
Yep. That's what I figured.
Am I a natural or what?
Sendou, please!
Teach us about Vanguard... um...
Specifically, the secret attacks
we need to beat Kourin!
Secret attacks...?
We're begging you!
So, like this, you ride and then attack.
If you put in more critical triggers,
it'll give you an attack-centered
deck that easily delivers damage.
Thank you! Now we'll be able to
enjoy club life with Kourin, too!
We lost!
Our club life with Kourin...
She wiped the floor with them again...
Well, they are just learning how to play...
Quit teaching all of these people!
It's Vanguard, so I just couldn't refuse...
Jeez...
I didn't come to this school so I could
be in a club with guys hitting on me.
Come to think of it, why did you
transfer to this school, Kourin?
And using "Tatsunagi" as your last name...
Oh, that...
It was Takuto's idea.
He's doing a lot to help me right now.
With the Circuit over, he
recommended going to school.
Huh...
Right there...
What's wrong?
It felt like someone was
staring at me just now!
Nobody else is here.
Since you're an idol,
it's probably a stalker.
Don't even bring up the idea of a stalker!
If you got a weirdo givin'
you trouble, let me know.
I'll take him outta commission!
Violence isn't the answer.
I'd just give him a little beat-down!
That's still no good!
Yeah, fine...
But seriously, tell me if
there is that kinda guy.
Who does that Ishida think he is?!
Targeted Idol
Hey, did you hear?
That idol girl one year below
us joined some Cardfight club.
Cardfight?
Isn't that Vanguard?
There's a really strong player
in the same class as Kourin.
Right, Misaki?
Yeah. That's right.
Huh. So Misaki knows him...
But rumor has it that the boy formed
the club to get close to Kourin.
Is the rumor true?
That's low! Making a club so
he can get cozy with an idol...
His ulterior motive is so obvious!
Aichi and Kourin...
Cardfight Club
Members Wanted
Beginners welcome!! I'll teach you the rules!
1-A Aichi Sendou
We need two more members to
officially establish the club.
Who says it has to be an official club?
Kourin, you said you wanted it to be a club.
Ah... did I?
But it'll be okay. I'm sure
we'll find more people.
Misaki! Perfect timing...
Don't run in the hallway!
She's...
Misaki, I've started a Cardfight Club.
With Kourin...
So I hear...
Will you join too, Misaki?
Apparently, the people at Hitsue High
started a Vanguard Club, too.
Eventually, we may be able to have
an intramural high school tournament.
Let's be in a tournament together again!
Sorry, but I can't join.
I've got the shop...
Oh, that's right...
But I'm sure you could find a little
time to participate in the club...
Hey, Aichi...
They call this girl the
"Boss Lady of Miyaji Academy"!
Boss Lady?
I'm telling you for your own
good. Steer clear of her!
Come on, let's go!
S-Sorry, Misaki. I'll see you later...
Darn it! I lost again!
One more time!
Fine.
Darn it! This shouldn't be happening!
One more time!
Sure.
You turned him down?!
I have to work here at the shop...
If that's the case, you've
got this guy to help out.
That's right, though I'd only be an
assistant to the sub-manager. Right?
What are you talking about?
This is my family's shop.
If I'm able to work, it only
makes sense that I work.
Yeah, true, but since you go to the same
school as Aichi, you oughta be in the club.
That's right!
I've already made up my mind!
Besides, it looks like Aichi's
already got new friends.
But still, what a waste...
Hey, Miwa! Izaki!
Get over here and fight the great Katsumi!
Yeah, yeah...
We're on our way...
After all, if I want to play
Vanguard, I can do it right here.
Huh? Is that a new deck?
So you've finally made a
new deck for yourself, Misaki?
You're racing through the blossom of
youth with Vanguard beside you!
I envy you! I sure do!
Shut up!
I lost!
Again?
Ishida isn't here today. Now's my chance.
That guy? I think his name is Shingo Komoi?
That's...
Hey, you!
Ishida!
Are you stalking Kourin?!
E-Excuse me?!
This magazine is proof plenty!
That's...
Come on! It'll be easier
on you if you confess!
What is this, a cop show?!
No, it ain't!
Is something wrong?
This guy is Kourin's stalker!
Come on, admit it!
Th-That's enough!
Wha...?! This guy doesn't
know when to give up!
How 'bout I pop you one?!
N-No fighting, Naoki!
But this guy...
That's right...
A fight would be wonderful.
What?!
Fight me with this, Naoki Ishida!
Wha...?! He's got...
A Vanguard deck?
We'll fight to the finish...
...and then I'll make you promise to stay away
from the person who means a lot to me!
B-Bring it on! I'll give you a crack at me!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Ambush Dragon Eradicator, Linchu!
Stealth Dragon, Magatsu Wind!
I go first! Draw!
I ride Stealth Beast, Night Panther!
Wha...?!
Magatsu Wind moves.
Now it's your turn...
...Naoki Ishida!
I ride Demolition Dragon!
Linchu moves.
I call Dui!
Jerk... What's he snickerin' about?!
Here I go! Demolition Dragon
attacks Night Panther!
Drive trigger check!
Yeah! I got a trigger right away!
I give +5000 power to Dui. And then...
I can't stand!
You're an absolute beginner, aren't you?
Never mind the stand trigger, but
you attack first with your Vanguard?
What's that?!
Jerk... Makin' fun of me...
Linchu boosts! Dui attacks!
Yes! 2 damage!
You get excited about that?
You really are a beginner.
You'd get crabby if I steamrolled you,
so I'll do you a favor just this once
and teach you some basic tactics.
Clam it about that beginner stuff!
I'm being polite! After all, I'm
saying "beginner," not "noob."
My turn.
I ride Magatsu Gale!
And then I call!
Listen up.
When you attack, it's a given that
you start with a rear-guard unit,
then attack with your Vanguard, and
then with your other rear-guard unit.
Do that, and your stand trigger
won't go to waste like last time.
You'll also have room to allocate
critical triggers or power-up effects
to your units based on
your opponent's guards.
Well, I doubt you're able to comprehend
my explanation with words alone,
so you can learn by watching my attack.
Bloody Mist attacks Demolition Dragon!
No guard!
Susei goes to the damage zone...
Not yet! My Vanguard, Magatsu Gale, attacks!
No guard!
Drive trigger check!
If I'd gotten a stand trigger here,
I'd be able to stand up Bloody Mist,
which has already attacked once.
And yet, you...
All right, my final rear-guard attacks!
Well, that's one of the fundamentals.
If you'd like, you can try
it out during your next turn.
He's givin' me a handicap?! Punk!
I stand and draw!
I ride Thunder Boom Dragon!
And then I call Spark Rain Dragon!
Spark Rain attacks Magatsu Gale!
Yes! That's the way you do it.
But it's not going through.
Guard!
Why, you...! Thunder Boom Dragon attacks!
Linchu boosts! Dui attacks!
Heal trigger! I heal 1 damage.
The damage is 3 to 3?
That's right! We're tied up!
Are you thinking that we're evenly matched?
Stand and draw!
I'll show you the difference
between you and me.
I ride Magatsu Storm!
When Magatsu Gale is in the Soul,
Magatsu Storm has 11000 power!
I call Shijimamaru!
Bloody Mist attacks!
Guard!
Shijimamaru boosts. Magatsu Storm attacks!
No guard!
Drive check.
First check.
Wha...?!
I give the power to White Mane and
the extra critical to Magatsu Storm.
Shoot! 5 damage!
Let's end it with this.
White Mane attacks with a
boost from Magatsu Wind!
I don't wanna lose!
Guard!
Well, that's okay.
I got you to 5 damage. Just a little more.
Just a little more, my foot!
I'm gonna torpedo you this turn!
I'm not the same person I was yesterday!
Here I go!
Strike, my avatar! I ride...
...Eradicator, Gauntlet Buster Dragon!
I call Dui and Red River!
I activate Gauntlet Buster Dragon's skill!
Especial Counterblast!
I retire one of your rear-guards!
Break through the limit! Limit Break!
I activate its skill one more time!
One more unit!
Burn through the ultimate limit! Limit Break!
That's a total of 17000 power.
And three criticals!
Here I go! Show him what a man you are!
Linchu boosts! Dui attacks Magatsu Storm!
Bloody Mist intercepts!
I'm not done!
I'm not the same person I was yesterday!
Dui, lend Gauntlet Buster your power!
How do you like that?!
This is what's wrong with beginners.
What?!
Did you forget?
I have this card in my hand!
Wha...?! Perfect guard?!
Dang it! Drive check!
Yes!
I give all of the effects to Spark Rain!
I'm countin' on you, Spark Rain!
Blow Magatsu Storm away!
Turn end.
If I can protect myself this
next turn, I can win this!
Are you thinking...
that if you successfully defend
yourself this turn, you can beat me?
So what if I am?!
Again, this is what's wrong with beginners.
You stacked your deck with Eradicators,
yet the first stand trigger you
drew wasn't an Eradicator card...
I'm surprised you're confident about
winning with that half-baked deck.
Naoki...
Honestly, Sendou, why did you let a
beginner like this into the club?
W-Why...?
I can't fathom why he's
in the Cardfight Club.
What the heck?! What have
you got against me?!
Since you asked, I'll explain.
It was this spring...
Even though there's nothing more
wonderful in the world than Vanguard,
everyone at this academy is so devoted to
their studies that they pay it no attention,
but this is where I met my hero!
I'm talking about the greatest of the great,
the backbone of the Vanguard world in Japan!
I'd only seen my hero on TV, but now,
in front of me, in the flesh...!
And then, a miracle occurred.
My hero formed a Cardfight
Club at this academy!
Every day, I waited for my chance
to strike up a conversation...
But standing next to my idol every single
moment is this juvenile delinquent!
That's right! You've destroyed every
chance I got by being a hanger-on!
Have I been with Kourin that much?
When did I say anything about Kourin?!
Huh? Not her?!
Then... don't tell me...
You mean Aichi?!
Why, Sendou?!
This guy doesn't have the faintest
idea of how great you are!
Why are you playing Vanguard
with somebody like this?!
My hero!
My hero...
...is being poisoned by
a juvenile delinquent!
Champion of the VF Circuit!
Team Q4 Won!
I cannot accept that reality!
Aichi Sendou Achieved Great Results!
I swear I'll win this fight and free Sendou!
I activate Magatsu Storm's skill!
Limit Break!
This is Magatsu-style Ninjutsu,
Secret Demon Dragon Avatar skill!
And then I call!
Magatsu Breath boosts! Magatsu Storm!
Guard!
Shijimamaru boosts! Magatsu Storm!
Not today!
Final judgment.
Magatsu Storm attacks with
a boost from Night Panther!
Now, draw the top card from your deck.
A damage check that will decide destiny...
I lost...
Naoki...
Naturally. So, set Sendou free.
W-What?! Is there something you want to say?!
Yeah!
There is!
Komoi, you...
W-W-What is it?
Join the Cardfight Club!
If you know so much about Vanguard,
teach me more about it!
Wait a sec...
Aichi! Help me out here!
This guy should be in the club!
Sure! He can join, right?
But all he did was beat Ishida...
We could both tell that
he's got plenty of skill.
Besides, he already passed
our membership qualification,
beating a member of the club.
Guess it can't be helped.
Fine, you can join.
Thank you!
Yeah!
Nice to meet you, um... Komoi?
Y-Yes! I'm Shingo Komoi!
Welcome to the Cardfight Club!
Th-Thank you!
I'm gonna count on you from now on, Bowl-cut!
H-How dare you address me like that?!
You... You boneheaded beginner, Ishida!
What'd you call me?!
There'd be no point in me teaching Vanguard
to a muscle-brained dope who's
quick to resort to violence!
Oh, yeah?! How do you figure
I'm muscle-brained?!
Want another match? This
time, I ain't gonna lose!
Now we just need one more member...
Oh, now you want another match?
Well, I'd get no thrill from
beating a clueless noob!
What was that?!
So this is what's disrupting
the order of the academy...
Cardfight Club...
I'd better report to the president.
Thank you for welcoming me
into the club, Aichi and Kourin!
W-What about me?!
I hope you improve, newbie Ishida!
Everybody's a newbie at first.
Now we've got four people.
One more, and the Cardfight Club
is officially established!
Next Time: The Football Team's Assassin!
The Football Team's Assassin
"Ready, set"? "Hut-hut"?
"Pass and run"? I don't understand...
Maybe it's like a
Limit Break is a first down...
And I don't get any of it,
so I'm "knocked down"?
Who asked you to make a pun?