So the black knight's attack
hit the gold knight...
In other words, the Cardfight
Club missed out on the chance
to participate in the high
school championship, yes?
Yes.
All right, then.
I assume you've come up with another plan?
Yes. I thought we could put them to work.
Them?
After being persecuted for many years...
Persecuted? Are you joking?
No, that's not what I meant.
I mean, as a consequence
of their peculiarities,
they haven't been able to gather members,
still haven't been able to go beyond
the barrier of an "association,"
haven't been given a clubroom...
That's a lot of "haven'ts."
Those three "haven'ts"
have become their strength
as they research hate-filled paranormal
power, befriend time and space,
with a wasteland as their den...
I see...
What's happening with that plan we discussed?
Relax. We'll lure them up here and
take them down in one fell swoop.
Paranormal Power Research Society
I've mastered this for that very purpose.
With our powers, it's simplicity itself.
Fine. Though I don't believe
in supernatural power.
It doesn't matter to me if
normal people believe or not.
Whatever. Just succeed, and the physics
preparation room will be waiting for you.
Here, take this.
Why, if that isn't...
...the key to sealed power!
The time has come! Now our
power shall be unleashed!
A Windy Day
Physics Prep
We challenge you to a Vanguard duel!
We'll be waiting at the gateway to the sky <<= the roof!!
- The Paranormal Power Research Society
We challenge you to a Vanguard duel. We'll
be waiting at the gateway to the sky.
The Paranormal Power Research Society.
Rise!
Bow!
Days with only morning classes
are perfect for Vanguard!
Aichi, to the clubroom at warp speed!
R-Right!
It looks like he enjoys himself every day.
Hey, you guys haven't forgotten, have you?
They still haven't shown up?!
Classes have long been over with!
The barrier has stopped spreading.
Don't fret. Haste makes waste.
What we need to grasp is victory.
Nothing more and nothing less.
You're right.
It seems that they've appeared.
Have you come? Your opponents are right here.
Oh?
So you don't mind having
a Cardfight with me, then.
Don't try to be funny!
You came here after receiving
our letter of challenge.
Yes. I thought I would warm up here before
going to the VF High School Championship.
I'm not surprised, given that Aichi Sendou
is a student here at Miyaji Academy.
This school's got unusual-looking fighters.
Wonderful! Did you people
call forth this weather?
Who is he?
Not Sendou, apparently.
Maybe that Ishida guy?
Girl, you have a penetrating eye.
That's right! We, the members of the
Paranormal Power Research Society,
are allies of all paranormal power!
Wind!
Clouds!
Only a little earlier,
it was a clear blue sky,
but now it celebrates our foray into battle!
My name is Eru Nakagami.
Whether it means your lives or not,
I challenge you to a bout of Cardfighting!
Are you surprised?
At this academy, we possess
power recognized by the gods...
That's why we're feared and
were banished to this place.
Grieving Senri and Nakao, my comrades...
at the end of the day, we're just wandering
nomads without a place to call our own.
Our leader, Nakagami, possesses
an awesome fearsomeness...
And you'll experience it firsthand.
We bear no grudge against you Cardfighters,
but it's in our sad nature
to seek out safe refuge.
Forgive us...
Leon...
He thinks you're somebody else...
I understand.
I shall accept this letter of challenge.
Leon?!
Wandering nomads, eh?
That strikes a sad note.
Let us fight and leave
no grudges behind.
Ready?
Y-Yeah...
It aches... My sealed right arm aches!
It's sobbing out, "I'm
going to beat you bloody!"
Not yet... It's still too early...
You two. It's possible
that something may happen.
Get back so you won't get
sucked into the maelstrom!
R-Right!
You women in the back! It's
dangerous over there! Move away!
Jillian, let's go! It's dangerous here!
He's right. Back up.
R-Right.
Hurry, hurry!
You're prepared?
Here I go.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Greedy Hand!
Advance Party Brave Shooter!
I can almost see you on your
hands and knees before my power.
How amusing...
I ride Doreen the Thruster!
Greedy Hand moves back!
Oh, Leon...
We came here looking for Aichi Sendou, but...
Physics Prep
We challenge you to a Vanguard duel!
We'll be waiting at the gateway to the sky <<= the roof!!
- The Paranormal Power Research Society
A Vanguard duel?
"We'll be waiting at the gateway to the sky"?
Tear Knight, Theo attacks. Drive check.
Turn end.
The Damage Zone stigma is 2-0, huh?
Nakagami hasn't gotten serious yet.
But when he does...
W-What?
Now it's my turn...
Get on your hands and
knees! Quiver in fear!
Th-That's...
What?!
I'll tell you.
That's Eru Nakagami's third eye,
which can see through anything!
Also called "Eru's Eye"!
Eru's Eye?!
Anyone that eye gazes upon, be they one
person or ten, will lose all resistance to him!
Watch this. The resurrection
of a terrifying power!
I ride Gwynn the Ripper!
I use the power of my third eye
to activate Ripper's skill!
Move out, Ill Arms!
Eru's Eye is scary!
Call!
Rear-guard Ripper, destroy him!
Continue!
Two stigmas in a row!
What kind of power is gonna be unleashed
next? It'll be a real spectacle.
Why am I getting the chills?
I can't stop shivering!
I don't believe you people... We planned
to all have lunch together today, remember?
Wow. Kourin, you made all this yourself?
I-It's not like I made it because
I wanted you guys to eat it!
I just ended up making too much.
Eh? Is that so...?
Takuto?!
Long time no see, Aichi Sendou.
Hey, what are you doing here?!
I told you I was coming today.
Who is he?
He's the greatest sponsor
of the Vanguard world,
Takuto Tatsunagi, chairman of
the Tatsunagi Financial Group!
Nice to meet you.
H-Hello.
It's an honor to meet you!
"Chairman"? This kid?
How rude! You're just an Ishida yourself!
What was that?!
Plus, "an Ishida"?! That doesn't even make sense!
What fun.
I'm happy you've made such good friends, Kourin.
After all, while you were making this lunch,
you were like, "I hope everybody eats it."
Takuto!
You looked like you were having
so much fun making it...
Is that right?
Boss Lady, did you prepare
a homemade lunch, too?
Wow!
Awesome!
You're amazing too, Misaki!
R-Really? Thanks...
...I can't...
...tell them that Shin made it...
I can't tell them...
Thank you for the food!
Come to think of it, there should
be one more guest here...
Tear Knight, Lazarus attacks!
Barrier with Cursed Doctor!
The stigma is 3 to 2...
The moment of truth is fast approaching.
Turn end.
I ride Blade Wing Reijy!
H-Here it comes!
The power is gonna be unleashed at last!
Wait... Wait, my right arm!
Not yet... Not just yet...
W-When this unit is placed on the Vanguard,
I choose one of my rear-guards on the field,
take up to three cards of the same name
from my deck, and move them to the Soul...
That's Reijy's power, Telekinesis Soulcharge!
Call! Destroy Lazarus!
Guard!
Greedy Hand boosts! Reijy, destroy Lazarus!
Twin drive!
The power is with me!
I give the power to Gwynn the Ripper,
and the critical to Reijy!
Heal trigger! I heal 1 damage point.
Destroy him, Ripper!
The tables are turned!
Blow, wind that alters destiny!
Blow on my dearest wish!
Rain?
It's not going to rain. And the sky
will clear up by the time we go home.
Do you have supernatural
powers or somethin'?
What are you talking about? I just
saw a weather report, obviously.
Um... Takuto, can I ask you something?
Sure. What is it?
What are Kourin, Rekka,
and Suiko like at home?
Granny Glasses, you're not supposed
to ask that kinda question.
I-I know, right?
Besides, I'm sure they lounge
around in long T-shirts,
laugh their heads off while watching sitcoms,
sleep three in a row next to
each other, snoring lightly...
Wha...?! We do not!
Good question...
Hey, Takuto!
If you talk out of turn, I'll
never speak to you again!
What the heck? Don't be so serious...
Idols are our ideals, and that's
what makes them idols, right?
You're the one who asked in the first place!
Good for you, Kourin. It looks like you
get along really well with your friends.
Kourin is like the pillar
of the Cardfight Club.
That's right. We can always count on her,
and she's a demonic drill instructor
to our two new recruits.
Come on, "demonic" is a little harsh...
No, I agree.
I'm glad I had you come to this school.
Sometimes, in order to change yourself,
you have to come out of your shell.
I attack with Lucas!
Psychic barrier!
Turn end.
Again? I hope he'll be okay.
Yeah. The damage is 4 to 4...
N-Now, the portal to space opens...
Five elements that are the building
blocks of the world, give me power!
I ride Master of the Fifth Element!
Call! Greedy Hand's skill!
It moves to the Soul.
And then I can put a grade 2
or lower unit into the Soul!
Nakagami!
No!
Don't do this! Stop!
Stop!
Th-There it is! God Hand!
God Hand?!
To all of life, it brings
the uncertainty of death.
And it deals out reborn affection.
That's why it's called...
...God Hand!
Doreen obtains power from the Soul.
Dimension Creeper, create life in my
Soul with the light breath of a soul!
Telekinesis Soulblast! And charge!
A total of eight cards for a Soulcharge?!
This is what makes the world go round,
the never-ending cycle of life and death!
No! Don't come out of me!
What is it?!
What's going to come out?
The power that's been sealed away...
Look... He can't hold back anymore...
Come forth, power of
destruction and creation!
Limit Break!
Fifth Element Enhanced Strength!
All of the units get +3000 power?!
Against my power, Vanguard fighters
are like helpless babies!
Obliteration! Gwynn the Ripper!
Fifth Element!
Guard!
Twin drive, check!
I give all of the effects to Werwolf Sieger!
Now I'm going to bring the
history of darkness to a close!
Doreen the Thruster! 33000 boost!
Obliterate him, Werwolf Sieger!
All of you, wake up!
Bring history to a close, you say?
You need to learn that you can't change your
own fate by borrowing someone else's power.
What?!
Huh? Is there a window open somewhere?
I'll tell you a story.
There was once a person who
was cursed with a sealed fate,
and he wanted power so badly
that he sold his soul for it.
He had lost sight of himself.
I'd forgotten my true objective.
If I hadn't had that fight with Sendou,
I'm sure I wouldn't be here right now.
Leon...
The point is, just as Sendou
guided me to the light back then,
I'm going to purify you people!
Last Card, Revonn!
I obtain the power of Trans-core Dragon
and cut through despairing destiny!
Break ride, my Vanguard!
Counterblast!
Titan of the Beam Rifle attacks!
5 damage...
Uh oh...
Lucas!
Shoot! It can't end!
It can't end like this!
And yet it is going to end like this.
Last Card, Revonn attacks!
There are two choices before you.
The first is to throw
down your hand and lose.
The other is to keep your hand and lose.
Wha...?!
It's cleared up. Just like Kourin said!
It's not me, it's the weather report.
Yeesh. Check the TV news or
a newspaper once in a while.
Shucks. It would've been cooler
if you had supernatural powers...
Nakagami...
Are we doomed to be wandering
nomads for eternity?
There's no reason to give up.
You work out your own fate.
If you believe in yourself,
believe in your comrades,
and devote yourself to your research,
a path will open naturally.
It was a good fight. I'm grateful to you.
Wait for us!
Leon!
Bye bye!
That guy... was the real thing...
Yeah.
I lost.
Kourin, Misaki Tokura, thank you for lunch.
Everything was really delicious.
If you're happy and full,
then it was worth making.
Yeah, exactly...
All right, now let's get to the club!
May I participate, as well?
Leon?!
You finally got here.
Sorry I'm late.
So your "one more guest" was Leon!
I wanted to fight you once before going
to the VF High School Championship.
Please indulge me.
Sure. It'd be my pleasure.
I-I can't believe it! I get to see a fight
between Aichi Sendou and Leon Souryu!
I'm moved!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Well, why don't we have a friendly fight, too?
Good idea.
I'm in!
All right!
Blaster Blade Liberator attacks!
No guard!
Guard!
Curse you, Cardfight Club!
Our next move... I need
to plan our next move!
No guard!
Heal trigger!
Did everybody eat it?
Of course. After all, I made it.
Yeah. And if they hadn't eaten it, I'm sure
right now you'd be all... down in the dumps.
I would not!
Oh. Did you take a photo?
Yes. I got a good shot of Kourin.
Oh, my...
That's adorable!
Hey! When did you take that?!
Give me that data!
Forget about it! This kind of thing is...
...totally cute!
Just look at that happy face!
He-ey! Takuto!
We went to all the trouble of making lunch,
and all the guys forgot about it! You know?
R-Right...
I-I mean, it's not like I put a
lot of effort into making it...
Your lunches were really delicious.
And I got to fight Leon, too.
I wish all days could be like this.
Next time: Mystery Dragon!
Mystery Dragon!
Huh? Kourin's absent today?
Naoki? You're acting kind of weird...
What? What's going on?!