Tetsu!
Nobody's here...
I see.
The last boss is waiting in a place
that's more appropriate for him.
That's fine.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Tetsu.
A villainous role actually suits you.
This is a new discovery.
As expected, you made it
this far, Ren Suzugamori.
The top fighter of Team Asteroid,
my king, is a perfect match for me.
"King," you say?
You never have been good at making jokes.
You're not even satisfied with the way I
perform as captain of the Vanguard team.
How long do you intend to
engage in this buffoonery?
Dunno. It's very amusing
to me, in its own way.
Amusing...?
That's what you always say.
But... that too shall end.
I suppose we really have to do this, huh?
Isn't that why you've come?
I suppose it is.
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Frontline Revenger, Claudas!
Amon's Follower, Fate Collector!
I had no idea a contraption
like this was in the building.
Isn't there a way to get to the roof?
Ren has a private elevator in the back,
but it won't work with my ID card.
Any other way?
Come to think of it, there's the
maintenance emergency staircase.
Why won't it open?
The Traitor General
I ride Revenger, Dark Bond Trumpeter.
Can I ask you one thing?
You're going to ask even
if I refuse, aren't you?
Yes. Who Reversed you?
Do you really think I'm going to answer that?
No. I figured you wouldn't.
After all, you're stingy.
If you knew that, then don't
ask in the first place!
I ride Amon's Follower, Phu Geenlin!
I call Amon's Follower, Hell's Deal!
Soulcharge!
Go! Hell's Deal!
There aren't many fighters out
there who could beat Tetsu...
...so who could it have been?
Stop it.
What are you referring to?
I'm not the kind of opponent
that you can defeat
while distracted by other thoughts.
Phu Geenlin attacks!
Very true, Tetsu.
Against you, I have to fight seriously.
Annihilate him! I ride my
avatar, Blaster Dark Revenger!
Then I call Blaster Dark and Dorint.
Go, Blaster Dark. Destroy Phu Geenlin!
Ren! Ren!
Ren!
What's the code to unlock it?
I don't know.
Only Ren and Tetsu can access
this building's security system.
I see...
I'll try to hack it.
You can do that?
I don't know.
But trying this is a lot better
than standing around doing nothing.
Ren Suzugamori. As expected, you are strong.
But then, why...
Why aren't you using that ability
in an appropriate manner?
I'm not? It may not look
like it, but I am trying.
Annihilate him, Blaster Dark.
It's the same way with Team Asteroid.
Even though you formed the team,
I was actually the one who pulled
together the organization.
Yes. I couldn't have done it without you.
A man like you...
What's the problem? Everyone has things
they're suited and ill-suited for.
Turn end.
Stand and draw!
Certainly, that's true.
You can leave the running of
the entire operation to me.
But you're the one who stands at the top!
It has to be you!
Ride! Gwynn the Ripper!
I retire Dorint.
Why does it have to be me in particular?
Because you're the one fighter
in the world that I acknowledge.
Gwynn attacks your Vanguard
with a boost from Fate!
No guard.
Drive trigger check.
The one fighter in the
world that you acknowledge?
That disappoints me, Tetsu.
What?
When did you become the kind
of man that says such trite things?
What are you talking about? I've always...
No! The Tetsu I knew long ago
was completely different.
I was nothing to you then. Remember
how coldly you treated me?
Long ago? You mean when we first met?
Yes!
You were really interesting back then.
Um... Would you get out of the way?
You see, I can't get by if you won't move.
Am I wrong?
Just take a detour!
Everybody's walkin' over there!
I refuse!
What?!
I want to walk under the cherry blossoms.
You got some guts, punk.
Lend me an ear for a minute.
Will you return it?
Just come with me!
It won't come off!
Of course not!
Watch your head.
Safety is number one.
Hey! Over here!
Um... What's this place?
Who the heck is this guy?
Seems to be a freshman at our school.
But he don't know his place, so I
thought I'd teach 'im a lesson.
Don't go overboard.
Hey, look at this.
See what this guy's got.
What the heck is it?
It's Vanguard.
Van... what?
It's a card game.
A card game, huh? Like playing cards?
What the...?!
Get back here!
W-What?!
You! Please fight me!
I can picture it.
I'm sure you could give
me an interesting fight!
No doubt about it!
Picture it? What are you talking about?
And this "fight" you wanna have,
I don't even know the rules.
Even so, I can tell! After all...
...the cards are glowing!
Hey, do something with this guy.
Yeesh.
Here.
You spoiled my mood...
What about fighting me?!
When it comes to fighting...
...this is the only kind I need.
Boring...
Nothin' interesting around here...
Hi!
You... The guy from the other day...
What are you doin' here?
Shouldn't you be in class?
I could say the same to you, Tetsu.
Yeah, you got a point...
Wait... how'd you know my name?!
And a freshman oughta treat
me with more respect!
Okay, okay. More importantly, let's fight!
You don't know when to quit.
I'm not interested in
your make-believe fights.
It isn't make-believe.
True, it doesn't involve
physically hitting or kicking...
...but the fight takes
place on the fight field is a genuine one.
It's a battle worthy of risking your life.
Like I'm gonna fall for
that? It's just silly.
I was trying to be persuasive...
Still, I'm not giving up!
Tetsu, you're havin' tempura again?
Yeah. 'Cause I can wolf it down fast.
True that. If you don't hurry up an' eat,
you won't have enough time to fight.
Yeah, yeah.
What the heck is this?!
Your pushiness back then
annoyed me to no end.
That's because you refused to fight.
But ultimately, you wore me down and initiated
me into Cardfighting, so I commend you.
Huh? Is that how it was?
Aren't you maybe whitewashing the past
a little to make yourself look better?
Come to think of it, that
was also on a roof...
Darn it...
That looks painful.
You again...
When you were walking down the street,
did a kitten suddenly jump out,
so you tripped on a rock and fell
while trying to avoid it?
What's with that?
How many were you fighting?
Eight.
That's a lot.
Up to five was a piece of cake...
Really?
You're strong, Tetsu.
But that kind of fight
isn't really much fun, is it?
That's why I say...
Rumble with me.
That is, fight me. I'm strong.
Crimson Butterfly, Brigitte attacks!
Um... I don't think I can guard...
Hey, what happens in this situation?
My attack succeeds. Please do a damage check.
Check...
No trigger.
Then that makes 6 damage,
so I win this fight.
I see. I lost, huh?
Don't be too disappointed.
That was your first fight.
I lost a fight...
One more time!
No... ten more times, or a hundred times!
However many times it takes to beat you!
I win fights!
Whether my opponent is a boxer
or a martial artist, I win!
I fight until I win!
Even if that makes me look
uncool, it's who I am!
I don't think you're...
Anyway, let's fight!
Tetsu...
Never mind.
But I'm not going to lose!
You'll see. Don't underestimate Tetsu Shinjo.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Demon World Marquis, Amon attacks!
Damage check.
No trigger. That makes 6 damage.
You beat me.
I... won?
Yes. Congratulations.
Is something wrong?
This is Cardfight.
This is Vanguard...
What do you think? Interesting, right?
Yeah. Now that I know it's like this,
I wish I'd fought you earlier.
Well, I kept asking you, didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
You're a foo fighter.
What's that?
A mysterious, unidentified fighter.
Foo fighter...
I like that.
Starting today, we'll be Team Foo Fighter!
We...?
Yes. A team of just you and me.
Team Foo Fighter...
That brings back memories, doesn't it?
Yeah. Then he transferred in.
You interrupted my nap because you've
got business with this, right?
Huh! You catch on quick.
Go, Dragonic Overlord!
Burn everything to ashes
with your white hot flames!
He was strong.
And you were drawn to that strength.
Despair! Then fall to your
knees and sip bitter water!
I ride...
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Call!
That's why you brought him into our team.
How about it? Would you
like to join Foo Fighter?
Foo Fighter?
That's our team.
Although at the moment, it
only consists of me and Ren.
That was when I decided.
If you were going to increase
the number of our comrades,
and emerge on the national, and
eventually international, stage,
I would do everything in
my power to support you.
So even when you became corrupted by power...
Look at yourself, helpless and beaten
before my overwhelming might!
Even then...
You're leaving.
And you're staying, huh?
I can't desert Ren.
I see...
I returned to you.
You led me into this world, so if you
wanted power, I would give it to you.
If it were your wish, I would even
accompany you to the deepest pit of hell!
That's what I thought.
However, Ren Suzugamori...
You've fallen!
Now that I'm Reversed, it's all so clear.
Power is justice!
Power is the law!
Affected by nothing, it is
the single, absolute existence...
...that is, yes, even equal to a god!
Ren! Picture it! And look for the power!
Your goal is at hand! The time has
come to create a world ruled by force!
Open your eyes! You have the power!
Now become the king of Team Asteroid!
Become the king of the world!
No thank you, Tetsu.
Why?!
Why won't you make a grab
for glory once more?!
Tetsu, haven't you noticed?
The cards you're holding now...
...aren't glowing!
I see. In that case, there's
nothing left to say.
As long as we're Cardfighters, a demand
will be made when one wins over the other!
Crawl out of the gates of hell
and wield that evil power!
I ride...
Demon World Marquis, Amon!
Ren! Surrender to me!
This time, I'll lead you!
And then become the king
that I seek, Ren Suzugamori!
Ren, become my king!
Honestly... What nonsense.
You'll get the highest power and glory.
That's not what I want.
Then what do you want?
That's a secret. Just saying
it would be boorish.
The words, "You have friends."
That's Ren's sincere feeling.
Next time: Kingmaker in the Moonlight!
Kingmaker in the Moonlight!
Tetsu. I'm going to bring you back.
Even if you don't like it.