Kourin...?
I'm Kourin Tatsunagi.
This is my first day at Miyaji Academy.
It's a pleasure to meet everyone.
Ultra-rare idol group's new single,
"ENDLESS☆FIGHTER," is soaring off the charts.
We just can't take our eyes
off of this ultra-cute trio!
Quiet, people! Quiet!
Tatsunagi, your seat is over there.
Okay.
Wow. So this is an idol...
Um, I... uh...
It's been a while, Aichi Sendou.
Yes... long time no see, Kourin.
Catching a Break
Kourin knows him?
She just said his name!
What's their relationship?
Brother and sister? Or else...
All right... quiet, everyone.
Yeesh. Why did Takuto have to send me here?
I'd like you three to experience
a normal school life.
Tatsunagi, I've got something to give
you, so come to the faculty room.
Okay.
I thought I'd stop breathing...
Hey, Sendou...
Hey, Sendou, how do you know Kourin?!
What's your relationship?
Hey, introduce me to her! Okay?! Okay?!
U-Um... uh...
Ah! Ishida!
Hey, Sendou, are you gonna
introduce me or what?!
And so, the drama is set in the
middle of the Heian period.
There are variations from the book,
but of the approximately one million
characters and 220,000 sentences,
with 400 characters to a page
in the original manuscript,
about 2,400 pages are covered.
And about 500...
What?!
Kourin transferred to Aichi's class?!
Morikawa!
Let go of me, Izaki!
Come on, don't give Aichi a hard time!
Shut up! Not only does he betray our
friendship by going to Miyaji Academy,
but now he's in the same class as Kourin?!
I'll never, ever forgive him for this!
Let go of me!
What up?!
Aichi!
Kamui the Great, there's trouble!
TT, yo!
What are you doin'?! Leave
him alone, Lose-umi!
Beast Deity Kick!
Oh, dear...
What are they doing?
Misaki, is it true what Aichi said?
Probably. Someone in my
class was also going on
about an idol transferring
in to the first-year.
Are you okay, Brother?
Yeah. Thanks. I hope Morikawa is okay...
What a disaster, Aichi.
Still, it's hard to believe
that Kourin would transfer in.
Yeah. I'm surprised, too.
Huh. I didn't know idols went to school.
I've decided! I'm gonna
transfer to Aichi's school!
Morikawa, with our grades, there's no
way we could get into Miyaji Academy!
Give it up, Lose-umi.
GU, yo!
Shut up!
I've got it! I'll live at Aichi's school!
There it is...
I-Impossible! Only students and their
guardians are allowed in the school!
In that case, I'll be Aichi's father!
From now on, just call me "Dad"!
I'm Aichi's younger brother! And I
don't accept you as our father!
Where's this going?
I disown any son who's disobedient to me!
What?!
In the first place, I don't want an
old man with weird hair like yours!
Like you've got room to talk?!
Cut it out!
It's kinda BOF, yo.
Yeah. Birds of a feather, I guess...
So Aichi, you were saying your school
doesn't have a Cardfight club?
Right...
That's too bad.
If you had a club, we
could get into your school
by setting up intramural matches.
Sorry.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
A club...
That's it!
Aichi's not coming down, huh?
I wonder if he's studying.
There!
Cardfight Club
Members Wanted
Please join!
Miyaji Academy, High School
I'm looking for members to form
a Cardfight Club! Please join!
Please! I'm looking for people
to join the Cardfight Club!
Kourin, good morning!
Kourin, you're as beautiful as ever today!
Um, do you happen to have any
free time after school today?
What the heck are they doin'?
Please join!
Please! I'm looking for people
to join the Cardfight Club!
Ah! Thank you...
Kourin?!
Cardfight Club? You intend
to form it yourself?
Yes, I thought I'd give it a try...
Isn't it hard making a club?
I think it's not only a
matter of gathering members,
but also getting permission from
the Student Council and school.
How many people do you have?
So far, it's just me, but I'm thinking
that if I do my best and not give up,
I'll be sure to get some members.
Huh...
Cardfight Club, he says...?
I'll join.
I'm saying that I'll join the Cardfight Club.
Th-Thank you!
I'll join, too!
Me too! I wanna be in the
same club that Kourin's in!
Let me join, too!
U-Um...
Wait!
Only those who are serious about
participating in the Cardfight Club will be admitted!
Of course I'm serious!
I'm totally serious!
Fine. If you can beat either of
the current members, Aichi or me,
we'll know you're serious,
and will let you join.
You're okay with that,
aren't you, Aichi Sendou?
S-Sure...
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's start.
Right!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Impossible... They're too tough...
I don't understand the rules...
None of them won, huh?
Nope...
It can't be helped.
We'll have to start the club
with just the two of us.
Wait a second!
I wanna join the Cardfight Club.
Ishida!
So you're interested in
Vanguard after all, huh?
Yeah. A little...
Fine. If you beat me, we'll let you in.
Of course. That's the idea.
At least it looks like you're not after me.
Sorry. I'm not a fan, Ms. Idol.
Don't worry about that. I'm
not gonna go easy on you.
Bring it on!
Picture it!
Gotcha!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Dreaming Jewel Knight, Tiffany!
Stone Bullet Eradicator, Houki!
I ride Stinging Jewel Knight, Sherry!
Tiffany uses her skill to move.
Turn end.
Here I go.
Strike, my avatar! I ride...
...Eradicator, Demolition Dragon!
His avatar already? A grade 1?
I call Red River Dragoon!
And Demolition Dragon attacks!
No guard.
Red River Dragoon attacks!
That's my attack! What do you think?!
That's great! You did 2 damage already!
Yeah, right?!
That's normal.
What's that?!
My turn.
I ride Dogmatize Jewel Knight, Sybill!
I use a Counterblast to superior
call Sherry, and then I call Tracie.
Attack!
Strike, my avatar! I ride...
...Eradicator, Thunder Boom Dragon!
Attack! Attack, I say!
That's the way, Ishida!
Yeah!
What?
Gleaming sword! Piercing light!
I ride Leading Jewel Knight, Salome!
Especial Counterblast!
Salome's skill. I can choose one
card from my deck and call it.
I superior call Pureheart
Jewel Knight, Ashlei!
I call Toypugal!
Five rear-guards in no time at all...
As expected, Kourin's mastered Royal Paladin.
With a boost from Tiffany,
Salome attacks your Vanguard!
Limit Break!
L-Limit Break?
It's a skill that can be activated
when you have 4 or more damage.
If there are four or more Jewel
Knights in my rear-guard,
I get +2000 power and an extra critical.
S-Seriously?!
Yeah.
To guard against that attack...
Here!
Drive check. First check.
Second check.
Yes! I protected myself!
Turn end.
All right. Next it's my turn!
What do you think, Ms. Idol?!
We both have 4 damage!
Right now, we're evenly matched, right?!
Not at all.
What's that?!
You're an absolute beginner, aren't you?
You've just learned the rules.
Unbelievable! H-How did you know?!
During my last attack with
Salome, you guarded with 10000,
but if I'd drawn even one
trigger with my drive check,
what do you think would've happened?
Um...
Salome had an extra critical,
so that's 2 damage.
Right now, my damage is 4, so...
Uh oh!
I see.
You've gotta think that far
ahead with Vanguard attacks...
Awesome! Vanguard is a blast!
Well, straightforwardness is your good point.
So, do you want to continue playing?
I don't mind if you get a little better
at it before taking the challenge again.
No, I'm ready now!
This match isn't about whether I
have a chance of winning or not.
I really wanna be a part of this club.
I wanna play Vanguard with Aichi Sendou.
Ishida...?
With Aichi...?
I remembered, Sendou.
You went to Miyaji Academy
once before, didn't you?
Right, for elementary school...
I've been here the whole time.
But you went to another middle school.
R-Right.
I'm thinkin' the reason was something
that happened in elementary school.
Right...
You always used to get beaten up back
then, both in and out of school...
Yeah. I was really lonely in
those days. It was hard on me...
My mother couldn't take it anymore,
and suggested I switch schools.
I noticed it, too. I knew
what you were going through.
But I pretended not to see anything...
It may sound like I wasn't interested.
But I didn't try to save
you. I didn't do anything...
I'm as bad as those jerks who drove you away!
No, that's not true!
No, it's bothered me all this time!
So now that you've come
back to the high school,
and I see you tryin' to establish a new club,
I can't help but wanna be part of it!
Ishida...
You've changed. You're completely different
than the way you were back then.
It's gotta be because of this!
That's right. Vanguard changed me.
I wanna change, too.
In the middle of this lousy high school life,
I wanna find somethin' I can
really be passionate about!
Ishida!
Call me Naoki, Aichi!
Do your best, Naoki!
All right! I'm fired up!
Don't forget. I'm your opponent.
Yeah! I'm picturin' it loud and clear!
I picture me beatin' you!
There's something wrong with that picture.
It's an illusion, or a hallucination!
Is that right, Ms. Idol?
Strike, my avatar!
I ride Eradicator, Vowing Sword Dragon!
I call Eradicator, Spark Rain Dragon!
Attack!
I guard with Gallatin!
Perfect defense with Iseult!
I guard with Rachelle and Prizme!
Th-Three attacks and no damage?!
0 damage...
Maybe Kourin is getting into it, too?
Now it's my turn!
Ashlei attacks!
Salome attacks!
Tracie attacks!
S-Somehow, I protected myself!
And it's my turn!
Naoki, you're doing great!
You only took 1 damage from Kourin's attacks!
Y-Yeah!
But you don't have any cards in your hand.
And you hardly have any rear-guards.
What do you plan on doing?
Draw!
Cool!
All right! Strike, my avatar! I ride...
...Discharging Dragon!
That's...
W-What?!
I rode a grade 3 on top of a grade 3...
Is that against the rules?
No, that's no problem. But that one...
It's Break Ride.
Break Ride?
Um...
You can tell him.
Right.
Vowing Sword Dragon has a new skill.
It's called Break Ride.
When you have 4 or more damage and ride it,
you can retire one of your
opponent's front row rear-guards
and have +10000 power for that turn.
That's the skill of Vowing Sword Dragon!
That's Break Ride!
That's awesome! That is so awesome!
Right?! Isn't it?!
Come on, be more impressed!
Yeah, it is fantastic.
That's right! Can I ride
from the beginning again?!
Kourin?
Fine with me.
All right.
My heart is burning!
It screams out, "Let me
join the Cardfight Club!"
Gaze upon my lethal...
...my invincible...
...my miraculous Break Ride!
Discharging Dragon!
Since I have at least 4 damage,
the Break Ride succeeded!
I'm gonna retire one of my
opponent's front row rear-guards!
I retire Tracie!
And then, and then...
...for this turn only, my
Vanguard gets +10000 power!
That's Break Ride!
This is my...
...Break Time!
That's wonderful, Naoki!
...Huh?
"Break time" means taking a break...
Break Time!
Discharging attacks with
a boost from Kohkaiji!
With Kohkaiji's skill, it gets another +4000!
And then, Limit Break!
Since I have at least 4 damage,
Discharging Dragon gets +5000 power!
That's 35000 power!
You can get that kind of power?!
No guard.
Drive... check!
Critical trigger!
I got a critical trigger!
That's +5000 power and an extra critical!
I won?!
Yep!
Yes!
I won!
Did you see it?! Did you?!
Um, Kourin...
Did you see my Break Time?!
Good grief.
Cool, right?! I won!
I lost to that beginner?
Vanguard is scary, you know?
Naoki's attack before...
Maybe you should've taken 1 damage from it.
You're right. I wasn't thinking clearly.
It means I've still got a ways to go, too.
Look at this!
But I think his feelings are true.
Me too.
So I get to be in the Cardfight Club, right?
Sure.
I'm lookin' forward to it, Aichi.
Me too, Naoki.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
And you can call me Kourin.
Nice to meet you, Kourin.
It starts here...
My new school life!
I'm lookin forward to it, Aichi, Kourin!
Well, I admit that you're enthusiastic
and surprisingly upfront.
Yeah! Now there are three of us!
To be recognized as a club...
We probably need two more members?
Hey! What the heck are you doin'?!
Followin' Kourin around...
Maybe an Ultra-rare groupie?
Next time: Targeted Idol!
I think he's one of our
classmates... Komoi, is it?
Maybe... Just maybe...
Wait! I intercept!