Silver Whip Liberation!
She filled in all of the rear-guard
spots with every grade.
It's all over now.
Ren will be my servant who gazes
only at me for all eternity.
Who said I don't look at you?
It won't get through! Guard!
Are you ready?
The punishment for angering me...
...isn't a light one.
I've known Asaka since I started gathering
fighters here in this building.
We've been on the same
team since I formed AL4.
Asia Circuit?
That's right.
Naturally, we were invited.
Asaka, you'll come too, won't you?
Of course. I'd love to, Ren.
Tetsu says he won't participate.
I'm busy preparing for
the new business venture.
But I will accompany you, and have already
recruited a new fighter in my stead.
A new fighter...?
Toshiki Kai!
It seems he was just killing
time on a park bench.
On a... park bench?
With Kai and me there, this
Circuit will be easy-peasy!
I... I'm just there because
they need three people.
Last Chance
Ren doesn't need me yet...
What are you doing? He told you to
follow him on the Circuit, didn't he?
I don't enter into the winning equation.
Is it frustrating?
Of course! I'm getting strong for Ren,
I win for him... and yet...
Shhhh!
I don't want to lose to Kai, of all people.
That's the spirit.
Maybe Ren is also...
I mean, Ren is counting on
that determination of yours.
It means you'll get stronger.
Yeah...
I am counting on you, Asaka.
The best part about Asaka is that
she hates losing more than anyone.
And she tries harder than anyone.
I'll have to disappoint you, Asaka.
I never would have guessed
that you wanted to control me.
But I'll use my strength right now to
defeat you and change those thoughts.
Give it your best shot.
You who moves beyond despair,
whether that be hell or
a land of nothingness,
take the power reflected in your eyes
and teach your opponent a lesson!
Break ride!
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Stand up again, my avatar!
Blaster Dark Revenger!
Go to Hades... Lilian!
Doreen's skill.
Blaster Dark attacks!
Guard!
Mordred Phantom!
Lydia!
Perfect guard!
Twin drive check.
I got one.
I give the power to this Blaster Dark...
...and heal 1 damage point.
That evens the damage.
Blaster Dark!
If I put them all out, I
could protect myself, but...
No guard!
You turned the tables on me.
But you weren't able to win.
All I need to do to win is to
give you 2 damage next turn.
Just a little more...
Just a little more, and Ren
will be mine and mine alone.
He'll be my personal puppet,
dancing with me forever.
Just a little more...
That's right, Asaka. You're
definitely going to win!
You're going to end this match next turn!
That's right. Beat him.
Defeat the strong fighter.
If you vanquish him, your
wish will come true.
He will be yours for eternity.
So beat him...
Beat him...
Beat him!
Beat the strong fighter!
Asaka?!
Defeat Ren Suzugamori, and make him taste
the despair of being turned into a doll!
That's my mission. It's the
purpose of this battle!
Asaka?
I'm not Asaka!
Call me "Queen"!
That's right. I'm a Queen.
A lonely queen who's surrounded
by obedient dolls.
But if you become mine, my
kingdom will be complete.
Come, Ren Suzugamori.
Together, we can build a happy kingdom.
Serve me. Get down on your knees before me.
Obey me!
And now the circus's last
act is going to begin.
When your whip of thorns cracks, all dragons
cower and throw themselves on the ground!
Crossride!
Silver Thorn Dragon Queen, Luquier "Reverse"!
What unit is this?!
Luquier? No, this is different!
That shining red and black form...
The power of Reverse has
reached it, just like Asaka!
Even the units are Reversed?!
That's right. That's the
tremendous power I wield now.
It's the supreme entertainment!
And seeing your face shiver
in fear excites me to no end!
You...
Even your useless struggles must end here,
because this Luquier "Reverse" is going
to bring you to your knees before me!
Luquier in the Soul! Give your
power to Queen Luquier "Reverse"!
Soar, Luquier! Fly to
the bright red darkness!
Shine, squirming power
and rubies of darkness!
Luquier "Reverse's" Limit Break!
I lock Barking Dragon!
And final performer waiting behind
the wing curtain, come up on stage!
Superior call!
Silver Thorn Beast Tamer, Maricica!
Another unit called up from the Soul...
The +5000 power makes up for the
loss of the Barking Dragon's boost!
Now, display your act that
will close out the finale...
Maricica!
I rubbed out one unit that was in the way.
But now it's time for the Queen to appear!
Silver Thorn Dragon Queen, Luquier "Reverse"!
Mordred Phantom!
Luquier "Reverse's" whip of thorns
will dye your hide bright red!
Guard!
Intercept!
Struggle, struggle.
Surrender to the writhing pain.
Twin drive check.
Critical trigger.
I give the effects to my rear-guard Luquier.
The stage revolves around me.
Now, show me, Luquier!
Take down Mordred!
And so it ends.
Ladies and gentlemen, please cheer
and give a big round of applause
to Ren Suzugamori, who's
had an agonizing loss!
Guard!
What?!
You won't beat me so easily.
Not even if you have a unit that's gotten
stronger through the power of Reverse.
Turn end...
I have five cards in my hand.
Against you, who's got only one.
And there's nothing in the
front row to stand in my way.
My victory in this showdown is still solid.
In other words, it's inevitable
that you'll become mine.
Oh, I know! Great idea!
Before the curtain closes,
I think I'll have you say:
"I'm delighted to have been
stomped on by your circus."
That's wonderful, isn't it?
That's enough!
Asaka Narumi...
Yes?
If you think I'm going to be a part of your
playtime forever, you're solely mistaken.
And if you really want to see a grand
finale, I'll put an end to this for you.
Take 'em down!
All right! Next!
Now this is what I call "hit and fun"!
I think you mean "hit and run"!
Yeesh!
S-Stop looking at me like that!
I'm not going to lose. I'm
not weak, like I used to be!
I... I...
I understand.
I understand, Asaka.
I know your best points...
and how strong they make you.
Is that the best you got?! Weakling!
One more time!
Alice attacks!
Guard!
And now it's over! Attack!
One more time!
Darn it!
You said I don't look at you...
...but that time...
...and that time...
...I was watching you closely.
Are you coming, Asaka?
Yes!
Asaka, to me, you're...
...a dear friend!
That's why I'm going to bring
you back with my own hands!
Break ride!
Mordred Phantom!
Stand up for me a third time!
Blaster Dark Revenger!
His third Blaster Dark?!
Be a good sport and go to Hades... Maricica!
Doreen's skill.
And one more unit...
What?!
In my battleground, there's no
victory without Blaster Dark.
Call.
It can't be...
His fourth Blaster Dark...
Doreen's skill. I turn over
one card in the Damage Zone.
Asaka, I'm only going to say this
once, so please listen carefully.
From here on out, stay with me!
Vamoose, Luquier.
It's not like I want anything in return.
Just by him... by Ren being
there, I could become stronger.
Asaka...
Mordred Phantom!
Cut through the darkness
that's holding Asaka captive!
Come back to me, Asaka!
Ren...
Asaka, are you all right?
I've got a splitting
headache for some reason...
Asaka...
What am I...?
What happened here?
You don't remember, do you?
I'll explain later.
R-Ren?
Hey, did I do something to
Ren that I have no memory of?
Maybe. You'll see...
W-What? What's with that?!
U-Um... Ren...
D-Did I say something rude to you?
Queen...
Excuse me?
W-What?! What happened?!
Asaka.
Y-Yes?!
Welcome back.
R-Right...
But... I won't forgive it a second time.
Let's go, Asaka. If you're okay with that...
Yes, Ren!
Hey, is there any purpose in
us playing along like this?
Yeah. I don't think we owe them anything.
That kind of thinking is why you're
not the brains of this operation.
If we cooperate with them without
thinking about gains or losses,
I bet they'll feel like
they owe us somethin'.
I get it. But I'm not sure that Ren jerk
has that kind of admirable quality.
Yeah, right?
Certainly...
Tetsu!
Nobody's here...
Tetsu is probably the one
who Reversed the fighters
from Fukuhara High and the
Team Asteroid building.
Surely not!
Ren?
I see.
The last boss is waiting in a place
that's more appropriate for him.
That's fine.
Ren...
Ren?!
Tetsu...
As expected, you made it
this far, Ren Suzugamori.
The top fighter of Team Asteroid
is a perfect match for me.
I suppose we really have to do this, huh?
I'm really surprised that you
thought of me like that, Asaka.
Eh? Did I say something rude to you, Ren?
I was shocked. I may not look
like it, but I'm sensitive.
I-I'm sorry! What on Earth did I say?!
Stupid! I'm such an idiot!
While Ren and the others are
caught up in a terrible situation,
we still don't know that anything is wrong.
Next time: The Traitor General!
The Traitor General!
Is someone waiting in the wings after this?
Well, I have a pretty good idea...