Dance, waves! Sparkle! The drop
of a soul that gives birth to life!
Glow with the seven colors
of the rainbow! Prism Splash!
I lost! Me...
Cute! Sweet! Charming!
Envelop the world with love!
Labrador's Limit Break!
Love Love Break!
I won, Mai!
Yeah! Good thing you put together
a new deck with cute cards!
I lost to an opponent whose
priority is cuteness...
Cardfight Circle
Sorry to make you wait.
Classy ladies are fashionably late.
Rekka!
So who's the munchkin?
What's that?
It's not like there's anything good...
...about being a giant!
Ow!!
Rekka, that's improper behavior
in front of your classmates.
Oh, he's just exaggerating the pain!
Being an idol, I don't have
that kind of physical strength!
Tee-hee!
R-Right...
Oh, he was just putting on an act!
It's... no act...
Idol Fight
Kourin, who is this girl?!
You don't know?
Like I'd know who this brat is?!
You really don't know, Ishida?
This is Rekka Tatsunagi.
She's part of Ultra-rare!
Ultra-rare?! I think I've
heard the name somewhere...
We're in the same club,
so how could you forget?!
Ultra-rare is a three-person idol group.
There's Suiko, the easygoing space cadet!
Kourin, the cool beauty!
And Rekka, the feisty one!
Miracle Trigger
I'm Sure Tomorrow Will be Ultra-rare!
Their debut song was "Miracle Trigger!
I'm Sure Tomorrow Will be Ultra-rare!"
That song was paired with
"Stand Up, Dream"...
...and that's not all.
They also act as the
Vanguard National Tournament's
official supporting idols!
What he said! Nice to meet you!
What are you, a fan?
No. I just want to know about
everything that relates to Sendou.
I happened to learn about them
through an extension of that.
Rekka is doing her best to balance
being a student and an idol.
She really is a wonderful girl!
Oh, that's not true...
You don't have to be modest, Rekka!
Aw, I'm just doing my best
because I really love it!
I didn't know she was this cute in person...
I feel like I'm going to become a fan...
Men are so simple...
They'll fall in love with even an
obviously cutesy act like that.
Isn't that part of your job?
True, it goes with the job!
Still, despite being split up between the
middle school and high school divisions,
what are the odds of two idols
going to the same school?
Could Suiko be going to this school, too?!
Of course not!
Yes, right...
I would know if she were...
Are you done with your idol work for today?
Yep. I can spend the rest
of the day with you guys!
Yay!
So how's the Vanguard showdown going
between middle and high school clubs?
The middle school club has two wins in a row!
Or put another way, the high school
club lost twice in a row, huh?
I'm so ashamed...
All right!
Then let's make it three in a row!
Yeah!
Who'll play against me?
I will!
I've always wanted to fight him...
The serious Aichi Sendou...
I'm looking forward to it!
Me too.
Then I'll watch from the sidelines.
Emi, Mai, you can relax right there.
Right!
Stand up, Vanguard!
First-aid Celestial, Penuel!
Wingal Liberator!
Angel Feather?
Also called the "Celestial Deck"...
Angel Feather is cute, too!
Yeah!
There they go with that
"cute" business again!
The important things for a fight
are your units' abilities and balance!
Says the boy who lost to Emi...
You just got lucky!
I don't think so, right, Emi?!
Right!
I go first. Draw!
Here I go!
Arena!
Yay!
My heart...
...is always burning!
Your heart...
Be scorched by Rekka's flames!
I idol ride Marking Celestial, Arabaki!
Rekka!
Yay!
Idol ride?!
She puts an idol's self-intro
into the middle of a ride...
And it's still incredibly cute...
Thank you!
Don't tell me you introduce
yourself like that...
W-Well, it's part of the job...
Turn end!
Draw.
Here I go!
I ride Future Liberator, Llew!
Wingal moves back.
Llew attacks, boosted by Wingal!
Damage check.
My turn.
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do...
No matter when or where...
Rekka is always on your side.
I'll always be with you, my fans!
I la-la-la-la ride...
Essence Celestial, Beka!
Rekka's do-re-mi-fa ride!
Cute!
What about the "ti-do" in
"do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do"?!
I call Wild Shot Celestial, Raguel!
Raguel attacks!
When I have a Vanguard with "Celestial"
in the name, Raguel gets +3000 power!
Damage trigger check.
No trigger.
Beka attacks with a boost from Penuel!
"Ti"... tremendous...
"Do"... drive trigger check!
What a cute "ti-do"!
You are a fan, aren't ya?!
N-No, I'm not!
I'm not a fan yet!
...Yet...
Stand trigger!
I add +5000 to the power of Raguel!
And then I stand her!
The standing Raguel attacks once more!
Turn end!
I'm not going to lose either!
Stand, my avatar!
I ride... Blaster Blade Liberator!
Oh, no, Sendou's Blaster Blade came out!
"Oh, no"?!
Call!
Gallatin! Escrad! Marron!
Gallatin attacks Becca!
Damage check!
Wingal boosts!
Blaster Blade!
Drive trigger check.
Turn end.
Now Rekka has 3 damage!
It'll be okay, Mai!
R-Right!
Chaste maiden who can hear God's voice,
heed His words and protect your loved ones!
Prophecy Celestial, Ramiel...
Zing! Bam! Ride!
That's cute, Rekka!
I feel like I should apologize...
What kind of ride is that?!
What the heck are you doin'?!
I-I'm not doing anything!
Turn end!
The damage is 3-4... Pretty much a tie...
I have a feeling it's going to be close...
Rekka, fight!
Thank you!
Kourin, aren't you gonna root for the
munchkin since you're in the same group?
Not especially...
That's cold...
Unless you're only friendly with
her when you're on the job?!
Of course not!
It's because I'm a member
of the Cardfight Club.
I see! So you want Aichi to win, huh?
Wh-What is this?
My heart's been beating like crazy...
Could it be that I, Shingo Komoi,
bearer of the steel heart,
have become a fan of Rekka?!
Rekka!
I've decided, I'm rooting for you!
He's totally a fan.
That's Aichi Sendou for you...
Even a Rekka ride doesn't
get him bent out of shape.
But I figured it wouldn't.
I'm just getting started.
Stand and draw!
Give me power with your noble white wings!
I ride Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
I call Liberator of Royalty, Phallon!
Phallon attacks!
When the Vanguard is a card with "Liberator"
in its name, Phallon gets +3000 power!
Damage trigger check!
Gancelot attacks with a boost from Wingal!
Gancelot's skill!
When he attacks a Vanguard,
he gets +2000 power!
Guard!
Drive trigger check!
First check...
Second check...
I attack with Liberator of the Flute, Escrad,
boosted by Little Liberator, Marron!
I guard with Ramiel!
Turn end.
Rekka is amazing!
She is amazing!
I'll show you what's frightening
about the Celestial Deck.
Play, you strong, pure melody!
Come in the name of the guardian angel!
Holy wings!
I break ride Solidify Celestial, Zerachiel!
I put one Angel Feather unit from
my Damage Zone into my hand!
Candle Celestial, Sariel!
I then move a unit from my
deck to the Damage Zone.
Next, I add +10000 to the
power of my Vanguard!
On top of that, I move Arabaki back.
With Penuel's skill, she moves to the Soul!
I superior call one unit
from the Damage Zone!
Underlay Celestial, Hesediel!
I put one unit from my
deck into the Damage Zone.
I'm not done yet!
I call Sariel and Counterblast!
When Sariel is called to the rear-guard,
I can take one Angel Feather unit
from my deck and put it in the Damage Zone.
Zerachiel.
I move one unit from my
Damage Zone to the Drop Zone.
With this, Hesediel's skill activates!
When Zerachiel is in the Damage Zone,
Hasdeya gets +3000 power!
You're doing a wonderful
job of linking skills!
And if you think I'm done, tsk-tsk-tsk!
You're gravely mistaken!
Dance, angel wings!
Glide with graceful intensity
to the rhythm of the sky!
Zerachiel's Limit Break!
Shining Feather!
When a face-up Zerachiel
is in the Damage Zone,
all units with "Celestial" in
their name get +3000 power!
Here I go, Aichi Sendou!
Sariel attacks with a boost from Arabaki!
Damage trigger check...
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Gancelot!
You've got him in a corner!
Good for you, Rekka!
Hey!
But this is a major trigger...
Zerachiel attacks!
I guard with Elixir!
And Phallon intercepts!
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger!
I give all the effects to Ramiel!
She drew a critical trigger!
Second check...
No trigger.
I'll end it here!
Ramiel attacks with a boost from Hesediel!
Perfect guard with Halo Liberator, Mark!
Shucks...
Turn end.
Wow, Aichi!
Emi...
Ah, that's right. Too bad...
Yeah. But if she can make it
through this coming turn...
You've still got a chance to win!
Good luck, Rekka!
Well, that's okay...
Yeah...
You...
I can see why Kourin acknowledges his skill.
She's strong...
But that just makes me want to win more!
Friend of my soul...
Join forces with the solitary king...
...and open up a new world!
Break ride!
Liberator of the Round Table, Alfred!
Break ride's skill!
My Vanguard receives +10000 power!
Three of my rear-guards
receive +5000 power each!
Alfred's Counterblast!
I superior call one Gold
Paladin unit from my deck!
Break through the limit!
Alfred's Limit Break!
Each of my "Liberator" rear-guards
receives +2000 power!
Wingal boosts Alfred!
Drive trigger check!
Damage trigger check!
No trigger...
Wingal's skill!
Wingal moves to the Soul.
When it boosts a unit with
"Liberator" in its name
and that unit's attack hits
the opponent's Vanguard,
I can call Blaster Blade
Liberator from the Soul!
Stand up once more, my avatar!
Blaster Blade Liberator!
Counterblast!
I retire one of my opponent's
rear-guard units!
Sariel!
Now she can't use any interceptors!
Blaster Blade attacks with
a boost from Pomerugal!
I guard with Shemhaza!
Escrad attacks with a boost from Marron!
I can't guard...
No guard!
Damage trigger check...
No trigger...
Too bad...
Aw, I lost!
Calling Blaster Blade one more
time is what decided the fight.
Rekka wasn't able to defend
herself against it.
I'm moved!
Vanguard really is interesting!
That was the best! I knew
you could do it, Sendou!
You little...
You were really cool, Rekka.
You too, Aichi!
Well, thanks!
You don't care if she
speaks casually to Aichi?
Getting bugged about something as trivial
as that is petty of you, Ishida.
Everything is trivial in
front of Rekka's cuteness.
Yeah, whatever...
Even though Shingo claims
to be such a fan of Aichi,
he doesn't even know that
Emi is his little sister...
What?! Little sister?!
No wonder she's strong!
Rekka, I really enjoyed our match.
I don't like losing,
but I had fun, too!
I had a good time, too.
And I was able to find new fight friends...
That's right!
Middle school division
Vanguard Fight Circle...
It seems even the next generation
is cultivating new abilities.
Rekka...
Welcome to the Komoi Corps!
Komoi Corps?
You're qualified to join.
You can join as well, Emi and Mai.
No thank you!
What?!
Th-Then I'll join Rekka's fan club!
Thanks!
You're welcome to join!
That's an idol for you!
Wow...
In the end, the middle school division beat
the high school division, two matches to one.
It's like, what did Shingo
and Naoki come here for?
Rekkaaaaaaa!
We maintained our dignity,
thanks to Aichi's win.
Rekka is so cute!
I'm head over heels...
I take back what I said!
We lost all our dignity!
Yeesh! How are we supposed to win
against other schools at this rate?!
Other schools...
Certainly, it is a little worrying...
Next time: Reunion with the Wind!
I-I don't believe it! Is that the guy...
...known as the one who bears the legend
of the wind and sea on his shoulders?!
L-Leon?!