Attack, Battler of the
Twin Brush, Polaris!
He withstood that attack?!
Now it's my turn!
Repel the darkness with the
brilliance of your proud soul!
Crossride!
Blazing Lion, Platina Ezel!
And then, Ultimate Break!
Let your souls soar! Spirit Unite Platinum!
The VF Circuit final
stage has come to an end!
With Aichi Sendou's victory,
Team Q4 becomes the champions!
You did it, Brother!
That was great, Aichi!
Oh, it was brilliant!
Q4 won against these formidable opponents.
And their ace is Aichi Sendou!
It was so very exciting!
Thank you!
There are now hundreds of millions of people
playing card games all over the world.
They've become a normal
part of our daily lives.
Cardfight! Vanguard.
That's the card game that's receiving
the most attention right now.
Some months after winning the VF Asia Circuit,
an international Vanguard tournament,
I became a high school student...
...at Miyaji Academy.
Morning, Aichi.
Good morning, Misaki.
Are you getting used to the school?
No... I mean, yes, kind of...
In other words, what happens in
various locations around the world
is no longer just confined to those areas,
but is becoming connected on a global scale.
This is what we call the
age of globalization.
In this age of globalization, what used
to be common knowledge no longer applies.
Um... How will you survive, Aichi Sendou?!
Yes?
Sendou, as a young man living in this age of
globalization, how would you like to get by?
U-Um...
Uh...
What's he so nervous about?
It's probably just an act.
I think this is the first time he's spoken
since transferring to this high school.
What's the problem, Sendou?
I... I, uh...
I guess I'd like to take
good care of my hobby.
Hobby? What is it?
Um... it's, uh...
Cardfight, for example...
Cardfights?
And that's how you live your life?
No, n-never mind.
Cardfighting is his hobby?
Does he think that'll help him
survive the age of globalization?
Jeez, he already looks like a little
kid. He doesn't have to act like one!
You could say he's pathetic
on a global level!
Quiet!
Our goal here at Miyaji Academy
is to cultivate young people so that
they thrive in the age of globalization.
Certainly, the object of your devotion
seems to be popular these days,
but don't you think focusing on academics
would be a better use of your time, Sendou?
S-Sorry...
Th-That didn't go well...
Boring dude...
Stand Up the High School!
Sendou, you haven't decided what club
you're going to join yet, have you?
You have heard that it's mandatory for
all students here to be in a club, right?
Ah... yes... uh...
Is there something that you like to do?
My hobby is...
Ah! That's right, you said before.
"Cardfight," I think? What is that?
Um, well...
It's a game where you fight
each other with cards.
If you'd like...
We don't have a Cardfight club...
Ah, I-I see...
I'm going home.
Make sure you decide on your
club this week, Sendou!
Oh, Ishida?
I haven't gotten your club application.
Oh, leave me alone...
Hey! You should listen when
someone's talking to you!
Sheesh...
Jeez...
Everything's as boring as always!
And everybody here is so darn serious...
It's like, there isn't anything you
can really be passionate about here...
What was his name... Aichi Sendou?
That guy...
I bet that kid never has any fun...
What's with him?
It's like, the second school let
out, his whole demeanor changed.
Has he got somethin' going?
Maybe he's actually an elite
athlete with some sports club...
Or maybe outside of school,
he's a gang leader...
Yeah, right...
Hello!
Card Capital? What is this?
Welcome!
What is this shop?!
Call!
This is...
This is a trading card game shop.
Trading card?
Um... it's, uh... Cardfight, for example...
There he is!
It's really been a long time!
He's talkin' to little kids?!
Yeah. We've come to research the card-playing population in Japan,
since Japan still has the
most Vanguard fighters.
You might be right.
So, how's Mitsusada doing?
He's doing well!
He's making awesome strides.
Well, not like us, though...
Oh? Remind me, who lost to him last time?
More importantly, I wanna meet
a Japanese maid while I'm here!
There you go again with that!
Wow! That's Singapore's Team Genius!
What's the problem? Everybody
looks forward to their own thing.
They're Aichi's rivals!
W-What the heck?!
Those guys aren't Japanese!
What's up, Sendou?
You're like a totally different
person here than at school!
And you're buddies with some
guys from another country?
Talk about global!
Anyway, how'd you get like this?
U-Um, here...
What is this?
Cardfight.
Cardfight?
It's Vanguard.
Don't tell me you've never heard of it?
You fight each other with cards.
It's a card game that's
really popular worldwide.
Vanguard?
Worldwide?
That's right.
A lot of countries hold
international tournaments, too.
You really don't know about it?
It's common knowledge!
Common knowledge, you say?
Oh, boy, you're a goner.
Girls aren't gonna go for
a know-nothing like you.
What was that?!
M-Me?!
So this is Vanguard?
Uh huh. You use this deck to battle.
Um... Do you want to try it?
F-Fine. I'll play along once.
This is a new trial deck.
Would you like to try it out?
Y-Yeah...
The VF Circuit champion has a challenger!
This guy's a tough opponent!
Have you finished reading the rulebook?
Yeah. I can do this.
Then I'll explain the rules as we go along.
Can I go first?
Yeah, sure...
This guy is nothing like he is at school!
I put a grade 0 card facedown
in the Vanguard circle
and the deck goes here.
Got it.
I draw five cards from my deck.
If there are any cards in your hand you
don't like, you can redraw them once.
You should try to have a lineup of
grade 1, 2, and 3 cards in your hand.
How's your hand, Ishida?
No prob.
Then let's get started.
Try to picture it...
Picture it?
Right now, we're weak astral bodies
that have appeared on the planet Cray,
a world much like our own.
You say this is the planet Cray?
On this world, we've been given two powers.
The first is the ability to summon units,
the creatures that live on this planet.
Call!
You summon units
from the five cards that
you drew from the deck.
Each card has a grade and
an ability score on it.
And the other ability is riding,
where your astral body possesses a unit.
The unit that we ride is called a Vanguard.
Vanguard?
So the game starts with us as Vanguards,
standing on the planet Cray.
We turn over the facedown
card at the same time,
and say "Stand up, Vanguard!"
Stand up, Vanguard!
Angelic Liberator!
Stone Bullet Eradicator, Houki!
So we're both standing on the
planet Cray as Vanguards.
I'm starting, so I get to move first.
First, I draw from the deck.
Then, if I have a card in my hand that's
one grade higher, I can ride it.
I ride Little Liberator, Marron!
And then I call Future Liberator, Llew!
The person who goes first can't
attack, so that's it for me.
I see.
All right.
I ride Red River Dragoon.
Like I did before,
you can summon a unit from
your hand as an ally,
if it's the same grade
as your Vanguard or less.
The units that you summon
are your allies and can fight along with your Vanguard.
That's what "call" is.
All right.
I call Dust Storm Eradicator, Toko.
The player who goes second
can attack from the start.
You rest a front row unit
by putting it on its side
and then announce your attack.
Okay, like this, right?
Red River attacks Marron!
When the Vanguard attacks,
you can turn over a card from your deck.
That's called a "drive check."
Critical trigger!
Critical... trigger?
Yup. Look at the top right mark.
See, there are four kinds of triggers.
This is a critical trigger.
You get an extra critical, which
increases your opponent's damage,
and gives you +5000 power.
For example, if you give
the critical to Red River
and the power to Toko...
That's what I'll do!
I took 2 damage.
So I turn over two cards for a damage check.
I didn't get any triggers, so I put
both cards into the Damage Zone.
Whoever gets six damage in this
space first loses the fight.
Now, you can attack once more.
R-Right. Toko attacks Marron.
Of course, you don't just have to sit
back and take your opponent's attacks.
I can call cards from my
hand to guard against them.
I guard with Fortune Liberator!
You calculate your guarding power
with this number on the side.
I used this unit as a guardian, so
afterwards, I put it in the Drop Zone.
Good job.
Now it's my turn.
Draw!
If I have a grade 2 card, I
can ride it as the Vanguard.
Here I go!
Stand up, my avatar! I ride...
...Blaster Blade Liberator!
Who would've figured, a Gold
Paladin Blaster Blade, y'know?
So this is Sendou's new deck...
I have a feeling it's
gonna be really popular.
Is this guy...
...really the same Aichi Sendou?
I call Gallatin and Zoom Down Eagle!
And now I attack!
Attack!
When you attack, you can have a
unit that was called to the back
boost the unit in front
of it to give it power.
I boost with Future Liberator, Llew
and attack with Blaster Blade!
Drive check.
Um... Is something wrong?
D-Darn it! I refuse to
buy into these images!
This is ridiculous... For a second
there, I thought this guy was cool!
Nothin's wrong! You gonna
attack again or what?!
It's my turn! Um...
Stand...
...and...
...draw.
Y-Yeah, that!
Stand and draw!
All right... stand up, my...
"My..."?
M-My mistake! One more time!
Strike, my avatar! I ride...
...Eradicator, Thunder Boom Dragon!
How's my ride?!
Y-Yeah. It's great!
Yeah, right?! Okay!
Now I'm gonna show you my power!
Here I go!
Call! Call!
Uh... Toko goes to the back
and I call all the rest!
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks!
Next, Jeem!
Thunder Boom Dragon!
I ride Dignified Gold Dragon!
Strike, my avatar!
I ride Discharging Dragon!
With a boost from Llew, Dignified
attacks Discharging Dragon!
Shoot! I can't guard!
6 damage...
So the game's over.
U-Um, Ishida...?
I'm outta here!
U-Um...
Old man! I'm buyin' this.
O-Old man...?
Ishida...
I wonder if I made him mad...
Hey, Aichi.
Kai! Guys!
Darn it! Darn it! Darn it!
Who is that guy?! Darn it!
He's actually cool!
What is that Vanguard?! Darn it!
Feels like my body's heatin'
up from deep inside!
So you had your first Cardfight with
someone from the same high school...
But I got caught up in it and won...
Nah, you went plenty easy on
that hot-blooded kid, Aichi.
'Cause no matter how many times you told him,
he kept calling all of his cards, even
the ones he could've used for guarding.
What're you lookin' at?!
Beginners have the tendency to
devote themselves to attacking.
That type's not popular with the ladies...
As if you're the popular one...
Huh, don't you know how many girlfriends I have?
...What?
No, I didn't know!
You laughin' at me, you little brat?!
You can't find a fellow Vanguard player...
...in a good school like Miyaji Academy?
Nope. It's a school that focuses
on preparing for college.
Besides, there aren't any
kids who are interested...
I see...
We've got a Vanguard boom at our school.
Wanna transfer over?
Thank you.
But...
Kai?
If he bought a deck on his way out,
that means he's interested in Vanguard.
I see...
Get your act together.
You're a leader, remember?
Oh, that's...
But...
If Ishida is interested in Vanguard,
I've got to reach out to him.
Thank you, Kai!
Jeez...
You're a different person
from when you fight...
I see. That's right!
You're a nice guy, Kai.
Exactly!
I just don't understand
the feelings of men...
He would've realized it even
if I hadn't said anything.
But you felt the need to say it?
That's not it.
It's just...
Seeing him sitting there
at a loss, it slipped out.
Even though he's already plenty strong...
Come on, seriously, switch to our school!
Yeah, it's a great idea!
I'll intro you to everybody
as my number one disciple!
Never mind that, but it'd be fun!
Aichi, you still haven't made
any friends at that school?
Nope...
Boy, you're helpless.
But if you insisted,
you could always come over to the
middle school during your lunch hour
and play Vanguard with Mai and me.
Thanks for breakfast!
Aichi...
Morning!
He's not here yet...
Rise!
Bow!
Take your seats!
Morning.
Starting today, we've got
a new student in our class.
Come in.
She's an idol!
I've seen her before somewhere, too!
Idiot! You don't know who she is?!
She's so cute!
Kourin...?
Kourin
I'm Kourin Tatsunagi.
This is my first day at Miyaji Academy.
Kourin Tatsunagi
It's a pleasure to meet everyone.
E-Ehhh?!
I'm Aichi Sendou, a first-year high school
student in Class A at Miyaji Academy.
I'm enjoying my life as a
Vanguard fighter to the full!
Sounds like you're leading a
fun, positive high school life.
Kourin!
That's my dream, anyway...
So you're starting your new life
with a heart filled with dreams...
Then your dreams will be destroyed
and you'll be grief-stricken.
Please stop that!
It's important to have hopes and dreams!
Next time: Catching a Break!
No matter what happens, I'm
going to break the limit and keep moving forward!