It's unusual for you to visit here.
I came to battle a strong fighter.
Are you strong?
In other words, I'll do as an opponent?
It's been a long time since we've fought.
I've gotten better, you know.
And I've got new power.
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
What is this?
Star-vader, Dust Tail Unicorn.
Greedy Hand.
What is that unit?
Link Joker.
Star-vader, Dust Tail Unicorn...
This fight is the start of
my new life with Link Joker.
The power I sense just
by getting these cards...
This is my new deck!
The Power of the Black Ring
Kourin isn't here today either?!
Hurry up and come back!
A time supposed to be the spring of
my youth has become as dry as a fall day.
Well, she is the element that
puts a spring in your step!
Kai isn't with you today, either?
Nope. I saw him at school,
but he blew us off again.
What?!
As a fellow Narukami player, I wanted
to pick his brain about building a deck!
I'll tell you everything you need to
know about putting together a deck.
After all, Kai is my disciple!
Seriously?!
In exchange, when Kourin comes back,
make sure I'm the first one to know.
S-Sure...
Cut it out! Don't just spout
whatever comes to mind
to somebody who doesn't
know any better, Lose-umi!
Excuse me?! My name is "Katsumi"!
I've gotten a little better, haven't I?
Hmm... I feel like I've seen
this scene somewhere before...
Until you beat me, you're gonna be Lose-umi!
Is it deja vu?
It's Katsumi!
Lose-umi!
Katsumi!
Kai...
I ride King of Masks, Dantarian!
Call! Gwynn the Ripper!
I use its skill to retire Radon!
I attack Krypton with a
boost from Greedy Hand!
Skill activated! Soulcharge!
Dantarian receives +1000 power.
Twin drive check.
I give the power to Gwynn and
the extra critical to Dantarian!
It seems you were telling the
truth about getting better.
Did you think I'd gotten rusty after
turning my efforts to training fighters?
No. We've fought beside each other, and
I acknowledge your skills as a fighter.
After all, if I didn't...
Gwynn the Ripper attacks with a
boost from Doreen the Thruster!
Guard!
This is fun for me too, Kai.
I don't get the chance to have serious
fights like this against my students.
You came when I had passion
I didn't know what to do with.
You saw the fight between Ren and
Aichi Sendou too, didn't you?
The fight that had a chance at the VF
High School Championship on the line...
Both of them were at the top of their game.
Both gave us a first-rate fight.
That got my soul fired up.
It made me want to strive for greater
heights, even aim for the top myself!
Aren't you the same way?
That's why you've changed clans, to expand
possibilities for yourself and try to improve.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
Stand and draw.
Ride the Vanguard!
The black and white link,
Star-vader, Infinite Zero Dragon!
I have an ominous feeling about this...
Call.
Here I go.
I attack Gwynn the Ripper!
Guard!
Infinite Zero!
Furious Claw Star-vader, Niobium!
Guard!
Turn end.
Impressive. But what was that
sinister power I sensed?
Power, huh?
This isn't anywhere near
the power I've tasted yet.
You should be able to...
What?!
You should be able to draw out that power.
What are you talking about?
Kai is acting strange!
You have my respect as a fighter.
I know you have what it
takes to handle Link Joker.
Don't tell me...
Is that how it is?
I've seen those eyes before!
They're the same eyes that Ren had when
he lost himself to the power of Psyqualia.
But I never thought that you, of all people,
would make the same mistake!
What about it?
When it happened to Ren, I didn't
have the power to stop him.
All I could do was watch.
But things are different now!
Stand and draw!
Spread the wings of your soul, and
unleash that noble power of darkness!
Break ride!
Demon World Marquis, Amon!
Link Joker...
Certainly, I sense an unknown power.
But you can only bring out the true
power of a deck after mastering it.
I'm gonna stop you with my Dark Irregulars!
I activate King of Masks,
Dantarian's break ride skill!
Demon World Marquis, Amon gets +10000 power.
And three Dark Irregulars get +1000
power for every card in the Soul!
When I move a Dimension Creeper
from my Soul to the Drop Zone,
I can Soulcharge two cards.
And because of that, three of my
rear-guard units get +5000 power.
Amon's power also increases with its skill.
Demon World Marquis, Amon attacks
with a boost from Greedy Hand!
Kai! I'll purify you with the
flames of the demon world!
Go, Amon! Purgatory Purification!
Yes. This is the power I was looking for.
Surpassing this strong power is what
awakens the true power of Link Joker!
Guard!
Perfect guard...
Next! Gwynn the Ripper!
No guard.
Tetsu. It was a fitting power for the
beginning of Link Joker's journey.
Final Turn!
Stand and draw!
Break ride the Vanguard!
Star-vader, Nebula Lord Dragon!
Break ride skill! 10000 power...
...and I can lock one of your
front and back row units.
Lock?!
Lock the rear-guard!
What?!
What is this?!
Cards... locked?!
The skill of Niobium and Lanthanum.
For every locked unit, they get +2000 power.
Nebula Lord Dragon, Counterblast!
I get to lock one of my
opponent's back row units!
Lock the rear-guard!
With this, they get another +2000 power.
Limit Break!
For each locked unit of my opponent,
all of my front row units get +3000 power!
All of your front row units get power?!
And what is "lock"?!
Call.
Unicorn boosts.
Go! Nebular Lord Dragon!
Intercept!
Locked units have had everything stolen.
What?!
So even if you manage to
make it through this turn,
the lock isn't lifted until
the end of your turn.
It lasts until the next turn?!
You're helpless to do anything
but crumple to my attacks.
First check!
I give the power to Neon and the
extra critical to Nebula Lord.
Second check.
W-What is this...?
What is this fearsome skill?
What is this fearsome clan?!
Picture it.
A destroyer with ultimate
power beyond imagining,
appearing after crossing millions
of stars and dimensions!
Good god...
W-What the...?!
It seems you were able to picture it.
That was...
I'm trembling.
Ridiculous... Me?!
That sinister vibe I sensed
before wasn't my imagination!
Kai! Wake up!
That's a power you mustn't get involved with!
So what?
Nebula Lord Dragon!
Mobius Breath Dragon!
More than I imagined...
This is Link Joker.
This is the ultimate power
that I was looking for!
Well done...
...Toshiki Kai.
Kai...
You must know better than anyone...
...the folly of being seduced
and corrupted by power.
So why?!
I haven't been seduced or corrupted.
Reverse...
I've been reborn.
That's all.
Reverse... What is that?!
Was that Toshiki Kai?
Shinjou!
What's wrong, Shinjou?!
A fighter who's been defeated by the power
of Link Joker loses control of his own power.
And... then he's reborn.
I will master this deck and make it mine.
Once I do that, Ren... and Aichi too...
Kourin's off today too?
Naoki...
But just 'cause Kourin's not here
is no reason to be bummed out
first thing in the morning.
I'm not especially bummed out!
Kind of strange weather, huh?
Yeah. It looks like the clouds
are covering the whole town.
I don't like that sky.
It really is nasty.
Aren't you coming in?
Suiko...
Long time no see.
Are you done working today?
My real work is just about to begin.
It feels like a lot of
weird things are going on.
And I don't like it.
Neither Tetsu nor Asaka came to meet me...
That's a first.
I wonder what's happening.
I can explain.
Let's go in and sit...
Huh?
I'll be waiting.
If I want to talk, I have to
beat everyone here, is that it?
Then so be it.
Well... Your turn is next, Ren Suzugamori.
Mordred Phantom!
Have a nice day.
We're your next opponents.
You?
You're as cold as always.
Even though all I did was dream about
becoming a member of your team, AL4...
But then it hit me.
If you won't let me be on your team...
I'll let you be on mine!
What a pain...
Hey, what's goin' on here?
We went to all the trouble of making
uniforms so we could infiltrate Fukuhara
and then enter the VF High School Championship,
but this hubbub wasn't part of the deal.
Although you're probably the
one who brought it on...
You're wrong. The person causing all this
is inside, but these four won't let me pass.
By the by, who are you?
You don't remember me?!
Darn it! All right, fine!
What are your intentions?
Shut up! This guy is my prey!
Get goin'! Nobody's gonna beat you but me!
Right. On my way.
W-Wait!
Shut up! Your opponent is me, jerk!
I'm gonna show you what
being outclassed means!
I appreciate this, Kyou Yahagi.
Y-You...
Rat! You little rat!
Come and get me!
"Crusher" Kyou Yahagi will take you all on!
That was fast.
I've come.
Now will you keep up your end of the
bargain and tell me what this is about?
Sure I will. If you can beat me...
You're really making me
jump through hoops here.
But it's making me all the more curious.
A fight with you, Suiko...
This should be interesting.
Even more interesting...
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Frontline Revenger, Claudas!
Micro-hole Dracokid!
This promises... to be quite fun.
The power that's coursing through me...
It's urging me to destroy!
This is the power that I've been longing for!
Those clouds hint at a storm to come...
And they're coming to smother this
fun, peaceful school life.
Next time: Dark Clouds
Over Fukuhara High School!
Dark Clouds Over Fukuhara High School!
My friends... My comrades...
The darkness in their hearts
has come to the surface!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Fukuhara High!
But... what am I angry about?
Somebody explain things to me!