From Miyaji Academy: Aichi Sendou!
And from Hitsue High School...
...Yuuta Izaki!
Go get 'im, Izaki!
Yeah!
Aichi... I'm gonna knock you for a loop!
Izaki...
Morikawa's not playing, after all...
I'm surprised, too. After he
went on about cutting me off...
Izaki? With his ability...
OOHL, yo!
Out of his league against
Aichi... Yeah, he sure is.
Yeah, right?
According to this information,
Yuuta Izaki has had no experience
participating in any of the official tournaments.
He's a completely unknown fighter.
And his opponent, Aichi Sendou, is
a member of the celebrated Team Q4!
This is a combination where one
side is at a distinct disadvantage.
A Man's Guts
With an unheard-of fighter like that,
this will be a piece of cake for Sendou.
So you say,
but who's the one that got his butt kicked
by Miwa, the guy who fought Boss Lady?
Sendou! Please don't let your guard down!
We haven't fought each other
in a long time, Izaki.
I'm going to go all out!
Just what I wanted to hear.
Come and get me, Aichi!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Wingal Liberator!
Ancient Dragon, Babyrex!
This is great! I didn't think I'd get
the chance to fight Aichi this early on!
Please!
When we fight Miyaji, let
me be in one of the matches!
W-What the heck? This is coming
from outta the black...
I think that's "out of the blue"...
Morikawa, please! I wanna fight Aichi!
This is the first time
I've seen you so serious.
Seems like you've got a reason.
Go ahead, tell the strongest
fighter about it.
We recently played against
Miyaji here, right?
Yeah.
You and Aichi fought...
It'd been a long time since I'd
seen Aichi fight up close...
A long time ago, he and I weren't
so different in terms of skill.
But now, to see him fight like that...
It made me wonder if I'm
satisfied with my own skill.
Thinking about it burned me up.
How far can I get?
I wanna find out for myself!
Izaki!
Morikawa...
I'm totally moved!
You're a real man!
I like that enthusiasm!
All right, I'll let you do it!
When we fight Miyaji, you get out there!
Morikawa...
"I wanna fight."
Is that all?
If you don't aim to win,
the fight has no value.
Win!
Come with me.
Kai!
I'm up next after Kai!
Miwa!
Every day, from now 'til the tournament,
we're gonna do special training. Got it?
Yeah!
All right! I'm next after Miwa!
I'll do everything in my
power to make you stronger!
I'm gonna focus on this alone and
not think about anything else!
Does that include Kourin?
Yeah! I'll show you!
I'll cut Kourin off, too!
Are you prepared?
Yes!
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Sendou's attack is finished.
Izaki has 4 damage.
Sendou is in the lead with 3 damage.
Thanks, Miwa... Morikawa... Kai.
Thanks for helping me train.
I'm gonna show you just how
much progress I've made, Aichi!
Put the pride of your fighting
tribe on the line...
...and come back from ancient times!
Break ride!
Ancient Dragon, Spinodriver!
The break ride's skill! I put two
units into the Drop Zone!
And that lets me prepare two new friends!
Draw!
On top of that, Spinodriver gets
+10000 and an extra critical!
Next, Babyrex's skill!
When I put it in the Drop Zone,
I get to superior call Tyrannolegend!
Call!
Here I go, Aichi!
Izaki... What fierce fighting spirit!
This is the first time I've
seen Izaki so psyched!
Go, Tyrannolegend! Attack Phallon!
Guard!
Spinodriver, attack Gancelot!
I'm not the same person I was yesterday!
You're gonna take that damage!
Perfect guard with Mark!
Criollofall, attack Phallon!
Izaki took out one rear-guard,
but wasn't able to do any damage.
Still, what an exciting devel-o-pment!
Right!
Well, it's Aichi. I never thought
this would be easy...
Izaki...
I've got to widen the gap
between us right now!
Call!
I attack Criollofall!
Guard!
I attack Spinodriver!
Perfect guard!
Alfred!
Sendou has Izaki on the
r-o-pes with 5 damage!
That makes the damage 3 to 5!
Sendou has a big lead!
Don't talk stupid!
Izaki was just warming up!
Cool down, Morikawa!
But he's right. The scariness of
Tachikaze is just about to be shown.
Watch this, Aichi.
I'm gonna win it this turn!
When this ballad of destruction rings
out, it signifies the end of the world!
Break ride!
Ancient Dragon, Tyrannolegend!
The break ride's skill!
Iguanogorg's skill! When I
put it in the Drop Zone...
...it can superior call
itself with a Counterblast!
What the heck is that?!
After Iguanogorg goes to the Drop Zone,
you can bring it back to the battle line.
Tyrannolegend's Especial Counterblast!
Your deck is Tachikaze.
Leave as many cards as you can in your hand.
Don't throw away cards by guarding.
Tachikaze's characteristic is powering
up by retiring your rear-guard.
So you've gotta look ahead to what you're
gonna do when the rear-guard is empty.
Call!
Oh, my! The rear-guard circle that was empty
has suddenly been filled with three units!
His offensive is plenty ready to attack!
And not only that, his Vanguard is the
mega-powerful dinosaur, Tyrannolegend!
Criollofall, attack Gallatin!
Izaki... is doin' great...
Hey, Aichi...
Way back when, just the idea of fighting
was enough to make us nervous.
But eventually, you got so strong
that I was nowhere near you anymore.
Aichi...
What you're looking at...
The view that only the strong can see...
I wanna see it, too!
Izaki...
Here I go!
Tyrannolegend, attack Gancelot!
Aichi, I'm gonna beat you!
And I'm gonna surpass the
limits constantly to do it!
Limit Break!
I sacrifice three units!
With those sacrifices, Tyrannolegend
gets +10000 and an extra critical!
That one unit has 36000 power!
And on top of that, it's got
a total of three criticals!
Is it a monster?!
If his attack goes through, Aichi
will lose right then and there.
Come back to life, Iguanogorg!
Epona! Please!
Also, Elixir Liberator! And Escrad!
You too, Marron!
Five cards to guard?!
He used up his whole hand!
If he hadn't, he wouldn't have
been able to block the attack!
Even so, it's not guaranteed
that he can stop it.
If Izaki draws two triggers, he'll
have more power than Aichi.
Right now, Tyrannolegend has three criticals.
If that attack goes through...
...the showdown will be decided!
He's incredible...
To paint Aichi into a corner like this...
Twin drive check!
There it is! A critical trigger!
Izaki drew a trigger!
I give the power to Tyrannolegend and
the extra critical to Beamankylo!
Second check!
If the second card is a trigger as well,
Izaki pretty much wins automatically!
Come on, trigger!
Come on, trigger! Come on, trigger!
Aww, too bad for Izaki!
The second card wasn't a trigger!
However, with that attack,
Sendou used up his entire hand!
He's unable to defend anymore!
Beamankylo attacks!
Beam Sweep!
Sendou takes 2 damage!
Now they both have 5 damage.
Sendou has also been boxed in!
Wow, what an amazing fight.
They're locked together!
Engaged in a powerful heated battle!
Sendou will do whatever it
takes to end it this next turn.
However, he has zero cards in his hand.
And his left column is empty. You certainly
can't call it a perfect framework.
If Izaki can hold out through this turn,
he's got a very good chance of victory!
Sendou's nerve-wracking turn has begun!
I managed to protect myself,
but it wouldn't have been surprising
if Izaki had won with that attack.
But... I want to...
...win this fight, too!
Stand up, my avatar!
Call! Blaster Blade Liberator!
Skill activated!
Alfred attacks!
Guard!
Gancelot!
18000 versus 21000!
At this point, he's possibly blocked it!
But we don't know yet.
If Sendou draws a trigger,
Izaki's defeat is g-o-ing to be certain!
I see...
So this is the sight that you saw...
Twin drive check.
Second check...
The winner: Aichi Sendou!
I lost...
Huh?
What is this?
I feel so frustrated...
Nice fight!
Both did great!
Well done!
The completely unknown Yuuta Izaki showed
us a wonderful fight with Aichi Sendou!
Right now, those two are being serenaded
with thunderous applause from all over the hall!
This is the High School Championship...
This is what the VF High School
Championship is all about!
Aichi...
You're cool, Aichi!
You're cool too, Izaki!
Our High School Championship is over, huh?
Sorry...
You got nothin' to apologize about.
Nice fight! Right?
Yes! I could see bushido
in your fighting spirit!
We're a team. And as a team,
we fought our best.
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Kai...
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah!
It's too bad I wasn't able to fight,
but now that the fight's over...
Love
...my denial of Kourin is over!
Kourin Love
From here on out, Kourin, fight!
Today, Izaki showed a lot of ability.
But still...
Just how strong is Aichi getting?
We are so late!
I wonder if the tournament's gotten far.
I just hope Aichi and the
others are still in it.
Miss Emi!
DDI! CCSLL, yo!
Don't do it! Cause a commotion here, and
you'll be on the same level as Lose-umi!
At last, the final fight of the VF High
School Championship, Kanto Block 3!
The two teams that have
won out to the end are...
...Miyaji Academy's Cardfight Club...
...and Fukuhara High School's Vanguard Club!
No surprise that they're here,
the most favored to win...
Well, no way are we gonna lose!
Let's give it all we've got, everyone!
Of course!
Both of you, that was a great fight!
Sorry. I lost after being
selfish about fighting...
Don't worry about it.
Kai, Miwa, and I all knew how you felt,
which is why we gave you special training.
Thank you, Izaki. Serious fights
like that make us stronger.
Hitsue High club members,
we're going to straighten up and aim
for the VF High School Championship!
Our next opponent is Fukuhara High School!
Next time: Challenger Naoki!
Challenger Naoki!
We've really got to get
on the ball for this...
Kourin, good luck!
You know, you never change...