You keep goin' on about bein' alone,
but in the first place, us Cardfighters
are alone when we fight.
But in the middle of fightin',
I think the feelin's between the
two opponents are communicated.
I mean, if it ain't a fight
like that, where's the fun?
It's big talk, I know, but
that's what somebody told me.
A fellow member of the Cardfight Club.
Ishida...
So fighters like us...
Me and you, we ain't alone!
Naoki! Shingo!
Sendou...
Hey. We did it...
While I was in doubt, Naoki and Shingo...
I've decided.
I'm through hesitating.
I'm going to Takuto's place.
Aichi...
I won't tolerate whatever
made the world like this.
Even if Kamui, Takuto...
...and Kai are the enemies.
I'll fight them!
Naoki?
It's nothin'.
Naoki...?
I think you should get some rest.
We can't have you dragging us down.
Says the guy whose knees are shakin'.
They are not...
I'm mortified.
You stayed up all night
putting together a deck
and then battling all
those Reversed fighters.
I don't blame you.
Leave the rest to Misaki and me.
From here on, even stronger fighters
are gonna come out to play, right?
Like I could rest now,
bein' a fellow brother-in-arms!
Y'know?
That's right.
Here we go.
I've been waiting for you, Aichi Sendou.
Kamui...
Aichi and Kamui
I've been waiting for you, Aichi Sendou.
Hey, kid. A middle school student
should respect his elders.
I'm not here for nobodies like you.
What was that?! You little...
Naoki!
I'll go.
You were with him more than anyone.
Fighting against him
seriously would be...
That's exactly why.
Aichi?
That's exactly why I need
to fight and beat Kamui.
Okay.
Let's go, Kamui.
Yeah.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Kamui... I swear I'll
bring you back to normal.
The great Kamui rides Beast Deity, Blank Marsh!
I ride Little Liberator, Marron!
Beast Deity, Damned Leo.
And then I call!
Damned Leo!
Hatred Chaos!
Damage check.
They both drew a heal trigger...
Who will get the upper hand?
Well, his opponent's just a middle
schooler, so Aichi should be fine.
In Team Q4, Sendou was
like the leader figure.
But it didn't start out that way.
At the beginning,
Aichi was a lot weaker than him.
Team Q4...
Sendou and Misaki...
And Kamui Katsuragi...
And Toshiki Kai...
I've idolized them as a top fighting team!
Yeah. For me, they're a huge goal.
Darn it! A fight like this...
It's gotta be frustratin' for Aichi
more than anyone!
I stand and draw!
Ride!
W-What?!
Kamui?
Aichi Sendou! Showdown!
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade!
Special move! Hell Stand!
I attack Gancelot!
Please let me call you "Brother"!
Brother!
Kamui...
Liberator of Royalty, Phallon!
Guard!
Escrad!
Attack!
Guard!
He protected himself three times!
What's wrong? Your attacks aren't even close.
Is this all the strength you have?!
Beast Deity, Ethics Buster!
Call! Attack!
Intercept!
Aichi Sendou...
Somewhere in my heart,
I've been waiting impatiently for
this moment, this fight with you.
The first time we fought,
you were pretty much a novice.
But before I knew it, you were
standing next to me as a teammate...
And now you're way ahead of me.
A top world-class fighter...
Kamui...
Don't get the wrong idea. I'm not like Kai.
I wanted to be like you, Aichi Sendou.
How could you get that far, when we were in
the same place, at the same time, together?
I thought you were totally awesome.
So, when I got the power of Reverse...
My heart is quivering with excitement.
With this power, I could even fight you...
Probably fight you on equal terms, I thought.
So come at me with everything
you've got, Aichi Sendou!
Hatred Chaos!
Guard!
Got it, Kamui.
I'll seriously beat you!
Stand and draw!
Sweep down on the battlefield
once again, solitary warrior.
Guide the new leader with your noble wings!
I ride Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Call!
Attack!
Counterblast!
Superior call!
Gancelot attacks!
No guard.
Twin drive check.
I give the power to Phallon,
and the extra critical to Gancelot!
Second check.
With Enide's skill, I draw one card.
Phallon attacks!
No guard.
He did it!
All right! All the way to 4 damage!
But... there's no way
it'll end this easily.
I stand and draw.
Here I go, Aichi Sendou!
The strongest on Earth!
Anxiety, evil, and anguish,
grovel before Kamui the Great!
Crossbreak ride!
Strongest Beast Deity,
Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
This is...
This is Kamui's Reverse unit!
Here I go, Aichi Sendou!
Call!
Ethics Buster "Reverse's"
strongest Limit Break!
I lock two units!
And that sets everything up.
You're strong.
Every scrape you get into,
you always get out of.
But... how about when
faced with this skill?!
First!
Intercept!
Second!
No guard!
Third time!
Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
Twin drive. First check.
Second check.
5 damage...
Normally, Aichi would be able to hold out...
...but all of Kamui's units...
...are standing!
I wonder how many more times
you can handle this attack?
My Infinite Hell!
Here I go! Fourth time!
Marron!
Fifth!
Guard!
His guard worked!
Just a little more! Hang in there, Aichi!
Sixth!
He's still standin'?!
I can't believe it...
5 damage...
He only has three cards in his hand.
Sword Formation Liberator, Igraine guards!
You really think you can hold
out with just one card?!
I still have comrades!
Quintet Wall!
Counterblast!
I call these five units
to my guardian circles!
Twin drive...
...check!
Check!
All right!
But Kamui's attack isn't finished.
And on top of that, he's
powered up with a critical!
Seventh!
Epona!
Hatred Chaos!
This makes eighth!
I win!
W-What?!
Wow! A second Quintet Wall!
How...? Even with this power...?
Kamui. Earlier, you wondered...
We were in the same place and spent the same
time together, so how did I get stronger?
The answer is...
It was thanks to you, Kamui.
What?!
You're more experienced, you're my rival...
I look up to you.
Liar!
Sometimes I'm a weak fighter
who hesitates over fights.
But you're not afraid of anyone.
No matter what happens, you push forward.
I've always admired that about you.
Admired...?
Kamui... I'm here because you and our other
comrades were there in the beginning.
Me? Our comrades?
May your noble power rain down
and become the world's bond!
Crossbreak ride!
Liberator of Bonds, Gancelot Zenith!
Solitary Liberator, Gancelot's
break ride skill!
I add +10000 to Liberator of Bonds,
Gancelot Zenith's power!
And then +5000 power to
my three rear-guard units!
I became strong? Yeah. Maybe...
I've felt like that before...
But let me prove it...
Let me prove what our
comrades and you have said!
That's...
Team... Q4...
Gorlois's skill activated!
Phallon attacks!
Guard!
Gancelot Zenith!
Counterblast! And then, Limit Break!
Superior call!
Blaster Blade Liberator!
Blaster Blade!
With its skill, I add +3000 to Bruno's power!
Twin drive...
Darn it!
Kamui!
Brother...
It's over.
Kamui, are you okay?
Brother...
Kamui...
Misaki...
...and the guys from Miyaji Academy...
I was... Reversed, wasn't I?
I probably... did some bad things. I'm sorry.
No, you didn't. You didn't, Kamui.
Shucks. I'm so lame...
To have you support me, Brother...
I'm fine. It should be the opposite.
I should actually support...
Kamui?
H-Huh?
My legs have no strength...
Kamui!
Are you okay, Kamui?
Sorry... um... Glasses?
The name is Shingo Komoi.
And Ishi... Wannabe?
What the heck is that?! It's Naoki Ishida!
Being Reversed must take
a lot out of a person.
Feels like I ran 42.195 km
at my fastest pace.
But I also feel refreshed somehow...
Sorry. You seem pretty tired, too, Naoki...
Don't worry 'bout it!
Any comrade of Sendou's
is a comrade of ours.
Comrade, huh?
Comrade... Sounds good...
You're pretty slick for a middle schooler.
What's that?! 'Til just recently, you were
still a middle school student yourself, Naoki!
Restrain yourself!
Shut up, middle schooler!
Took you long enough.
But I guess the fact that you got this far
proves you're a tough nut to crack.
Miwa...
Kai...
Brother Aichi... Misaki... and, um...
Yeah, yeah! We're your merry
Miyaji Academy comrades!
Sorry to make you fuss over me.
No worries, middle schooler.
You did your best.
Right. Kamui, I'm the one
who needs to apologize.
After what happened in the
middle school division...
I'm sorry, everyone.
Next time: The Form of Friendship!
The Form of Friendship
Kai! Takuto!