Critical trigger.
I give the +5000 power
to Nullity Revenger.
I didn't think he'd draw a trigger there...
Ren Suzugamori... You're stronger
than I had imagined.
You're up?
It looks like you're back to normal.
The Reversed fighter has to lose.
In other words, I can't lose.
It stopped.
What is this?
Asaka's room...
The whole floor?
I see. You basically just got
here, Suiko, so you don't know.
The members of AL4 each have their own
private floor for fighting practice.
Team Asteroid is impressive.
It encourages the fighters
who are aiming for the top,
although I'm not sure who decided on it.
Huh? Was it me?
But out of all the members of
AL4, my room's the smallest.
Actually, this room used to be Kyou's...
Who's there?
Strong fighters just have to join us...
Asaka!
As I suspected, Asaka too...
Welcome to my stage, Ren-sama.
I've been waiting for you all this time...
Waiting for the chance
to fight you like this...
Ah... The power... The energy...
It's increasing!
It's like I can hear the crowd's
applause and roars of approval.
Suiko, please get back.
R-Right...
And now, the curtain is rising
on Asaka Narumi's gorgeous stage!
Ladies and gentlemen...
beginning with the very first act,
you won't be able to take
your eyes off this show.
With this one deck, Ren will become mine!
Yeesh! Let a guy take five at least!
Anyway, what in the world's wrong with them?
What's happening...?
I dunno... But that jerk Ren will
probably explain it to us later.
Now then, take out your deck, Ren.
Yes, that's it.
I can't wait!
I'm going to defeat you at this
circus and make you mine forever!
Asaka... You don't have
what it takes to beat me.
We'll just see about that.
This isn't my usual deck, you know.
Don't you feel this wondrous power too?
I'm going to take you down with this
power and turn you into my doll.
After that, you and I will dance forever.
It's not going to happen.
You'll see, once we get under way.
Eternal Marionette
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Frontline Revenger, Claudas!
Silver Thorn Assistant, Ionela.
And now, our circus begins!
I ride Revenger, Dark Bond Trumpeter!
Claudas moves back.
I can hear it...
The heartbeats of everyone in the audience,
becoming one and surging towards me.
I love this tense feeling.
As manager of this show, I wonder how many
of the crowd's hearts we can capture.
My heart's beating fast, too.
Keep your eyes peeled. You won't want to
miss a moment of the performers' moves.
I ride Silver Thorn Assistant, Irina!
Irina's skill. One card goes to the Soul.
It takes a wonderful trick
to make a wonderful show.
And wonderful performers as well.
Come, Silver Thorn, Breathing Dragon!
And now, let's begin the act.
Attack!
Next! Irina attacks!
Check.
Skill activated.
It's your turn soon.
That's Asaka all right.
Even Reversed, she still
makes use of the Soul a lot.
It's your turn, Ren.
I'm looking forward to the
second half of the show.
Yes, sure is something to look forward to...
Although why wait for the second
half when we could do it now?
I ride Nullity Revenger, Masquerade!
And then I call.
Attack!
Oh my, looks like it came through for me.
I give the power to Irina.
In that case, I attack Breathing Dragon!
The performers on stage won't exit so easily.
I have to protect my beloved performers.
After all, I am the manager.
So I constantly have to lead them, you see.
How does it feel to be under me, Ren?
So this is how you've really felt?
I'm surprised.
Don't talk like you know it all!
You know nothing... Nothing...
But I know a lot about you.
I know just how little you care
about what's going on around you.
When I met you for the first time...
I thought you were weird, because you
couldn't even open an automatic door.
Did that really happen?
You don't remember, do you?
Even though that was only a few years ago...
A lot sure has happened since then...
Harsh training, hard battles, bitter
relationships with rivals...
Number 40 out of 493 people...
Sometimes I wondered why I was
going to such a tough place
when I was still just a
middle school student...
But... you were there.
Your deck has gotten even more
interesting than last time.
You're a fast learner.
Ren...
Please keep up the good work.
I'm expecting to see a wonderful circus.
Right!
I was able to do my best all
that time because Ren was here.
I wanted to get even a little closer to Ren...
...to fight alongside him as a member of AL4...
So I never stopped trying to catch up.
But... those who lost were tossed aside.
As if you were looking at something foul.
telling them to get out of your sight.
You discard people who lose.
Huh? Do I?
But I don't do that any more, right?
Wrong! You're just the same!
You're the same!
You haven't changed...
Your eyes say "I have no need for the weak."
All you need is...
And no matter how much I catch up, you
won't look at me like you look at them.
That's right. I've been dancing
by myself this whole time.
A doll that belongs to no one...
But I'm saying goodbye to my former self!
I ride Silver Thorn Marionette, Lilian!
Okay, prepare to dance, Lilian.
My favorite marionette, let's
have one final lovely dance.
After all, once this fight is over, Ren will
become my dancing partner in your stead.
Call!
Now, the curtain rises on the second act!
Breathing Dragon attacks!
Guard!
Lilian!
Check!
I give the power to Rising Dragon
and the extra critical to Lilian!
Ionela's skill.
I present a fifth card to Ren's Damage Zone.
The damage is 5 to 1...
Ren Suzugamori is on the ropes?!
You become this much stronger
when you're Reversed?!
Lovely... The power is running through me.
I feel it!
That's right. The circus needs overwhelming
power to support its brilliant skills!
It's a real honor to be able to
drive Ren into a corner like this.
Asaka...
Bread and milk!
Gotta charge up! Gotta charge up!
Here ya go, sustenance!
Eat this and we'll be ready to go again!
You're a thoughtful guy.
What is this? A bean jam bun and milk?
All stuff I don't like!
Ah... is that right?
Yeesh. It's not good for
a growing boy to be picky.
What was that?!
You makin' a crack about my height?!
No, I wasn't!
H-Hey!
Ah! They found us!
Darn it!
Kyou...
I'll eat this for now!
I'll complain about it later.
You're gonna complain?
I'm gonna pound all you guys to bean jam!
Maybe you weren't expecting such a
big difference between our scores?
As someone who's putting on a show,
it's very important for me to
prepare unexpected developments.
You don't mind the idea of becoming mine
and dancing together forever, do you?
No, it sounds like fun.
But let's not go there. Here I go.
Despair! Then sprawl on the
ground and sip bitter water!
I ride Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
And then I call!
The emissary of fear appears
out of the ebony darkness
and lures you to the
netherworld without a sound.
Doreen's skill.
I'm going to counterattack.
I attack Breathing Dragon!
Mordred Phantom!
No guard.
Twin drive check!
I got a heal trigger.
I give the power to Blaster Dark.
And heal 1 damage point.
Second check...
Another trigger.
I give the critical to Mordred,
and the power to Blaster Dark.
My avatar, Blaster Dark!
The damage is 4 to 4...
That's just like you, Ren.
Even with my huge advantage,
you tied us up in one turn.
Have you forgotten?
I've never lost to you, Asaka.
That's true.
No matter how hard I've tried to
catch up, I never have beaten you.
Far from it. Even in the high school
club, I was trying desperately.
VF High School Championship
Team will be chosen in:
7 days
What's wrong, Asaka?
Apparently, among the members who
were selected for the preliminary,
your scores haven't gone up.
In fact, it looks like the new student,
Suiko Tatsunagi, is going to pass you by.
Y-Yes. I'm sorry.
In your case, keeping up your
motivation is number one.
That, and effort.
Right...
If you just coast by on
being a member of AL4,
you'll end up being ousted from
the select team by somebody else.
Your motivation...
It's Ren, isn't it?
You wouldn't mind not fighting
at Ren's side anymore?
No! That's the one thing
I don't want to lose!
I've been at Ren's side all this time.
For me to be forced off the team...
Bido! Fight me!
Hiromi, Harumi, Ayumu! You three as well!
VF High School Championship Team
I'm going to announce the members.
The representatives of Fukuhara High for
this year's VF High School Championship are...
...Ren Suzugamori...
...Suiko Tatsunagi...
...and Asaka Narumi.
Victory is essential to Fukuhara High.
No embarrassing fights, please.
Good. Now I can fight alongside Ren again.
And so, even in high school, I got
to be on the same team as Ren.
But...
I'm glad I could make a contribution for
Ren's sake at today's regional tournament.
Ren needs me next to him.
I'm sure he thinks so too.
You look happy, Asaka.
Y-Yeah. After all, I won for your sake.
Me too.
I had a great time today.
Aichi was amazing, wasn't he?
I bet he'll keep getting better and better.
I can't wait.
R-Right...
You think so too?
But I'm the one who's gonna fight Aichi.
I won't give that privilege up to anyone.
Right...
My victory... hardly meant anything.
At the end of the day...
that's all I am to you, Ren...
But you'll look at me if I
show you how strong I am.
No... if I beat you with
this overflowing power,
you'll only look at me!
When your whip of thorns cracks,
even dragons fall to their knees!
I ride Silver Thorn Dragon Tamer, Luquier!
There it is.
That's right. You've seen
Luquier's show countless times.
And today, it's going to
give you a splendid display.
Luquier's Limit Break!
Performers waiting behind the wing curtains...
Right now, come up on stage!
Silver Whip Liberation!
She filled in all of the rear-guard
spots with every grade.
That's right! When players all
appear together on stage once more,
Luquier's power reaches its climax!
High-powered Luquier is complete!
Now to raise the curtain on the third act!
Dance, Lilian!
Luquier! Crack that beautiful whip!
No guard.
What?! If she draws a
critical trigger here...
Are you sure?
I see. Perhaps you're
accepting the inevitable.
Then I'll end it for you here.
First check...
Second check...
Don't appear!
It's all over now.
Ren will be my servant who gazes
only at me for all eternity.
That was a narrow escape.
But... what about this?
I'm offended.
Who said I don't look at you?
W-What?
It won't get through! Guard!
W-What's that look?!
Nothing's changed! I've
still got the upper hand!
Are you ready?
The punishment for angering me...
...isn't a light one.
Asaka, I never thought you'd
take that attitude towards me.
I apologize if I touched a nerve...
...but soon, you will become mine.
Asaka, this get-tough
stance of yours isn't bad,
but go too far, and you're
going to be disciplined.
And meanwhile, I had no idea that a fierce
fight was playing out between Ren and Asaka!
Next time: Last Dance!
Last Dance!
Oh, I'm so scared!
But you're going to get
on your knees before me!