Brazil!
Old man ninja.
Sword
I am Ninja Master Neo-degozaru.
Old man! How dare you send
Kamui off to another woman?!
Young girl, I did it to save you,
as you've been Reversed.
And not only that, but to
protect the world-degozaru.
Kamui is at the center of my world!
But you trampled on a young maiden's love!
And now you'll pay!
I promised the boy that I would
beat you and return you to normal.
Putting one's life on the line to accomplish
a mission is the code of the ninja.
A woman who's dedicated
her soul to love is scary.
Prepare yourself!
Make my day-degozaru!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Beast Deity, Riot Horn!
Stealth Beast, Kuroko!
I haven't seen that clan before.
I would expect not.
This clan was born in the shadows
and lives in the shadows
and has been passed down from ninja to ninja.
This is Nubatama.
Nubatama, made stronger by the
booster deck, Catastrophic Outbreak,
is going to defeat you.
Too bad for you.
You can't beat my Nova
Grappler. Not a chance.
A Reversed girl using Nova Grappler...
I'd better be on guard-degozaru.
Ninja Master Returns
I go first.
I ride...
Beast Deity, Blank Marsh!
Riot Horn moves.
Ninja Art: Transformation Technique!
Stealth Rogue of the Night, Sakurafubuki!
Ninja Art: Summoning Technique!
Tempest Stealth Rogue, Fuuki!
Ninja Art: Slashing Technique!
Fuuki and Sakurafubuki attack!
I want the old Nagisa back,
but it's also hard to see her lose.
Which one of them should I cheer on?!
Beast Deity, Damned Leo!
Call!
Damned Leo attacks!
Check!
That's...
As I thought, that's no ordinary
Nova Grappler-degozaru.
Hatred Chaos!
Turn end.
My ninja techniques will dispel the darkness
that resides in your Reversed heart-degozaru.
Ninja Art: Transformation Technique!
Stealth Rogue of a Thousand Knives,
Oborozakura!
Fuuki moves.
Ninja Art: Summoning Technique!
Stealth Beast, Tamahagane!
Ninja Art: Straitjacket Technique!
That technique's a pain in the neck!
The unit that's bound returns to
the hand at the end of the turn...
And if the Vanguard attack hits,
Kuroko's technique will be activated and the
bound unit will be sent to the Drop Zone, Brazil.
I hate men who are persistent.
Persistent?
Targeting the opponent where it
hurts is the way of the ninja!
Ninja Art: Flame Windmill!
Oborozakura attacks with a boost from Kuroko!
I've got no choice.
Guard!
Drive trigger check!
Draw trigger!
I add +5000 power to Tamahagane.
And then I draw.
Ninja Art: Claw Attack Technique!
Tamahagane attacks with a boost from Fuuki!
Check.
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Damned Leo.
I heal 1 damage point.
My turn is over!
Thanks to the heal trigger, it's 2 to 2.
Even her strength at drawing triggers
is better than her brother's, Brazil.
Which of them should I cheer on?
Listen to me, young girl-degozaru.
The kanji for shinobi,
meaning ninja, depicts a heart under a sword.
Love is a heart that is in chaos,
like an entangled string.
The ninja patiently endures, facing
the heart with a drawn sword.
Patience is a form of love-degozaru!
I've been patient like you wouldn't believe,
but Kamui still won't come to me!
So no matter how I have to do it,
I'm gonna make him pay attention to me!
And I won't let you get in my way, old man!
I ride Beast Deity, Ethics Buster!
Call!
Hatred Chaos!
Its technique gives it +3000 power!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique!
Ethics Buster attacks!
No guard!
Drive trigger check.
Draw trigger!
I give the power to Damned Leo!
And then I draw.
Damage trigger check!
Stand trigger!
I add +5000 to the power of Oborozakura!
I stand Tamahagane!
Damned Leo!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique, Number Two!
Turn end!
The way of the ninja is the way of Shura.
Conquer isolation and open a path!
Ninja Art: Super-Transformation Technique!
Shura Stealth Dragon, Kujikiricongo!
Ninja Art: Summoning Technique!
Stealth Dragon, Kokujyo!
Ninja Art: Smokescreen Technique!
Kokujyo attacks Hatred Chaos!
Guard!
Ninja Art: Marionette Technique!
Drive trigger check.
Critical trigger.
I give the power to Tamahagane
and the extra critical to Kujikiricongo!
Damage trigger check!
Ninja Art: Slashing Technique!
Go, Tamahagane!
She's on the ropes, with 5 damage!
But our Nagisa is...
Brazil...
Old man ninja.
If you think you've got me
cornered, you're sorely mistaken.
I've been waiting quietly for this moment.
This moment when I deliver the final blow.
5 damage.
You've created the right conditions
to use an ace in the hole.
You catch on quick.
You're going to lose this turn, old man.
All the while regretting that you
ever stood in the way of my love...
I'll make you wet your pants in fear
at my attack that's starting right now!
Miss Emi!
Darn you, Rekka Tatsunagi!
Where did you take Miss Emi?!
Kamui the Great!
No good. We haven't seen her anywhere!
HS, yo!
Sense them... Miss Emi's cries...
Help us, Kamui!
This way!
Kamui the Great!
It's intuition! His animal
instinct has awakened!
AI! I believe in you, yo!
You're gonna atone for the sin of
interfering in my love with Kamui!
My instincts are crying out!
My feelings of love won't be stopped!
Love-love break ride!
Strongest Beast Deity,
This is...
Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
So this unit was her ace
in the hole-degozaru...
For its break ride skill,
Ethics Buster "Reverse" gets +10000 power
and the ability to stand a rear-guard!
Then I call!
Beast Deity, Desert Gator and
Beast Deity, Solar Falcon!
Until my love comes to fruition, until
he becomes mine, this will keep standing!
Ethics Buster "Reverse"
love-love Limit Break!
I lock two units!
After I attack the Vanguard,
I gain the ability to stand!
Ability to stand...
There it is. Nagisa's you-know-what...
The entrance to an endless
hell just opened, Brazil.
This Reversed deck is the true Nova Grappler!
Here I go!
One!
Hatred Chaos attacks!
Ninja Art: Ambush Technique!
Two!
Damned Leo!
Ninja Art: Ambush Technique, Number Two!
Three!
Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
Break ride skill.
All front row rear-guards, stand!
Beasts awaken fellow beasts.
Riot Horn's skill activates!
Stand!
Drive trigger check!
Heal trigger.
I give the power to Hatred Chaos
and heal 1 damage point.
And then Ethics Buster "Reverse" again,
this time with a Limit Break!
After it attacks the Vanguard, it stands.
Even though her three attacks are over,
she gets to attack again three times?!
The soul of a beast never sleeps!
It won't stop attacking, even unto
eternity, until the enemy is destroyed.
That's right.
This is Infinite Hell.
Four!
Damned Leo!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique!
Five!
Hatred Chaos!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique, Number Two!
Six!
Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
Front row rear-guard, stand!
With its skill, Riot Horn also stands!
Again?!
Check.
Critical trigger!
I give the power to Damned Leo
and the critical to Ethics Buster "Reverse"!
Her attack with the critical hits!
6 damage, Brazil!
You... You won, Nagisa?
6 damage...
But as a ninja, even if I die,
I must carry out my mission-degozaru.
Damage trigger check!
No trigger!
Brazil.
I mustn't give up-degozaru.
Second check...
I've obtained a Comeback Technique!
I give the power to Kujikiricongo
and heal 1 damage point!
Heal trigger...
But even so, you won't be able to
get out of Infinite Hell, old man.
I can still attack two more times!
Eight attacks...
A Circle of Transmigration Technique.
No...
A Woman's Tenacity is Fearsome
Technique-degozaru!
You can't guard anymore, can you?
I'm going to drive home how deep my love is!
Seven!
Hatred Chaos!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique, Number Three!
You could still use a card?!
But my next one...
Eight!
This is the end! Damned Leo!
Ninja Art: Shield Technique, Number Four!
I don't believe it. He held
out against my Infinite Hell.
I made you think I was dead,
but I actually survived.
A ninja has two lives!
Turn end...
But he's only got one card in his hand.
Only the Vanguard is in the front row.
I've got two perfect guards
and two intercept units.
I healed 1 damage, so I just have 4.
There's no doubt that I'm going to win.
Though I've returned to life,
I'm in a desperate situation indeed-degozaru.
Still, I'm a ninja.
Even in a showdown that I'm going
to lose, I can't afford to withdraw!
Ninja Master Neo is here!
Blade of the unleashed heart!
Ultimate secret...
Ninja Art: Exploding Transformation Technique!
Shura Stealth Dragon, Kabukicongo!
Break ride! I didn't think he
still had a unit like that!
Ninja Art: Assassin Straitjacket Technique!
You have to discard one
of the cards in your hand,
and I get to bind one of
your cards-degozaru!
But I can still protect myself.
Ninja Art: Summoning Technique.
Kokujyo!
Ninja Art: Amplification Technique.
Kabukicongo gets +2000 power!
And now a Counterblast!
Kabukicongo attacks!
Ninja Art: Limit-Breaking Technique!
Even a Limit Break?!
Young girl, I bind all of your rear-guards!
No way!
If three or more units are
bound, it gets +10000 power!
Nagisa!
That's not all.
Kokujyo powers up too.
Drive trigger check!
Critical trigger.
I give the power to Kokujyo and
the extra critical to Kabukicongo!
But if I draw a trigger...
Second check!
Nagisa...
Nagisa lost?!
Brazil!
How could he have attacked me like
that in those circumstances?!
Flexibility
I laid down my life and gained my life.
That's the way of the ninja.
It seems you're back to normal.
Boy, the ninja accomplished his duty.
Smoke
Brazil!
Huh?
I...
Nagisa, you're back to normal.
Thank goodness...
There's nothing good about it!
I had a dream!
And when I woke up, there was some
strange old man ninja in front of me.
In fairy tales, it's the prince who's
supposed to wake up the princess!
I can't just stand around.
I'm going after Kamui!
R-Right!
Whoops!
Brazil!
Oh, no, you don't. If you
want to pass by here...
...you have to fight, Brazil!
You think there'll be no consequences
if you get in the way of my love?!
Th-That force... She's actually
scarier when she's not Reversed!
Brazil!
Let's do this, Bro!
Yeah!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Guiding Zombie!
A dreadful power that I've never experienced
before has brought me this close to disaster...
But I'm not the one who's
destined to save the world.
That would be the young ones.
That was a nice nap. Are we
almost at Miyaji Academy?
With all this traffic,
the bus has barely moved.
Say what?!
But whatever. Guess I'll go back to sleep...
Again?! How much sleep can one guy get?!
You put Rip Van Winkle to shame!
Kourin left before us. I wonder if
she's arrived at the academy yet.
Next time: Runaway Angel Rekka!
Runaway Angel Rekka!
Ahh! I forgot to go to the bathroom
at that last service area!
Shut up! Don't shout in my ear!
Just hold it already!