VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
So this is the venue, huh?
I'm totally pumped!
I'm gonna do this!
I'm gonna be on fire! I'm gonna win!
You're overexcited.
That's what makes you a noob...
Shut up! Be quiet while I get fired up!
What about you?
For a fighter like me, there's the expression
"The man of virtue should
enjoy the mountains."
Perfect composure, confidence to spare.
Your legs.
This is... Uh...
Captain, please say a few words to everyone.
My body is producing too much epinephrine...
Right.
Um...
Anyway, today is the first tournament
for the Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club.
Let's do our Vanguard best,
and have no regrets!
Yeah!
Vanguard Cardfight
High School Championship
VF High School Championship...
It goes back a long way,
with the first tournament being
held many, many years ago.
VF High School Championship Arena
Since then, countless high school fighters
have shown us much drama.
Victory and defeat,
friendship and effort...
Every year, we witness new inspirations.
The Road to VF High School Championship
And so!
This year, new high school student
fighters will make their pages in history.
Out of 4,000 schools nationwide, the battle
to decide which one is the top begins now!
Let the VF High School Championship,
Kanto Block 3...
...start!
Hidden Fighting Spirit
Y'know, I had no idea that VF High School
Championship had such a rich history...
You call yourself a Vanguard fighter and
you don't know about an event like this?
Your ignorance knows no
bounds, Porcupine Head.
What's that, Granny Glasses?!
Excuse me?!
It's Ren and the others!
So they're strongly favored to win?
They do give off that aura...
Sailor Suit...
I totally wanna fight her one more time!
People are saying good
things about you guys, too!
Miwa! Kai!
After all, two of your
members are from the team
that won the national tournament
and the Asia Circuit.
Naturally, all eyes will be on you.
Still, our Hitsue High team isn't gonna lose.
Morikawa! Izaki!
What in the world happened to you two?
Don't think we're the same as always, Aichi.
We're gonna win this elimination round!
Vanguard Club
Yes! The VF High School Championship is a
high school fighter's dream celebration!
As one of those students, this time
especially, they're serious to the max!
Morikawa?
I'm sorry, Kourin.
Y-Yes?
Because of my mighty hopes
today, I'm cutting you off.
I'm going to deny myself
my love for you today.
Please forgive me.
I-Is that right?
I'm looking forward to
going up against you guys.
Please excuse me, Kourin.
What was that? He seems totally different...
Thank you for your patience.
We will now announce the
pairings for Kanto Block 3.
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
The pairings for the first fight are...
Miyaji Academy
Hitsue High School
Yeah! Right from the get-go!
Just what we were hoping for, right?
Well... maybe not...
All right: The VF High School
Championship, Kanto Block 3!
The first tense match is about to begin!
It's so exciting!
Participating in the first match, from
Hitsue High School's Vanguard Club,
Toshiki Kai!
Kai...
And facing off against him, from
Miyaji Academy's Cardfight Club,
Shingo Komoi!
T-Toshiki Kai! He's had great
matches at countless tournaments,
but his unofficial duel with Ren Suzagamori
is famous throughout the Vanguard world!
To be able to fight him... this is
the best day of my entire life!
Why can't I be out there?!
Me, the VF High School
Championship powerhouse!
We did it like you said, deciding it fair
and square by drawing lots, remember?
So don't complain.
All right, begin the first fight!
Stand up...
...the...
...Vanguard!
Dragonic Descendant attacks!
P-Perfect guard with Marilyn!
Limit Break!
If the attack doesn't hit, Descendant
gains an extra critical and stands again!
Attack!
The winner of the first match: Toshiki Kai!
I really wanted to fight you...
Kai...
C-Complete defeat...
No, wait a second!
He's a fighter who could even
win at the tournament proper.
Looking at it that way,
my ability could be deemed "runner-up class"!
Get over here, Granny Glasses!
Would you be quiet, you meathead?!
What the heck?! He's excited, he's depressed...
Man, is that guy annoying.
What about the next match?
Who's the opponent?
All right! We won the first match!
All we need is one more win
to go on to the next round!
Shoot! Now I get nervous!
I don't blame you.
This is your first time at the grand stage
of the VF High School Championship.
Strongest Water
H-Huh? My water is acting up...
H-Hey, you're even more nervous than I am!
Nervous? Me, the strongest
fighter? Don't be ridiculous.
M-Morikawa...
Staying hydrated is fine. Just make
sure you wipe the floor later.
Okay.
Good grief. I can't watch
any more of that, y'know?
That reminds me...
Blaster Blade attacks!
What?! Guard! And intercept!
Can't watch any more of that, huh?
Well, I know how you feel...
Kamui, you really are strong!
Aww... You're the strong one, Brother!
We're getting close to your first
national tournament, right?
I'm sure you wanna practice
a little bit, don't you?
But I have to mind the store...
It just so happens that I have
nothing better to do right now.
It doesn't count as minding the
store if you're daydreaming.
Go ahead. I'll watch over things for you.
Even if it doesn't seem like he's looking,
he watches over his friends
and comes through for us.
As a friend, that makes me really happy...
...but right this moment, his
friends are all Hitsue students
and the help he's giving is
designed to make me lose.
Sorry, but I'm not going to cooperate!
All right, then. Let's
begin the second match!
Misaki, we're counting on you!
From Hitsue High School: Taishi Miwa!
And from Miyaji Academy: Misaki Tokura!
That was your first serious
fight back then, right?
Don't think I'm going to hold back on
you just because we go back awhile.
I'm going to fight you
with everything I've got.
I recall that, a long time ago, it seemed
like you weren't even interested in cards.
And now here you are, in a
club with your friends...
You've changed. But I don't
have anything against that.
Let the match begin!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Seal Dragon, Terrycloth!
Witch of Prohibited Books, Cinnamon!
He's got serious skills as a fighter.
I can't let my guard down.
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Turn end!
Tokura's turn is over.
She's pushed Miwa into
a corner with 5 damage.
You weren't kidding about not holding back.
You, too!
SD, yo!
Same damage!
Figures. Both Misaki and Miwa are strong...
Remember, Miwa's your senior!
RMYS, yo!
Yeah, I only wish we could get those
guys into the tournament...
That being said, I'll never be able
to beat her if I take this casually.
And so, it's time for me
to get totally serious!
When the seal is broken, the dragon's
flames will reduce everything to ashes!
I ride...
...Hellfire Seal Dragon, Blockade Inferno!
Seal Dragon, Blockade is in the Soul,
so Inferno's power is 13000!
Flannel moves back!
Call!
And then, break through
the limit! Limit Break!
Especial Counterblast!
I get to retire all of my
opponent's grade 2 units!
He mowed down her rear-guards!
Her defensive capability has
been slashed in one stroke!
With Miwa, I'm not surprised...
But that's not all!
Blockade Inferno gets +10000 power!
It mows down the enemy and
increases its own power.
That's Blockade Inferno's
Vanishing Field Ultimatum!
He means to beat her with one blow?!
Here I go!
Blockade Inferno attacks!
Perfect guard! Kushinada!
Even 28000 power can't break
through a perfect guard!
I give the effects to Jacquard!
Next! Even though this attack isn't
going through, I still have Jacquard!
Miwa...
What's with Miwa?
Where did his usual carefree personality go?
It's because he's serious.
Do you know why?
With its skill, Jacquard gets +3000 power!
Go, Jacquard!
You're gonna take this damage!
This is the first time I've
seen you looking like that.
You've got a serious look.
It's because I can't take this fight lightly.
Perfect guard!
I'm still not done! Blockade!
Guard!
All right! Boss Lady didn't take any damage!
Th-Thank goodness...
Misaki...
Doing the best you can for
the sake of your friends...
That's the kind of guy you are.
I don't know about that...
But to seriously come at me
with everything you've got...
I blocked all of your attacks this turn,
but I'm impressed that
you've gotten this far.
Well, I can't afford to pull my
punches when you're my opponent.
Sorry, but this fight is mine.
It's your turn, but unless a miracle happens,
you won't be able to deal me any damage!
Oh?
In that case, I'll make a miracle happen!
Even when besieged by a storm of despair,
if you grab the rudder of fate,
you'll find the sea route
that leads to victory!
Goddess of Good Luck, Fortuna!
I break ride on top of Oracle Queen, Himiko!
Fortuna!
The break ride's effects!
I give the power to Fortuna, +10000.
And then I add +5000 to
the power of Tatsutahime!
Skill activated!
I do a Soulblast, which
gives +5000 to Fortuna.
Chamomile's skill!
Counterblast!
When Chamomile is moved from the Soul to
the Drop Zone, I can superior call!
I do the same thing with my other Chamomile.
Melissa has the same skill.
Wow! Her rear-guard was practically empty,
but she's filled it up again all at once!
This is the decision the goddess
of fortune handed down for me.
Destiny Decision!
Nice! You set the board up perfectly.
But I wouldn't call that a miracle...
After all, I may be able to protect
against that attacking power.
Shoot. Guess my bluff didn't work...
Now then... I wonder which of them
will make the miracle happen.
Fortuna, attack Blockade Inferno!
Dragon that brings on a disaster,
go from whence you came!
Rinocross! Perfect guard!
Twin drive check.
All right! No trigger! Now he'll be able
to guard against her other attacks!
But! The real issue is what happens next...
Fortuna brings about a miracle!
Break through the limit! Limit Break!
Soulblast!
With that, I get to do one more drive check.
Second check!
She gets to drive check... again!
Third check!
Dang. With this timing,
that really is a miracle.
A miracle caused by someone
who's totally serious?
I'm the same as you.
It's because I want to go to
the High School Championship.
Together with my friends from Miyaji...
Figures. I understand.
Seriousness wouldn't come out unless
you're doing it for your friends.
Here I go!
I give the +5000 to Chamomile, then draw!
Chamomile attacks with a
boost from Tatsutahime!
I guard with Biella and Artpique,
and intercept with Jacquard!
My other Chamomile attacks!
No guard!
If I draw a heal trigger here,
I'll be able to make it to my turn!
I'm sorry, everyone...
The winner, from Miyaji Academy's
Cardfight Club: Misaki Tokura!
She did it! That's our Boss Lady!
That makes it one win and one loss.
That's right. So we've got
another fighting chance.
I see.
Well, shucks.
A crushing defeat, I'd say.
Guess I just can't beat you...
You had me backed into a corner, too.
If I hadn't drawn Fortuna, you would've won.
Let's fight again sometime.
But I'm not gonna lose!
Got it?!
Same goes for me!
That was a great fight!
Sorry...
It wasn't a fight you need
to apologize for. Right?
Yeah!
Shoot...
The verdict of Miyaji versus Hitsue all
depends on who wins the third match!
Will we survive the elimination
round or be defeated?
This match will decide everything.
All right, then... the fateful third
match is about to begin!
Yeah! I bet Brother's gonna be in this one!
It's inevitable!
II, yo!
From Miyaji Academy: Aichi Sendou!
My opponent?
All right! Leave the rest to me!
Morikawa?
Aichi...
I mean, Captain, please!
We're counting on you!
And from Hitsue High School...
...Yuuta Izaki!
Go get 'im, Izaki!
Yeah!
Izaki...
Aichi... I'm gonna knock you for a loop!
Those Hitsue guys are dangerous!
Boss Lady was this close to losin'!
They're much more aggressive than
the last time we fought them!
All of the Hitsue members have
seriously come here to win.
Next time: A Man's Guts!
A Man's Guts!
My opponent is Izaki.
My friend, who's always a nice guy...
I see. It's kinda hard to do, huh?
Uh uh. I'm going to hit him with everything
I've got because he's my friend!
I'm sure Izaki feels the same way.
I understand.