Crawl out of the gates of hell
and wield that evil power!
I ride...
Demon World Marquis, Amon!
Ren! Surrender to me!
This time, I'll lead you!
And then become the king
that I seek, Ren Suzugamori!
Got it!
Ren!
They've both got grade 3 Vanguards...
The damage is 4 to 3 with Ren in the lead...
...but it looks like Tetsu's turn is next.
Be patient. All we can do right now is watch.
Wrong. There is something that I can do.
I'll have faith in Ren.
I'll keep believing that he'll bring
Tetsu back. I'll wait for that.
Right.
Kingmaker in the Moonlight
I call Doreen the Thruster and
Amon's Follower, Hell's Draw!
Soulcharge!
With this, Demon World Marquis, Amon
receives +6000 power.
On top of that, Doreen also gets +6000 power.
This is...
That's right. My units get more power
every time a card is put in the Soul.
The more turns you have,
the stronger the effect.
That skill is a pain in the neck.
Well, if you can last that long...
Ron Geenlin attacks!
Since my Vanguard has "Amon" in
the name, Ron gets +3000 power!
Take Demon World Marquis's
slashing attack, Ren!
That's fine. No guard.
Twin drive!
Heal trigger?!
Now they've got even damage...
I give the power to Hell's Draw.
Second check!
Oh, wow...
Fate Collector moves to the Soul.
With its skill, I draw one card.
That's not like you.
What?
What happened to your usual poker face?
You've clearly drawn a good card,
but by letting it show on your face, you're
going to miss out on using it effectively.
Don't underestimate me.
The card won't lose effectiveness
because of something like that.
Besides, shouldn't you worry
about yourself first?
Very true. Not only has Tetsu taken
the lead, his turn isn't even over yet.
Ren...
Go, Hell's Draw!
That makes 5 damage!
I'd like to fight to the finish right here,
but unfortunately, my turn's over.
Boy, you don't get it, Tetsu.
Saying "I'll save my fun for later!"
...is just not very villainous.
Nonsense talk. Do you understand
your position, Ren?
If you don't beat me this next turn,
you'll have no chance of winning.
Of course I understand that.
Blaze up, flames of fury!
With thoughts of raging wrath,
reduce to ashes everything
reflected in your eyes!
Break ride!
Revenger, Raging Form Dragon!
Superior call.
Call!
Transient Revenger attacks!
Guard!
His first attack failed.
Ren...
You are good.
An attack like that was easy to brush off.
Then how about this one?
Raging dragon, use your passionate roar
to crush everything to pieces!
No guard.
Twin drive!
There it is! A critical trigger!
I give the power to Nullity Revenger and
the extra critical to Raging Form Dragon.
A critical of 2!
5 damage just like that!
Ren! If your next attack succeeds, it's over!
But will it go that smoothly?
Critical trigger! I give the power to Amon.
Even though you've raised your power a bit,
that won't stop my Raging Form Dragon.
Limit Break!
Tremble with fear before
an even greater rage!
Superior persona ride!
Raging Form Dragon!
He went from one Raging Form
to another Raging Form.
And it's standing!
What do you think? This way,
I have two more attacks.
Meanwhile, you can't withstand
even 1 more damage, Tetsu.
Your number is up.
I'll pay you back for before.
Oh?
The man who talks too much before
the final stroke always loses.
Am I wrong?
You know that theory too?
I'm impressed.
And here's your reward.
Unleash your thunder! Raging roar,
destroy Tetsu's delusion!
Come, my follower! Vlad Specula!
Perfect guard...
Nullity Revenger, Masquerade!
Ren! That's your final attack!
Ron Geenlin, Hell's Draw,
protect Demon World Marquis!
It seems you've fully realized
how much power I have.
But you can be at ease, Ren.
There's no need for you to fight any longer.
When you become king,
I'll demolish all challengers.
You can sit on the throne in peace, and...
What are you saying, Tetsu?
The fight isn't over yet.
You don't think I'd throw in the towel
over being in a pinch like this, do you?
Just the opposite.
This is more fun than ever.
That's just like you, Ren Suzugamori.
That's exactly why you're
worthy of being my king.
Please don't make me keep saying it.
I'm not a king.
I'm just an ordinary Cardfighter,
the kind that can be found anywhere.
You're ordinary, you say?
This is also the last time you'll
be spouting nonsense like that!
Final Turn!
Demon of demons, god that
rules the demon world!
Appear before me, and turn
this whole world to hell!
I ride...
Demon Marquis, Amon "Reverse"!
Here I go, Ren.
This is our final turn!
Doreen moves.
Call!
Soulcharge.
Doreen gets +6000 power.
Limits are meaningless to the Demon Marquis!
Demon Marquis, Amon "Reverse's" Limit Break!
Lock!
With this, Amon "Reverse" can get +1000 power
for every Dark Irregulars unit in the Soul.
That's a total of +10000 power.
On top of that, if there are six or
more units, he gets an extra critical.
Even without a boost, that's 23000 power.
And a critical of 2?!
Attack, Doreen!
Guard!
The finishing blow! Go, Amon "Reverse"!
Bring the new king into being!
I guard with Air Raid Dragon
and Grim Revenger!
Check!
Draw trigger.
I give the power to Ron Geenlin!
What's wrong?
It's taking you an awful lot of time
and trouble to do that final 1 damage.
I'm not done!
My turn isn't over yet!
Go, Ron Geenlin!
Bury Raging Form Dragon!
Fly! Two Masquerade units!
It can't be...
My Final Turn...
I believe your turn is over?
That's my Ren! Only he could protect
himself against that attack.
But that doesn't change the fact
that he's still in a tight spot.
He doesn't have any rear-guards,
and there are only two cards in his hand.
On top of that, his opponent
has a perfect guard.
It'll be okay.
With Ren, I'm sure of it.
Stand and draw.
Call.
Tartu's Counterblast.
Superior call!
He used a Counterblast to build up
his right and left lines. But...
Can you break through this defense?!
Attack!
Guard.
Raging Form Dragon, broiling with rage,
reduce Amon "Reverse" to ashes
with your flames of fury!
Counterblast!
Perfect guard with Vlad Specula!
Do you think you've already won, Tetsu?
That's why your cards have lost their glow.
Apparently you didn't notice it,
but the cards in your hand were glowing.
It's a different glow than
mine or Kai's or Aichi's.
Tetsu... It was a glow all your own.
Twin drive...
Raging Form Dragon!
Just one card changes the whole game.
That's what Vanguard is
about, isn't it, Tetsu?
What?
Mordred, Tartu, Nullity Revenger...
Give your souls to Raging Form Dragon!
Limit Break activated!
I can now superior ride the
Raging Form Dragon in my hand!
Rise again, Raging Form Dragon!
It gets +10000 power.
Here I go, Tetsu.
I'm going to open your eyes now.
Raging Form Dragon attacks Amon "Reverse"!
Take your glow back, Tetsu!
Tetsu!
Tetsu, look out!
What are you doing?
Ren...
What'll happen if you don't
keep your act together?
After all, the leader of Team Asteroid is pathetic!
Please support me.
Tetsu, I'm no good without you.
Ren...
Tetsu, who Reversed you?
I don't know.
My memories are all jumbled up.
Really? But...
...if there's a fighter around who can
beat you, this will be hard to deal with.
Ren?
Oh, nothing.
Come on, Tetsu, let's go.
Asaka and Suiko, too.
Right!
It seems we've got more
trouble waiting for us.
Watch!
This is Crusher Kyou's latest secret weapon,
obtained after crisscrossing
the world seven times!
Fabulous Immortal Finally Crush Rush Type Z!
You did it.
Yeah!
I never thought you would
defeat everyone here but me.
To be honest, I underestimated you... um...
It's Kyou! The great Crusher Kyou
Yahagi, former member of AL4!
Oh, pardon me.
I just can't seem to remember
the names of all the small fry.
Is that right?
In that case, I'll just have to carve my
name into your poor excuse for a brain!
The name of the man who's gonna beat you!
If you like.
Although there's no chance
that I'm going to lose...
Here I go!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Ren!
Oh, are we disturbing you?
Since Tetsu and Asaka are
with you, that means...
Yes. My work is done.
Then fight me!
Wait! I'm the one who's going to defeat Ren!
Then... Ren will be mine...
What are you babbling about?! I'm first!
No, I am!
Not that I care, but haven't both of
you already stood up your Vanguards?
Ah! Shoot!
Once a fight is started,
you can't give it up.
I know that!
We have no choice.
I'll be done with this guy
soon, so hang on, Ren!
My apologies, but we're in a hurry.
Right?
W-What?!
See you around!
Excuse us.
Take care.
Well, I'll leave the rest
to you, Kyou Yahagi.
Hey, you! Don't say my name only
when it's convenient for you!
Wait, Ren!
This is Miyaji Academy.
Why did we come here?
Well, there's something
I really need to confirm.
"Confirm"?
Yes.
Ren?!
And everyone else...
What are you doing here?
Actually, I wanted to check
on the Ultra-rare girl.
You mean Kourin?
That's right.
Um... Apparently, Kourin's
been busy with her idol work,
so she hasn't been to school for a while.
Huh? But isn't it the
same way with you, Suiko?
Yes... well...
Oh! What are all of you doing here?
Kourin?!
Huh? Even Suiko's here!
Where were you last night?
You didn't come home.
Ah... That's...
Isn't staying out overnight kind of risky?
Don't forget, you're an idol!
R-Right...
Come on, Aichi, we'll be late if
we keep lollygagging around here.
Right...
Never mind, Aichi.
I guess I had the wrong idea.
Oh? Well, then...
Bye bye!
I thought the other two Ultra-rare
members would be like Suiko,
but they don't seem to be
showing any of the signs.
I'm glad you seem well, Kourin!
Be careful, Aichi.
What's up? All of you guys came over...
It's a long story.
But we came to check on you and the others.
I just followed Ren here.
I'm just glad that nothing seems to be amiss.
I just remembered,
Mitsusada from Team Caesar is apparently
coming back from Singapore.
I bet he's gotten even stronger.
Next time: Daiyusha Falls!
Daiyusha Falls!
Koutei is coming back? Now?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What's wrong, Ren?