Are you okay, Amaterasu?
Thank you for your patience!
The hero, King of Knights, Alfred, is here!
I was waiting for you, Kourin!
I had faith you would come!
Thank goodness she got here in time...
Yeah, but this is wrecked...
We've reached the climax at last!
Alfred's battle is going to begin!
The dragon you're supposed to
fight can't come out any more.
What should we do?
No problem.
The true enemy that I'm going to fight...
...is over there!
Daigo?!
It's Daigo!
D-D-D-D-D-Daigo?!
The genuine legendary
fighter, Daigo, is here!
Daigo?!
Wow! That's the genuine Daigo!
What's he doing here?
What's gonna happen now?
I... I don't know...
Daigo!
It's Daigo!
Awesome!
Hi!
Hello...
Have you met him?
Once, a while back...
So that's Daigo...
Daigo is appearing in my play...?!
I'm touched! Gratified!
Nice to see you!
So you're Daigo, the one who kidnapped
Amaterasu under orders from the dragon, huh?!
I guess there's no point in denying it now.
That's right! I'm your opponent!
I'll tell you one thing. You
can't take me down with a sword.
If you want a showdown with me,
it'll have to be a Vanguard Cardfight!
Don't worry! I'm sure Kourin will win!
Is it really true that Daigo's here?!
He's doing something on the stage?!
Really?!
We have to go see!
Maybe I can get his autograph, too!
Stand back, Amaterasu.
I swear I'll win,
then save you!
I believe in you, Alfred!
What the devil is this?!
I don't know myself...
It's Daigo!
The real deal!
I don't believe it!
I'm glad I brought my camera!
Never thought I'd get to see Daigo
fight at Miyaji's school festival...
We're so lucky!
Yeah... You could say totally lucky!
I'm looking forward to this.
Good luck, Kourin!
Move it, would you, old man?!
I can't see Daigo!
That's right! Move it!
Move!
I'm not giving up the front row!
I'm not giving it up!
Legendary School Festival
Stand up the Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Dreaming Jewel Knight, Tiffany!
First Legend, Ambrosius!
All right! At last, the battle between
Alfred and Daigo has begun!
I go first. Draw!
I ride Regret Jewel Knight, Ulien!
Ambrosius moves!
It really is Daigo!
He looks just like he does on TV!
So handsome!
They're into it...
At this rate, the play
is going to be a success!
...Yes, sir.
Still, all we can do is
watch for the moment...
If we tried to interfere now,
I have a feeling we Student Council
members would be injured.
Unbelievable...
Draw.
I ride Jewel Knight, Prizmy!
Tiffany moves back.
I call Shellie!
I never imagined this would turn into
a fight between Kourin and Daigo...
But how did he...?
He gave us a ride here.
Suiko!
Sailor Suit!
After the shoot was over.
Kourin, you're going to
the school festival now?!
I have to go!
You won't make it in time!
I'm a member of the Cardfight Club!
Oh, Kourin...
Even though she was blown off
yesterday... She's too soft.
If you're headin' to the festival,
there's still time! Hop in, lady!
"To show your gratitude, a
Vanguard fight is okay-wish!"
He never changes.
So that's why he's here...
That Daigo guy is kinda cool!
Is he some kinda heroic type that
shows up to help people in trouble?
No...
Daigo is a genuine hero.
With a boost from Tiffany, Prizmy attacks!
No guard.
Check!
Critical trigger.
Alfred strikes first, doing
3 damage to the opponent, Daigo!
Love
That's the way! That's my Kourin!
You got me. That's Ultra-rare for you.
I think I'll be in big trouble
if I don't stay focused.
As always, you're the least
focused person I know.
Really? Maybe...
And as always, you appear
in unexpected places.
Why did you show up right
in front of me today?
It can't be a coincidence.
Well, I'm Daigo.
Come on, let's have a good time Vanguarding!
It's my turn. Draw!
I ride Battle Flag Knight, Constance!
Call!
I attack Shellie!
Guard!
Here I go!
Constance attacks!
Superior call, Rendgal!
Rendgal boosts Owain!
Shellie attacks!
Sybill!
Guard!
Tracie!
Yeah! Two out of three!
Go, go, Kourin!
Stand and draw!
Pure, proud knight!
I ride White Dragon Knight, Pendragon!
Pendragon's skill!
Pendragon gets +5000 power!
Gordon attacks Sybill!
Guard!
Go, Pendragon!
No guard.
Twin drive, first check.
Second check...
I got a heal trigger!
I'm not surprised!
Strength in drawing is the
mark of a strong player!
He heals 1 damage point,
and the power goes to Owain,
who's going to attack next!
That's right!
Owain attacks!
He turned it around!
Kourin...
Alfred was so close to winning!
But victory's been snatched away
by the enormous power of the strong,
evil Daigo, who's after Amaterasu!
Now Alfred's in a major pinch!
Kourin!
Even Kourin can't beat the
legendary Cardfighter, Daigo?!
Win!
Win, Alfred!
I'm with you... We're all with you!
Do your best, Alfred!
We're with you!
Alfred! Don't let it end like this!
You're the hero of this play!
Everyone...
Hang in there, Kourin!
Kourin
The critical that's Morikawa
and the grade 3 named Katsumi are with you!
Don't lose, Daigo!
Do your best!
Alfred!
Daigo!
Kourin!
This crowd's really livened up!
Now this is what I call a festival!
I swear that I'll win, Amaterasu.
Stand and draw!
The unchanging light of determination
shines longer than eternity!
Lead me!
I ride Leading Jewel Knight, Salome!
Shellie moves!
I call Palamedes!
Tiffany moves to the Soul.
Tracie and Prizmy both get +3000 power!
Salome's Especial Counterblast!
Superior call!
Palamedes attacks!
No guard.
Just 1 more...
Salome attacks with a boost from Shellie!
Glittering more than gold,
sparkling more than the sun,
silent torrent of fierce light,
now is the time to be unleashed!
Limit Break!
+2000 power and an extra critical, huh?
I guard with Elaine and Govannon!
First check.
Second check.
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Tracie!
With a boost from Prizmy,
Tracie attacks!
Tracie and Prizmy are both powered up!
With Tracie's skill, the
total is a whopping 30000!
Slam 'im!
Flogal! Marron!
Gordon!
Didn't quite turn out like a fairy tale, huh?
That's too bad!
No... I'm not done yet!
That's what I like to hear!
You never know what kind
of miracle can happen!
That's what makes Vanguard so much fun!
Right?! You guys think so too, don't you?
Everybody!
Yay!
We're leaving.
What kind of farce is this?! What kind of...
Tell me!
It's just a lousy, nonsensical play...
That's it!
Stand and draw.
Pendragon's Limit Break!
I look at the top five cards of my deck,
choose a grade 3 Royal Paladin,
and perform a superior ride.
Marvelous Vanguard!
From the absolutely beautiful, sacred world,
swoop down on luminous wings!
Sanctuary Guard Dragon!
Skill activated!
I put one card from my hand into the
Drop Zone and superior call Rendgal!
Okay, here I go! Sanctuary
Guard Dragon's Limit Break!
Each grade 1 or lower
Royal Paladin gets +3000 power!
Get ready!
Rendgal attacks!
I guard with Rachelle!
With a boost from Ambrosius,
Sanctuary Guard Dragon!
No guard!
Twin drive check!
First check.
Second check!
Sanctuary Sunshine!
I'm the winner!
Kourin Love
She lost...
So that's Daigo...
He really is strong! And cool!
Um... How does this fit into the play?
What's the fate of the princess?
Thank you! Thank you!
I'm your next opponent!
The princess is going to avenge the prince?!
Hey, Misaki! I mean...
What are you saying, Amaterasu?!
I'll protect you, Alfred...
I'll protect all of our friends!
I'll protect them, too!
M-Me too!
You beat my hero without
even getting permission?!
That calls for a showdown with Magatsu Storm!
This has turned out to be a fun performance!
A showdown, Daigo!
Marvelous...
You...
Just when I thought I was
about to get the princess...
Friends... Friends, you say?!
To be beaten by the things I hate,
like love, friendship, and
the bond between comrades...
But...
...you remember this!
When the bond between you looks
a little frayed around the edges,
this evil archenemy will
appear before you again!
Sorry! Let me through, 'kay?
Sure!
'Til we meet again!
Give me your autograph!
After the Cardfight Club's play is over!
H-Hey! Later, I said!
The play...
Misaki! Kourin!
What are you doing?! Come on, hold hands!
Thanks to Alfred and Amaterasu
being wonderful comrades,
they were victorious over
their archenemy, Daigo!
And so, they lived happily ever after...
The End.
That was fun!
Yeah. I'm actually kind of moved.
That was awesome!
You've got "I wanna fight Daigo"
written all over your face.
Do I?
I suppose I do...
That was great!
Kourin Love
Kourin! You were fantastic!
Misaki! Look this way!
Thank you for believing in me.
Efforts will be rewarded...
...definitely.
The adulation...
One of these days, I'll be
walking down a red carpet...
Good outcome, huh, Emi?
Yeah!
Misaki, you're so cool!
That was the victory of teamwork.
There's a lot to be said
for school life, huh?
True.
Thank you very much!
Miyaji Academy Festival
I bought a lot.
Yakisoba, okonomiyaki, takoyaki, et cetera...
This stuff is the best
part of school festivals.
His name = Daigo
Daigomi = The highlight of something
Oh! That pun wasn't intended...
Hey...
Miyaji Academy Festival
Give me some reaction!
Daigo! That was Daigo!
Yeesh...
What was all of that?
Yes, sir... I'm terribly sorry.
But the connection between the Cardfight
Club and Daigo was unforeseen...
Even setting aside the
idol group, Ultra-rare,
they surprise me.
Enough...
Yes, sir.
That'll be all for today.
Drinking tea is so comforting.
I expect better of you next time.
Sir?
I expect better of you!
Yes, sir!
What's wrong, Aichi?
I didn't get the chance to thank Daigo.
Daigo is a hero, right?
Thankin' him would probably
just make him mad.
I see...
You're right.
Thank you very much, Daigo.
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Daigo... That guy sure does show
up when you least expect him...
I know...
Hi! I'm Taigo!
I'm your Vanguardian ally!
That doesn't sound like him...
Boys love heroes...
Well, everyone, the curtain's about to
rise on the VF High School Championship!
Next time: Hidden Fighting Spirit!
Kanto Block 3
The Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club
sets their sights on the goal
of high school Cardfighters
from all over Japan. Fight!
Everybody, do your Vanguardy best!
He's still doing it...
Wish!