Swoop down from beyond illusion,
cruel blade!
Transient dreams!
Break ride!
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Kai, show me your ultimate power.
But I'll show you that I'm even higher.
In that case, I'll meet your expectations.
But when you see my power...
Ren, it'll be the end of you!
I feel it.
Even as we do this, the
time limit is drawing near.
When the gate opens, the world will
be swallowed up by Link Joker.
And when that happens,
everything that exists on Earth
will be Reversed and fall
under Link Joker's control.
I won't let that happen!
If Ren beats Kai, you'll be all that's left.
Haven't you realized?
What Toshiki Kai hasn't played yet...
You mean...
I'm looking forward to what transpires next.
Resurrection of the Dragon
2 more damage and I win.
So, Kai, show me your ultimate power.
Then I'll KO you from
my position above yours.
Bring it on, Kai.
I call Nehalem.
Nullity, Masquerade attacks!
Intercept!
Overlord attacks with a
boost from Calamity Tower!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
I give the power to Nehalem and
the extra critical to Overlord.
I got a heal trigger.
I give the power to Mordred
and heal 1 damage point.
Nehalem attacks with a boost from Griffin!
Guard!
Turn end.
He hasn't brought out a Reverse unit yet.
You're making this fun, Toshiki Kai.
Reverse units deal out fatal blows.
I'm sure the best opportunity
for that is coming soon...
...since I'm fighting the
strongest man I know.
Ren... just as you can read my thoughts,
I know what you're thinking, too.
This tension, as if we're crossing swords
without protective equipment...
The last time I felt it was...
When you were running amuck under
Psyqualia's spell and we fought a vicious battle.
Since then, I've wanted to have
another fight like that with you.
But your and Aichi's fights...
Both of your power had eclipsed mine.
You both became strong,
so I wanted to beat you.
That fervent desire grew within me.
I threw away everything,
and gained Link Joker's power.
You're one of the two people
who have shaken my soul.
And now that I've beaten Aichi...
Ren, defeating you will be proof that
I've become the strongest of all!
I'll be the one who wins!
I will!
Kai... Ren...
Strongest enemies... supreme rivals...
I couldn't ask for anything more.
But the fight is going to end here.
Final Turn!
Come on then, Ren!
Mythical beast that appears from beyond!
Confuse his heart and crush his soul!
Crossbreak ride!
Revenger, Drag Ruler Phantom!
Counterblast!
+10000 power!
Superior call!
Nullity, Masquerade!
On top of that, Limit Break!
By retiring two Dorint units,
it gains +10000 power!
And then my opponent's
Vanguard takes 1 damage.
1 damage without even attacking?!
This is Drag Ruler Phantom's Mirage Strike!
Mirage Strike...
I didn't know that skill existed!
I got a critical trigger.
I give the +5000 power and
extra critical to Overlord!
Kai got another trigger, too.
But he has 5 damage,
and Ren is about to attack...
It's a little too early to attack.
Call!
He's gathered five rear-guards...
...and has Kai in a tight corner.
Are you ready for this, Kai?
Beast that feeds on illusions
and generates even more of them!
Destroy chaos...
...and lure it into a world of illusions!
Fanatic Illusion!
If this hits, Ren wins.
Listen to your master's voice!
Assemble for the sake of victory!
Dragon Knight, Gimel!
Quintet Wall!
A +30000 shield Quintet Wall?!
A skill that wasn't in a Link Joker deck...
Kai continues to grow stronger,
even now, at this very instant!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger!
I give all of the effects
to Nullity, Masquerade!
Quintet Wall...
But I've got two attacks left.
Intercept.
Final Attack!
Nullity, Masquerade boosted by Dorint!
Guard!
I put my heart and soul into those
attacks, but he blocked them all!
That's you all over, Kai.
That's why I want to beat you,
my strongest opponent.
Turn end!
No way! He blocked
all of Ren's best attacks?
He even held out against
a break ride and Limit Break...
Kai... just how strong
have you gotten?!
That's exactly why Link Joker
chose Toshiki Kai.
But the fight isn't over yet.
Now it's my turn to block your attacks.
Those were awesome attacks.
But that's Ren... the man I want to defeat.
Compared to me, looking to get
stronger by having fight after fight,
you see through to the essence of a deck,
using intuition to grasp
its special properties.
Capricious and delicate, as if you
might break, but with a strong heart.
Totally different from me.
That's why I want to beat you.
The opponent who's always
been worth beating...
I think I get it.
We're both opponents who want to beat the other
so badly that he'd sell his soul to the devil for it.
That being the case, I'm going to use this power
given to me by the devil known as Link Joker.
Ren... I'm going to defeat you!
Final Turn!
But of course.
Amid the flames of purgatory that reduce
everything to ashes, rise from the dead again!
Resurrection!
Strongest fiery dragon!
Crossbreak ride!
Dragonic Overlord the Reverse!
Because of the break ride,
it gains +10000 power.
Overlord the Reverse?!
What is this? I didn't know
about that Reverse unit!
Call!
Second coming of dragon of explosive flames,
use your fiery roar to
reduce all order to ash!
Limit Break!
I lock all rear-guards!
He locked all of his own rear-guards?!
By locking five units, Overlord
the Reverse gains +10000 power.
With the break ride and that Limit Break,
he now has 33000 power!
Let me show you...
...a reborn Overlord the Reverse's true power!
True power...
Overlord the Reverse attacks
Nullity, Masquerade!
No guard!
Check the drive trigger.
The flames of purgatory never extinguish.
Break ride skill activated!
Rise from the dead, Overlord the Reverse!
Overlord stood!
This is that...!
Next attack.
Overlord the Reverse!
No guard!
Check the drive trigger.
Second check!
Even when it stands,
it doesn't lose twin drive?!
Ren has 5 damage, too...
Flames feed on flames.
Hellfire keeps burning.
Reverse Limit Break activated!
Come back from the dead a third
time, Overlord the Reverse!
Again?! It stood!
If going toward the opposite
direction means "reverse,"
then being born again is also a "reverse."
That's right. This is Eternal Flame Reverse!
Eternal Flame Reverse...
Combined with a break ride,
it's even more powerful than
Eternal Flame before...
This is Eternal Flame Reverse!
Are you ready, Ren?
Final Attack!
Overlord the Reverse!
Guard! Intercept!
The power tops 10000!
In that case...
Kai...
He really does mean to win it here.
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
I give all the effects
to Overlord the Reverse!
Second check.
I got a critical trigger!
I give the power and the extra
critical to Overlord the Reverse!
Double critical trigger?!
Kai's attack went through!
Ren had 5 damage, so with a critical of 3,
Ren will have to draw three heal
triggers in a row, or he'll lose!
You're strong...
You're really strong.
This trembling is excitement at having this strength
you've finally reached right before my eyes.
It's the intense desire to beat you!
It would be a crying
shame to let it end here.
Ren isn't giving up.
Bring it.
Damage trigger check...
If it's not a heal trigger, Ren will...
Heal trigger! I heal 1 damage point.
There it is!
But he needs two more...
Second check.
Heal trigger! I heal 1 damage point.
Double heal trigger?!
Wow!
If he can draw just one more...
I win.
I know.
Haven't you noticed, Aichi Sendou?
Look carefully at the field.
There are already four heal triggers out...
Both of them know it, but he's
still doing a trigger check?!
I don't understand it at all myself.
You're strong.
Exactly what I expect you to be, Kai.
Ren!
That's right.
This is the kind of fight I've wanted to
have with you for the longest time...
Ren!
Ren...
I knew it, Ren...
You were the perfect opponent
for my final fight.
Toshiki Kai...
You're definitely still under my control.
This is what you'll be in
the future, Aichi Sendou.
Or rather, in your case, instead of being
Reversed, it's death that waits for you.
Ren Suzugamori has fallen.
You're the last one left.
If you lose, the world
will belong to Link Joker.
Scary, isn't it?
But even if you say you want
out now, I won't allow it.
If I can bring the world...
bring everyone back to normal,
I don't care what happens to me.
I'll fight!
Dear, dear. The people of this
world just don't know when to quit.
Toshiki Kai!
Please defeat Aichi Sendou now.
I refuse.
I already beat Aichi.
Wha...?
Kai?
All right, fine.
It can't be helped.
I'll teach you who's in charge later on.
Okay, Aichi Sendou. This way...
You should feel honored.
I'm going to settle this myself.
I will say this.
Aichi Sendou, you won't beat me.
Not a chance.
That's right. Nothing will change.
You can't change anything.
This world is already finished.
Ren... Even though the fight was over...
Good grief. Talk about useless strugglng...
That's right, Takuto Tatsunagi.
You never will understand.
Toshiki Kai...
I understand.
Ren wanted to enjoy the fight
with Kai for as long as possible.
Next time: Perfect Black Ring!
Perfect Black Ring
But right now, I can't enjoy fighting!
Show me a fight that surpasses Ren's!
Stand up, Vanguard!