Why do you have bags under your eyes?
I stayed up all night standing.
Sorry, Maki. Address everyone for me.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning...
Did you all get a good night's sleep?
For the second day of our camp,
cooking outdoors is on the agenda.
Cooking outdoors?
As in, we have to do the cooking.
We're having fine weather today too. Great!
I'm a woman who brings out the sun
wherever I go. So I beat you, Misaki!
What are you saying? I bring out the rain?
Huh? Where's Kourin?
Since the weather is nice,
we'll have a campfire this evening.
We'll probably be able
to see the Milky Way too.
Everyone, on this second day, please keep in
touch with nature in a meaningful way.
Apparently, Kourin doesn't feel well,
so she's staying in bed in the room.
I see. That's too bad.
Okay, please prepare your group's meals.
These are the results of the lottery.
Akari will make the salad.
Okay!
Shingo and Naoki are in charge
of the pork miso soup.
Leave it to me!
It'll be a showdown to see which
of us can make the tastier soup!
And then Misaki and I
will make the rice balls.
Roger.
After we turn it upside down
and steam it, it'll be ready.
Oof!
It's supposed to be pork miso soup!
What's the point of stir-frying?
I'm stir-fryin' it 'cause that makes it tastier!
That's not what the recipe calls for.
Well, you'll see.
Now I just need to dish it out.
You use your bottom hand for pressure,
keeping your top hand for support only.
Maintain a good rhythm, using as few
grips as possible to complete it.
Shin just taught me how to do it.
The top hand is only used for support...
I did it!
Well, it looks like everyone has
finished their preparations.
Out of respect for the ingredients, even if
you had a cooking failure, let's eat heartily.
Okay!
Thank you for the food!
Delicious!
It has a nice savory smell.
H-How is mine?
It's simple, but it has a gentle flavor.
Thank you!
I created a gentle flavor!
Your soup is good too, Shingo.
Yes! That's two to two, a tie!
I'm the one who got Aichi's point!
Wrong! I did!
I wanted to eat with Kourin too.
Let's hold another Cardfight camp
and cook together then, too.
Sure!
Under the Starry Sky...
Everyone, please wear your uniforms
for the campfire this evening.
The time has come at last, Suwabe.
Yes, President. Let's dismantle the
Cardfight Club with our own hands!
Like summer moths to a flame...
I guard with Seiobo and Castor!
He should have intercepted. Instead,
he's wasting cards in his hand.
We're more advanced than they are.
Even though we've only had one night's
worth of intensive training.
You see?
For global citizens such as us, card games
are simple if we just turn our attention to them.
All right!
Your temporary confidence ends here!
This is my break ride!
It's break time!
Wha...?!
You used it before me! Darn you, Ishida!
Hey, Suwabe. Exactly what kind
of skill is "break time"?
I-I don't know.
Maybe you say "break time" to call
for a brief rest during a long fight?
But it seems there's an
advantage to using it first!
I wonder what it is...
We'll just have to withdraw for now.
When we do confront them
directly, we mustn't fail!
This mysterious skill, "break time"...
it confounds me!
Find out what it means!
Yes, sir!
All right! That makes three wins!
Listen! The correct way to say
it is "three wins and two losses"!
Either way, I got one more win than you!
Huh? Just you two?
Aichi isn't here.
Aichi went with Kourin over
that way a little while ago.
Over that way...
By the legendary tree!
I can't just stand around here!
Akari?
Come on, let's go, Misaki!
I'm not gonna miss that legendary moment!
Legendary moment...
H-Hey, Akari!
U-Um...
Do you feel better now?
We all cooked together this afternoon.
I'd like to do that sometime
with you too, Kourin.
Oh?
The stars are really pretty, aren't they?
Without the lights of the city,
the Milky Way looks so beautiful.
I wonder which constellation that is.
Ah! A shooting star!
What did you wish for, Kourin?
I wished that all of us could go to
the National High School Championship.
Let's win together for sure!
Hey, Akari!
Shhh, quiet!
I was right, those two are
going over by that tree!
I've got it! This is what
Kourin has been brooding over!
Come on, Akari. Let's go back.
What are you talking about?!
Aren't you curious?
I sure am! And it should be interesting!
Actually, I think...
Well, it's not like you'd leave me
alone in a place like this!
Right, Misaki?
This tree.
I can hear its voice.
It echoes in my heart.
Please, lend me your power.
Kourin?
Um... Aichi...
Yes?
I want you to fight me.
I want to have a serious showdown
with you under this legendary tree.
Kourin saw yesterday's fight too...
Understood. I'm honored by your request.
Jeez! Just a fight?!
Boy, you guys and your fights...
Even all the way out here...
I'm going back.
I'm going to stay and watch.
Something about this fight... bothers me.
Aichi. After this fight is over...
...you'll be mine.
Stand up, Vanguard!
I ride Stinging Jewel Knight, Shellie!
I ride Future Liberator, Llew!
I ride Dogmatize Jewel Knight, Sybill!
And then I call!
Kourin... I sense even greater
determination in her than usual.
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
I retire Tracie!
Call!
Marron attacks!
Guard!
Blaster Blade!
Drive check!
Damage check.
Draw trigger.
Phallon!
Guard!
Hey. What's going on there now?
The damage is 3 to 4,
with Kourin on the defensive.
But...
...it's too early to say who's going to win.
Ride!
Pure Heart Jewel Knight, Ashlei!
But this isn't my trump card...
When that card comes...
That's when our destiny will be decided.
I swear I'll win this!
Shellie moves. And then I call!
Tracie attacks Blaster Blade!
Guard!
Ashlei!
No guard.
Drive check.
I give the power to Olwen...
...and the critical to Ashlei!
Now she's in the lead!
Aichi is in a pinch?
I was right... Kourin is many times
stronger than her usual self tonight.
What's doing this to you?
Olwen attacks!
Guard! And then I intercept!
You're incredibly strong tonight, Kourin.
Your determination to have a serious
showdown really comes through.
But... I have no intention
whatsoever of losing, either.
We met around the time I was
just starting to get into Vanguard,
and a lot's happened since then,
but you've always helped me.
I never imagined we'd one day be students
in the same class in high school,
but I'm thrilled to share a friendly rivalry
with you, as a fellow teammate.
I want to keep fighting with
you as we both aim for the top.
So I'm going to answer
your seriousness in kind!
Even in solitude, you fear no battle.
Only a strong soul knows true friendship!
I ride...
...Wolf Fang Liberator, Garmore!
I'll show Kourin how serious I can be!
Cheer Up Trumpeter's skill!
During this turn, every time a
rear-guard is called from my deck,
Garmore gets +3000 power!
Garmore's skill activates!
Limit Break!
Brave ones, gather together
around this solitary soul.
I superior call Gold Paladin comrades!
With that, Garmore's power
is a total of 23000!
How very like you, Aichi.
You've gathered comrades all across the field.
Here I go.
Garmore attacks Ashlei!
Skill activated!
Garmore gets +4000 power!
This is me being serious, Kourin!
You're naive, Aichi.
Perfect guard!
Drive check.
I give all of the effects to Alfred!
Gallatin attacks Tracie!
Alfred attacks Ashlei!
Guard! And intercept!
Aichi's serious attack
didn't even do 1 damage!
Aichi...
I want to keep fighting together, too.
Kourin Tatsunagi
When we first met,
it never crossed my mind that we
might be together so much.
Thank you, truly, for all of the memories.
But...
...the time for fun is over!
With this card, I'll make
you my true comrade!
My new ace in the hole...
Become a blade that decides fate!
I'll protect myself!
Those eyes...
Aichi's straightforward eyes...
That's right.
Aichi never does give up until the end.
He just puts all of his faith in winning.
Now, too...
He has no idea what I'm trying to do.
He's just looking straight ahead.
Kourin is acting strange!
Kourin?
Stop it! Don't look at me with those eyes!
Are you okay, Kourin?
If you're not feeling up to it...
Stay away!
Why? Why can't I ride?
Even though I'm Reversed!
Those eyes of yours bind me!
I'm sorry, Aichi!
Kourin!
I wonder what's wrong.
Misaki?!
Misaki, what are you doing here?
Oh... I was... uh...
Let's go after her!
Right!
Hey! Guys?
It's time to return to
the dormitory, you two.
Leave Ms. Takanagi to me and go back.
Uh... But...
I'm in the same room as her, so I'll
take responsibility and look after her.
So in the end, we didn't get to see
what happens with the legendary tree.
I wanted to see it so badly!
In fact, if possible, I wanted
to be part of the legend!
Kourin got picked up
yesterday, but is she okay?
I'm worried.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, Aichi!
Kourin...
Orienteering, cooking outside...
That was so much fun!
And my pork miso soup won!
That's nonsense! I say
we have another showdown!
I hope Kourin is okay.
I bet she's better already.
You're probably right.
Meanwhile, Kamui and the
others are in trouble!
Next time: The Pirate Flag
Fluttering at Miyaji!
The Pirate Flag Fluttering at Miyaji!
Pirates... Meaning Team Handsome?
What's happening with them?
I've got it! I've just made a
decision about the Komoi Corps!
Back to that again?