Suiko, would you tell me what's
going on in this building?
Where are Tetsu and Asaka?
Fight me, and you'll understand everything.
I don't have to fight to understand.
You're my teammate. I know your ability.
Oh? My ability...
It's fun talking to you,
but could we cut to the chase?
That seems to be a creepy, disquieting deck.
It pleases me that you catch on quickly.
The name of this deck's clan is...
...Link Joker!
Link Joker...
Link Joker. This is the first
I've heard of that clan.
It has the power to outmatch
all the other clans around.
It's the ultimate forbidden clan,
and depending on how you use it,
it's even possible to obtain infinite power.
That's Link Joker.
You're really a cheerleader
for this clan, huh?
Fighting with this deck
makes me feel ecstatic.
The reason is that...
I'll be able to beat you!
You feel it, don't you?
Link Joker's magnificence.
You're dying to find out what
kind of power this deck holds.
You've fallen under the
spell of its power, huh?
And it seems that the only way I can look
for Tetsu and Asaka is by fighting you.
Dark Clouds Over Fukuhara High School
Did you come here to defeat me?
I did... and I didn't.
My former master was monitoring you.
My current master craves your power.
Your master, huh?
That strange feeling I sensed from you...
Maybe that's the reason I found it
hard to discern your true feelings.
Say what you will.
There's my master, and then there's me.
That's all there is.
Well, shall we get this over with?
Tetsu Shinjou... Asaka Narumi...
Are you that worried about those two?
It's because they're my teammates.
I wonder if they would
appreciate your concern.
What are you trying to say?
Beginning now, you're going to
learn the various sides of humans.
Everything you know will be overturned.
...Reversed.
There is nothing that won't change!
Can we just get started?
I'll understand everything after
fighting that deck, Link Joker, right?
Yes.
Darn it! There's no end!
What's with these guys?!
Darn it! More of 'em?!
This darn necktie...
It's hard to move with
this stupid uniform on!
Stand up, Vanguard.
Stand up the Vanguard.
Micro-hole Dracokid!
Frontline Revenger, Claudas!
Certainly, this is the first
time I've seen this clan.
Despair comes to all who
gaze upon Link Joker.
Ride! Gravity Ball Dragon!
I ride Nullity Revenger, Masquerade!
Claudas moves. Call.
Attack.
Turn end.
The wait is over. I'll show
you the power of Link Joker.
Ride! Gravity Collapse Dragon!
Gravity Collapse Dragon's skill.
When Gravity Ball Dragon is in the Soul,
Gravity Collapse gets +10000 power.
On top of that...
When I ride this unit on
top of Gravity Ball Dragon,
I can lock one of my
opponent's rear-guard units!
Lock...
Lock... It's the ultimate binding.
The spell won't be lifted until
the end of your next turn.
You can't move; you can't attack;
you can't even retire.
All you can do is float there.
This is Link Joker...
That was just an introduction.
No more than a taste of what's to come.
Interesting...
This looks like it'll be kind of fun.
All right. It won't get drenched
from the rain here.
Attack!
After the trouble I went
through to get a uniform!
Jerk! Treat other people's
things with respect!
Are you the one who stirred
up the club members?
I did... and I didn't.
You've actually already
realized it, haven't you?
Those people... this deck...
the otherworldly power...
It's all because of something
much greater than any of us.
You don't mean...
That's right. This is all Void's will.
Void.
A transcendent existence that takes
in everything with its darkness,
and returns all life to nothingness.
Void will swallow up not only the planet
Cray, but everything in existence.
That includes the Earth.
By Reversing Earth's Vanguard fighters
and turning them into its own,
the Earth will destroy
itself, along with Cray!
"Reverse"?
All those who lose a fight against a
Link Joker deck also lose their own will,
and become one with Link Joker.
That's "Reverse."
Fighters who lose to Reversed
fighters become Reversed themselves.
Link Joker is becoming more powerful.
People who lose are Reversed...
That includes the club
members who challenged you.
Gimme a break! There's no way you
punks could beat Kyou the Great!
I didn't go around the world
ten times over for nothing!
Seven times, right?
Maybe seven and a half...
Whichever!
A bluff works better with a bigger number!
What about Tetsu and Asaka?
Ah... why don't you see
with your own eyes?
You've gotten serious at last.
This is the mode I want
from you, Ren Suzugamori.
If you join us, Link Joker
will become even stronger.
That's right. When this fight is over,
you'll also become one with
Link Joker, body and soul.
You'll be Reversed!
Two sides of the same coin, both
good and evil reside within your blade.
I ride...
...Blaster Dark Revenger!
Blaster Dark's Counterblast!
When my Vanguard has "Revenger" in its name,
I can retire one of your
front row rear-guards.
Gamma Burst!
Doreen's skill.
When Blaster Dark appears in the same column,
I can turn over one unit in the Damage Zone.
Do you think Blaster Dark's skill can
hold out against Link Joker's lock?
If so, you're badly mistaken.
You need to get a better understanding
of just how fearsome Link Joker is.
I'm not interested.
Call.
Knight of Nullity, Masquerade.
Masquerade attacks!
Attack!
Blaster Dark Revenger!
Turn end.
And Transient Revenger's lock opens.
From your expression, you seem to think
that getting one unit locked is nothing.
I'll show you the true power of
the ultimate clan, Link Joker!
Dragon of darkness, born of dark flames...
Convey an unending nightmare
to those who incur my wrath!
I ride Schwarzschild Dragon!
Schwarzschild Dragon's Counterblast.
I look at the top five cards of my deck,
and if Schwarzschild Dragon is there,
I can add it to my hand.
And if Gravity Collapse Dragon is in the
Soul, Schwarzschild gets +1000 power.
Call.
Furious Claw Star-vader, Niobium.
Gravity Collapse Dragon.
Devour the same soul, become
the dragon king of darkness,
and release your roar of destruction!
Limit Break!
Schwarzschild Dragon...
I can lock three of my
opponent's rear-guards!
Lock three units?!
This is a Link Joker Limit Break?!
Niobium and Lanthanum's skill!
They get +2000 power for every
locked rear-guard of my opponent.
With three locked units,
that's a total of 6000.
The more I lock, the more power I gain,
while my opponent loses power.
This is Link Joker!
You understand how wonderful
it is, don't you?
You've fallen to the dark side before.
With you...
Even the great Ren Suzugamori
is shaken and scared
when faced with the power of Link Joker.
But that weakness will be wiped away.
When you're Reversed, that is...
I don't need that kind of power.
I wonder how long that tough talk will last.
Even if you manage to ride out this turn,
you'll only be able to attack once next turn.
Gravity Collapse Dragon attacks.
Schwarzschild Dragon attacks
with a boost from Lanthanum.
Perfect guard with Dark Revenger, Mac Lir!
Niobium attacks.
Turn end.
It's your turn, but you can only attack once.
So, what are you going to do?
Considering the situation, no one would
criticize you if you forfeited the game here.
I would criticize myself.
If I can't help Tetsu and Asaka, there was
no point in our forming a team together.
Team? What are you talking about
at this stage of the game?
When we formed a team, I decided
that I would protect them.
I'm prepared to put my own
life on the line for that.
Then I think I'll see just
how prepared you are.
I ride Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Attack!
Guard! Intercept!
Turn end.
Even with the locks undone, your
despair-inducing disadvantage doesn't change.
I like those eyes!
But...
Your useless resistance is over.
Call!
I attack your rear-guard!
I attack your Vanguard!
Guard!
I attack once more.
Turn end.
Well done. But as a result of that guarding,
you only have one card in your hand.
You won't be able to block my next attack.
Meanwhile, I've got all these cards
in my hand, and an intercept unit.
I wonder if you'll be able
to get an attack through.
I told you, remember? I'm prepared.
Final Turn!
Tremble in fear in the
face of even greater rage!
Break ride!
Revenger, Raging Form Dragon!
The Vanguard gets +10000 power.
I can superior call a grade 2 or lower
Shadow Paladin from my deck.
Nullity Revenger, Masquerade.
And it gets +5000 power.
This is...
Call!
Transient Revenger attacks.
With its skill, it gets +3000 power.
Raging Form Dragon attacks
with a boost from Doreen.
Raging Form Dragon's Counterblast.
+3000 power.
Perfect guard with Barrier
Star-vader, Promethium.
Drive trigger check.
Even though you got multiple
break rides... Too bad.
Your last hope is over.
I'm not done yet.
Endless wrath...
Even when your body changes, your soul carries on.
Be reborn!
Revenger, Raging Form Dragon's Limit Break!
When the attack is over, I can
retire three of your rear-guards.
Superior persona ride with the Revenger,
Raging Form Dragon unit in my hand!
And it gets +10000 power.
Raging Form Dragon stands?!
Attack!
Wrathful dragon, pulverize
them with your brutal roar!
Because of that Limit Break,
he's got two more attacks left.
I have a damage of... 4.
As long as he doesn't draw a
trigger, I can protect myself.
No guard.
He's confident that he'll draw a trigger?!
Drive trigger... check.
Second check.
Critical trigger.
I give the +5000 power
to Illusionary Revenger
and the extra critical to Raging Form.
I didn't think he'd draw a trigger there...
Ren Suzugamori... You're stronger
than I had imagined.
You're up?
It looks like you're back to normal.
Now I know at least one way to
deal with this weird situation.
The Reversed fighter has to lose.
In other words, I can't lose.
Let's go, Suiko.
You don't remember, do you?
When I made that vow to put my life on
the line, I didn't just mean for those two.
I meant everyone on the team.
Suiko went to their side...
No good. It's not only Kourin and Rekka.
I can't get through to Aichi either.
Some kind of strong force is at work...
Tetsu... Asaka...
Aichi, what are you daydreaming about?
I know what it is. You're thinking
about Kourin, aren't you?
You said she hasn't been going
to school at all lately.
Right. But I heard she's just busy,
so I'm not worried any more.
Easy for you to say! You at least
go to the same school she does.
All I can do is come here to Card Capital
every day in the hopes of seeing her!
What is... this feeling?
It stopped.
What is this?
Asaka's room...
Asaka...
So fighters who lose to Reversed fighters
themselves become Reversed...
Right. I think that's how it works.
Yeah, probably...
Do you remember who Reversed you, Suiko?
I'm sorry.
The Reversed fighters are increasing.
Secretly and out of sight, but surely.
Next time: Eternal Marionette!
Eternal Marionette!
Who will be the next person
to be menaced by Link Joker?!
Everyone, please be safe!