Hey, hey, what's the Tea
Ceremony Club going to do?
Huh? As usual, we'll serve tea and
refreshments in a quiet setting...
Art Museum
Sharpen the Eye of Your Heart
Miyaji Academy High School Division
10 More Days Until the School Festival
Archery
Huh?! You're not gonna do a maid cafe?!
Rocks are Beautiful!
Earth Science Club
That's low!
Tea Ceremony Club, females, maid cafe...
Your thinking is way too simplistic!
School Festival
It's rude to girls in tea ceremony
clubs all over the country!
Apologize!
S-Sorry...
Miyaji Academy High School
Division Student Council
The Cardfight Club will participate
in the school festival too?
All clubs in this school are required
to take part in the festival.
Good. We're a brand-new club, so I
thought maybe we wouldn't be able to...
I'm looking forward to it.
How about we open a Cardfight dojo?
Let's also do a card exhibit!
Anyway, let's get started!
Oh, that's right. I forgot to tell you...
Suwabe...
Right.
You didn't submit an entry beforehand,
so right now, the only opening is the stage.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I wonder what kind of
performance you'll put on.
P-Performance?!
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
He's telling us to put on a play?!
Yeah, since the stage in the gym
is the only place we can use...
He knows how ridiculous that is.
I say we do it!
Right, Aichi?
Let's show 'em the strong
will of the Cardfight Club!
I hate to say this when you're so fired up,
but preparing a play is no simple thing.
Kourin...
First we'd need a script and staging,
then we'd have to prepare costumes and a set.
How do we do that with just five people?
Five people...
Come to think of it, where's Shingo?
Exciting School Festival
Secret
Ladies and gentlemen!
Shingo?
Marron's Glasses
Hayate and Nehalem to the Battlefield
W-What the heck is all this?!
Gancelot Returns!
by Shingo
Scripts?!
Scripts that I've written
over the past several years
that are set in the world of Vanguard!
Tristan Flies
Wow... Can we use them?
My debut as a scriptwriter has
come sooner than I expected.
Aichi! Leave the costume-making to us!
We're good at sewing.
Emi! Mai!
But of course! That's my Komoi Corps!
Laughing Invincible
All right! It looks like we
can actually do this thing!
Yep!
Well, everybody, let's all do our
best to make the festival a success!
Yeah!
I bet they're all excited about it right now.
What can rank amateur actors
do in just ten days?
Exactly.
They'll fall on their faces in
front of the whole student body...
The reputation of the Cardfight
Club will plummet even more,
making it only a matter of
time before the club folds.
A tea stalk is floating
straight up in my cup.
It looks like something
good is going to happen...
M-Misaki is going be in a
play at the school festival?!
She has practice, so said she'd
be coming home late for a while.
Misaki's first time on stage...
Misaki's proud moment! The
first page of her adolescence!
I have to capture the moment on film!
Suppose so...
Brother's school festival, you say?!
Hey, neat! That sounds like fun!
Right, Kai?
Sure...
Well, that's the reaction
I expected him to have...
Who cares about Kai?!
If Aichi and the rest are gonna
put on a play, then of course...
...Kourin is gonna be up on stage, too!
Well, that's the reaction
I expected you to have...
Kourin!
The Bamboo-Cutter
Vanguard
Long, long ago, there lived
a Little Sage, Marron.
One day, when Marron went to the
mountains to get some bamboo,
she found the beautiful CEO Amaterasu
inside some shining bamboo...
It turns out that King of Knights, Alfred
is in love with the beautifully-raised Amaterasu,
but her shy young maiden's
heart always stands in her way,
so she can never express her true feelings.
Then tragedy suddenly strikes
this sweet-and-sour couple!
Amaterasu is kidnapped
by Vowing Sword Dragon!
The poor thing is shut
up inside a dark cave!
Alfred goes out to save her,
fights bravely, and wins!
"Are you okay, Amaterasu?"
"I had faith you would come!"
"I would go anywhere for you."
And so, they live happily ever after.
The End
The End!
What do you think of this high fantasy
amalgamation between Vanguard and a fairy tale?!
That was interesting as heck!
That Vowing Sword Dragon
was especially awesome!
Eh, I don't know...
We have no choice but to do it.
We don't have time to be picky.
In that case, I'm going to
announce the casting!
How is it you get to decide?!
It's my script, and I'm going to direct it.
You don't speak back to the man at the helm.
First, Little Sage, Marron will
be played by Aichi Sendou.
O-Okay!
Vowing Sword Dragon will
be played by Naoki Ishida.
Yeah! Good call!
The heroine, CEO Amaterasu,
will be Misaki Tokura.
And the hero, King of Knights, Alfred...
...will be played by Kourin Tatsunagi!
Me?
In my scripts, Kourin of the popular
group Ultra-rare is the heroic character.
This will cause a stir and be a colossal
success, no two ways about it!
We can even set our sights on Broadway!
Yeah, that's what I said!
Misaki is the perfect
choice to play Amaterasu!
I've got to do my best to make the costume!
Aichi, you're going to be in it too, right?
Yep. I play Marron...
Maybe I'll go see you and
bring my camera along.
O-Oh, you don't have to do that...
I'll capture your performance amazingly,
spectacularly and perfectly, Misaki!
So wait for me!
I said you don't have to come...
Next up, our guests who are at the
pinnacle of popularity, Ultra-rare!
Hello, everyone!
We're Ultra-rare!
What do you mean you can't practice?!
We suddenly have to tape a show.
Even though every single day 'til
the performance is precious...
You've got the hero role.
Sorry.
Yeesh...
This is how actors get once they've
experienced a little success.
Let's start rehearsing.
It's hard on her, being an idol as
well as a student here at the academy.
That's why we've got to
do what we can on our own.
Misaki...
She's right.
And as for Kourin, it'll be fine if
she misses a day or two of practice.
It can't be helped...
Sendou, please say Kourin's
lines in her place.
S-Sure.
All right, this is where Alfred
defeats Vowing Sword Dragon
and saves Amaterasu...
in a touching scene!
Curse you, Alfred!
U-Um... Are you okay, Amaterasu?
I had faith you would come...
...Alfred.
Miyaji Academy High School Division
School Festival
6 Days Left!!
Isn't that Kourin?!
Yeah! She's as cute as always...
What's she doin'?! Walkin' back and forth...
What are you freshmen doing?
Sorry!
We're not doing anything!
Cut it out! No running in the hallway!
Okay! Sorry!
There are a lot of red lines...
So that's how you learn your lines, huh?
Even while working as an idol, this
play is a learning experience for you.
I-It's no big deal! I'm a pro.
Yeah. The day before the play, we'll
be doing a run-through from 3:00...
If you can make that with the rest
of us, there should be no problem.
Got it. I'll be there for sure.
"I had faith you would come..."
That's Amaterasu's line.
Page 27, line 6.
5 more days until the fest!!
3 Days Left
Days remaining until the school festival... 2!
I left that in the room...
Sorry!
No, it was my fault...
The idol seems busy today, too.
Huh? What did I forget again?
Oh, whatever! The school
isn't going anywhere.
That was Tatsunagi, right?
I had an emergency message to give her...
...so what should we do?
You look pretty fast.
Yeah, well...
My apologies, but would you catch
up with her and pass on the message?
Sure?
School Festival
Days Left Tomorrow!!
Kourin ain't here...
Good grief! She doesn't even bother
coming to the full rehearsal?!
Does she really have any
interest in doing this?!
Misaki...
But man, what's with Kourin standin' us up?!
She's really been busy with work.
Still, today was the full rehearsal!
You'd think she'd make it no matter what!
She'll come tomorrow.
I thought my casting choices
were inspired, but...
Yes! That's it!
Alfred! Sendou should play our hero, Alfred!
Yeah! If Kourin doesn't come
tomorrow, Aichi should do it!
You gotta have insurance!
In fact, you oughta do it either way!
That's right! I'll chuck
Kourin, who's undependable,
and aim for the star of
Broadway together with Sendou!
Yeah! That's the best way, Aichi!
But...
We agree for once, Ishida!
Yeah! Not bad, Bowl-cut!
You too, Bowl... You had to
sneak an insult in there?!
What the hey?!
Come on, you two!
Excuse me?!
Stop it!
Miyaji Academy School Festival
Yakisoba
Um...
Can I help you...?
Come on, you're making him
nervous. Don't stare like that.
They're using a good sauce.
I got a program!
It says Brother's play starts at 2:00...
Huh? Where're Manager and Lose-umi?
Karate Club Presentation
Kourin Kourin Kourin
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
It's past noon, already...
Kourin...
Come to think of it, Rekka said she'd
be on a shoot today until lunch...
That's right!
Kourin must be there, too...
Give me a break.
I guess she doesn't know how
to manage her schedule.
I can't deal with these
last-minute schedule changes.
Okay, Sendou, take this!
Please ride King of Knights, Alfred!
But the play is at 2:00. I'm sure
she'll show up before then...
Vice-president?!
What's this? Were you expecting someone else?
I have an emergency message.
There was a mistake in the program.
I'm terribly sorry, but the Cardfight Club's
play will actually start at 1:00.
What?!
At 1:00?!
How can you just change it?!
Well, you people study at Miyaji Academy,
which churns out the human resources
needed to deal with a global society...
So I have faith that you'll be able
to handle this level of trouble
by adapting to the circumstances.
What should we do?! What should we do?!
Things just went from bad to
worse! It doubles our trouble!
Shut up!
There's been a change in the program.
The Cardfight Club's performance
is going to begin shortly, at 1:00.
Cardfight Club?
You know, the one that formed recently...
I'm not really interested.
But it could be fun!
Yeah! And I hear that girl
from Ultra-rare is in it, too!
Huh...!
There are a lot of people here...
Of course! This is Kourin's stage.
Mai, help me get Misaki's costume on her!
I can't! My hands are full!
It's heavy!
Yoo-hoo!
Akari...
I came after hearing that your
performance was moved up,
and it's just as chaotic as I imagined.
I'll help... um...
This is Emi Sendou from the
middle school division.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Anyway, you guys sure are unlucky.
Your full rehearsal was pushed back,
and now the actual performance
is gonna start early...
What did you just say?
Don't move!
I'm talking about your run-through yesterday,
which was pushed from 3:00 to 5:00...
Who said that?
The vice-president...
He had me tell Kourin that
the time was changed to 5:00.
Cardfight Club
Love and Youthful Vanguard
Misaki... Kourin will come, won't she?
Of course. Let's go.
Right!
Long, long ago, there lived
a Little Sage, Marron.
Oh?! What's that glowing bamboo?
When Marron splits the glowing bamboo,
the beautiful CEO Amaterasu,
of all things, is born!
There's Misaki!
Amaterasu is raised beautifully...
But one day, tragedy strikes!
I'm Vowing Sword Dragon!
I'm taking Amaterasu with me!
Amaterasu...!
Amaterasu is shut inside
the Celestial Rock Cave!
Will the hero that appears to save her...
...actually appear to save her?!
Suck it up, Aichi. Come on,
put this on and fight me!
But...
The story can't finish 'til
Alfred appears and beats me!
Come on! It doesn't look like Kourin's
gonna be here, so forget about her!
You're right. We have to
handle this somehow...
It's for Kourin's sake, too.
There ya go! That's the Aichi I know!
Okay, I'll be waitin' for you on stage!
What's happening?
This isn't part of the show, is it?
What are you doing?!
Get your act together, Cardfight Club!
Who cares about this?! Where's Kourin?!
Yeah! Get Ultra-rare out here!
That's what we came here to see!
Yeah!
If I don't get to see Kourin,
there was no point in coming!
I came to see Kourin!
Oh, dear. The budget they were
given was too small after all.
It's only natural for a
cheaply-built set to collapse.
W-What the heck is this?!
Is... Is this my fault?
It's over... My script...
My stage... My Broadway...
I'm sorry, Aichi... I'm sorry,
Boss Lady... I'm sorry...
No, it's not your fault, Naoki...
That's right!
This, that, everything
is the fault of this...
Wrong!
That's wrong!
Are you okay, Amaterasu?
Th-Thank goodness!
One second later and I would've blamed it
all on this impossible script of Shingo Komoi's!
I see... By "this," you meant...
Thank you for your patience!
The hero, King of Knights, Alfred, is here!
I was waiting for you, Kourin!
I had faith you would come!
Thank goodness she got here in time...
Yeah, but this is wrecked...
We've reached the climax at last!
Alfred's battle is going to begin!
The dragon you're supposed to
fight can't come out any more.
What should we do?
No problem.
The true enemy that I'm going to fight...
...is over there!
Daigo?!
It's Daigo!
D-D-D-D-D-Daigo?!
The genuine legendary
fighter, Daigo, is here!
Daigo?!
That's the legendary fighter, Daigo?!
Daigo?! He's cool, sure, but is he strong?
What are you saying?!
When it comes to Vanguard, he's God-plus!
Wow! I never imagined I'd get
to see Daigo fight at school!
Next time: Legendary School Festival!
Legendary School Festival!
What will the outcome of the fight be?!
More importantly, what about the play?!
It's all messed up!
It's fine! I expected something like
this would happen, so I plotted it out!
This was all part of my plan!
You total liar!!