Stand up, Vanguard!
Cardfight Club
Members Wanted
I decided to form a Cardfight Club in the
high school division of Miyaji Academy!
And so I had to gather at least five members
to be recognized as an official club.
We got to tentatively use a club room, and yet,
just when I thought our club was underway...
Permission denied.
I can't give your Cardfight Club
the official seal of approval.
Oh, no... Isn't there
anything that can be done?!
It is possible.
How?!
Create a track record.
If you accomplish outstanding results,
you'll be treated as a special
case and recognized as a club.
We put all of our slim hopes
on an intramural match...
Vanguard Club
Welcome to Hitsue High's Vanguard Club!
But it turned out to be with
Hitsue High's Vanguard Club!
Kai, Miwa, Morikawa, Izaki, and Kamui, too!
The fight that we can't lose continues.
Wha...?! What the heck is this?!
This isn't my deck!
Those jerks...
Is that a Kagero deck?
Maybe that's...
What's going on?
Kai put together Morikawa's deck.
You can't think of him as the
usual Morikawa, right, Kai?
Dang it! I didn't think I'd get stuck
fighting with a deck like this.
I ride this guy.
Even so, the great Katsumi is going to win.
Because...
The great Katsumi is a genius!
Red Pulse moves.
Bahr does the strongest attack against Llew!
Drive trigger check.
That's...
Kai's strongest card!
Dragonic Overlord the End!
If he has the End, then there's no doubt...
That's Kai's deck!
And it's a serious one. But why...?
How does my strength compare
to yours right now?
This way, we'll find out.
Now, show your true form!
Crossride,
Dragonic Overlord the End!
Kai's Shadow
I can't lose this fight.
So that we'll be able to have our
Cardfight Club at Miyaji Academy...
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
There it is! Aichi's avatar!
Blaster Blade attacks!
Come what may, I have to win this fight!
This looks like it'll be an
interesting fight, right?
Call!
Counterblast.
Berserk's skill!
I ride Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Gancelot attacks!
I strongest ride Dauntless Dragon!
Here I go, strongest attack!
Now you've got more damage than me, Aichi!
I can't believe it... Lose-umi
is actually a match for Brother!
Just what you'd expect from Kai's deck!
How about that, Aichi?!
Goes to show that I can master any deck.
You're doing well, Morikawa.
But I'm definitely going to win!
Your proud, noble white wings
enhance my courage and strength!
Break ride!
Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Break ride's effect!
Gallatin, Wingal, and Escrad
each gain +5000 power!
Gancelot himself gains +10000 power!
Wonderful! All of the
units powered up at once!
This break ride powers up the
Vanguard and three rear-guard units.
It's called Breaking Shining Wing!
I call, then attack!
Go, Escrad!
Berserk does the strongest intercept!
Gancelot attacks!
On top of that, he gains
+2000 power with his own skill.
Llew's skill!
Gancelot gets +4000 power!
Because of the combo with Llew, the
total attacking force is 33000!
Awesome, Aichi! Ain't no
way he can block that!
Twin drive check!
Heal trigger!
I add +5000 to the power of Gallatin.
Then I heal 1 damage!
Second check.
Critical trigger!
I add +5000 to the power of Gallatin.
Then I give the extra critical to Gancelot.
Uh oh...
Yeah! Just 1 more damage!
Sendou, finish him off!
It isn't going to end just yet...
My deck isn't that easy to beat.
Gallatin attacks with a boost from Wingal!
Strongest perfect guard with Wyvern Guard!
Shoot! Right when he almost had him!
You're not my number one pupil for nothing.
You're doing pretty well, too, Aichi.
But if I'm defeated by my pupil,
my fame as the strongest
fighter goes out the window.
Time to get serious!
His strength is neverending!
My genius is also neverending!
If two neverendings join hands,
everything else comes to an end!
I strongest break ride
Dragonic Overlord the End!
There it is!
And this is this break ride's strongest effect...
The End gets +10000.
And on top of that, the strongest skill!
Strongest skill?! What's he talkin' about?
Hey, what's wrong?!
Th-This isn't good... The End's skill is...
That's it...
Strongest call!
And then Garp does the strongest attack!
Escrad intercepts!
The End attacks Gancelot!
Perfect guard with Mark!
Twin drive check.
Draw trigger.
I add +5000 to the End's power, then draw!
Here's where I activate that
strongest skill from before!
The End! Strongest stand again!
This is the skill that Dauntless
Dragon gave to the End!
After attacking,
if I discard three cards from my
hand, the End can stand again!
This is my special move!
It spells "the end" for you!
W-What skill is that?!
Ahem... The End can attack one more time.
And... with that trigger just
now, its power is 26000...
I'm impressed that Morikawa has
mastered Dauntless and the End...
But even Kai, who put together that deck...
Now, Aichi...
You're going to be shaken to
your core by the End's power.
The End does another strongest attack!
No guard!
Strongest twin drive!
Oh, no!
What's wrong?!
Another the End shows
up at a time like this?!
And again, it's strongest time!
This time, I activate the End's skill!
Here's where he can use the End
that came to his hand.
Counterblast.
Next, the strongest Persona Blast!
And then, the End doesn't end!
That darn thing stood up again!
The End can stand up with a
Counterblast and Persona Blast.
He can do another attack with 26000 power...
Aichi...
Here I go! Strongest attack! Neverend!
5 damage!
Just 1 damage to go...
And he still has one attack left!
I...
I can't afford... to lose!
Here comes the finishing blow!
I won't let it be! Guard!
And I just had to do 1 damage...
Turn end!
He didn't take any damage that turn?!
So not even the End can reach Aichi now?
Very impressive, Morikawa. And so was...
But...
...I made up my mind that I wouldn't fall.
I swore to myself that I'd win!
Break ride again with Solitary
Liberator, Gancelot!
Wha...?!
Amazing!
I never thought he'd be able to break
ride with Gancelot another time!
Now Gancelot can do that attack again!
Breaking Shining Wing!
I add +5000 to the power of
Gallatin, Llew, and Wingal!
Gancelot himself gets +10000 power!
His units powered up again!
Call!
I'm going to end it this turn...
Gancelot attacks with a boost from Llew!
Gancelot's skill!
+2000 power!
Llew's skill!
Gancelot gets +4000 power!
Since it's come to this, strongest no guard!
Morikawa, Kai...
I'm going to win.
For our sake...
For the sake of our Cardfight Club!
The final winner: Aichi Sendou!
As such, Miyaji Academy wins this
fight between the two schools!
Yeah!
Hitsue High School               Miyaji Academy
I knew he'd do it...
You achieved a great victory against
the strongest fighter, Morikawa...
Rejoice, my number one pupil!
Yikes. Izaki, you'd better get outta here!
Eh? Me? But...
Here he comes.
Izaki, you lousy...!
Um, Kai...
You did great! Now we get to have
our Cardfight Club at school!
That was a tremendous fight, Sendou!
Th-Thank you.
No, seriously, it was freakin' awesome!
Aw, no...
He really has gotten stronger, hasn't he?
Yeah.
Even if I fought him directly right now,
it's possible Aichi's power
would be beyond my reach.
Now, even at Miyaji Academy...
...we get to have our Cardfight Club!
Miyaji Academy High School
Division Student Council Office
What?! Would you repeat that?
I-It really is an unpleasant result...
...but, uh...
...the tentative Miyaji Academy
Cardfight Club... beat Hitsue.
Then you're telling me we have
no choice but to accept it?
The establishment of the Cardfight Club?!
Y-Yes... But I have an idea...
Congratulations, Aichi!
Thank you.
Congratulations, Brother!
Thank you!
Izaki, you imbecile!
Now that we've both got our clubs,
Where did you put my strongest deck?!
I'm sure we'll get the chance to fight again.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too!
It was a wonderful fight, Miyaji students.
Every member of Hitsue High School's
Vanguard Club faced you with all they had.
But you folks brilliantly
overcame those obstacles.
And I'm sure the pride
and victory you attained
will support and encourage
your club in the days ahead.
I'll say it one more time.
Congratulations, Miyaji Academy
Cardfight Club members!
Hitsue members...
Thank you!
Tea with a fine fragrance
calms the agitated mind.
Indeed.
I don't know how to apologize
for the failure of this plan...
Forget about it. There are
still plenty of measures left.
What kind of measures?
The least you can do is
think of them yourself!
Y-Yes, sir!
For now, have you "sent salt to the enemy"?
Yes, sir. Modeled after the
history of Kenshin Uesugi...
Note: 16th century warlord who was
even honorable towards his enemies.
Good job.
Now I'm sure they realize
how magnanimous we are.
Yes, sir. I appreciate the kind words.
All right!
So from now on, this really
is our club room, huh?
Are you kids the club members?
The Student Council informed
me that a new club was forming.
Every club needs a faculty advisor, right?
Um... Who are you?
I'm Nakamurabashi.
H-Hello...
By the way...
What does the Cardfight Club do?
Excuse me?
Of course, we play Vanguard...
What's Vanguard?
Sorry. I'm a little behind the times...
You don't know, and you're
going to be our advisor?
Because he's a teacher at this school...
Why is the Student Council being nice to us?
Don't tell me he's a spy or something...
Oh, come on...
That's funny.
Ah, what's the diff?
No matter which teacher,
an advisor's an advisor.
The important thing is, this
makes us an official club!
Now that we're an official club, all
kinds of activities are waiting for us,
like intramural matches and
Vanguard tournaments...
That's right. Today we took the
first step of our Cardfight Club.
From this moment on, we're Miyaji
Academy's Cardfight Club!
Going forward, let's all
have fun and do our best!
Stand up...
...Vanguard!
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
All right! The Cardfight Club stood up!
We can ride and call and
nobody will complain!
I don't know what you
two are talking about...
but let's do our best!
Yeah!
We erased the "tentative" from
the club room's nameplate...
...so the next thing we have to do is...
Next time: Who's the Co-Captain?!
Who's the Co-Captain?!
...figure out who's going to
be the captain and co-captain.
Ahem. On this auspicious day, I am very
honored that you have chosen me...
Pain in the neck! Anybody who
wants to do it should just do it!