So the camping trip is over...
Yeah. It was surprisingly fun.
That's right. What should we do
about a Cardfight camp?
Good question. Should we invite the
middle school division kids too?
Sure. It'll be an assembly
of the Komoi Corps!
What are you talking about,
"Komoi Corps"?! Who talks like that?
Come to think of it, what was
the middle school division up to
while the high school division
was on a "global" camping trip?
Um... I remember Emi said
there was something...
Today must be...
Miyaji Academy Middle School Division
Open House
Oh...?
This is it!
Miyaji Academy's middle school division...
Wow! All kinds of people have come!
Yeah. Well, it is the middle school
division's open house today.
The kids out there might be
first-year students next year.
That's right. Next year, we'll
be veterans of the academy.
Second-year Emi!
Second-year Mai!
I feel kind of embarrassed for some reason!
Me too!
Miyaji Academy lives up to my expectations!
Huh? Those people...
Gouki... and Nagisa?
This is our district's greatest prep school.
I can feel its refinement and
grace all over the place.
What do you think, little sister?
Do you like it?
Hmmm...
Not really!
But...! Nagisa...
You're like a delicate flower.
Without a classy place like this,
you'll easily break off at the stem.
See, unlike me, you've got a shy personality.
Kaboom?
...Shy?
Kaboom...?
Can you understand how I feel?
But I want to go to Hitsue
Middle School instead.
Kamui goes there, you know!
I want to go to the same school he does!
I can't bring myself to say that having
you and Kamui apart is a terrible thing.
Look, don't they say "absence
makes the heart grow fonder"?
Kaboom?
But...
Captain! Then why don't we go
to Hitsue and kidnap Kamui?
Having him transfer here would
solve everything-kaboom!
Consider your surroundings! You don't act
like pirates in a classy place like this!
Kaboom?
You want Nagisa to feel ashamed
of us when she starts here?
Kaboom...
From now on, we've gotta change.
Even if we're pirates,
we can't be actin' bad.
We gotta be peaceful gentlemen.
Like... Yeah. Like so-called
"gentlemen pirates."
W-What the heck?
Kaboom?
Anyway, we can't be kickin' up
a fuss here as pirates. Got me?!
Yes...
Then let's keep lookin' at
this school. Come on, Nagisa!
Okay...
Gentlemen pirates?
That's a tall order...
The Pirate Flag Fluttering at Miyaji
Yeesh! Gouki and Nagisa are at Miyaji?!
If they find Miss Emi,
all heck will break loose!
Miss Emi is my princess!
But she's their mortal enemy!
Or that's what he says...
But the truth is GE, right?
He's using Gouki and Nagisa
as an excuse to see Miss Emi!
Shut up!
Open House
Pirate Membership Drive
Pirate membership drive?!
I don't want to think about it, but I can
only imagine one person who would...
N-No, I don't think even
he would go that far...
N-Not possible!
NNP...
Indoor Pool
Long time no see, Kamui!
Gouki!
What are you doing?
I'm on guard against Nagisa's flying attack!
She's not here now.
When she sensed you coming, she took off.
How could she sense me?!
It's like she's got a Kamui detector.
KD, yo!
It seems you two just missed each other,
but I'm sure she'll be back soon.
Wait here with anticipation,
bridegroom of my little sister.
I ain't Nagisa's groom!
I-I think what's more important is...
MI, yo...
So what the heck are you up to?
Me? Well, I'm...
...expanding the ranks of my crew!
Th-Then you really are the one
who's behind all this?!
Pirates are grand!
We steal the things we want.
We forge new courses with our own power.
The only thing that binds
us is our own rules!
Now that's the ideal way of livin'!
Spreading that philosophy across the
globe is the mission I was tasked with.
And it begins here at this school!
So speaks the king of the pirate geeks...
You've gotten even more into it
since the last time we met.
Kamui! Fight me!
If you lose, you'll become a pirate too!
This is an offer you can't refuse.
Miss Emi!
And Miss Mai too!
EM, yo!
Kamui?!
Help!
If you turn down this fight,
it'll be a let-down.
The princess is waiting to be rescued!
As a brave hero, it's my duty to save her!
Princess! I'm gonna help you!
"Princess"?
It's a showdown! I'm gonna beat you,
then save Princess Emi and Princess Mai!
Music to my ears.
Emi, he called me a princess too!
Kamui, be careful!
Princess! There's no need to worry!
Listen to me seriously! This doesn't
seem to be just any ordinary fight!
Attack! Brazil!
That makes another pirate.
W-What was that?!
That's what's been happening to everyone
who's lost to them, one right after another!
Are you surprised, Kamui?
All who lose to us become Reversed like that.
Reversed?
They become Reversed, Brazil!
This Reversing is the method
by which we increase our ranks.
Kamui, you're gonna be a pirate too!
Gouki... You...
Come!
I don't know what this is about, but if
I just let Miss Emi and Mai hang there,
it looks like they'll be in serious trouble.
Kamui...
I'm gettin' the idea that if I don't
kick his butt, no good can come of this!
Kamui the Great!
Gouki! I swear I'll win this!
BC, yo!
Be careful!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Skeleton Assault Troops Captain!
Beast Deity, Riot Horn!
I ride Romario!
Beast Deity, Max Beat!
Attack!
Commodore Blueblood attacks!
Beast Deity, Damned Leo!
Desert Gator!
Heh. Now the real fighting starts.
Here I go!
At the bottom of the sea, where no light
penetrates, he gathers undead pirates together.
With the power of his savage soul, his ship rises
and sails over the vast expanse of sea!
I ride...
Lord of the Seven Seas, Nightmist!
Call!
You pirates of dauntless
courage, come to me anew!
I'll introduce you to this guy.
Ice Prison Hades Emperor, Cocytus "Reverse"!
Cocytus "Reverse"? Is there a
card like that in Granblue?
You don't know what kind of
moves this guy's got...
So... will you be able to hold out
against my attacks until you find out?
Attack!
Next is your Vanguard!
Ruin Shade!
The vibe Gouki's giving off today, it's
not simply strength or anything like that.
I sense something unknown...
Don't tell me!
Gouki himself has been Reversed,
and this weird vibe is...
...something inside Gouki that's changed?
Attack me. It's your turn.
Unless maybe you're so terrified of
pirates that you're unable to move?
There's only one thing I'm sure about!
If I don't win this, I won't be
able to help Miss Emi and Mai!
This is the rumored beast god!
Its fists are absolutely invincible!
It's crushed innumerable opponents!
The newest! The greatest! The zenith!
The great Kamui rides Strongest Beast
Deity, Ethics Buster Extreme!
Call!
Desert Gator attacks Blueblood!
Guard!
Hatred Chaos!
I attack Blueblood again!
And now for my main event!
Ethics Buster Extreme attacks Lord
of the Seven Seas, Nightmist!
Twin drive check!
No trigger with his first card!
Even if I don't draw a trigger here,
I've got a skill you're gonna be
on the receiving end of!
Limit Break activated!
With this Limit Break, if a grade 1 or
higher card is revealed during a drive check,
I can stand a rear-guard!
Stand, Hatred Chaos!
Next up, Riot Horn's skill.
If a Beast Deity in the same
row stands, he can stand too!
And then my second check!
This time it's a grade 0, Brazil!
Shut up with that nonsense! Look closely!
A stand trigger, Brazil!
I stand Desert Gator and give it +5000 power!
His left and right rear-guards
are back in business!
And Kamui the Great can
attack two more times!
TT, yo!
This is a game-changing chain attack!
And its name is...
World Ultra Mega-Ultra-Super-Destruction!
I dedicate this attack to the princesses!
Please watch closely.
Kamui said he's dedicating an attack to us!
This has loosened a little.
Emi?
The captain's damage is 4, Brazil!
Kamui caught up to him! Hmph...
Desert Gator attacks Ruin Shade!
You ain't got any more rear-guards
to protect your Vanguard.
This is where I win!
Hatred Chaos, attack Nightmist!
Gouki, prepare yourself!
You're naive, Kamui.
You can't lower my pirate
flag with power like that!
Guard!
I couldn't do any more than
1 damage with that attack?!
No matter how desperate your attack,
you won't be able to get
in the way of us pirates!
No! Stop it, I said!
Fight! Fight!
Stop struggling, Brazil!
I don't want to fight like that!
Emi!
Hiroshi! Kaoru!
Stop it!
SI, yo!
What do you guys want?
Brazil?!
Jerks! You promised not to lay a hand
on Miss Emi 'til my fight was over!
That promise is over!
As long as I have this card,
victory is in the bag.
In other words, this fight is all but over.
I don't need hostages anymore.
Hiroshi! Kaoru!
Turn those little girls into pirates!
No!
Gouki! Miss Emi doesn't want to!
Is this the way you've always been?
Like I care about the feelings of
an opponent who doesn't wanna fight!
You really have changed.
Or more like you were changed by the Reverse.
The Gouki Daimonji that I know
would never say anything like that!
Handsome
Why won't you join our Team Handsome?!
Right now, instead of joining up
with friends, I wanna test myself.
To see how far I can get...
What's that?!
Would ya leave him alone?
A Team Handsome man doesn't try and force
somebody to do something they don't wanna do.
Gouki...
The true Gouki treats people's
feelings with respect.
He doesn't try to force 'em to do
stuff they don't wanna do!
That's the old, weak Gouki.
I would never have been able to
increase the ranks of my pirates
in these tough times that way.
I'm gonna bring you to your senses!
Before that, I'm gonna make you a pirate!
Huh?
It's not here! It's not here!
What? What's wrong?!
My deck's disappeared!
Say what?! Look for it!
Strange. I know I left it here...
Right?
I wouldn't know!
Brazil...
What about you guys?
I wouldn't know!
WK!
Those guys...
Good timing! While he's lookin',
take care of these two, Brazil.
Don't tell me it's on the
underside of the table?
Sure.
I see! No, that'd be impossible.
Do a good job lookin' for it.
Yeah...
Emi and Mai, are you two okay?
Rekka?!
Shhh! If you make a fuss, they'll notice.
Did you come to save us?
Sheesh! Worthless minions...
Kamui! I'm gonna take care of you first!
This sorcerer lying dormant in the abyss has
obtained an even more accursed power!
The power to end the life of all beings
on the face of this Earth!
Ice Prison Hades Emperor, Cocytus "Reverse"!
Break ride!
Break ride skill...
And for pirates, the Drop Zone
is a sea of reincarnation!
It's a place from which souls can return!
Superior call!
Corrupt Dragon's skill!
Sea Strolling Banshee's skill!
Limit Break!
I put three cards from my
deck into the Drop Zone!
I lock Dancing Cutlass!
"Lock"?!
This way, I can superior call one unit.
Be resurrected, Ruin Shade!
I call the finishing stroke.
The rear-guard circle was empty,
and now it's filled.
And his attacking power for all
the units has majorly increased!
MI, yo!
You've been performing a lot
of skills that you're good at.
Combos with the Drop Zone,
bringing back units,
strengthening all of them with
your Infinite Resurrection Hell...
This is the true value of a Granblue deck.
And its name is...
Eternal Resurrection Final Hell!
That's right. Pirates can keep comin' back!
A deck like your Nova Grappler won't be
able to defend against my upcoming attacks.
But be happy! When you turn into a pirate,
I'll switch it out for a Granblue deck.
Whether you like it or not!
You know just what to say
to keep things interesting,
but things aren't gonna
go your way so easily!
A long time ago, I made a vow.
Nova Grappler is my partner.
I swore I wouldn't part with it lightly!
So you've decided on that
as your partner, huh?
During my training here, I've
tried out various decks,
but of them all, this one fits me the most.
I'll swear this right in front of you, Gouki.
I swear that no matter what rough
waves comes from here on in,
this deck and I will ride 'em out together.
I'm not gonna part with it lightly.
Right.
That's right. Just like I vowed back then,
my deck and I are gonna
overcome this rough sea.
And then I'll bring you to your senses!
What do you think?! Look at
all the pirates I've recruited
through my intervention efforts,
and in such a short time!
Intervention efforts, my foot!
What are you saying?! Yielding in the fight
is the same as yielding to my pirate flag!
Gouki... I swear I'll bring
you back to your normal self!
Kamui!
...Huh?
I just had a strange dream.
In it, Kamui and Gouki were fighting,
while a masked ninja fell into a pool.
Next time: Kamui's Fist!
Kamui's Fist!
You're... Ninja Master?!