What the...?!
A Link Joker unit?!
Kamui! Are you okay?!
Y-Yeah!
Does that steal your
lifeforce if it hits you?
Ali!
The complete opening of the gate is at hand.
This kind of scene is happening
to fighters all over the world.
World End
You're trying to take away the
happiness of so many people.
By being Reversed, they've become
stronger than ever before.
As a fighter, do you think there's
anything more pleasing than that?
Completely cold-hearted is
what you are, Aichi Sendou.
I'm... cold-hearted?
It affects Kourin, too.
How long have you known Kourin now?
A year... No, two?
You're trying to crush
everything she holds dear.
But I... I'm not...
I'm trying to crush what she holds dear?
It's not over!
I'm not ready to give up yet!
Even if we've got only a little time left,
we have to fight to the very end!
I won't let Link Joker take over!
Darn it! I don't care what those
things are! I ain't givin' in!
Anyway, I can start by beatin' these guys!
W-Well said, juvenile delinquent.
All right! That's what we gotta do right now!
Okay! We've gotta hold out a little longer!
Let's go!
Of course!
The fools. All of their resistance is futile.
No, it isn't!
Aichi...
So you want to be punished even more?
Guard!
After seeing everyone, I understand.
What you're saying is all wrong!
Reversed fighters have become strong
with the power of Link Joker.
But that's not their true power!
Even if it is my fault
that they lose that power...
Goooo!
...if they continue to Cardfight, they'll
eventually become that strong on their own!
They'll be able to have that
strength again, or even greater!
Open your eyes!
You guys...
...are Vanguard fighters, too!
We're all on the same side!
Don't give in to Reverse!
Just like my friends, who are
fighting out there right now!
Cold Death Dragon.
As for Kourin and the others...
If they lose their memories with us,
I'll be terribly sad.
But... someday, somewhere, in the
not-too-distant future, Kourin and I will...
I'm sure we'll meet again!
Aichi...
I'm going to protect this world,
so that we can all meet each other again!
How dull.
That's your response, even after I've shown
you what's happening to the world?
It looks like he held out somehow.
But the conditions required
for "World End" are all met.
Your rear-guards can't help, and it'll be
impossible for your Vanguard to break through alone.
Struggle as you might, there's
no escape from "World End."
I'm telling you, I will break through.
And then I'll set the whole world free!
To set free those who are
held captive by a spell,
now more than ever, enter the
fray, king of all knights!
I ride...
Liberator of the Round Table, Alfred!
Alfred...?
I'm going to protect this world.
Limit Break!
I remember that skill!
You move rear-guards to your deck
and call forth five new units.
However...
...since they're locked,
they can't do a thing!
That's not true!
What?
Liberate the lock!
What's that light?!
What?!
W-What...
...is this?!
What's happening?!
With the skill of this Limit Break,
I can move locked cards to my deck!
What?!
And now...
Five comrades, gather on the battlefield!
My comrades were
set free from the lock!
The other Takuto gave me this Alfred.
This is... "Liberate the Lock"!
If you overcome this trial,
I'm sure this card will give you power.
The way he broke through the lock...
It's very Gold Paladin-like.
It's very Aichi-like.
On top of that, the rear-guards
that were locked are gone!
Now that the condition of having five
or more cards locked isn't satisfied,
he can't bring about "World End"!
Even Takuto couldn't stop it.
But he...
Sendou, who fought even though
it meant putting his life in danger...
He was able to do this precisely
because he overcame that trial.
You've been locking units,
Reversing fighters, capturing hearts...
...and now you're trying to put
the whole world under your spell.
But I won't let you get your way anymore!
All you knights!
Give power to Alfred!
Alfred!
Attack!
For the sake of everyone who is dear to me...
For the sake of this world that I love...
...I'm going to beat you!
Sendou!
Aichi...
I-It can't be...
This is...
What?!
What's happening here?
Look! Sis! Koutei!
The ring is starting to break!
I see...
Aichi did it!
Aichi!
Sendou is okay!
That jerk did it!
Sendou...
Aichi!
What?!
Ta...kuto...!
You ruined everything...
You're coming with me!
It's you!
You've stared to come apart,
so I can finally return to normal.
Let go of me!
Takuto...
Thank you, Aichi.
Yeah.
And all fighters...
What's that voice?
This world was protected because of you.
Our world, Cray, as well...
Link Joker's ambition has failed.
I'm sure there will be
peace for the time being.
I'm profoundly grateful to you all.
You...
Takuto!
And finally...
Suiko.
Rekka.
Y-Yes?!
Kourin.
Yes?
I have to leave this world.
And so, you three will be set free.
I can't express in words
the gratitude I feel for you.
I've had such a good time
being with you three.
We have, too...
And...
...I'm sorry.
Takuto...
The time has come for us to part.
Let me go!
I won't let go.
We're going together.
No!!
And so... I guess it's all over?
I think so...
It's over...
To think that the opponent I was
really seeking was right here...
Kai...
Aichi...
Link Joker's mentor has left.
Kai... And yet we still must fight.
That's your fate...
Or maybe it's my fate.
A Vanguard fight...
That's the only way you and I
can understand each other.
Next time: The Intersecting Path!
The Intersecting Path
I'll fight, putting everything on the line!
The fight I was searching for is right here!
And I'm... going to win!