Ren Suzugamori has fallen.
You're the last one left.
If you lose, the world
will belong to Link Joker.
Scary, isn't it?
But even if you say you want
out now, I won't allow it.
If I can bring the world...
bring everyone back to normal,
I don't care what happens to me.
I'll fight!
You should feel honored.
I'm going to settle this myself.
I will say this.
Aichi Sendou, you won't beat me.
Not a chance.
That's right. Nothing will change.
You can't change anything.
This world is already finished.
I'm definitely going to beat you...
and save the world.
No matter what happens to me!
The time for the gate to
fully open is drawing near.
This wind is proof of that.
Perfect Black Ring
It's totally beautiful,
but also dangerous, right?
It probably means we're
just about out of time.
Yeesh. There ain't no end to 'em!
Tell me about it.
Let's roll!
There isn't much time left.
If I don't defeat him as
quickly as possible...
Not yet...
Wait until after I finish this fight!
It's cute how brave you are, boy.
Exhausted as you are, taking
a stand against me...
I'll crush you with all my might.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Star-vader, World Line Dragon!
Liberator, Cheer Up Trumpeter!
I ride Ruin Magician.
I ride Marron!
Attack!
I attack with Krypton!
Is something wrong, Aichi Sendou?
N-Nothing.
All right!
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride...
Blaster Blade Liberator!
Attack!
I ride...
Star-vader, Infinite Zero Dragon!
Attack!
Guard!
What's this?
Still think you're going
to beat me, even like this?
It looks like it'll be over
faster than I thought.
It won't be over.
There's still the fight between me and you.
What on Earth are you talking about?
You would betray me?
Trying to save the world at this late date?
You're the only strong guy
that I haven't fought yet.
The way I am now, I can take you down.
What arrogance...
You won't have that fight, Kai.
Because I'm going to defeat Takuto!
Radiate noble power
and turn it into a universal bond!
I ride...
Liberator of Bonds, Gancelot Zenith!
Here I go!
Is that the last of them?
These guys were such pushovers,
it doesn't matter how many there were!
I'm not surprised.
The fighters from
Fukuhara High School are strong.
Phallon attacks!
Kourin!
Where are we?
Look, Kourin.
Aichi...
Gancelot!
I got a critical trigger!
I give the power to my rear-guard Gancelot,
and the extra critical to my Vanguard!
He's driven him to 5 damage...
All right, just one more step!
Take him down, Aichi!
Oh, no...
How so?
If he doesn't finish the fight this turn...
If he doesn't... then what?
That guy has 5 damage.
So now he can use an Ultimate Break.
His Ultimate Break is...
Attack!
Guard!
It's no use.
Struggle as you may, I'm going to
be the one who wins this fight.
Sword of despair that dyes
all brilliance jet-black!
Break ride!
Star-vader, "Omega" Glendios!
"Omega" Glendios?
Be careful, Sendou!
What's wrong?
That "Omega" Glendios...
Break ride skill!
I lock Gancelot and Cheer Up Trumpeter!
Call!
I use Glendios's skill to give
one of my rear-guards power!
On top of that, I lock Phallon!
And then...
Limit Break!
What's this?!
Your rear-guards have been Omega Locked.
This lets me keep your rear-guards
locked for eternity!
Now Sendou can only attack
with his Vanguard!
What the heck is that?!
That's not all.
If five rear-guard units become locked...
...he'll win during his
turn with Ultimate Break.
That's "World End."
"World End"...
What kind of skill is that?
Isn't there some way to stop it?
There's just one...
Making sure he doesn't have five rear-guards.
Aichi...
Take this!
Dauntless Drive Dragon!
All right... now I'll show you a real attack.
Glendios!
When your Vanguard takes damage,
it feeds back to you, too.
That's a real attack.
It's the power I obtained after
the other Takuto and I became one.
I'm going to give you some more.
What the heck is that?!
Even when Sendou's life is
in danger just by fighting...
If he keeps gettin'
hit by attacks like that...
Gancelot, attack!
Perfect guard.
Aichi Sendou...
Your life is in danger just from fighting.
Let's find out how much more
your body can take!
Glendios...
...lock Marron!
Call!
Ruin Magician's skill.
For each rear-guard "Reverse" unit,
I put a card from the
Drop Zone into my hand.
Then... Glendios Limit Break!
Omega Lock.
Call!
Plasmodium's skill!
I turn one damage card up.
And now I can Counterblast yet again.
Attack!
Guard!
Glendios!
Perfect guard!
At any rate, Aichi Sendou...
I didn't know until now.
You're actually quite callous, aren't you?
Guard!
You're trying to take away the
happiness of so many people.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm talking about the Reversed fighters.
By being Reversed, they received
more power than they had ever had.
They became stronger than ever before.
As a fighter, do you think there's
anything more pleasing than that?
If you beat me, their
Reversals will be undone.
For them, that would be
stealing their happiness.
Like that's logical?!
Attack!
It's not just them.
It affects Kourin, too.
What do you mean, it affects Kourin?
Call!
Cold Death Dragon's skill!
Counterblast.
The top card of my opponent's deck...
...is put in play in a locked state!
Even though he only had
four rear-guards out...
Aichi...
Even though Aichi didn't call it,
he was forced to put a locked unit down!
If there aren't five units out,
"World End" can't be achieved...
...but if Omega Lock is
used with a Limit Break...
Sendou has as good as lost.
Even the other Takuto couldn't
overcome "World End."
Limit Break!
You seek to win this fight
and wipe me from existence.
But if I disappear,
Kourin's memory will also be
wiped away without a trace.
Picture it!
How long have you known Kourin now?
A year... No, two?
During that time, you've
made many memories together.
Those memories...
No, those memories of you...
are everything to her.
Indeed, they're her very world.
She even fought you to preserve that world.
I'm going to defeat you here...
...to protect my world!
You're trying to crush
everything she holds dear.
But I... I'm not...
Completely cold-hearted is
what you are, Aichi Sendou.
I'm not...
Omega Lock!
A cold-hearted human should
be punished accordingly.
And that punishment is...
...your own destruction, Aichi Sendou!
Aichi!
Is this the end?
That's right.
And now, your world will end!
This is the true "World End"!
What the...?!
A Link Joker unit?!
Observe! The gate is now fully open!
Your loss will Reverse the entire world.
Unfortunately, you won't be able
to see that wonderful sight.
I...
No... Cardfighters all over the world...
will never give up!
We won't lose heart!
We won't let you have your way!
Next time: World End!
World End
The end of the world... I don't accept it!