Break through all bindings and descend!
My strongest avatar of savage lightning!
Break ride!
Eradicator, Tempest Bolt Dragon!
As long as I have this deck, I ain't alone.
Granny Glasses...
The real Shingo and I
are gonna fight together!
And I'm definitely gonna beat you!
Here I go! Break ride skill!
On top of that, I'm knockin' two of
your units for a loop with this skill!
And then Tempest Bolt Dragon's skill!
This skill gives it +2000 power
for every rear-guard circle
that doesn't have a unit!
There are four empty rear-guard circles.
And not only his own, but his
opponent's circles count, too!
Eradicator, Tempest Bolt
Dragon's power is 29000.
What tremendous power...
I knock out my enemy's units and
power up with their empty spaces!
This is lightning that announces the
arrival of my enemy's destruction!
Voltaic Kaiser Thunderbolt!
To get you back to normal...
So we can fight again,
shoulder to shoulder...
Let this attack bring
you to your senses, Shingo!
Shingo!
You guys help, too!
R-Right!
Smash Through Everything!
It's raining buckets out there.
Yes. It's like the English expression,
"When it rains, it pours."
Shingo!
You jerk! You made me worry about you!
Tears...
Idiot! It's just rain!
Don't talk nonsense! Like I'd
cry over somethin' like this!
Thank you, delinquent wannabe...
I feel like I ought to tell you that.
N-Nothin'!
That's friendship.
Yeah. It's the same all over the world.
That's what I call a global standard!
Good grief.
This is...
What's wrong?
That's right. This is where...
...I followed her that day.
Hey!
Ishida?
Sendou... It seems you don't realize it,
but your heart is locked.
My heart is locked?
The usual hot wind didn't
rise from Blaster Blade.
You're troubled by the
thought of fighting Kai.
Your heart is locked!
Until you unlock it,
victory will not be yours!
Troubled?
Me?
Naoki and Shingo aren't here?
Yeah. I haven't seen them
since they left yesterday.
Where did they go?
I bet those two are trying
to do something on their own.
Don't tell me they went to Takuto's place?!
That, or even closer to home
to beat Reversed fighters.
What's this?
Just a wall.
I think she did this...
It seems you've recalled
what happened, Naoki Ishida.
Nagashiro!
You're the one who Reversed me back then!
I'm also the one who Reversed
Shingo Komoi there.
You jerk!
I'll Reverse you once more.
Shingo Komoi, too.
And then... after that...
President, Vice President...
It'll be your turn!
L-Let's talk about this! We can talk it out!
You ain't gonna be able to
Reverse anyone ever again!
'Cause I'm gonna beat you!
Why do you dislike the idea
of being Reversed so much?
What?!
Link Joker will take away
your pain and sadness.
Huh?! I don't know what
you're goin' on about!
I'm sure you'll understand as soon as
I've Reversed you once more.
I don't wanna understand it!
If you're Reversed, I'll
bring you back to normal!
Fine with me.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Ambush Dragon Eradicator, Linchu!
Maiden of Physalis!
That unit is...
Isn't it from the
Brilliant Strike booster set?
Neo-Nectar... I don't remember
what kind of fight we had,
but I'm takin' you down!
Linchu moves back!
Maiden of Cherry Stone attacks!
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks!
Iris Knight!
Guard!
Maiden of Cherry Bloom!
Cherry Bloom's skill. Superior call.
What the...?!
To be precise, Link Joker is nothingness.
It spreads over everything that exists.
Like this Neo-Nectar, which has
gained the power of Reverse.
Disgusting!
You had the same reaction
when I Reversed you.
S-Shut up! Don't try to be cute!
Ride! Call!
I don't care how far your garden spreads,
my Eradicators are gonna mow it down!
And then, with Linchu's skill,
I retire Corolla Dragon!
He's actually doing well!
Indeed!
Ride! And then I call.
Attack Spark Rain Dragon!
I guard with one unit!
Attack!
Guess I haven't mown enough down yet...
So... break ride!
Eradicator, Tempest Bolt Dragon!
Break ride skill! I retire two units!
This is Voltaic Kaiser Thunderbolt!
Tempest Bolt Dragon attacks!
All right!
No matter how much you struggle,
you won't be able to stop this growth.
Say what?!
Life of darkness released
from the gates of Hell,
grow in abundance until
you cover everything!
Break ride!
Maiden of Venus Trap "Reverse."
Break ride skill. Superior call!
The nothingness likes you.
You understand what nothingness is.
I don't know what you're sayin'!
I know what you used to be like.
What?!
You used to be a loner, right?
Miyaji is full of first-class students.
You weren't able to find anyone then...
Anyone you really wanted to meet.
When a person becomes isolated like that,
their heart embraces nothingness.
Isolation is scary. Everyone thinks so.
But the more you thought about it,
the lonelier you felt.
It quickly spread throughout your heart...
Suffocating, endless darkness...
You who knows what that is
cannot reject Link Joker.
I understand that.
I was the same way myself.
I felt different from everyone around me.
I came to feel that their insignificant
existences were beneath me.
True, I was alone for the longest time...
And yet, I also felt
hopelessly lonely and empty.
Until, one day...
I'm having more trouble than
expected with the Cardfight Club...
Look, dealing with them
is your job, Suwabe!
R-Right!
Yeesh.
And then I gained power.
The power to utilize my isolation
and the emptiness in my heart!
Limit Break!
Okay, here I come! Attack!
Guard!
Attack!
Guard! And intercept!
He held out...
But Ishida is almost...
Isolation has approached again, hasn't it?
Accept it, Naoki Ishida!
And be Reversed!
Dang it! Somebody...
And then Link Joker, which
returns everything to nothingness,
will make your pain
and sadness go away.
Ishida...
Juvenile delinquent wannabe!
You can't let yourself get caught up in that!
Hurry up and get out of there!
Th-There's no way he can hear you...
Ishida, you're not alone now!
Everyone in the Cardfight Club is with you!
You've got Sendou! Misaki! And me!
So... So...
Thanks... Granny Glasses...
I see. This is your image.
Your image almost swallowed me up there.
You...!
You're right. I used to be alone.
But...
...I ain't alone now!
All of the rear-guards...
Not just his opponent's,
but his own, too...
But with that, Tempest Bolt
Dragon's skill can be used!
Call! And skill activated!
You keep goin' on about bein' alone,
but in the first place, us Cardfighters
are alone when we fight.
We fight all on our own.
But in the middle of fightin',
I think the feelin's between the
two opponents are communicated.
I mean, if it ain't a fight
like that, where's the fun?
It's big talk, I know, but
that's what somebody told me.
A fellow member of the Cardfight Club.
Ishida...
So fighters like us...
Me and you, we ain't alone!
Guard!
Not to mention, there ain't no
need to fall prey to nothingness!
Juvenile delinquent wannabe, you did it!
Ishida, here!
Nagashiro!
This is...
Those two did all this?!
Aichi!
You did it!
Yeah.
More importantly, I hope she's okay...
Thank goodness! You're up.
What was I...?
You need to rest.
I know! Let's fight next time!
You're not alone anymore.
That's right. But right now,
you need to rest up.
Will Nagashiro really be okay?
Yeah. She was possessed by something.
But that wonderful fight...
And Ishida's passionate feelings...
I believe they had the power to banish it!
President...
It's like I've always said:
Vanguard is great!
Certainly! This truly
is the global standard!
It looks like they've changed a bit, too.
Ishida!
Naoki! Shingo!
Sendou...
Hey. We did it...
What the...?
Naoki?
He was up all night.
Right after that, he had this big
cleanup at school. So it's no wonder.
Why didn't he say anything?
That was the juvenile... I mean, Ishida's...
way of being considerate.
He said he didn't want Sendou to worry.
While I was in doubt, Naoki and Shingo...
I've decided.
I'm through hesitating.
I'm going to Takuto's place.
Aichi...
I won't tolerate whatever
made the world like this.
Even if Kamui, Takuto...
...and Kai are the enemies.
I'll fight them!
Wake up, Ishida!
Let me sleep a little more.
Are you talking in your sleep?!
Are you sure? Sendou is about to go!
What?! What are you sayin', Shingo?
If you space out, I'm gonna leave you here!
What's that?!
Naoki... Shingo...
Next time: Aichi and Kamui!
Aichi and Kamui
Kamui, I'm your opponent for this fight.
In fact, it has to be me!
Wait for me. I promise I'll
bring you back to normal!