Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
Starting today, we're an official club!
The Vanguard club I've always dreamed of!
My high school life is smooth
sailing! Spring in full bloom!
You're seein' the world through rose-colored
glasses! Although I feel the same way...
No, no! Someone with a twisted personality
like you can't say stuff like that, Ishida.
Have you ever heard the expression
"Inscrutable are the ways of heaven"?
Don't make like I'm an idiot! It means you
never know what life's gonna throw at you, right?
For you Ishida, it'd be more appropriate to say,
"Lights are usually followed by shadows."
What's that?! What are
you tryin' to say, jerk?!
Huh? I'm here last...
Didn't you hear me?
Um... well, shall we begin club activities?
Yes!
I'm totally ready!
I'm thoroughly prepared!
Um, actually...
Before you play cards, there's
something I'd like to do...
What is it?
The Student Council told me to have you
decide your club's captain and vice-captain.
So let's talk about that today.
Who should be the captain and
vice-captain of the Cardfight Club?
Captain...
Vice-captain...
I see... I guess it is necessary, huh?
What the hey? Aren't we gonna fight?
Well, there need to be two people
present at Student Council meetings,
and there are a lot of other things that needs to be done by two people ...
This club only has five
members at the moment,
so voting for two of you wouldn't
be too complicated, I think...
Um, okay... Sendou...
Yes?
You formed this club, so why
don't you become the captain?
M-Me, be captain?!
But, see, I've never been a captain before...
And I don't have any experience as a class
representative or as a leader in anything either...
So I can't do it!
What are you talking about, Sendou?
That's right! You're the one who led Q4.
But...
Quit going on and on and just do it!
Exactly. Do it!
Um...
A-All right. I'll be the captain.
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Who's the Vice-Captain?!
So about the vice-captain...
Does anyone want to do it?
Yes! I want to do it!
Um, Shingo Komoi...
If I become the vice-captain,
I'll get started right away
on making the Cardfight Club
Miyaji Academy's shining star.
First, I'll build up the
number of club members,
with this month's target being one hundred!
Then I'll establish Cardfight Clubs in the
middle school and elementary divisions,
to raise Miyaji's future fighters.
Further, we will spread beyond Miyaji
into community-based club activities,
accepting locals into our club, and
eventually people from all over the country!
Ultimately, the Miyaji Academy Cardfight
Club will have links worldwide,
and make every effort
to bring about world peace!
That's all!
I-Is anyone else interested?
I got no interest in bein'
vice-captain or whatever...
Why not let the person
who wants to do it do it?
Agreed.
Yes!
I don't know... Why don't we
all sleep on it overnight?
We'll decide tomorrow.
Whatever...
Guess it can't be helped...
Guess not.
Magatsu Storm attacks!
I guard with these two!
Can you successfully guard
with 18000 against 20000?
Shoot! All this hassle
about the vice-captain...
He should've just decided on you!
Tell me about it!
Do you know how long I've dreamed
of being in a Vanguard club?
No one wants to improve
this club more than me,
and if it's left to me,
everything will go well!
So I'm going to announce
my candidacy tomorrow, too!
Y-Yeah. Good luck.
Miyaji Academy, High School Division
Sorry, Misaki!
I was on duty and it looked like
I was almost finished with work,
but then more and more came up...
Good job.
Didn't you have your club today?
All we did was talk about deciding
on the captain and vice-captain.
Huh... Maybe you're the captain, Misaki?
Yeah, right! Aichi's the captain.
Oh, yeah. He is the one
that formed the club, huh?
Then you're the vice-captain, right?
Why?
You're an upperclassman, so you don't want
a first-year student running the show.
Oh, I don't care...
Well, you should! Besides, the captain
and vice-captain are both leaders,
so you'd share a special feeling, you know?
With those two in charge,
even if you shared your opinion, they'd
treat you like you were a pain in the neck!
Scary!
So to keep that from happening, too, get it?!
You worry too much...
Oh, Akari, welcome!
Hello! You're carrying
around big old boxes again.
Are you okay?
I can handle this much, but
I appreciate your concern.
I think you're overdoing it,
especially for somebody your age...
not young
pops
old man
geezer
What did you just say?!
old man
your age
Manager!
How have you been?
Cute!
That tickles!
What's with him?
You got me.
I wonder what's wrong with Shin...
Misaki, think about what I said before.
Yeah, yeah...
What's wrong?
I've counted twenty sighs
coming from you today.
You haven't changed out of your uniform
and you've been on the same page
of that magazine forever...
Did something happen at school?
Just at the club...
That makes twenty-one.
So what happened at your club?
Our faculty advisor said we're
going to decide on the vice-captain,
so tonight, he wants us to think over
whether we want to do it or not.
Aichi's been chosen as the captain...
...but to be honest, I have no idea
what a vice-captain even does...
Then why don't you give it a try?
You've never done it before, so of course
you don't know what it entails.
That's why you should give it a shot.
Besides, it would let you spend more
time with Aichi, and that'd be fun!
That last part was uncalled-for!
I'm going to bed.
Alright!
Mornin'!
Morning, Naoki!
Yeah, mornin'! Let's make
it another great day!
If you try, you can make it happen.
If you don't try, nothin' happens, am I right?
Uh... Yeah...
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
Well, everyone, did you give it some thought?
So who would like to be the vice-captain?
Wonderful!
Everyone... Thank you!
Unfortunately, not everyone can do it...
What should we do here?
Um...
Is there someone you would
especially like to do it with?
Oh, no... I can't decide something like that!
Let me see then...
I've got it! Look over here!
At a time like this, ain't
that the reason we got these?
A fight! The four of us!
Whoever wins...
...becomes the vice-captain.
I see! So you play Vanguard
at a time like this!
I guess...
Tokura
Kourin
Ishida
Komoi
First Match
Second Match
Okay, the first match.
Misaki versus Shingo, please.
I'm going to play seriously!
Naturally.
All right... Begin!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Turn end.
I still have only 4 damage...
If I protect myself the next turn...
Draw.
Sorry, but if you think you can protect
yourself, you're sorely mistaken.
I ride Eternal Goddess, Iwanagahime!
Th-That card...
Call.
Iwanagahime's Limit Break!
I'm retiring your front row rear-guards!
Saffron attacks with a boost from Cumin!
Tatsutahime boosts Iwanagahime!
I-I lost...
Alright! Time to fight, Kourin!
And I'm definitely gonna win!
The challenged is going
to beat the challenger!
Okay, please go ahead with the second match.
How disappointing...
Stand up, Vanguard!
I go first. Draw!
Vice-captain... It's my dream post...
If I became vice-captain, I'd beat that
violent, rude noob Ishida so badly,
he wouldn't be able to get back on his feet!
I'm not sure if that's
the vice-captain's job...
Prizmy attacks!
Spark Rain Dragon attacks!
Tracie attacks!
Vowing Sword Dragon!
Ashley attacks!
It's impressive how fired
up both of them are.
She is strong... but today, I'll
show her what my will power can do!
I stand and draw!
From here on out, it's my break time!
Watch this! My invincible...
surefire... miraculous...
Gauntlet Buster Dragon and Vowing Sword Dragon...
Break Ride!
I retire Tracie!
Call!
I'm gonna retire another of your cards!
Now Gauntlet Buster has 27000
power and three criticals!
I'm gonna drive you into
a corner all at once!
Vowing Sword attacks!
I guard with Polli!
Gauntlet Buster attacks with
a boost from Red River!
I'll take it!
Now I'll finish you off!
Vowing Sword Dragon's final attack!
Guard!
Wha...?!
And intercept!
Everything's going according
to plan... so far...
Shoot! You totally blocked it!
I sensed your enthusiasm plenty.
But don't think you're the
only one who can break ride.
I break ride with Leading
Jewel Knight, Salome!
Salome's skill activates!
Another Salome unit, superior call!
And then I call Shellie!
Wha...?!
When there are four or more
Jewel Knight rear-guard units,
Salome gets +2000 power
and an extra critical!
That's 22000 power...
And three criticals!
This is the real final attack!
Salome attacks with a boost from Shellie!
Shoot! I don't have enough!
I lost!
Kourin, Naoki, nice fight.
Tokura
Kourin
Ishida
Komoi
Now we just have the deciding match, right?
Right!
That's incredible spirit!
We lost the mental battle.
Don't you think so, Ishida?
Pathetic...
Ishida?
Pathetic... Pathetic!
What's that? I can't hear you.
Pathetic!
Sendou! Ishida's acting weird!
Naoki! Are you okay?!
Do you feel sick or something?
Ishida! Get a hold of yourself!
Pathetic!
Ishida...
I'm just pathetic...
Even though I finally found somethin'
to be passionate about...
...I'm just... just pathetic!
Aichi...
When we were talkin' about
the vice-captain yesterday,
I thought it sounded like a real pain.
I joined this club to get passionate about
something and here I'm thinkin' it's a pain...
But after I thought about it last night, I
realized I really did wanna be vice-captain...
I realized I wanna do somethin'
for the sake of this club!
And yet, I lost! That's doubly pathetic!
I mean, I know actin' like
this is pathetic, too...
I know I lost, so I gotta
give up on the idea...
Besides, just like me, it didn't look
like Kourin or Boss Lady had any interest
in bein' vice-captain either,
but today, they volunteered.
No matter what anyone says, this
club is full of people with passion!
My bad for interferin' with your fight!
Go ahead and decide who's
vice-captain with your match!
Um...
I just felt obliged to do it
after Takuto egged me on...
I just raised my hand because
of what Akari said...
Um... This fight...
I agree with your idea.
We're on the same wavelength.
That's right.
Um... Why don't you be the vice-captain?
I'm saying we're leaving it to you!
But... I lost...
Listen. You have pure, passionate
feelings. And that's great.
Boss Lady...
W-What is this development?
Even though the club would be
much better off if I did it...
What's that, Shingo?
You don't have any complaints, do you?
W-What the heck? It looks
like you're motivated...
It's okay with me if you
become vice-captain, Ishida.
Really?! You don't mind if I...
I don't mind! I'm fine with it!
But in return, do a good job!
If you do anything weird, I'll
file a censure vote right away!
I think this was resolved very nicely.
Right! It'll be good
working with you, Naoki.
Together, let's put this club on its feet!
Yeah! I'll do my best!
Right!
Look at that. That bright red setting
sun is the same as our hot blood!
Well, the setting sun is red.
Or rather, because of the
wavelength of the light,
the sun just looks red from
all this distance away.
W-What are you doing? You run off
when someone's talking to you?
You're so rude, Ishida! Listen to me, Ishida!
Naoki! Shingo!
Wait up, Ishida!
I-I can't stop!
Hey!
Listen, from today, I'm vice-captain
and you're just a basic member!
You volunteered just so that you
could bully me around, didn't you?!
I should never have agreed to let you do it!
Let go! Let go of me!
You told me to let go!
There's no need for old gags like that!
But back to what I was saying!
You became vice-captain just because
you want to lord it over us?!
Ha! You're the only one I'm gonna lord it over.
Aichi's the captain, see?
Why, you...! Even though you're a noob,
you were thinking the same thing I was?!
What was that?! What'd you just say?
Sendou, please drive this jerk like
a horse! Run him into the ground!
What the heck do you think you're doin'?!
You started it!
Yeesh... Men...
They're children...
But...
I feel like I lost in more ways than one...
I, Naoki Ishida, vice-captain of the
Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club,
will fight for the development of the club
and for fun, passionate Vanguard fights!
I-I'm not gonna lose to you!
Naoki... Shingo...
That was a yell?
That was the wailing of my soul.
What the heck is that?
Let's make this a good club.
Yes.
Come on, Aichi, you yell, too!
For some reason, yelling
makes you feel refreshed.
All right...
1... 2...
Cardfight Circle
Ishida, a total noob, is the vice-captain?!
Since I became vice-captain, I'm
gonna go like gangbusters!
You better follow me, too!
Acting all high and mighty!
Back in the day, you used to always
be behind me, going, "Shingo! Shingo!"
You followed me around like a little puppy!
Naoki, Shingo, that's the
middle school division.
You're making a raid?!
I don't think we can get away with that...
Next time: Miyaji Academy,
Middle School Division!
Miyaji Academy, Middle School Division!
Standing by to form the Komui army!
Forget it, that army's lame! I'm goin' in.