The American Football Club
challenged the Cardfight Club?!
I won the fight with them, so
all's well that ends well...
...but it means the Student Council
doesn't think much of the Cardfight Club.
Have they accepted you
guys as an official club?
Not yet. We need at least five people,
and right now, we only have four...
So you're one person short...
But if you don't hurry up
and get another person,
won't the Student Council challenge
you again or plot against you?!
Yeah. Except the condition for joining
the club is beating one of the members...
Kourin is so strong that even the ones who
are her fans keep giving up, one after another.
And even if that can't be helped,
recently, students aren't
taking our invitation flyers.
It seems word of the Student Council's
disapproval has spread to the student body.
They're probably worried about
getting a black mark on their record,
or are keeping their distance because
they wanna have a decent school life.
There's only one thing to do!
Katsumi Morikawa, a man's man,
will transfer to your school
and join the Vanguard Club!
I told you before that your test scores
make getting into that school impossible!
It's possible, as long as
I have love for Kourin!
If only I went to the same school...
You're still in middle school...
Are you gonna give up?
No. I'm definitely going
to make the club official!
Welcome back, Misaki.
I'm back.
Misaki!
Aichi...
Let me ask you once more.
Won't you join the Cardfight Club?
I want you in the club, Misaki.
If it's the shop you're worried
about, there's no need.
The sub-manager and I have
things well in hand here.
I mean "manager"!
Please, Misaki. Let's fight again together.
Well, I guess...
Huh?
Kourin!
Cut it out!
Blocked!
BL-yo!
Dang it! Let go of me!
If you'd gone ahead and
grabbed her, it'd be a crime!
That's right!
Aichi, you came here to
invite her, didn't you?
Yes.
A club isn't something
you're persuaded to join.
We don't need anybody who's
not serious about it.
You're saying I'm not serious?!
Are you saying you seriously want to join?
I never said I wanted to join...
Misaki...
Oh, boy...
I can't think of anybody
else but you, Misaki!
Please join the Cardfight Club!
Sorry...
Poor guy. You rejected him again, Misaki?
Don't put it like that.
I just refused to join the club.
He's cute, coming here every day to beg you.
Akari...
You hate Vanguard that much?
That's not what it is...
I figured.
If you weren't interested in this stuff,
you wouldn't bring it to class, right?
Misaki, you aren't straightforward
with your feelings.
"Why did you invite that
idol to join before me?!"
"Even though you've known
me much longer than her!"
That's not what I'm thinking!
We don't need anybody who's
not serious about it.
Why does what she said bother me so much?
The Birth of the Cardfight Club?!
Physics Prep Room
Cardfight Club (tentative)
Boss Lady already has her hands full.
Anyway, it's her destiny
to stand alone at the top.
According to my investigation,
Misaki works at the shop, and that's it.
I don't believe she's busy
shaking students down for money.
You have no clue how a
big shot thinks, shorty!
"Shorty" is not my name.
It's Komoi!
I wonder why Misaki won't join...
If she really wanted to,
I'm sure she'd come to us.
Kourin...
Miyaji Academy High School
Division Student Council Office
So the Cardfight Club hasn't given
up on getting more members, eh?
Correct.
Thanks to the rumors we spread about
the Student Council watching the club,
I believe there are no
hopeful applicants left,
but there is still a remote chance.
If we're going to cut off
the head of the snake,
now would be the time, before
they get five members.
Do you have an idea?
I do.
This is a message from the Student Council.
Clubs that wish to be granted official
status must have at least five members,
and the Student Council must be
notified of this, by 6 p.m. today.
If there is no notification, the club will
not be granted official status this year.
I repeat...
Clubs that wish to be granted official
status must have at least five members,
How 'bout I just grab a random person from
over there and force 'em to sign up?!
and the Student Council must be
notified of this, by 6 p.m. today.
You do that, and you're out of the club.
I-I was only kiddin', of course!
I'll ask Misaki one more time...
Misaki...
Boss Lady...
Why did you invite me?
Um...
Because I wanted to play
Vanguard together with you, Misaki.
When I thought about who
I wanted to do it with,
you're the person
who came to mind, Misaki!
Please!
We're beggin' you, Boss Lady!
Does it make you feel good,
having people bow to you?
Hey, you don't have to talk like that!
I don't accept her.
Her joining out of sympathy
only puts me in a bad mood.
The purpose of the Cardfight Club
is to fight seriously.
We don't need anyone who isn't serious.
I am serious!
Your "serious" and Aichi's "serious" are
different. Different from ours, too!
Kourin...
Misaki...
Wait!
Misaki!
You don't need to chase after
her. She's the problem.
But...
If you still go after her, then I'll quit.
You would...?
Misaki...
The Cardfight Club is
looking for new members!
Please join the Cardfight Club!
Cardfight Club
We don't need anyone who isn't serious.
Your "serious" and Aichi's "serious" are
different. Different from ours, too!
I seriously wanted to help
Aichi out of a jam...
Help...? For Aichi's sake?
No!
Drat! Almost all the students've
gone home already!
So you were still trying to get new members?
Hey, would you give us
just a little more time?
The Student Council's decisions are absolute.
If somebody hadn't said all that to Misaki...
Did you say something?
N-No, nothing!
Looks like it's all over.
The Cardfight Club's fifth member is me.
Misaki!
B-But...
I thought everybody went home...
That makes five people!
You got no gripes, do ya?!
Let's go!
Y-Yes, sir!
Come back the day before yesterday!
They can't come back the
day before yesterday.
Shut up, you!
Misaki, I knew you'd come!
You're a busy girl, with all
your comings and goings.
Your reason?
If I don't like it, I won't approve you.
I'm not doing it for somebody else's sake,
or to help the club become official...
I'm joining because I seriously
want to play Vanguard.
For now, you pass.
Yes!
As a fan, I'm thrilled to be
in the same club as Misaki,
a member of Q4, the world's
best Vanguard team!
And now we can keep on playin' Vanguard!
First, you need to take the club exam.
If you don't beat a member of the club,
you can't become a member yourself.
What?!
Oh, come on...
You're fighting...
...Aichi!
If you beat Aichi, I'll
accept you as a member.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Wingal Liberator!
Aiming for the Stars, Artemis!
That's not Oracle Think Tank, is it?
I felt like trying out various things.
Genesis... I've got a good
feeling about this clan.
Misaki has kept up her studies
in order to get stronger...
I really do want to be
in the same club as her.
But if I...
If you hold back...
...I'll never forgive you.
If you go easy on her, I'll quit.
This is what they call being caught between
the tiger and the wolf, huh?
That's exactly what they look like!
Of course, I'm going to give it all I've got.
I want to participate in this club seriously!
Here I go. I ride Little Liberator, Marron!
Wingal moves.
I ride Bowstring of Heaven
and Earth, Artemis!
I look at the top seven cards of my deck,
and if Twilight Hunter, Artemis
is there, I put her in my hand.
Call! And then I attack!
Bowstring of Heaven and
Earth, Artemis attacks!
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
Call!
Gallatin!
Damage check.
Blaster Blade!
Check.
Phallon!
This isn't just a fight
between me and Aichi...
It's also a fight against you,
with my "seriousness" at stake.
I think you already know
this, but Aichi isn't so easy
that you'll be able to beat
him with lukewarm feelings...
I ride Twilight Hunter, Artemis!
Broom Witch, Callaway and Bowstring
of Heaven and Earth, Artemis!
Callaway attacks!
I guard with Escrad!
Twilight Hunter attacks!
Trigger check. Critical trigger!
I give all the effects to Twilight Hunter!
I Soulcharge with Twilight Hunter's skill.
Then, since I've got a Bowstring of
Heaven and Earth in the Soul, I do it again.
Man! Four cards into the Soul all at once?!
The Soul is the key to
Misaki's clan, Genesis.
After this, I'm sure there'll be
some big effect that uses the Soul.
Misaki, you put together a deck like this...
When it comes to fighting Aichi, I really
have to throw everything I've got at him...
Enter the fray, King of all Knights!
I ride...
Liberator of the Round Table, Alfred!
Gallatin attacks!
I guard with Witch of Owls, Paprika!
Here I go.
I'm looking forward to it.
Break through the limit! Alfred!
Limit Break!
There are four rear-guard units,
so that's +8000 power!
Alfred attacks with a boost from Flare Mane!
Flare Mane's Soulblast!
When it boosts Alfred, he gets +5000 power!
Twin drive check. No trigger.
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Phallon
and heal 1 damage point.
Phallon attacks!
3 to 5... What's going to happen next?
Now I'll show them how serious I am...
I'll show them the true power of Genesis!
The heat of silent souls like stars...
...and deep, intense emotions like the sea...
...are for eternity!
I ride Eternal Goddess, Iwanagahime!
Surpass the limits and open up a new world!
Limit Break!
Soulblast!
Take the tune of unchanging life,
and vanish beyond a time
that's longer than infinity!
Everlasting Vanish!
I retire all of my opponent's front
row rear-guards from the field!
Gallatin!
Phallon!
Now you can't intercept!
Whoa...
I call Witch of Wolves, Saffron
and Battle Maiden, Kukurihime!
Saffron attacks!
I guard with Gwydion!
Iwanagahime attacks with a boost
from Bowstring of Heaven and Earth!
Twin drive!
I got a critical trigger!
I give the power to Callaway and
the extra critical to Iwanagahime.
Damage check.
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Alfred!
I attack with the boosted Callaway!
I guard with Elixir Liberator!
Turn end.
Those two look like they're
having a good time.
It's like they don't even care
whether they win or lose.
Seriousness brings out the
opponent's seriousness.
They heighten each other.
It's a passionate fight between the two of
them that no one can get in the middle of!
Alfred's Especial Counterblast!
I turn over two Liberators in the Damage
Zone, look at the top card of my deck,
and superior call Escrad!
One more Especial Counterblast!
Superior call, Gancelot!
He brought back the front line that Misaki
retired without even using his hand!
Incredible...
1 more damage...
Show me how serious you can get.
Gancelot attacks Callaway!
In order to ensure his win, he started
by retiring a unit that can intercept!
Alfred attacks with a boost from Flare Mane!
Flare Mane's Soulblast! +5000 power!
Also, because of the Limit Break's effect,
Alfred gets +8000 power this turn, too!
This is the power of Alfred's bond!
I guard with Goddess of
Self-sacrifice, Kushinada!
Perfect guard?!
I've got more!
Escrad attacks with a boost from Wingal!
I guard with Kukurihime!
Turn end...
She made it through with no damage...
If Misaki could protect
herself... then so can I!
Not while I'm around!
Pure battle maiden, cut through the
darkness with your moonlit bow.
I ride Battle Deity of the Night, Artemis!
Battle Deity of the Night!
A grade 3 on top of a grade 3!
I call Paprika.
Kukurihime's skill.
I put her in the Soul and
give +3000 power to Saffron.
Now there are three units in the Soul.
Paprika attacks!
When she attacks, if there's a Genesis unit
on the field that has a Limit Break ability,
she gets +3000 power!
Guard!
I attack with the boosted
Battle Deity of the Night!
Limit Break!
Soulblast!
Battle Deity of the Night's Limit Break
increases units in the hand while attacking!
That ain't all!
Your blue rays control the tide
and shine a light on life...
Blue Moon Rising!
Battle Deity of the Night
receives +5000 power!
Guard!
Drive trigger check...
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Battle Deity of
the Night, and heal 1 damage point!
Damage trigger check!
Critical trigger...
I lose.
This is me being serious.
Jeez, she's strong... She beat Aichi!
That's the Misaki I know!
Misaki, welcome to the Cardfight Club.
I'm looking forward to it.
You look happier than when I joined the club.
Come on, let's go to the
Student Council office.
To get their approval to
make this club official!
Yeah!
I can't believe they have five members.
President...
What is it?
I have a good plan.
Cardfight Club application
for authorization...
Yes.
Permission denied.
I can't give your Cardfight Club
the official seal of approval.
What are you talkin' about?!
We got five people!
It's because you don't
have a faculty advisor.
Faculty advisor?
There's a rule that states that
official status can only be granted
if there's a faculty advisor.
Oh, no... Isn't there
anything that can be done?!
It is possible.
How?!
Create a track record.
If you accomplish outstanding results,
you'll be treated as a special
case and recognized as a club.
What should we do?
Fight against a powerful high school
team of my choice and achieve victory.
We'll do it. Please let us do it!
Our Vanguard Club has a new challenger.
You really are a great fighter, Misaki!
No, I owe it to your seriousness, Aichi.
Again, let's both give a
boost to the Cardfight Club.
I'm game.
I-I'm looking forward to it... Boss Lady.
All right! Now our club can be made official!
Next time: First Match! Miyaji
Academy vs. Hitsue High School!
Faculty advisor, matches outside of school...
We're off to a rocky
start, but we won't lose!
You're getting a fighter's face, Aichi.
I'm fired up!