The way I can express my
gratitude is by winning here.
I started the Cardfight Club, and now
I have to take responsibility and win!
Stand up, my...
no, our avatar!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
Blaster Blade Liberator...
That's your avatar, the one that
was captured by Void, isn't it?
Yes.
So you got your avatar back and plan on
challenging me with all of your power?
Exactly.
Because I can't afford to lose this fight.
Good to hear.
But you're not the only one who
got his avatar back, Aichi.
Envelop everything in darkness, my avatar!
I ride...
Blaster Dark Revenger!
The fight between them
is showing me this image?
All right, it's the final round of the VF
High School Championship, Kanto Block 3!
The third match is heating up, too!
It's picking up steam!
And small wonder! The combatants are
Aichi Sendou and Ren Suzugamori!
Both of them had great success at the Asia
Circuit and are among Japan's best fighters!
A match-up between these two
wouldn't be out of place
during the final round of the VF
High School Championship proper!
When all is said and done...
which one of them will win this fight
and go on to the VF High
School Championship?!
Showdown at the Summit
Blaster Dark attacks Blaster Blade!
The attack succeeded!
That makes 3 damage for Sendou!
Turn end.
He's strong...
Now that Ren has Blaster
Dark back, this is his...
This is Shadow Paladin's true power!
Ren is even more powerful than before...
He's improved so much, I can't even
compare it to the way he was back then.
It's like he's a different person...
Or, no...
He hasn't changed...
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
Yes. The last time we fought
each other was in Seoul.
A lot has happened between us, hasn't it?
Well, some of it has been a hassle,
but overall, it's been fun.
To be honest, it was kind of hard on me.
But you've become stronger, right?
And so have you, Ren.
I like this.
I knew that putting our fight off 'til
we got here was the right thing to do.
Yes. And it's a fight that
I absolutely have to win.
For the sake of the Cardfight Club
that we all built together...
And more than anything, for their
sake, since they helped me!
So you're doing your best for your friends?
That's very you.
But...
...if we're talking friends,
I've got them, too.
So I have no intention of losing, either.
Now, it's your turn.
Show me how you and your army
of knights have developed.
Although whatever you do
won't work on me, of course.
We'll see whether it works on you or not.
I ride Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Escrad! Phallon!
Escrad attacks!
Guard!
What fierce spirit!
And yet, they're still...
Looks like they're having fun, huh?
I'm talking about those two.
Yeah.
This is the hottest match at the
VF High School Championship.
That's probably why it's such a
passionate, not to mention fun, fight.
Why...?
Why was I transported over there...?
Gancelot moves out!
No guard.
Twin drive, check!
Yeah!
Critical trigger!
Heal trigger.
I heal 1 damage point and give
the power to Blaster Dark.
He pulled a heal trigger
at just the right time.
That's my Ren!
Phallon! Attack Rugos!
Turn... end...
Stand and draw.
Despair!
Then fall to your knees and sip bitter water!
I ride...
Illusionary Revenger, Mordred Phantom!
Call!
Here I go. Venomous Breath attacks!
Guard!
Mordred!
No guard!
Twin drive.
Grim Revenger. Critical trigger.
I give the power to Rugos
and the critical to Mordred.
Suddenly, he's up to 5 damage!
Charon boosts. Rugos...
...attacks Phallon.
Turn end.
5 damage...
Ren only has 3 damage...
The fight will be decided... this turn!
Stand and draw.
From your solitary summit,
where you see everything,
set free those who have
been captured by evil!
I break ride Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Gancelot on top of Gancelot...
Huh...
With the break ride,
Gancelot gets +10000 power!
Escrad and Wingal also receive +5000 power!
I call Marron!
Gancelot attacks with a boost from Wingal!
No guard.
Twin drive!
I give the power to Escrad...
...and the critical to Gancelot!
Love
Kourin Love
Yes! Ren has 5 damage!
Aichi! Let's go to the
High School Championship!
Go, Brother!
With that attack, a boost
from Wingal means...
Yeah...
Skill activated!
Wingal moves to the Soul.
Stand up again, my avatar.
Superior call! Blaster Blade Liberator!
Blaster Blade keeps on standing...
That Aichi...
That Blaster Blade...
I can't believe how far away they are...
Counterblast!
I retire your Darkness Revenger, Rugos!
Escrad!
Guard!
Just 1 more damage...
With 1 damage, I can go with everyone...
...to the VF High School Championship.
That's why...
I'm putting it all in your hands...
...Blaster Blade!
Go, my avatar! Attack Mordred!
Guard.
I have a shield of 21000.
Blaster Blade's power is 16000.
Your attack fails, huh?
Wow! He withstood that attack?
That's Ren Suzugamori, all right.
He's so strong, you can't help but hate him.
He even blocked Blaster Blade's attack?!
Just a little more...
I was only one step away...
That was close.
But that's Aichi for you...
Still, that too is over.
I'm going to crush you with all of my might.
Using the true power of Shadow Paladin...
You're the only one who
can take all of my power.
It seems the fight is decided, Leon.
So Fukuhara High School will be going
to the High School Championship...
Not so fast.
The fight isn't over yet.
Make the wind rise up, Aichi Sendou.
That's right! I'm not going to lose...
I'm going to the VF High School
Championship with everyone!
And to do that, I have to win!
At last, the fight is in the home stretch!
Both of them have 5 damage.
Will Suzugamori win it this turn?
Or will Sendou hold out and
find his way to victory?!
It's s-o exciting!
You are s-o right!
Break ride!
Mordred Phantom!
Mordred gets +10000 power!
And then, from my deck...
Enshroud everything in darkness...
The eternal darkness that even
the light of hope cannot reach!
My avatar!
Blaster Dark Revenger!
Blaster Dark!
Counterblast!
The emissary of terror...
...appears from out of pitch
darkness and takes his victim
to the realm of the dead
without making a sound.
Go to Hades, Blaster Blade!
Now Sendou can't use any intercepts...
So the wind won't blow?
Destroy him, my avatar.
Attack Gancelot!
I lost...
This fierce fight is over at last!
The winner is Ren Suzugamori!
Fukuhara High School has
conquered Kanto Block 3,
and will go on to the VF
High School Championship!
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Ren!
Aichi! You did great, too!
It was so close!
HL, yo!
He lost...
Still, Brother was really cool out there...
It was a duel between
Blasters there at the end...
What an incredible fight.
It's too bad that Aichi lost, but
man, that was exciting, right, Kai?
Kai?
I knew you would win, Ren!
You were really cool.
Aw, shucks...
And now we can participate in
the VF High School Tournament.
I guess I'll say you did well.
Eh...? I think you could dish out a little
more praise than that without tempting fate...
I'll save the real praise for when
we win the High School Championship.
You're stingy, Tetsu...
Still, are there fighters at the
High School Championship proper
who are at the same level as Aichi?
Good question. I suppose
one possibility might be...
Even with Sendou's wind,
it didn't reach far enough.
Ren Suzugamori is to be feared...
But perhaps because of that,
there is a reason to fight him.
He lost, but Aichi Sendou... no, all of
Miyaji Academy... was pretty impressive!
Like they say, after a storm
comes... whatever it is.
"Fair weather."
I'm sorry, everyone...
We can't go to the VF High
School Championship together...
Is it necessary to apologize?
Sendou, you gave it your all.
Am I wrong?
No, of course not!
In that case...
...we have no complaints.
What she said.
Everyone...
In the first place, if you hadn't formed the
Cardfight Club, we never would've been here.
Same goes for this passionate feelin'...
You're the same way, right?
While you were fightin' that guy,
you got all fired up, didn't ya?
Yeah. I was incredibly fired up.
As if all the blood in my body was boiling...
Then that's good enough, ain't it?
Right?!
Yeah. You're right. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Naoki.
Looks like the awards
ceremony is gonna start.
Let's go, guys.
If it had been me standing there...
what would've happened?
Facing Ren after he regained
Shadow Paladin, would I...?
There you are. What's up
with you all of a sudden?
Miwa... I...
Right now, they're too far away from me.
Ren and Aichi both.
Kai...
It really is over, huh?
Our challenge against the VF
High School Championship...
Quit your whimperin'!
There's always next year!
I know that, but...
Besides, it's not like the
VF High School Championship
is the be-all-end-all for Vanguard.
That's right. We can always
fight at the club,
and have intramural matches
with other schools.
Plus there are other tournaments.
If you want to fight, there
are plenty of opportunities.
And drop by the shop once in a while.
You'd make Shin really happy.
I see... You're right!
All right! Then let's get
back to the club and fight!
Good idea! I'll train you hard!
So don't you drag us down again
next year, Porcupine Head!
What's that, Granny Glasses?!
Excuse me?! You got a problem?!
Y-You two...
Leave them be.
Yeah.
So, what?! I'll appreciate
your help from now on!
I know you will! And I'm gonna
crack the whip on you!
I can take whatever you dish out!
You better steel yourself!
That's enough, you two!
So they're starting again, with
their sights set on next year?
That's if they still have
a club by next year...
Miyaji Academy Cardfight Club,
defeated in the finals of the VF High
School Championship preliminaries!
It's too bad, but I think I did a good job!
It is a little frustrating,
but I'm really happy that I got to
fight alongside such good friends.
Huh? Have lunch together?
Next time: A Windy Day!
Kourin, Misaki, those lunches are amazing!
Homemade idol cooking!
Awesome! Is that your
homemade cooking, Boss Lady?