And now, roulette! Our
second match is between...
Miyaji Academy
Kourin Tatsunagi
Miyaji Academy's Kourin Tatsunagi!
Hitsue High School
Yuuta Izaki
And... Hitsue High School's Yuuta Izaki!
Yuuta Izaki is on the way!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Leading Jewel Knight, Salome!
Brandish your bold, brave sword!
Attack Deathrex!
The winner of the second match, Kourin
Tatsunagi from Miyaji Academy!
I knew you'd win, Kourin!
That makes one win and one loss!
You're the one who lost, Ishida.
Shut up!
Sorry, guys.
Don't worry about it.
We've got another chance.
Izaki!
Thank you for losing!
I commend you for not being disrespectful
and beating Kourin, but...
Why...?!
...you went over my head and fought her!
You deserve to die 10,000 times for that sin!
This is what you get!
Mr. Mark, what's the next pairing?
O-Okay, everybody!
Hitsue High School        Miyaji Academy
The pairing for the third match...
...from Miyaji Academy...
Stop!
Miyaji Academy
Misaki Tokura
...Misaki Tokura!
And from Hitsue High School...
Hitsue High School
Ringer
What the heck is that?
"Ringer"?
The long-awaited appearance
of the mysterious ringer!
Help-man, come on!
That's...
Sorry to keep you waitin', everyone!
The Ringer is a Middle School Student!
Kamui is the ringer?!
That's right.
I go to Hitsue too, so they called me
up from the middle school division.
Huh. That's great!
I've heard about your situation...
But even so, I ain't gonna hold back one bit!
That's what I hoped you'd
say. I'm going all out, too.
That middle school twerp is their ringer?
We've already won this fight.
You don't know what you're
talking about, newbie!
What?!
Kamui Katsuragi is a member
of Q4, just like Sendou!
He's one of the warriors
who won the Asia Circuit.
Even with Misaki on our side, he's not
an opponent who can be beaten easily!
Right now, it's one to one...
Whoever wins this third match will bring
their team one win away from victory.
It's an extremely important match.
I'm counting on you, Misaki.
This may be the first time I've
fought Misaki in a real match.
I'm totally pumped!
As teammates, we've fought together at the
national championship and on the Asia Circuit.
But I'm going to win here.
So we can form a Cardfight
Club at Miyaji Academy!
Well, you two, are you ready?
Okay, let's Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Aiming for the Stars, Artemis!
Riot Horn!
That's Genesis! Then Misaki
has a new deck, not Oracle...
But Misaki's my opponent.
I bet she's mastered that one.
I can't get careless...
Her opponent is a middle school student?!
Yes. They're calling him "Hitsue's
ringer" or something...
Can they win with a kid like that?
No kidding. Hitsue must be having
problems with their club, too.
Whatever. I'll be waiting for the good news.
It's still the third match.
The result won't change.
Beast Deity, Hatred Chaos attacks
Twilight Hunter, Artemis!
Golden Anglet attacks with a boost
from Beast Deity, Hilarity Destroyer!
Trigger check.
Damage check.
Riot Horn!
Turn end!
The damage is 4 to 1!
That's a big gap!
Apparently, the middle school
student has her on the ropes.
Oh. Not bad at all.
That's right. He isn't.
Even though the damage is
4 to 1, Misaki is unmoved.
He comes charging out of
the gate early in the game.
That kind of fighting style is pure Kamui.
Then I'll really let loose, too!
Even a delicate, faint light becomes a
strong glow when the time of fullness comes!
Ride!
Battle Deity of the Night, Artemis!
Battle Deity of the Night...
Twilight Hunter is in the Soul, so Battle
Deity of the Night's power is 11000!
Call!
Witch of Cats, Cumin's skill. Soulcharge.
Saffron attacks Hatred Chaos!
I guard with The Gong!
Next!
Battle Deity of the Night, Artemis
attacks with a boost from
Battle Maiden, Tatsutahime!
Here it comes!
Exceed the limit and blaze
a trail to a new world!
Limit Break!
Soulblast!
I draw two cards!
I put one card from my hand into the Soul.
Battle Deity of the Night gets +5000 power!
Misaki is awesome!
Powering up and increasing my hand size,
this is Battle Deity of the
Night's Luna Glorious Glowing!
Twin drive check.
I give the power to Witch of Owls, Paprika,
and the extra critical to
Battle Deity of the Night!
Right here, I'm going to
activate Tatsutahime's skill!
Since Battle Deity of the Night's attack
hit, three cards Soulcharge!
Paprika attacks with a boost
from Witch of Cats, Cumin!
Battle Deity of the Night is the
Vanguard, so Paprika gets +3000 power!
No guard!
Turn end.
Yeah!
She caught up! Now they have the same damage!
She's just started using Genesis...
...but she's already totally mastered it!
Misaki really is incredible...
And I'm fired up, too!
The great Kamui rides
Beast Deity, Ethics Buster!
Hatred Chaos attacks Paprika!
I guard with Laurier!
Ethics Buster attacks
Battle Deity of the Night!
Perfect defense with Kushinada!
Saffron attacks with a boost
from Witch of Cats, Cumin!
Trigger activated. I give
the power to Ethics Buster!
Battle Deity of the Night attacks
with a boost from Tatsutahime!
And then, Limit Break!
Perfect defense with Twin Blader!
Sahohime attacks with a boost
from Witch of Cats, Cumin!
I guard with Wall Boy!
Turn end.
They're evenly matched!
Both of 'em are amazing...
Great fight!
You weathered those attacks,
suffering just 1 damage.
It's scary making an enemy out of you, Kamui.
Yeesh. You're makin' this fight
a real nail-biter, Misaki...
But the more I'm driven into a
corner, the more my blood boils.
That's me, the great Kamui Katsuragi!
It's my turn. Draw!
Misaki!
Sorry, but from here on out, the
great Kamui is gonna be on stage!
Your holy light is the proof of hope!
Envelop the world with that light!
Ultra Beast Deity, Illuminal Dragon!
The great me break rides Ethics Buster!
Illuminal Dragon and Ethics Buster...
That's a dangerous combination.
H-Hey. Is it really that bad?
What are you talking about?! Of course!
Although, having said that,
I could easily ride it out.
Get through this. The formation
of the club depends on it.
This is the effect of my break ride!
Illuminal Dragon gets +10000 power!
Call!
Riot exits the field!
His break ride... It ends like that?
He just gets +10000?!
No, Naoki. The really scary
thing about that break ride...
Hatred Chaos attacks with a
boost from Hilarity Destroyer!
With his skill, another +3000 is added!
Guard!
King of Sword attacks with
a boost from Blank Marsh!
Guard!
Next! Illuminal Dragon attacks with
a boost from Hilarity Destroyer!
And then... rise again, brave souls!
W-What the heck is that?!
That's one more effect of his break ride.
Now Kamui can attack two more times...
He can do that?!
And that's not all...
Next up, Illuminal Dragon's Limit Break!
Counterblast!
Stand up, warriors who bear
the name "Beast Deity"!
These brave fighters...
can stand up again and again to deal
their extreme, matchless blows!
This is my secret weapon,
Full Metal Battle Grapple!
So now Kamui can carry out two
attacks in a perfect form.
What kind of skill is that?!
Kamui really is a great fighter!
Girl, are the odds against you?
The formation of the Cardfight Club
is getting further and further away.
Misaki Tokura, is it?
How embarrassing, getting beaten
by a mere middle school student...
That jerk...
Vice president... is it?
Whatever it is you're anticipating,
I'm sure it'll be turned upside down.
So please close your mouth and just watch.
Kourin...
Twin drive check!
Draw trigger!
I give the power to King of Sword, then draw!
Second card...
1 damage left!
Misaki has already used two cards
with 10000 shields to guard with!
I doubt the last three cards in her hand
have decent defensive capabilities!
It's my attack again!
I activate Hatred Chaos's skill!
Hatred Chaos, go with a boost from Hilarity!
Guard!
She still had defense?!
Awesome! That was awesome, Boss Lady!
I'm not done yet! King of Sword!
Guard! And then I intercept!
Sh-She protected herself again!
Stopped at 5 damage...
That's Misaki, all right.
Turn end!
She blocked 'im! She totally blocked 'im!
Hey, Boss Lady rules, right?!
But it doesn't look good for what's next.
She only has one card left in her hand...
And her front line isn't full.
On top of that, her opponent's field
has two units that can intercept...
And he's got three cards in
his hand, including Sentinel.
She's ruined!
Can she win this turn?
It's okay.
She'll get through it somehow.
My turn. Draw.
The heat of silent souls like stars...
...and deep, intense emotions like the sea...
...are for eternity!
Ride!
Eternal Goddess, Iwanagahime!
I forgot about that card!
What do you mean?
Iwanagahime's Limit Break!
I retire all of my opponent's
front row rear-guards!
Everlasting Vanish!
Now he can only guard with
the three cards in his hand!
This is what makes Misaki great.
Call!
Cool...
By perfecting her attack formation,
she's seconds away from victory.
Impressive, Tokura.
Misaki's got me beat...
Sorry, Kamui. But I can't
afford to lose this fight!
Saffron attacks with a boost
from Witch of Cats, Cumin!
She's got two more attacks...
With that in mind, I don't
have enough defense...
In that case...
No guard! I'm gonna bet
on drawin' a heal trigger!
Here I go!
Go!
Too bad...
The winner of the third match:
Miyaji Academy's Misaki Tokura!
Vanguard
Nice fight!
You did it!
Wonderful!
In the end, you can't rely
on a middle school student.
You totally had me cornered.
I was really impressed, Kamui.
Right back at ya! You're one
of my strongest rivals, Misaki.
All right, that's two wins!
Who's next?
Okay, the pairings for the fourth match!
Miyaji Academy
Shingo Komoi
Uh oh. Me at last, huh?
Hitsue High School
Taishi Miwa
I haven't seen Miwa fight
in a long time, you know?
Me neither.
He's the captain of the team, ain't he?
You did great!
Then I figure he must be tough, huh?
I've never seen the name "Miwa"
in an issue of Vanguard Monthly.
Obviously, he's weak.
They've probably got a
shortage of decent fighters.
Oh?
You've got some nerve.
Maybe I should ask you to go easy on me...
Don't be too hard on him...
What are you talking about...?
Take this! Iron fist of the dragon's fury!
Dragonic Lawkeeper!
The winner of the fourth match:
Hitsue High School's Taishi Miwa!
Miwa's a fighter who holds
fights with Kai regularly.
Ehhhhhhhhhh?!
You should've told me that before!
It's a tie, two to two!
There's one match left...
Whether or not we can keep our
Cardfight Club at Miyaji Academy...
The next fight decides everything!
Yes. Everything will be decided...
...Aichi Sendou.
Miyaji Academy
Aichi Sendou
Hitsue's Vanguard Club's strongest
man for the final match...
The invincible man who's hailed as a
genius and has never known defeat...
At last, the great Katsumi
Morikawa's turn has come!
Hitsue High School
Katsumi Morikawa
This match may be in the bag.
The composition of his deck is unbalanced.
Approximately half of the cards
in his deck are grade 3...
Excuse me?
So he always loses in the end.
That's macho, ain't it?!
Of course, Aichi can't have a fight
where he looks down on his opponent.
He can't, but still...
Miyaji's victory is a done deal.
Ah, well, this way Brother gets
to have his Cardfight Club, too.
I don't know about that...
Morikawa...
Too bad for you, Aichi.
Of all people, you were chosen to face
the strongest and smartest fighter,
the great Morikawa.
But don't think I'm about to go easy on you.
Final fighter!
Here.
Thanks.
Morikawa is the same as ever...
I'm the strongest, which makes
Hitsue's Vanguard Club the strongest!
Yay!
Oh! Pardon me.
All right, you two, are you ready?
Yes!
Yeah!
Okay, let's Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Wha...?! What the heck is this?!
This isn't my deck!
Those jerks...
Is that a Kagero deck?
Maybe that's...
What's going on?
Kai put together Morikawa's deck.
You can't think of him as the
usual Morikawa, right, Kai?
Misaki really is strong!
There's no way a middle school student
can beat a high school student!
What?!
Okay, okay. Kamui, you've
gotten even stronger!
Well, I may be just a little stronger
than the four-eyes upperclassman over there.
Shush it! I lost on purpose before!
It was a strategic maneuver.
Talk about having no shortage of excuses...
Next time: Kai's Shadow!
In order to have our club, I can't
lose against Morikawa! But...
I don't believe it! Sendou is near defeat?!
If you underestimate him,
you'll be in trouble!