Come, irreplaceable soul brothers!
Respond to my voice!
Sword Formation Liberator, Igraine!
Quintet Wall!
Yeah! He blocked it!
Now only 1 more damage!
Aich's gonna win this,
no doubt about it!
I'm going to win this turn.
I'm going to release Kai from that darkness!
It's impossible.
Your attacks won't get through.
It looks like I've surpassed you!
Aichi...
The darkness is
going to swallow you up!
Soon, this whole world
will belong to our Link Joker.
Now that I have the power of Link Joker,
you can't beat me.
No matter how strong you've gotten, Kai,
I'm going to win this fight!
I'll win and break you free
of that Reversed spell!
That's my...
...our...
...wish!
Beyond the Bond
Radiate noble power
and turn it into a universal bond!
Crossbreak ride!
Liberator of Bonds, Gancelot!
It gets +10000 power!
Escrad, Flame of Victory,
and Bruno get +5000 power!
With his Quintet Wall, he did a break ride,
and even a crossbreak ride!
But two units are locked,
so Sendou can only attack twice!
Lock! Link Joker! So what?!
Aichi can still beat him!
It's impossible!
I'm going to throw everything
I've got at him.
I'm going to win this turn!
Escrad attacks!
Intercept.
He's got one attack left!
Flame of Victory boosts
an attack from Gancelot Zenith!
The bond between souls
that's deeper than blood!
For dreams! For justice!
For friends!
Resonate!
Gancelot Zenith's Limit Break!
Escrad goes to the bottom of my deck!
Then I superior call!
Phallon!
He switched out a unit after it attacked!
Yeah!
Now he can not only attack once more,
he powers up, too!
Great, Brother!
Perfect guard!
Drive trigger check...
Second check!
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Phallon!
One more time!
Phallon, attack!
Perfect guard.
My turn is over.
He couldn't even do 1 damage.
Who would've figured there'd
be two perfect guards?
Aichi...
It's not over. If Kai can protect himself,
then so can I!
Final Turn.
And this is our...
...final fight!
You weren't able to win this turn.
That shows your true ability.
Your strength.
The strength that lit a fire under me,
that changed my principles and
made me choose Link Joker.
I've surpassed that strength.
Is that really Kai?
Kai...
Kai, you're possessed by Link Joker!
I'm going to bring you to your senses!
I'm sick of hearing those words.
I'm going to beat you this turn.
It's all over.
Kai...!
Roar that shatters both good and evil!
Fangs that cut through light and darkness!
Absolute dragon, everything
grovels before you!
Break ride!
Star-vader, Chaos Breaker Dragon!
Lock the rear-guard!
Chaos Breaker gets +10000 power.
Lanthanum gets +2000 power for
every unit that was locked.
Aichi...
You're going to be locked by me forever!
Counterblast!
I lock Phallon!
And then Lanthanum's skill!
Lanthanum moves up
and attacks!
Guard!
He guarded against the first attack!
Lanthanum boosts...
...Chaos Breaker!
Again, Sword Formation Liberator, Igraine!
Quintet Wall!
All right! That's 25000 total shield!
Amazing!
That's his second Quintet Wall!
That's Brother Aichi for you!
Now he's got a chance!
There is no wall that
cannot be broken through.
Check the drive trigger.
Second check.
Heal trigger!
I give +5000 power to Chaos Breaker,
and heal 1 damage point.
No...
The 25000 Quintet Wall...
...was broken through!
Aichi...
I don't believe it...
It's not over yet! Damage trigger, check!
Farewell, Aichi.
Aichi...
...lost...
It was a perfect fight for Brother Aichi...
...and yet...
Sendou!
Brother Aichi!
Aichi!
Miwa?
I'm okay!
More importantly, Aichi is...
I told you.
I've surpassed you.
I don't need this deck anymore.
Link Joker's power has become my own.
Brother Aichi!
Has the Reverse begun?
Brother...
Aichi!
I threw away everything
to obtain this strength.
But you're different, Aichi.
You're trying to help friends
who have become enemies
and save a world that's already
starting to become Reversed.
The opposite of me,
you're carrying everything on your shoulders.
One threw away everything;
the other took on the burden of everything.
That's what separates us.
I was obsessed with you.
But that's over, too.
As you become Reversed...
I...
I won't become everyone's enemy!
No way!
I swore to turn you back to normal, Kai!
Impressive, Aichi Sendou.
To resist being Reversed like this...
But it's in vain.
It's impossible to stop the Reverse process.
Nothing can withstand Link Joker's locks.
The more you struggle,
the more you'll suffer.
Surrender to the darkness that's welling up.
Do that and it'll be much easier on you.
Resisting being Reversed will only cause
your soul to be worn away
and your strength to be sapped.
After that, what you have waiting for you
is the worst result ever.
Kai...
Aichi!
Brother!
Sendou!
Aichi!
Brother!
Sendou!
Aichi!
Miwa...
Miwa!
Everyone's worn out.
Darn it! Aichi...
Ain't there anything we can do?!
Leon Souryu!
Move it, move it!
Sorry!
Hey!
What're you...?
Helping Sendou... so don't get in the way.
Aichi Sendou...
Raise your Psyqualia!
Psyqualia...
Takuto...
Aichi Sendou.
I can't stop the Reverse
process with my power alone.
Whether it can be stopped or not
depends on you, Aichi.
Aichi...
Keep your feelings strong.
There's still something that you have to do.
I have to help him.
Kai!
Aichi!
Sendou?!
It looks like we were in time.
Takuto?
This may seem sudden, but your world...
...is going to be destroyed.
Why did you help me?
You're trying to destroy...
He's not the Takuto you know.
He looks like me, but there's
another consciousness inside.
Link Joker.
The cause of all of this.
How long has it existed?
Where did it come from?
A clan I knew nothing about
sealed me away.
And then,
it swallowed up the planet Cray
and is now trying to claim this planet.
In short, you're saying
the person who saved Aichi
was the real Takuto,
who's been sealed away?
That's correct.
He ain't here.
The real Takuto, who no longer has
a physical body in this world,
can only be seen by someone
who possesses Psyqualia.
...Psyqualia?
No idea what that is,
but if you say it, I believe it, Leon.
Takuto is right about there, right?
Yes.
Did you help Takuto?
You could say that.
It happened when I was
fighting a Reversed fighter.
Suddenly, I heard Takuto's voice calling out.
I followed the voice's directions
and came to the real Takuto.
He was in a state of paralysis,
sealed away on the planet Cray.
I have to foil Link Joker's ambitions
and bring Cray back to normal.
Of course, this world too.
But it's already mostly been
swallowed up by Link Joker.
Not much time is left.
The only remaining measure
is to defeat Link Joker,
the cause of all of this!
Even then, there's no guarantee that Cray
or this world will return to normal.
But that's the only thing
we can pin our hopes on!
Right now, Takuto and I are going
in there to beat Link Joker.
I'm...
...going, too.
Aichi!
Brother, you can't!
Sendou!
Takuto...
Me, too...
You can't do it exhausted like that.
Stay here.
You're in no shape to move.
I'm... fine...
Sendou, I think you can hear him,
but I'll tell everyone else what he said.
"Aichi Sendou,
you miraculously stopped the Reverse process
with the power of your strong will.
But the price you've paid
is major damage to your body and psyche.
It's impossible for you to fight."
But...
I'll lay it on the line, Aichi Sendou.
Even fighting right now
would put your life in danger.
His life?!
It's unfortunate,
but the Reverse process was
stopped only temporarily.
If you fight again,
and the power that was held back
gets released all at once,
the force of it
attacking your body...
Absolutely do not fight anymore!
Even so, I'm going to save Kai...
Aichi!
Stop it! You can't!
Brother!
Sendou!
Kai...
I'm going to...
Only Takuto and I are going in.
The rest of you,
take care of Sendou.
But...!
Aichi...
I've come to beat Link Joker.
I'm prepared for it.
The power to defeat Link Joker...
That power is...
We're going to beat it.
So watch over Sendou.
Got it. You can count on us.
Um... Leon...
We want to go, too!
No.
Jillian... Sharlene...
I want you to protect Sendou, too.
I have faith in you.
But this mirror...
You need it so that Takuto Tatsunagi
can appear, don't you?
Leon...
Take this...
Takuto Tatsunagi should be
able to appear with this...
Thank you. This works fine.
Just be sure to return it, Leon!
I will.
You'd better!
You'd better give it back!
I'll catch up...
I will go in later!
Takuto...
Aichi!
It looks like he fell asleep.
Kai... I'm going to save Kai...
Aichi Sendou...
You're deeply wounded, in mind and body.
Don't overdo it. Just relax.
We'll handle the rest.
Leon... Takuto...
I...
Next time: The Two Leons!
The Two Leons
Well, well. Leon Souryu...
I'm going to give you the
red-carpet treatment.