You... Leon Souryu...
Thank you, Leon.
I won't let your fight go to waste.
It's my turn next!
I'm definitely going to beat you!
You little...
The One Who Cuts Through Chains
Half of him was used to
bring forth the future Leon.
It seems he took a lot of damage.
So what?
Even if I've lost power,
there's no way I'll lose to you.
Aichi Sendou was defeated,
and Leon Souryu has run out of steam.
This is the final battle, as they say...
Before that, release Kourin!
She's an Earth girl!
Kourin?
Oh, that girl...
Not only that girl!
You used Suiko and Rekka, too!
In the first place, you called on them to become
your pawns to help you operate on Earth.
You're the one who used them.
I just did the same thing.
What, have you become attached to them?
Shall we fight with the stakes
being your precious Cray and Earth,
as well as the fate of your pawns?
Although I think your
struggling will be in vain.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Scarlet Lion Cub, Caria!
Star-vader, World Line Dragon!
I ride Star-vader, Rune Magician!
I ride Knight of Elegant Skills, Gareth!
Strike Star-vader, Krypton!
Forget it, Sharlene! Leon gave us orders.
He told us to wait here, remember?
But...
We've got company, huh?
Miwa, are you okay?
Yeah. No problem!
Hmph! This'll be fun!
This deck can't be held
in place by any case now!
I, Shingo Komoi,
will protect Sendou to the end!
Here I go! My heart's on fire!
Naoki!
It's yellin', "Kick all their butts!"
Hey!
We've got no choice!
Let's split up and beat 'em all!
Roger!
Wake up!
Take this!
I ride Infinite Zero Dragon!
Krypton, attack Viviane!
I absolutely will not let you have your way!
Draw!
Warrior enveloped in incandescence!
Use those glowing flames to lead
the despairing people to hope!
I ride my avatar!
Incandescent Lion, Blond Ezel!
I thought I'd gotten rid of you long ago,
so I'm surprised to see you back.
Leon... and the other Cardfighters...
led me back.
That's a laugh.
I'm responsible for your existence here.
I'll definitely beat you!
Superior call!
Attack!
Twin drive!
Critical trigger!
You think you're going to beat me?
Oh, please.
Do you really think you can defeat me
just because Leon stole some of my power?
Feel the terror!
Break ride!
Star-vader, Infinite Zero Dragon!
Break ride skill!
I lock two of your rear-guards!
Now, shiver in fear at
the terror of Link Joker!
Your locked rear-guards can't do
anything until your next turn.
From here on in, you'll stay powerless,
absorbing my attacks until you lose.
You should have just stayed
obediently spellbound.
Blame your powerless self for this.
Go, Krypton!
Guard!
I like it!
Useless, yes, but it's boring if
you don't resist me a little bit.
I haven't just been sidelined all this time!
I've been looking for the
power to crush Link Joker!
That doesn't exist!
All power is nullified before my locking!
It's a waste! It won't help you one bit!
We'll see.
I stand and draw!
Even under the rule of a long darkness,
light resides in strong hearts
that haven't lost hope!
Look upon the brilliance of tenacious souls,
awakened by power that can crush the spell!
My avatar, obtain even more power!
Your holy blade!
Use it to break through the
chains of detestable darkness!
I ride my warrior of the shining heavens!
Salvation Lion, Grand Ezel Scissors!
Grand Ezel... Scissors?!
What is that light?!
This light smashes the spell of Link Joker!
Limit Break!
Break through all locks!
Holy Dispel Scissors!
What?! It can't be!
My locks have been broken?!
What?!
What the...?!
Leon Souryu?
No. Maybe it's...
...the other Takuto that
Leon was talkin' about?
Takuto versus Takuto?
Whichever way, all we can do is
have faith that those two will win!
Leon!
Takuto...
How?! It's impossible!
My locks... My locks have been broken?!
I see...
He finally did it... Takuto...
My locks...
The invincible Link Joker...
On top of that, skill activated!
I've got five rear-guards,
so Grand Ezel gets power
and an extra critical!
Caria boosts! Grand Ezel!
Begone with your evil power, Link Joker!
Perfect guard...
Twin drive...
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Bagdemagus!
Torre boosts!
Bagdemagus attacks!
Guard! Intercept!
Blond Ezel!
No guard!
Turn end.
Grand Ezel Scissors...
I didn't know there was a trump card
that could smash through locks...
Destined guidance awoke Grand Ezel
and gave it the power to crush Link Joker!
Already, the locks have lost their power!
The next turn is your last!
Next? Certainly, if there is a next turn...
But surely you know that you just
missed your one chance of beating me.
Break ride!
Sword of despair that dyes
all brilliance jet-black!
Star-vader, Omega Glendios!
Omega Glendios?!
You just said you were going to bring
the era of Link Joker to an end.
In that case, I'll bring to an end...
your whole world!
Lock!
Another lock?
Your locks no longer work on me!
Is that right?
The time has come for you
to be summoned, my servant.
Destroy my enemy!
Call!
Dauntless Dominate Dragon "Reverse"!
Observe. This is the power of Glendios!
Ascendant Joker!
Dauntless "Reverse" becomes Link Joker!
What?!
Becomes Link Joker?!
That's right.
Under Glendios, all "Reverse" units
become servants of Link Joker!
On top of that, it gets +4000 power!
It turns into Link Joker...
and also powers up?!
Now what?!
Hey! These jerks...
I'm scared!
Don't be, Sharlene! We have
to do our best for Leon!
Yeah. I'm okay. I won't lose!
Whoa...
Be careful. The power of all
these guys is increasing!
Yeah...
I... I bet that aura has some
kind of effect on their power.
I lock Knight of Passion, Torre!
I told you that your locks
were useless now.
Did you think it was a regular old lock?
Don't underestimate the power of Glendios.
Limit Break!
Omega Lock!
What?!
Even after the opponent's turn ends,
this lock won't come undone.
This is an Omega Lock!
You'll never break free of my lock!
It... It can't be...
You underestimated me.
While you have a trump card,
did you really think that I didn't?
Omega Glendios!
Attack Bagdemagus!
Attacking a rear-guard?!
Guard!
Twin drive!
I give the power to Dauntless "Reverse"!
Dauntless "Reverse"!
Turn end.
Your lock will last forever.
This is the beginning
of the end of the world!
If I could only use Grand Ezel,
I'd be able to get rid of the lock...
...but I don't have enough for the cost!
His aim is to just attack the rear-guards...
All you can do is watch as
I lock all of your rear-guards!
Call!
Lock!
Omega Lock!
I call Bagdemagus!
I lock Bagdemagus!
Omega Lock!
I attack Glendios!
Guard.
I won't give up!
As long as I don't have
6 damage, I haven't lost!
I have cards in my hand.
I'll send all of his attacks back
at him and then counterattack!
At some point, the locks will break!
And that's when I'll...!
The locks won't have a chance to break.
Final Turn.
And also...
...the world will end!
What are you saying?!
The world will end?
What is he talking about?!
Well, then...
One card, two cards, three cards,
four cards, and five cards...
Just before, you said you hadn't lost
unless you got 6 damage.
But that was only true before
Glendios came to this world.
That was in the past.
In the past?
That's right! Glendios and I
are changing the world!
Ultimate break! World End!
If five or more of my opponent's
cards are locked, I win!
You... automatically win?!
Unbelievable! He can win
without doing 6 damage?!
That's World End.
That changes the world.
This is the true power of Glendios...
of Link Joker!
It's over, Takuto Tatsunagi.
This is...
Be careful, everyone!
That's not so easy!
S-Sendou?
Sendou!
Where did you go?!
Aichi!
Brother!
Where did you go, Aichi?!
Aichi!
You've lost, Takuto Tatsunagi.
Takuto!
Don't push it with that exhausted
body of yours, Leon Souryu.
That's right.
I can use you in a better way
than just being Reversed.
Give me that body... and power!
Stop!
Lock!
What?!
Stop... it!
And now, no one stands in my way!
No one can defy me!
Cray... and this Earth...
both of them are my worlds!
...Oh?
Takuto...
No... Fake Takuto!
What?
Takuto... Tatsunagi...
Ah...
But the Takuto you people know
no longer exists.
I'm not used to this body yet, but...
What are you saying?!
His power is being sublimated by mine!
Takuto... I'll make you pay for this!
No matter what happens to me,
I'll make sure you pay!
Next time: Kourin!
Kourin
I'll use my power to do everything I can!
I don't want to lose anybody!
I'm going to get the original Kourin back!