This is...
Be careful, everyone!
That's not so easy!
S-Sendou?
Sendou!
Where did you go?!
Aichi!
Brother!
Where did you go, Aichi?!
Aichi!
Takuto...
No... Fake Takuto!
What?
I won't let you get away with it...
You, who did this to Earth...
You, who Reversed everyone...
And you, who gave that power to Kai!
And what is it that you think
you're going to do?
Beat you!
Why did you come?!
If you fight now, you'll...
Good grief. One right after another...
I feel like I keep getting
asked to dance at a ball.
I could take you up on it...
...but there's something else
that I need to focus on.
So instead, your perfect match is right here.
She would love to dance with you.
I'll introduce you.
This is a daughter of the Tatsunagi family.
Kourin!
Kourin
With the blade of intellect,
fight off destiny and lead me!
Minerva, attack!
I make it look like I'm
running away, and then...
Magatsu Storm!
Yeah!
Aichi...
Go!
Miwa...
You're worried about him, aren't you?
We can handle the situation here.
More importantly, hurry up and stop Brother!
If he fights again, he'll...
I'm countin' on you, Kamui!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Coiling Duckbill!
Dragon Monk, Gojo!
Tempest Bolt Dragon!
Storm Rider, Diamantes!
Same! Storm Rider, Basil!
Kourin...
Save your breath, Aichi.
Win or lose. Those are
our only two dance steps.
In that case, I'll win!
Then I'll take a break for a little while.
How...? He was so exhausted
that he couldn't stand up.
Spirit...
He's standing on that alone?!
That's...
I'm definitely going to
bring back your old self.
Kourin...
You're going to fight to
regain the bond of friendship.
But... if you win, that bond will...
I can't lose.
I'll win this fight...
...against you.
Aichi!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Liberator, Cheer Up Trumpeter!
Desire Jewel Knight, Heloise!
I ride Marron!
Prizmy attacks!
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride...
...Blaster Blade Liberator!
Attack!
Banding Jewel Knight, Miranda attacks!
Aichi!
Misaki Tokura! Wait!
Leon?!
Look!
I'm not done yet!
To release those who are
in the grip of a spell,
come forth, king of all knights!
I ride...
Liberator Black Sanctuary, Alfred!
What is that unit?!
That's the new Alfred.
Thank you...
...for helping me encounter new comrades.
Hmph. That guy...
He still had a final trump card.
That Alfred...
...is supporting Sendou's spirit.
There are things that I have to protect.
The world that I know...
The people that I know...
I swear I'll save them!
It's my turn.
I'm going to defeat you here...
...to protect my world!
Blanket the light, evil darkness!
I ride...
...Broken Heart Jewel Knight,
Ashlei "Reverse"!
Tilda's skill.
Superior call!
Limit Break!
Jewel Sword, Noir!
Lock!
I command you by this jewelled sword!
Escrad, leave the battlefield!
By this jewelled sword, come forth...
...my new knight!
I sense more determination in her than ever!
But right now, Kourin is...
She's lonely.
It's no wonder.
She's burdened with a sad fate.
What do you mean?
I'm definitely going to win this
fight and protect it to the end!
Protect my world!
And also my memories!
Is that true?
On the way here, Takuto told me...
Kourin doesn't have any old memories?
Where am I?
Ow...
Who are you?
Me? I'm...
You wouldn't know.
I'm taking good care of your memories.
No one must know of my activities henceforth.
What activities?
Protecting this planet, Cray...
Furthermore, that's connected to
protecting your own world.
Our world...
And I can't do it alone.
My name is Takuto.
From now on, you three are
going to be my allies.
That's... That's not fair!
Back then, he saw them as no more than pawns.
But even if things are different now...
...they were absolutely necessary then.
Allies of this world...
Alfred attacks!
Guard!
Aichi's really gotten strong.
To think he would come this far...
Back then, I could never
have imagined it.
I didn't believe it at first.
He was a leader?
But his skill kept growing more and more.
I kept watching that...
...and somewhere along the line,
I couldn't take my eyes off of him.
Then I met the people
around Aichi, his friends.
To me, someone without a past,
all of those memories were just...
were just too bright...
If Takuto is beaten, what'll
happen to Kourin and the others?
The other Takuto was absorbed.
If the current Takuto is defeated,
I'm sure both of them will disappear.
And then her role as an ally will be over.
Her memories of this time...
...will vanish.
To her, the idea of having her current
memories erased must be worse than death.
That really would be losing her world.
Jewel Sword, Noir!
Phallon, leave the battlefield!
So to protect that, she can't
let Takuto be defeated.
That's why Kourin is trying
to beat Aichi here.
Ashlei "Reverse," attack!
Check.
Critical trigger.
I give the power to Miranda and the
extra critical to Ashlei "Reverse"!
W-What is this?
Aichi...
You'll be Reversed soon.
You may change,
but it's better than losing you!
Kourin, don't!
Attack!
Guard!
I'm going to end it with this!
I won't let you!
Wha...?! Aichi!
Here I come, Kourin!
Cheer Up Trumpeter gives its power to Alfred!
And then Alfred's Limit Break!
I send all of your rear-guards to your deck!
And then, five allies
gather on the battlefield!
He filled up the entire rear-guard circle!
Bruno's skill!
It gets +3000 power for every rear-guard
unit that appeared from the deck!
This Bruno's skill is activated too!
Cheer Up Trumpeter's skill!
Alfred gets +3000 power for every
rear-guard unit that appeared from the deck!
On top of that, Alfred gets +1000
power for every rear-guard unit!
With this rear-guard combo
centered around Alfred,
my attacking power
increases dramatically.
This is the new Alfred's
power of the bond!
Call!
No! Aichi!
Tokura!
I'm sure Sendou has a firm resolve.
Stopping him now would only steal his spirit.
Aichi...
Alfred, attack!
Guard!
Quintet Wall!
I guard even more!
I can't afford to be defeated here!
Twin drive...
Critical trigger!
I give all of the effects to Gancelot!
I attack Miranda!
My intercept...
There are friends that
I want to protect.
Kourin, you're one of them!
That's why, even if I put
my life on the line...
...I will save you!
Kourin... Aichi...
Darn it! There's no end to them!
Don't lose heart, senior!
Leave it to me, junior!
You take the ones in back, Shingo!
Roger! You'd better not
let me down, Ishida!
Several of them are going inside!
How dare you do that to Jillian?!
More of 'em?
Darn it! I'll fight all of them together!
Kourin, I don't want to...
Aichi, I don't want to...
...lose you!
Gancelot!
Quintet Wall!
The shield...
It's not enough!
You're strong, Aichi.
But this is my...
It's over.
Kourin!
Both of you are fools!
Aichi, why did you push yourself this far?!
Just fighting puts your life in danger.
And yet, you...
I'm... fine...
But...
Aichi.
You're always this way...
Giving no thought to yourself...
...as you help other people...
Thank you for your trouble, Kourin.
You bought me the time I needed.
Misaki, please take care of Kourin.
Aichi?
There's still something that I have to do.
Kourin...
I'm sorry, Kourin.
If only I'd noticed earlier...
And not only you.
Kai, too, and everyone
else who's been Reversed.
You can't do this, Aichi.
You can barely stand up. Besides...
Misaki, this is my responsibility!
Next time: Ren's Wish!
Ren's Wish
The Reversed fighters have even come here?!
Neither Aichi nor Leon are
in any shape to fight!
I'll handle this!
Huh? You people are...!