Attack!
You wiped me out.
All right... I did it!
I did it!
The deck that I could see in my mind's eye
while fighting Leon is given form at last!
You're tough. And I'm worn out.
Sorry for makin' you hang
out with me like this.
You can sleep there for a while.
I got somewhere to go.
Go where?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Miyaji Academy!
Miyaji Academy?
Yeah, that's right.
It ain't like me to just run away
with my tail between my legs.
Besides, one of them black
rings is above the school.
Bet you anything those Reversed
fighters are gathering there.
By hook or by crook, I gotta crush 'em.
You don't think you should
consult with Sendou first?
He's got his fight with Kai.
I don't want him to worry about other stuff.
Good grief...
And I thought I could get a little sleep...
Shingo?
In the first place, you're the weakest
member of Miyaji Academy's Cardfight Club!
Only your motivation is strong.
What's that?!
That's why I said...
"It may be impossible for Ishida alone,
but if both of us go, maybe
we'll get somewhere!"
Granny Glasses!
Let's go, juvenile delinquent wannabe!
Recapture Miyaji Academy!
Irritating ring, isn't it?
It ticks me off.
You two are admirable for
coming to school so early.
Oh, we're studious as all heck.
But today is Sunday.
Where are Aichi Sendou and Misaki Tokura?
They got somethin' important to do.
Where are Kamui Katsuragi and Kourin?
They also have something to do.
Then are you gonna study with us?
I wouldn't mind teaching you a thing or two,
but there are other kids
who just love to study.
Ready, set...
Lock! Lock! Lock!
Reverse formation!
The American football club!
At last, we've obtained true power
from the black ring in the sky.
It's our destiny to spread
it throughout the world.
Even those guys...
Tomorrow is Monday.
When the other students come to school,
we'll make even more Reversed fighters.
And the gate will become bigger, too.
What kind of person are you?!
The one who received an order from
Takuto to keep an eye on Aichi Sendou
and the Cardfight Club as the
Student Council Secretary.
That's me, Maki Nagashiro.
I see... So you're the ringleader.
In that case, I'm gonna be sure to beat you!
Wait!
It seems we've got to beat them first.
Guess it's like warming up
before the main event...
What you said this morning...
It warmed my heart.
H-Huh?
About us maybe gettin'
somewhere together.
Let's give it our best shot.
Together!
Don't lose, Granny Glasses!
Same to you, delinquent wannabe!
Let's go!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Spark Rain Dragon attacks!
Demonic Hair Stealth Rogue, Glenjin attacks!
Thunder Boom Dragon attacks!
Paper Umbrella Stealth
Rogue, Sukeroku attacks!
Attack!
I attack!
One more time! Attack!
Jeez, feels like I'm goin' 100 rounds here!
Granny Glasses, you doin' okay?
Shingo?
S-Sorry... Ishi...da...
Shingo, if you're here, answer me! Shingo!
Hey, Shingo!
You guys are from the Student Council...
So?
After we came back from camping, we
went to the Student Council office.
The work had been piling
up while we were out.
Break Time!
Bravo, President. You're strong, as expected.
Then it might not be a dream after all.
I could even be in the
VF High School Championship.
That's right!
I wanted to fight, but
Suwabe was just too scared.
Th-That's not fair! You were
hiding behind me the whole time!
Listen, guys, did you see
Shingo before you met me?
No.
Then do you know where that
Naga...shiro girl or whatever is?
Nagashiro? Do you mean our secretary, Maki?
She stayed behind here, too?
If you don't know, never mind.
I-Ishida? Where are you going?
I got somethin' to do.
Stick around, run away, it's up to you.
Wait! Will you take me with you?
Hey, let go of me!
Y-You're like the Spider's Thread...
No, like Rapunzel's hair!
Hey, let go!
I-If you do, I promise to officially
recognize the Cardfight Club!
We've sabotaged you like crazy up
to now, but we'll never do it again!
Please!
P-Please, Ishida!
We're helpless by ourselves...
Look, just let go of my leg!
Granny Glasses!
I been lookin' for you, dummy!
Don't run off like that! Make
a guy worry about you...
Are you... strong?
Naoki Ishida. You're going to
become a member of my Komoi Corps.
Shingo... You too?
I'm full of invincible power.
It screams inside of my body.
"Defeat the enemy..."
I'm going to crush you.
It'll be like taking candy... from a baby!
I wanted to stand shoulder-to-shoulder
with you an' fight together.
That's what I was plannin'.
It's too bad...
But I'm gonna turn you back to
normal if it's the last thing I do!
Win, Ishida...
If you lose, then we become the prey.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Ambush Dragon Eradicator, Linchu!
Rogue, Boem!
I ride Ceremonial Bonfire Eradicator, Castor!
I ride Stealth Rogue of Silence, Shijimamaru.
Linchu's skill!
Paper Umbrella Stealth Rogue,
Sukeroku moves to the Drop Zone!
Call! Swift Archer, FUSHIMI!
Eradicator, Demolition
Dragon attacks FUSHIMI!
Eradicator, Ignition Dragon attacks!
Supreme Army Eradicator, Zuitan attacks!
That makes 4 damage!
And that attack just now
wiped out his rear-guards!
That's Ishida for you!
Hang on... I swear I'll
bring you back to normal.
Mowing down the enemy's rear-guards,
battling for the advantage...
Eradicator... Certainly,
that's a powerful tactic...
...but it doesn't work against Murakumo.
What?!
No one has ever successfully escaped from
the curse of pandemonium on the loose!
Ride!
Covert Demonic Dragon,
Hyakki Vogue "Reverse"!
Hyakki Vogue "Reverse's" skill!
Superior call.
I call Oboro Cart.
Oboro Cart's skill.
Superior call!
Suddenly three units?!
It's like Hyakki Vogue "Reverse"
has duplicated itself, doesn't it?
And next...
Limit Break!
Lock!
With this, all of my Hyakki Vogue
"Reverse" units get +10000!
What?!
The doubles fill the unit-less gaps and
then turn to an even more powerful attack!
That's Murakumo's Devil's Shadow Cloning!
As long as I have this, you're powerless!
Right after you used an Eradicator
to mow down my units!
And now...
I attack!
Guard!
Attack!
Attack, I say!
Have you realized just how powerless you are?
The Hyakki Vogue duplicates disappear
after their work is done...
So what?
In other words, the duplicates
are just duplicates.
They're not the real Hyakki Vogue.
Just like you're not the real you right now!
I'm gonna get you back with these attacks!
It's no use.
Ignition Dragon attacks!
Perfect guard.
Twin drive check!
Heal trigger activated!
I heal 1 damage!
I give the power to Zuitan!
Spark Rain Dragon attacks!
Guard.
Zuitan attacks with a boost from Castor!
Turn end!
Shoot! I couldn't make that last step!
It looks like you're giving
it everything you've got...
...but to be honest, I'm
not entirely satisfied.
I'll quickly get you out of the way,
then fight people who have more spirit.
What's that you're sayin', dillweed?
Do I have to spell it out for you?
Aichi Sendou and Misaki Tokura.
Are you serious?
I don't care who it is.
I'll wipe the floor with them.
The power flowing through my body
is crying out to beat the enemy.
Devil's Shadow Cloning.
Oboro Cart's skill.
And now, I'll finish this!
Limit Break!
And then, lock!
You...
Do you really intend to make
enemies of Aichi and Misaki?
You used to idolize them, remember?
And you gotta have memories of
bein' at the Cardfight Club...
You mean to destroy all that?
What's so important about those memories?
To me right now, those people are just
opponents that need to be Reversed.
And you're the same.
Hyakki Vogue "Reverse"
attacks Ignition Dragon!
President! Now he's got 5 damage!
At first, I thought he was a superior fighter,
but this is beyond even his power?
President...
If we're going to escape, now's the time.
What?!
If we stay here, we're
going to be beaten next.
But... are you saying we should just
turn our backs on him and run?
I... I don't think I can win this...
Is this... as far as I go?
What are you lying down for,
juvenile delinquent wannabe?!
Don't let something like this
take the wind out of your sails!
Get up right now!
Then hurry up and save me!
Granny Glasses...
But against you right now...
...I'm not...
Don't be pathetic!
This is the deck that was made when
you and I were driven to desperation.
With the two of us...
maybe we'll get somewhere!
President, please hurry
up and make your decision!
Ishida!
He got up!
Granny Glasses...
You're incorrigible. I'll make
it so you can't stand up again.
Attack!
I guard with a perfect guard!
Guard! Intercept!
He protected himself!
I just talked to the real you.
I didn't make this deck alone.
This deck got made 'cause you were there too.
Your feelings are in here.
This is definitely you.
You summon the strongest guy
at exactly the right time.
Break through all bindings and descend,
my strongest avatar of savage lightning!
Break ride!
Eradicator, Tempest Bolt Dragon!
As long as I have this deck, I ain't alone.
Granny Glasses...
The real Shingo and I are
gonna fight together!
And I'm definitely gonna beat you!
The power is surging
through me, overflowing...
Naoki Ishida, you're going
to surrender to me now.
There's no shame in losing to me!
Shingo...
Naoki, Shingo... Did you guys really
venture into Miyaji Academy?
Even though the whole
academy may be Reversed...
Next time: Smash Through Everything!
Smash Through Everything!
Hang in there, Naoki and Shingo!
I'm gonna bust you up with this
deck that you and I put together!