One... two...
2nd
Sorry
3rd
1st
Aww!
I go first!
I don't get to go at all...
Sorry
2nd
Kourin is second, and you're third, Aichi!
Sorry                             3rd
Yep!
Suiko Tatsunagi's going first over there...
Ishida already lost to a Fukuhara
opponent once. Will he be okay?
I swear I'll get my revenge this time!
All right! Let's go, everyone!
Let's give it our all!
Miyaji Academy's Cardfight Club... let's fight!
Yeah!
Oh yeah, everyone in the
auditorium is fired up, too!
As you'd expect from the
team that's favored to win,
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Fukuhara's got an incredible cheering section!
Cheering helps the fighters.
And I'm sure they know that.
Fukuhara! Fukuhara!
Draw! Ride! Call! Attack!
This is all we got to cheer our guys on?
And most of the people on this
side are from our school!
Even if it is just us, let's
do our best to cheer on Miyaji!
Yeah!
Miss Emi! I'm totally behind Miyaji!
Me too!
MT, yo!
Come on, guys, cheer for all you're worth!
Miyaji! Miyaji! Miyaji! Miyaji!
Hey! You two cheer 'em on, too!
Miyaji! Miyaji! Miyaji!
Don't you think the third
match should be interesting?
Yeah. It should.
It promises to be a fight that shows
the true potential of both parties.
VF High School Championship
Luck's taken them this far,
but they're out of it now.
When they fail to win, that's when...
Have you improved a little?
Yeah.
We ain't gonna have a repeat
of what happened last time.
At last, the big day is here, Aichi.
I'm really looking forward to it. I really am.
Ren...
Thanks to you, Shadow Paladin
has returned to me.
That's why I wanted to thank you...
...by defeating you.
That Ren has come back...
But I have no intention of losing!
Nice eyes, Aichi.
I know we're third, but I'd
like to fight right now.
Unfortunately, you may not
get the chance to fight, Ren.
Suiko and I can handle Miyaji
Academy all by ourselves.
I'm not going to let that comment go.
Oh, dear. Your mouth is
twitching, Ms. Ultra-rare.
If you can't maintain your smile
over a little remark like that,
isn't that a failure as an idol?
Come on, Kourin, smile! Smile!
Thank you for the advice.
Either way, let's all
have a good final round.
Right, Aichi?
Right! I look forward to it.
Challenger Naoki
All right! In just a moment, the first
match of the final round will begin!
Naoki, give it your all!
The first match is all-important in
building up momentum for the whole team!
We're counting on you!
Keep a clear head!
Thanks, everyone...
All right, let the first
match of the final round...
...begin!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Hope Child, Turiel!
Flag of Raijin, Corposant!
Okay, the curtain has risen on this battle!
A heated battle between high
school students is s-o exciting!
Fight, Miyaji Academy!
Go! Go! Fukuhara!
I ride Crimson Mind, Baruch!
I ride Ceremonial Bonfire Eradicator, Castor!
Attack!
I ride Core Memory, Armaros!
Dragonic Deathscythe!
Deathscythe's skill activates!
I retire Million Ray Pegasus!
Call!
Thunderstorm attacks Armaros!
Guard!
Deathscythe attacks!
Trigger check!
Corposant!
And Deathscythe!
I give all of the effects to Armaros.
Mess her up, Corposant!
I guard with Nociel!
Nociel's skill is activated.
Turn end!
Like they say, "prepare everything
when the mind is patient."
I won't lose as long as I keep
movin' ahead with perseverance!
Ishida is making a valiant effort
to fight carefully today!
I can tell that he doesn't want to lose!
Ride!
Prophecy Celestial, Ramiel!
Call!
Attack Deathscythe!
Ramiel attacks Deathscythe!
Ramiel's skill activates.
She gets +2000 power!
Million Ray!
Guard!
The damage is 4 to 4...
They'll be able to use Limit Breaks now,
so this is where they both get serious.
Here I go! Ride!
Armor Break Dragon!
Call!
Will he use its skill here?
He wouldn't! This is an important match!
A mistake like last time
will blow the whole thing!
Yeah...
If it means losing all the cards in my hand,
I'll take it slow and steady instead!
Naoki...
Thunderstorm!
The left-side Million Ray!
Red River boosts!
Get her, Armor Break Dragon!
Aniel!
Perfect guard.
I'm not done yet! Red River boosts!
Go, Corposant!
Draw trigger.
Turn end.
All right! She's just got 1 damage to go...
Just a little more!
What?!
You chose not to use the Limit Break
skill that I guarded against before, huh?
"If it costs three units and she's
able to guard against it anyway,
I'll just attack her steadily instead."
So what if I thought that?!
Oh! Don't get mad about it.
I'm impressed, that's all. I can
see you're getting wiser.
But...
...I'm not afraid of you at all anymore.
It's too bad.
I thought this match would
be more interesting.
Shut up! You've got just 1 more damage to go!
If I can protect myself this turn, I'm
gonna knock you for a loop next turn!
Is that right?
Then before that happens, I'll let
you hear the song of love again!
Break ride!
Chief Nurse, Shamsiel!
She's comin' at me with that?!
Ramiel's skill activates!
Listen to the song of love!
Eternal Song for the Injured!
Call!
Million Ray Pegasus attacks
Armor Break Dragon!
Intercept!
Turiel boosts! Shamsiel attacks!
Shamsiel's skill!
And now, the second song! Listen
to the melody of inexhaustible love!
Eternal Song for the Injured!
This time, four units?!
Well? Are you happy to
be able to hear so many?
This is the final round for Kanto Block 3.
We're near the end of the first
match, with 5 to 4 damage!
Ishida of Miyaji Academy is in the lead!
But Tatsunagi is expertly empl-o-ying
the Angel Feather skills,
putting her opponent in
a precarious p-o-sition!
Shamsiel's power is 24000, making
it a total attack of 29000,
so he needs a lot of guards.
And if she gets a trigger, he'll lose!
This fight is already over!
Let's put our hopes on the next
matches with Kourin and you, Sendou!
But...
What are you talking about?!
He hasn't given up yet!
Too bad for you!
I guard with Guld!
That's a perfect guard!
Not bad.
But don't count your chickens
with just a perfect guard.
Trigger check.
First check...
Second check...
Heal trigger!
I give the power to Million Ray
and heal 1 damage point.
Thousand Ray Pegasus boosts.
Million Ray Pegasus attacks
Armor Break Dragon!
Turn end.
Stand and draw!
Shoot!
The damage is still 5 to 4, but reversed,
with me just 1 point away from losing!
If I use my Limit Break, I may win,
but if she's able to protect
against it, it's all over for me!
Whatever it takes, I wanna win today!
But I don't have to make a huge
gamble by dumping three cards!
After all, I still got a pair
of perfect guards in my hand...
So if I just hang on through the next turn...
But... But...
I don't wanna lose!
But...
I don't wanna make a mistake either!
What should I do?!
Naoki!
Trust yourself!
Trust... myself...
Armor Break Dragon...
What the heck?! Jeez...
A person who's just thinkin' about safe
choices and runnin' away from the fight...
...isn't me!
I started Vanguard to get
fired up about somethin'!
To get passionate about somethin'!
How could I have forgotten
somethin' as important as that?!
I'm a complete idiot!
When there's courage in the
heart, there are no regrets!
Corposant's skill is activated!
Armor Break Dragon gets +3000 power!
If you can do the impossible,
logic goes by the wayside!
If you can get past pride,
the limit backs off!
That's the way a man lives!
Armor Break Dragon! And
what I'm doin' right now...
Limit Break!
Armor Break Dragon!
Cast off your armor and turn its
protective power into an iron fist!
I call Vowing Sword Dragon!
Red River boosts!
Armor Break Dragon attacks Shamsiel!
I guard with Critical Hit Angel,
Samyaza, and Ramuel!
That's 32000 power versus 40000!
Suiko's guard is higher.
But that doesn't scare me!
Armor Break Dragon! Feel
the flames of my heart!
Drive check!
He got a trigger!
Yeah! I add +5000 to the
power of Armor Break Dragon!
Second check!
He got another one!
I give all of the effects
to Armor Break Dragon!
Get her!
At the eleventh hour...
...he managed to draw two triggers...
He really is an interesting boy.
The winner of the first match,
from Miyaji Academy, Naoki Ishida!
VF High School Championship
Kanto Block 3
Amazing! Miyaji Academy's
Ishida lost his lead,
then regained it, becoming victorious!
He used Armor Break Dragon's skill without
fear to attain a courageous victory!
You are s-o right!
Yeah!
That was awesome!
What's the big deal?
You did it, Naoki!
Beating Suiko, that's really something!
You've grown.
Th-Thanks...
I did it...
I did it!
I was able to contribute to the team!
Having to cheer on a fight that makes no
progress... Think how that feels from our end!
What's that?!
A true fighter draws on his units' abilities.
As famous military leader
Shingen Takeda once said,
"Use sour persimmon as sour persimmon."
Did he say that?
Shut up! You lookin' to start
the Kawanakajima campaign here?!
You want to start it?!
Calm down, you two!
I'm sorry.
I was done in by passion.
Maybe his rapid improvement
is down to his youth, too.
Honestly... Giving Ren's team a defeat
is a sin worthy of dying 10,000 times.
Right, Ren?
Okay, okay, Asaka.
I don't mind.
We can afford one loss.
Wha...?! Ren...
It was a worthy effort, Suiko.
Come on, have a seat.
Thank you.
Hey, what?! That's too close!
First, let's cheer Asaka on.
Certainly.
Calm down, Asaka!
But even if I don't root for her,
I trust that Asaka will win her match.
O-Of course!
I'll be of service to Ren as sure
as I'm this club's vice-captain!
Such confidence!
I also have faith that you'll win.
Do us proud, Asaka.
I-I will!
Just for you, Ren, I'll put on a
beautiful, victory-achieving show.
All right! Let's throw each
other in the air to celebrate!
Too premature.
Whoops. That's right, we
gotta win one more, don't we?
Then you're next, Kourin. Have a good fight.
Keep this momentum goin'!
Don't give her any mercy!
Leave it to me!
Be careful of her Soul.
Thank you. I'll be back soon.
Good luck, Kourin!
Win it for us!
Win it, you say?
I'm going to win, for Ren's sake.
And there's no way that Ren will lose.
In other words, your victories are over.
Huh...
That's some confidence.
But I have no intention of losing either.
You put up a good front.
Love
Kourin Love
Hooray! Hooray!
Kourin!
Let's join in!
Miyaji Academy, fight!
Give it your all, Miyaji!
Good luck!
Looks like everybody's fired up.
Asaka is strong,
but I'm sure Kourin will be okay.
Good luck, Kourin!
And now, everything is in place for
the second match of the final round!
Let's fight!
Stand up, Vanguard!
That fight was nerve-wracking!
Shut up! It was the best I could do!
Kourin is up next. You can do it!
Her opponent is Asaka Narumi.
Nicknamed the Beautiful Assassin, she
peppers her flashy show with lethal attacks!
I'm sure it'll be a different kind
of fight than the one we observed.
Next time: Feelings About Victory!
Be careful, Kourin!
Her opponent is a cornerstone
of AL4. My heart's pounding!
They both look like fierce
opponents, don't they?