It's nonsense. Absolute nonsense!
Excuse me?!
How can you have fun doing this?!
This is your school, isn't it?
Everyone here is your friend... your comrade!
Especially Miss Emi and Miss Mai!
That's right! Rekka, wake up!
Stop doing these terrible things!
We're your friends! And so is
everyone else at this school!
Friends?
Friends...
Comrades? School...
Rekka?
What's so funny?!
I'll tell you.
I didn't come to this school
because I wanted to.
Moreover, I have no comrades here.
And I need no friends.
Rekka?
Couldn't you hear me?
I said I don't have any friends.
That's why I'm...
...going to Reverse everyone!
Did you hear me?
I have no comrades.
And no friends, either.
No friends?! Of course you do!
Miss Emi and Miss Mai!
Rekka...
I didn't come to this school
because I wanted to.
Ultra-rare Concert
School?!
Miyaji Academy, the same as me.
I'm Rekka of Ultra-rare.
I don't wanna go to school with normal kids!
You're not normal, so the point
is to learn what normal is.
Throwing a tantrum won't get you out of it.
Takuto's already arranged everything.
It'll be fun having friends your own age.
Friends?
Me?
Rekka Tatsunagi
I'm Rekka Tatsunagi, and I start here today.
Let's be friends, okay?
It's Rekka!
I wonder if I can get her autograph...
She's as cute as on TV!
How annoying... What am I, a panda?!
Say, why don't we invite Tatsunagi to go
to the crepe stand with us on the way home?
Good idea!
But if we go with an idol, we'll be mobbed!
I see... You're probably right.
Yeah, let's not ask her. If there
was a panic, we'd get blamed for it.
Oh no!
Forget it. Let's throw
that idea out the window.
School and classes were boring.
And I couldn't make a single friend.
Over there! Look over there!
Then... Then what are those two to you?!
I'm jealous that you even get
to go to the same school as...
I mean, they seem like wonderful friends!
Friend
Rekka! We've always been together, remember?
And we did our best creating
the Cardfight Club!
Excuse me...
What? You want my autograph? Or a handshake?
Neither.
We were thinking about
starting a Cardfight Club...
Cardfight Club?
I'm Emi, Aichi Sendou's younger
sister. And this is...
I'm Mai Tobita.
Aichi Sendou's younger sister?
Aichi said that you're really
strong, Miss Tatsunagi.
So... I'd be really happy if we could
create a Cardfight Club together!
Me too!
Well... I guess I'd be willing to hang out
with you when I'm not busy with work...
Yay!
What? Does it make you that happy?
Of course!
Miss Tatsunagi...
I look forward to working with you.
Okay, yes, I did have comrades
in the Cardfight Club.
That ain't all! I would've given
anything to be in the same club...
No, I mean... Aren't they your friends?!
I don't have any friends.
Rekka...
Now you've seriously ticked me off!
I'm seriously gonna crush you to the max!
Kamui, don't!
Those aren't the feelings of the real Rekka.
After all, Rekka would never
say things like that to us!
That's right. She was Reversed into a bad girl!
Turn her back into the original Rekka!
Please, Kamui!
S-Sure...
M-Miss Emi really is an angel!
Just watch, Rekka!
I'm totally, seriously gonna turn you
back the way you were to the max!
Go for it!
I think you're gonna be Reversed first.
The great Kamui stands and draws!
Go! Burning fire! Roaring thunder!
The great Kamui break rides the furious
Strongest Beast Deity, Ethics Buster Extreme!
Its power increases to 13000!
Ethics Buster's break ride skill!
Call!
Hatred Chaos attacks!
Ethics Buster!
Just one more... Please!
Extreme attacks!
Ethics Buster's break ride skill...
Hatred Chaos and Ethics Buster stand!
Then Riot Horn stands with its own skill.
Guard!
Perfect guard!
Twin drive check!
If he draws a grade 1 or higher card...
...he can stand one more time!
Max stands. Second check.
Hatred Chaos attacks!
Guard.
Ethics Buster attacks!
Guard!
Three cheers for Rekka!
Now do you recognize Rekka's power?!
RRP, yo!
Reiji... Eiji...
This is boring!
What's that, you brat?!
I said this was boring.
There's still time before Aichi Sendou
gets back from camping...
I wanted this to be a little more fun.
There's still time before Aichi Sendou
gets back from camping...
I wanted this to be a little more fun.
Jerk!
Are you sayin' I'm not a worthy opponent?!
I'll fight too!
Even if Kamui loses...
Even if Kamui loses, I'll turn
you back to normal, Rekka!
That's right! I'll fight too!
Miss Emi...
It's not like I've lost yet...
Th-That's right!
What are you saying?!
This fight isn't over yet!
Besides, you two are hostages
to lure Aichi Sendou here!
Hostages?
Anyway,
all you have to do is be quiet over there.
I'm not afraid of being Reversed.
More important than that,
I hate the thought of you not
turning back to normal, Rekka!
Enough! Shut your mouth!
That's strange.
Certainly, Miss Emi is right.
If you want to lure Brother Aichi to you,
it doesn't matter whether Miss Emi
is Reversed or not, right?
I'm not saying that it's okay
for you to be Reversed!
In fact...
It's more convenient for you to have
cooperative Rekka Corps soldiers
than stubborn hostages, isn't it?
That's what I think.
And there's no way it didn't
cross your mind too.
Shut up! I didn't ask for your opinion!
Rekka...
You sure know how to annoy a girl.
But if that's what you really want,
I'll bring this to an end!
Stand and draw!
Well, now the orchestra
door has been opened!
Come on down...
Cleanup Celestial, Ramiel "Reverse"!
Rekka's raging fire cross break ride!
Arabhaki in the Damage Zone
goes to my hand.
In exchange, I put one card from
my deck into the Damage Zone.
I call Arabhaki!
Here I go.
Ramiel "Reverse"...
...Limit Break!
Darkness temptation!
I choose two rear-guard units
that have "Celestial" in their names...
...and lock them!
I entrust the power of angels who have
fallen into darkness to three guardian angel units.
I'm not done.
What?!
Move your Extreme that's in the
Damage Zone into the Drop Zone.
In exchange, choose one of your rear-guard
cards and put it in the Damage Zone.
Shoot!
Go, Sariel!
Guard!
Ramiel "Reverse" attacks!
Perfect guard with Beast Deity, Solar Falcon!
Twin drive...
First check.
Second check.
Draw trigger.
I give the power to Ramiel...
...and draw one card.
Ramiel!
Guard!
Turn end.
It can't be!
Rekka!
This doesn't look good...
No, Rekka will be fine!
WBF, yo!
I was right.
I finally figured it out.
What?
You don't wanna Reverse
Miss Emi and Miss Mai, do you?
You won't lay a hand on
those two, who are dear to you.
W-What?!
Kamui, what do you mean?
This jerk... I mean,
Rekka thinks of you two as friends,
from the bottom of her heart.
So you're safe, even now.
Wrong!
It's because you're hostages...
Rekka...
Vanguard doesn't lie.
When your attack before didn't
go through, you were relieved.
Why was that?
You're wrong...
The curtains are frilly!
Cute!
You like them?
Yeah! Right, Mai?
Yeah, they're pretty!
I'll bring some flowers!
I'll bring stuffed animals!
Wrong...
You two are hostages...
Rekka...
Wrong...
Wrong! Wrong!
Attack!
Damage check!
I lost!
Don't worry about it, Emi.
Miss Tatsunagi's love love
ride is cute, isn't it?
Maybe I'll add something to mine too...
Yeah, let's see...
How about "lovely ride"?
Cute!
And you can do "pretty ride," Mai.
That's great!
Lovely ride!
Nice!
You try it too, Mai.
Sure!
Pretty ride!
Um... thank you, Miss Tatsunagi.
Thank you!
Um...
Would you stop calling me
"Miss Tatsunagi"? "Rekka" is fine.
Rekka...
Rekka!
Wrong... Those two are...
Those two are...
Rekka!
Kamui, Rekka is suffering! Help her!
Right! I'll break through
her wall of delusion!
I'll get her friendship back!
That's what Vanguard is about!
The great Kamui stands and draws!
I call Beast Deity, Max Beat!
Hatred Chaos attacks!
Sariel intercepts! Nociel!
With Nociel's skill,
I exchange a card in my hand
with one from the Damage Zone.
Ethics Buster!
Guard!
I won't lose to the likes of you!
Ethics Buster Extreme!
Guard!
I won't lose... I won't lose...
I won't lose!
Twin drive...
First check!
With Extreme's skill, Max stands.
Max's Counterblast.
Hatred Chaos stands!
Second check!
Max stands.
And then...
...Ethics Buster stands!
With a boost from Max Beat, Ethics Buster...!
Here I go! Wake up, friendship!
Special friend fire crush!
Why?! Why is my Angel Feather...
Miss Emi! Miss Mai!
Rekka!
CB, yo...
I can't believe it...
Rekka!
Rekka, are you okay?!
Huh? Emi? Mai?
What am I doing here?
Rekka!
Thank goodness!
What?! What's wrong, you two?
You! We're gonna take our Rekka back!
Yeah!
Look at that beautiful sight, Nagisa.
Now that's a flower garden.
I was right. This academy
is a perfect fit for you!
Forget it! I'm going to Hitsue,
the same school as Kamui!
What a pain! We've gotta
beat these guys, too?
What was that?!
What?
We'll explain later.
Let's take these punks down!
Okay! Let's go, Emi and Mai!
Right!
I'm gonna beat all you jerks!
Here I go!
Rekka's...
...love love ride!
Lovely ride!
Pretty ride!
The great Kamui rides Max Beat!
All's well that ends well!
AWEW, yo!
You guys...
I mean, it's fine, but...
Kamui!
M-Miss Emi!
Thank you so much for today!
I-It was nothin'!
Kamui?
What's with him?
Who knows?
That's right! I have to tell
Brother what happened today!
Kourin?
Boy, we had a heck of a time with Rekka
in the middle school division just before!
Kourin?
I'm done hesitating.
Kamui! Thank you so much!
You were great, Kamui!
I bet Mai and Rekka are grateful, too!
We finally got through the traffic
jam and are almost at Miyaji Academy.
The school seems different than usual...
Is that Kamui over there?
And Kourin?
Next time: Countdown to Despair!
What? What's going on?