I won't give up. Not as
long as there's a chance!
No trigger.
I win.
Mitsusada...
Mitsu...sada...
Well, Yuri...
Let's paint the world in darkness together.
Yes. As you command, Your Imperial Majesty.
So you bought a raincoat
and a large backpack...
Um... what else?
An extra pair of sneakers.
Why another pair?
We're only gonna be campin' for three days.
Just in case it suddenly rains, and
her shoes get soaked during athletics.
A juvenile delinquent wannabe like
you probably needs five or six pairs.
Excuse me?! Three pairs are plenty!
You need three pairs...
And now, our Vanguard segment.
Dr. O, the VF High School Championship
is almost upon us, isn't it?
Oh, yes, it certainly is! And
I couldn't be m-o-re excited!
VF High School Championship
Fukuhara High, led by Ren Suzugamori,
is heavily favored to win,
but you never know when someone will become
a new hero and star. That's Vanguard!
Ren Suzugamori...
I wish we didn't have to go camping!
I wanted to go all out fightin' tough
opponents at the VF High School Championship!
There'll be a next time, Naoki.
Come on, we've got more shopping to do.
Right.
And the other contender is Leon Souryu,
who uses the legendary Aqua Force clan.
He's certainly being watched
with keen interest.
VF High School Championship
Good luck, everyone.
Let's go, Sendou!
Oh, right!
He refuses to meet me?!
Why, for heaven's sake?!
Has he taken ill? Or something
along those lines?
I appreciate your concern. But that's not it.
Right now, prior to the VF High School
Championship, is a very important time for Leon.
So I hope you'll leave him alone.
There are a lot of people like you.
Fighters who want to make a name
for themselves by challenging Leon.
Well, that's what you say, but perhaps
Leon Souryu is hiding from me?
Because my Megacolony is so fearsome...
Yeah, that's right!
The legendary Aqua Force,
I'd wager it doesn't stand a chance against
the full moon-like brilliance of my bugs.
No one's stronger than you, Bro!
Dark Dimensional Combination!
Reversed Daiyusha
Attack!
Guard!
Get 'er, Bro!
You're doing well.
You blocked my attacks not
only twice, but three times.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry for being a
woman who doesn't know her place.
What's this? When did I ever call you that?
I never said anything like that.
Bro never said that.
You've got some nerve!
There it is! That's what I'm talking about!
What the heart thinks, the mouth speaks!
Here I go!
Actually, most of that was
just to get you riled up.
Sorry.
No.
As the eldest, I'm responsible for any
crudities my younger brothers utter.
Now, come and get me!
You impudent female!
Bro!
You make me want to apologize.
It looks like you're actually good people.
I mean, you're all so close...
N-No, my Megacolony is a den of evil!
It's outrageous to call me a good person!
Attack!
Cobalt Wave Dragon! Marine Blue Splash!
I'm shocked!
Bro!
My Megacolony will never perish.
But I'll let you off the hook today.
Thank you.
Retreat!
Bro!
Yeesh...
Jillian!
Sharlene. Where's Leon?
Shhh.
He's mentally focusing.
He said he absolutely has to
win the tournament this time.
Leon...
Say, Sharlene...
Will we have to live on this
island for the rest of our lives?
Of course not!
Look!
If you ask the birds to take
you with them, it'll work out!
Sharlene, you should really grow up.
Then... Then ask the fish...
You're a dummy, aren't you?
We really are stuck here.
Jillian...
I'm sorry, Jillian! If only
I weren't so stupid...
You're not.
You're not, Sharlene!
I'm the one who's stupid!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Jillian!
It's all right.
Leon!
This island has a legend.
Legend?
Yeah. It says the Souryu child
will take us, the Souryu
tribe, to the free world.
So...
...both of you, smile.
The revival of Aqua Force and the
restoration of the Souryu tribe...
We've been relying on Leon for everything.
But we can't afford to keep doing it.
As expected, my greatest
enemy is Ren Suzugamori.
Unless...
No. Whoever it is, I have to win.
That's the mission of the Souryu child.
That's my mission.
Huh?
I messed up again.
We're just not as good at
making them as Leon!
What are you doing?
Leon!
This is...
When we were little, you would
make these boats to cheer us up,
so now it's our turn...
Since you're exhausted,
we thought we'd try to do
something to make you happy.
But we can't make a decent
one between the two of us...
You're doing your best all by yourself,
and there's nothing we can do for you.
I'm sorry.
Jillian... Sharlene...
That's no good.
Leon?
Thinking I have to win...
It seems I've been too self-absorbed.
Smile for me, Jillian and Sharlene.
The three of us are Souryu
children. We'll fight together.
Leon!
I'll do my best!
I'm thrilled that you're letting
us practice fighting with you.
Sharlene, you brought that along?
It'll be my good luck charm!
And I know you have yours too!
What's wrong with that?
Who are you?!
Oh, come on! It's me!
Me!
You don't mean anything to them, Ali.
How rude!
When a girl meets me once,
she never forgets me.
I remember them now!
Team Genius...
We haven't seen you since VF Circuit.
Are you...
...strong?
I'll make the introduction.
This is Kenji Mitsusada,
an SIT fighter like us.
He's dying to fight you.
Kenji Mitsusada?
Forget it!
Right before the tournament is
a very important time for Leon.
He's going to train now!
Then this is perfect.
Our friend here has beaten
Ren Suzugamori before.
You've beaten Ren Suzugamori?
I hope you're up for a match.
That's strange. Where did
my sister and Koutei go?
And they haven't answered my texts...
Where did they go?!
And I thought I'd get the
chance to fight Leon...
I like you, my strong-willed bambina.
Yeah, you really are my type.
Leon...
I promise you I'll win!
Please watch me!
Those two are cute, aren't they?
They're Leon's teammates,
as well as childhood friends and some of the
few remaining descendants of the Souryu tribe.
During the VF Circuit, no matter what,
those two never left his side.
But what about this time?
You have fine subjects.
They're not "subjects."
Oh. I guess I got the wrong idea.
Kenji Mitsusada, a.k.a. the Emperor,
I'm looking forward to seeing just
what kind of fight you've got for me.
I'm looking forward to this, too...
Souryu child.
Leon Souryu...
Stand up, Vanguard!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Advance Party Brave Shooter.
Dimensional Robo, Daimagnum.
Dimension Police...
Stand up, Vanguard!
Bubble Edge Dracokid!
Acorn Master.
Stand up, Vanguard!
I go first. Draw.
I ride Dimensional Robo, Daitiger.
Draw.
I ride...
...Wheel Assault!
Call.
Mercenary Brave Shooter.
Attack!
Wheel Assault!
I see.
So this is the legendary Aqua Force...
That's right. It's a deck that's been handed
down to those of us in the Souryu tribe.
The Souryu tribe, eh?
That's a "tribe" in name only. You're
one step away from extinction.
Historically...
...small, weak nations are fated to be
crushed underfoot by large, strong nations.
With that in mind...
...how long are you going
to cling to your legend?
Don't insult the Souryu tribe!
I'm just talking about reality.
You, an all-but-extinct king,
are in battle with me,
the emperor of an empire!
Draw.
Ride!
Dimensional Robo, Daiheart.
Call.
Counterblast.
I attack with a boost from Daimagnum.
No guard.
Check...
Daiheart's power is 13000!
And this brings forth another skill.
Your tribe...
Your clan...
...are powerless, unable
to bring forth anything.
You're about to realize that.
Dimensional Robo, Daiheart's
skill is activated.
I take two Daiyusha cards from my hand
and move them to the Soul.
And then...
I'm sure this will be passed down from
generation to generation, for eternity.
Tyrannus, who claims the sparkling
crown in the darkness!
Superior crossride!
Dark Dimensional Robo...
..."Reversed" Daiyusha!
What?!
Since there's a Daiyusha in the Soul,
its power increases to 13000.
It's unfortunate,
but it can only make its debut this turn.
Assuming you keep riding properly,
your next turn will be a grade 2,
with only about 10000 power.
And the next one will be a grade 3,
with 11000 power at best.
Each time it comes to your turn,
you'll experience the despair
of falling short of the mark.
Even though his opponent's
Vanguard is still grade 1,
he managed to crossride
to "Reversed" Daiyusha.
Brilliant.
I feel an unusual wind coming from that unit.
In fact, I sense its power.
What is this?! I'm scared!
King of the jungle darkness!
Use your sharp fangs that can crush anyone...
...to devour the weak!
I ride...
...School Punisher, Leo-pald "Reverse"!
What?! What is that unit?!
You're cute when you're shocked!
Show me more expressions, bambina!
I'm going to keep winning with this unit.
It's a logical necessity.
Are you worried?
But instead of your subjects, maybe you had
better be concerned for your own welfare,
Souryu king.
Legends aren't necessary
during a war-torn era.
Power is!
And that's what I have!
Well? You can feel the grief
of a minor nation, can't you?
And right about now, your subjects...
Leo-pald "Reverse"! Obsidian sword!
I can't...
Leon!
Leon...
If we lose,
Leon will...
The three of us are Souryu
children. We'll fight together.
Leon...
Looks like it's over.
Jillian! Sharlene!
Watch from there.
Yes, Your Imperial Majesty.
As you command.
The loser becomes a subject of the winner.
You see the same thing occurring
in history from time to time.
It's only right. A logical
consequence, don't you agree?
So, tell me.
How does it feel to become a king
without even a single citizen to rule?
Your power, and Aqua Force too,
are so close to being annihilated.
Won't you become my subject?
Imbecile! Aqua Force
will never be destroyed!
I am the Souryu child!
Leon Souryu. Cease struggling and surrender.
In the face of absolute power,
everything is useless... powerless... in vain!
I'll be the one who decides
if it's useless or not!
It's a shame.
I'll just have to destroy you with my power!
The fierce battle between Mitsusada and Leon
is approaching its end.
Next time: Tight-knit Ship!
Take this, tyrant...
This wind that I've stirred up!