This may seem sudden, but your world...
...is going to be destroyed.
This is unavoidable.
The world will be dominated by Link Joker.
I hope you all spend the scant remainder
of your peaceful days in despair.
For a world ruled by Link Joker,
despair is a perfect fit.
Takuto Tatsunagi...
I didn't know he was so evil!
We should've shut 'im down last time we met.
The Earth invaded by Link Joker...
And the majority of Cardfighters
have turned into the enemy.
This is serious trouble.
I've sensed that something was wrong
for a while now, and this must be it.
Kai... chose to be Reversed...
Leon!
Aichi Sendou...
I'm going off to beat Toshiki Kai!
I saw Takuto Tatsunagi's message.
Earth is in imminent danger.
There's only a little time left.
I understand the logic, but what can we do?
The only way to cure someone who's been
Reversed is through a Vanguard fight!
A Vanguard fight...
If you beat a Reversed person in a
Vanguard fight, they'll return to normal.
In other words, we must defeat Kai...
Let's go, Aichi Sendou.
...Right.
But before that, Aichi Sendou...
...you must fight me.
This is no time for that...
Fight.
If you say so, Leon...
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
Each One's Determination
I ride Future Liberator, Llew!
Draw.
I ride Mercenary Brave Shooter!
Attack!
I ride Blaster Blade Liberator!
I was right...
Leon?
Sendou... It seems you don't realize
it, but your heart is locked.
My heart is locked?
The usual hot wind didn't
rise from Blaster Blade.
You're troubled by the
thought of fighting Kai.
Your heart is locked!
Until you unlock it,
victory will not be yours!
Troubled?
Me?
There's no value in fighting
beside you right now.
Leon Souryu!
Ishida?
What do you intend to do?! Ishida!
Do I not want to fight Kai?
Even under these circumstances, when beating
Kai is the only way to save the world?
You made him do it, Aichi.
Kai wishes to fight me?
You can't avoid that fight.
It should be a good one... right, Aichi?
I started playing Vanguard
after Kai led me to it.
For the longest time, my
goal was to catch up to him.
And the one who drove him to this was... me?
That was never my intention...
Kai never relied on anyone else, just stuck to
getting stronger on his own. And now he's...
Wait, Leon Souryu!
Sendou's teammates...
I'm Naoki Ishida.
Ishida, you delinquent, don't do this...
What are you talkin' about, Granny Glasses?
What do you want?
O-Oh, yeah. You might be right.
But you didn't have to
talk to Aichi like that!
They're not going to wait.
I know that! That's why...
...I'm goin' with you!
I'll fight in Aichi's place!
Wha...?
You? Out of the question.
I already got Reversed!
The only way to bring a Reversed person
back to normal is to beat 'em in a fight.
After hearin' you talk, it all made sense.
I dragged Aichi down that last time...
I don't wanna be a burden anymore.
Especially now that Aichi's miserable,
I wanna do somethin'!
Show me your skill.
Sure!
Stand up, my Vanguard!
Stand up, Vanguard!
I ride Dragon Dancer, Agnes!
I ride Accelerated Command!
Vowing Sword Dragon attacks!
Drive trigger check!
I got a critical trigger!
Tetra-drive Dragon's skill is activated!
It receives +6000 power!
Go, Tetra-drive Dragon!
6 to 3. You were spanked.
That's Leon Souryu for you.
A wannabe is no challenge to him.
Darn it! One more time!
I like your spirit...
Bring it on!
Fellow underground fighters,
I take it you saw Takuto Tatsunagi's message.
It's easier on us, since we
don't play in the limelight.
But our love for Cardfights
is the same as theirs.
And this is the greatest
threat to Cardfighting ever!
It's time for underground
fighters to rise, too.
We're gonna beat 'em!
Yeah!
Miwa?
I see. You're going to join us.
Jun Mutsuki, I'm not going
to let you interfere.
Miwa! Don't tell me you're Reversed...
Who do you think Reversed me?
Somebody strong enough to beat you...
Don't tell me it was Kai?!
A strong fighter like Toshiki Kai...
I don't know how he got Reversed,
but I imagine you tried to stop
him and got Reversed yourself.
Because you're Kai's friend,
the only one he trusts.
But tell me, Miwa!
Why are you helping Kai?!
He's obviously mistaken about all this!
I know that...
Then why?!
Because it's Kai.
He's always alone...
What's the harm in just
staying by his side?
I see.
Kai and I are neither friends nor rivals...
We just pit our skills against each other.
Kai chose solitude in order to become strong.
He doesn't try to get close to anyone...
But you're different from me.
If you're a true friend,
you should be able to stop him from
going down the wrong path somehow.
I have one answer...
I won't let anyone get in Kai's way.
Fine. I'll start by bringing
you to your senses, Miwa.
Stand up, Vanguard!
Larva Beast, Zeal!
Lizard Soldier, Conroe.
Kagero...
Kai's deck?
That's right. Being Reversed
has made me even stronger...
And I'm going to use this
to Reverse you guys.
Join me...
Jun.
I ride...
Eye of Destruction, Zeal!
I ride Dragon Monk, Gojo!
Conroe moves back!
I ride Devourer of Planets, Zeal!
Call.
Attack!
I ride...
Berserk Dragon!
Berserk's Counterblast!
I retire Vipple!
No grade 3s, but...
Call!
With its skill, I draw one card.
My victory is certain.
A bluff like that doesn't
work on underground fighters.
Conroe retires! Counterblast!
I add this guy to my hand.
And then I call!
Nehalem, Berserk Dragon, attack!
I ride Original Savior, Zero!
And then I call.
Attack!
Turn end.
3 to 4. We've pretty much been dead even.
Did you know that in a fight, the
one with stronger feelings wins?
In that case, I'm going to win.
You're only thinking of Kai,
while I want to save Kai, you,
the underground fighters,
Cardfighters, and everything.
The important point is the
depth of the feelings.
I'll show you mine.
Squirming black dragon
slashing in the darkness,
bestow despair upon him with
your fangs of destruction!
I ride Dauntless Dominate
Drive Dragon "Reverse"!
This is a Reverse unit...
I call Calamity Tower Wyvern!
Soulblast!
I draw one card!
Dominate Drive Dragon!
Here I go!
Ruler of darkness, use your accursed roar
to return everything to nothingness!
Dauntless "Reverse's" Limit Break!
I lock Gojo!
Okay, here I go!
Dominate Drive!
Guard!
Dauntless "Reverse" attacks!
Drive trigger check.
Skill activated!
If a grade 1 or higher Kagero
is drawn during a drive check,
a grade 1 or lower rear-guard
unit can be retired!
Eye of Destruction, Zeal!
And +3000 power!
Second check.
Skill activated one more time.
Gigabolt retires!
On top of that, +3000 power!
Next. Nehalem!
Guard!
Turn end.
It hurts to have had two
rear-guard units retired...
But now the real fight begins.
I have this!
Draw.
I have no intention of preaching reason,
but as we're underground fighters here,
there's one thing I'm sure of.
Miwa! You're making a mistake!
Beast of destruction that was born from
the Big Bang, along with the universe!
Show your power of the stars here!
Break ride!
Galactic Beast, Zeal!
Dauntless "Reverse" loses 5000 power!
The greater the gap between power,
the easier it is for an attack to hit.
Your damage is 4.
Admit defeat, Miwa.
Let's go together to bring Kai to his senses!
You're not interfering with Kai or me!
In that case, we'll go 'til I beat you!
Call!
Plus Galactic Beast, Zeal's Limit Break!
Black hole power that swallows all light!
For three of your rear-guard units,
a total power loss of 3000!
Down 3000 power...
Zero attacks!
Guard!
I longed for the relationship you guys had.
So I won't... I won't let
it be twisted like this!
Go back to what you two were, Miwa!
Galactic Beast, Zeal attacks!
Perfect guard.
Still, you just used up the
last card in your hand...
You can't guard for my next attack...
In other words, if I draw a
critical trigger here, I win!
Can you draw one?
I'll show you!
I'm going to bring you and Kai back!
Drive trigger check!
Still one more!
Second check!
This is the difference between
my feelings and yours.
Vipple attacks!
I'll protect myself and bet
everything on the next turn!
Jun, I won't let you even reach Kai.
Final Turn!
Final limit break!
I lock Calamity Tower!
Here I come.
Nehalem! Attack Vipple!
An intercept unit...
Dauntless Dominate Dragon
"Reverse," final attack!
No guard...
Drive trigger check!
Skill activated!
Second check!
Critical trigger!
I give the power to Dominate Drive and
the critical to Dauntless "Reverse"...
I won't give up.
I'll stake everything on this trigger!
Critical trigger...
You lose...
It's over, Kai.
If you wish to fight Aichi,
I'll eliminate anyone that
would get in your way.
Jun!
Jun...
Jun, I'll leave these guys to you.
Count on it.
One more time!
No matter how many times Ishida
loses, he's not giving up.
That spirit...
This is how strongly he feels about Sendou...
Armor Break Dragon, attack
Tetra-drive Dragon!
Yes! You have him on the ropes with 5 damage!
Tetra-drive Dragon attacks!
That's enough. At your level,
you would only be a hindrance.
Remain here.
I still can't be of any use to Aichi...?
Wait, please!
I want to fight together with you, too!
It may be impossible for Ishida alone,
but if both of us go,
maybe we'll get somewhere!
For Sendou's sake!
Granny Glasses... I mean, Shingo...
Me too! I'm asking you one more time!
You said your name was Naoki Ishida, yes?
I'm leaving Aichi Sendou to you two.
Leaving Aichi to us?
Is that some kind of approval?
Your feelings moved the heart
of that boy over there.
Your hot wind isn't bad.
Shingo, help me here.
Training. I gotta get strong, and fast!
I'm gonna give form to the deck
I saw in my head during that fight!
Sure thing, Ishida!
Stand up, Vanguard!
My heart is locked...
Hey, Granny Glasses...
Who's that?!
We can't let the whole burden fall on Aichi.
Especially me!
Ishida, you delinquent...
Kai... Why?
And Miwa too...
Next time: Recapture Miyaji Academy!
Recapture Miyaji Academy!
Let's go, Shingo! From now on,
don't leave my side!
That's my line!