Before being Reversed, you acted
as Kai's beneficial brakes.
That's the person...
...I'm going to bring back!
After all...
I'm your friend, too!
Kai!
She did it! Boss Lady won!
Yeah!
She did it!
I...
What is this... discouragement?
It just means you thought a little
too much about your friend.
You'll get better soon.
Yeah.
Thought too much... about my friend?
That's an embarrassing expression
if I've ever heard one...
Look, guys, I don't remember anything,
but don't try to snow job me with cheap praise!
Fight me, Kai!
Aichi...
Kai...
Why? Why did you choose...
...to have Link Joker Reverse you, Kai?!
Psyqualia...
The power to hear the voice of the
deck and see what's going to happen...
Kai rejected the idea of
Ren and me using Psyqualia.
He didn't depend on a special power,
but had faith that he'd get
stronger through his own efforts.
And yet... Why?
The Two Leaders
I saw it that day.
The absolute strength that
I'd been pursuing single-mindedly.
And I wasn't the one who had it.
That's right.
You were shown the strength of those two,
and felt impatience, yearning, envy, and fear.
You were caught up in emotions that
you'd never felt before and became unhinged.
You're right. I fought strong people and became
stronger myself through experience.
I believed that was the only way
to become the strongest of all.
But...
...you and Ren embraced the
power called Psyqualia.
And then you two, who had chosen the
path that I'd rejected all along,
obtained strength that surpassed me.
Your psyche wavered...
...because you'd thought that accepting
an alien power was weakness.
But those two, who obtained the strange power,
had become stronger, far stronger than you.
Aichi, like someone who can drink
water from the sand of a dry desert,
you get stronger every time you fight.
You even turn your mistakes into sustenance
and continue to grow like there's no tomorrow.
And how did you feel about
that strength of Aichi Sendou?
Longing, jealousy, and fear.
That's why...
...I accepted the alien power of Link Joker.
To become the strongest...
With this power that I've taken on,
I'm going to beat you and Ren
to prove that I'm the strongest!
You're...
You're making...
...a huge mistake!
Kai, every time you win a fight
with the power of Link Joker,
someone becomes Reversed.
As a result, this world may
be swallowed up by Link Joker.
You don't care what happens
to everyone... to the world?!
I'm interested in becoming
stronger. That's all.
Kai...
Wake up and smell the coffee, Kai!
He's ignorin' me?!
That's Reverse's fault too.
But as always, he isn't
good at expressing himself.
Even though I'm out of Reverse's
spell, I know how he feels.
Kai's thinking that he's
gone beyond good and evil.
He's not focused on anything
but getting stronger.
That's awful...
Dang it! I know how he
feels. I get it, but...
Kai...
The only thing to do is beat you.
Humans are weak.
No matter how they try to
stick to their firm beliefs,
they'll waver, get hurt, be tormented.
And that's where they can
be taken advantage of.
Since they've got a strong will,
they can't surrender.
They don't notice the cracks forming there.
Humans are such fools.
Aichi, please help Kai!
I've been waiting for this moment.
Aichi, I'm going to beat you,
then move forward.
So I can become stronger than anyone,
the strongest of all!
Stand up,
the
Vanguard!
Holy Squire, Enide!
White Night Fenrir!
This is Kai's Link Joker deck.
I ride Little Liberator, Marron!
Enide moves!
Ride!
Hollow Twin Blades, Binary Star!
Fenrir moves back.
Attack!
Turn end.
My turn! I draw!
That's right. This is where it started.
With this Blaster Blade...
He introduced me to Blaster Blade that day.
Kai brought me together with Vanguard.
When I was lost, when it looked like
I was going in the wrong direction,
Kai was the one who brought me to my senses.
I am who I am now because of Kai.
I've been able to dedicate my
heart and soul to Vanguard.
I've made irreplaceable friends.
I've made a place that's important to me.
It's all thanks to Kai.
So now it's my turn.
Stand up, my avatar!
I ride...
...Blaster Blade Liberator!
Kai...
I swear I'll get you back to normal!
Kai... I swear to the Kai from that day...
...that I'll win this fight!
Call! Please, Marron!
Blaster Blade!
Turn end.
Ride!
Strike Star-vader, Krypton!
Attack.
Turn end.
Aichi and Toshiki Kai, an awesome match-up
of Cardfighters goin' at it like this...
I would've preferred to see them
fight at the national championship.
Brother, please win!
Aichi...
Come back to us, Kai!
For all of Kai's friends, who care about him...
...I'll win!
Give me power!
Your proud, noble white wings!
Ride!
Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
Marron moves. Call!
Phallon attacks Radon!
Guard.
Gancelot attacks with a boost from Enide!
Drive trigger, check!
Critical trigger!
I give the power to Escrad and
the extra critical to Gancelot!
All right! Critical trigger!
Damage trigger, check.
Second check...
I got a heal trigger.
I give the power to Krypton
and heal 1 damage point.
He turned 180 with that heal trigger.
Enide's skill...
When a boosted attack hits, I can draw!
Escrad attacks Radon with
a boost from Marron!
No guard.
Turn end.
Fighting with Kai always
gives me butterflies,
but I don't feel that
sense of excitement now.
I didn't want to have this
kind of fight with him.
Remember, Kai!
Stand and draw.
Ride!
Star-vader, Infinite Zero Dragon!
Call!
Krypton! Mana Shot Star-vader, Neon!
Neon attacks Phallon!
Guard!
White Night boosts Infinite Zero!
No guard.
Check the drive trigger.
I got a critical trigger.
I give the power to Krypton and the
extra critical to Infinite Zero.
Now he gets a critical?!
White Night's skill.
I draw a card.
Krypton attacks Phallon!
Guard!
Turn end.
4 to 3!
He's made a comeback!
Until now, it was a perfect fight,
with both of them totally guarded.
But I've seen Brother Aichi
perform miracles before!
At a time like this, he always wins!
I'll bring you back to normal!
There was a time when I pursued strength
and became lost, but a leader guided me...
That was you, Kai!
Give me even more courage!
Your proud, noble white wings! Break ride!
Solitary Liberator, Gancelot!
It gets +10000 power! And three
rear-guard units each get +5000!
Escrad! Marron! Phallon!
I call May Rain Liberator, Bruno!
Gancelot attacks!
No guard.
Drive trigger, check!
Heal trigger! I add +5000 to the power
of Escrad and heal 1 damage point!
Escrad!
No guard.
Escrad's Counterblast!
I superior call Flame of Victory!
Bruno's skill, +3000 power!
5 damage! Only 1 more to go!
He has him on the ropes!
Go, Aichi!
Aichi...
Come back to us, Kai!
Kai, I'm going to put everyone's
feelings for you into this one attack!
Phallon attacks with a boost from Bruno!
Guard.
Turn end...
He couldn't finish him off...
It's okay! The damage is 3 to 5.
Brother still has the advantage.
I know he can do this!
That's right! Victory is
right before his eyes!
He's too quiet.
I don't think it'll be over
for Kai just like that.
Miwa...
Aichi, you showed me plenty of your strength.
In exchange, I'll show you the power
of Link Joker that I was given!
Beast of war that's come from another world,
seal the power of the entire army!
Break ride!
Star-vader, Infinite Zero Dragon!
Lock the rear-guards!
Infinite Zero gets +10000 power.
By locking units from the front
and back of different lines,
he protects against boosted
attacks and intercepts!
Neon moves.
I call Demon Claw Star-vader, Lanthanum
and Star-vader, Colony Maker!
Colony Maker's Counterblast!
I call one Star-vader unit of
grade 1 or lower from my deck.
Lanthanum!
Infinite Zero attacks with
a boost from Lanthanum!
Check the drive trigger.
I got a draw trigger.
I give the power to Colony Maker and draw.
Second check.
I got a critical trigger.
Double trigger!
Th-That's...
...Toshiki Kai.
I add +5000 to the power of Krypton
and give the extra critical to Infinite Zero.
He's strong... But that's Kai for you!
Shoot! Now Aichi is the one on the ropes!
Neon boosts.
Colony Maker attacks!
Oh no, you don't!
Guard!
He just has to block one more time!
Krypton attacks with a boost from Lanthanum!
I'm going to win!
Come, irreplaceable soul brothers!
Respond to my voice!
Sword Formation Liberator, Igraine!
Quintet Wall!
Turn end...
Yeah! He blocked it!
Now only 1 more damage!
Aich's gonna win this,
no doubt about it!
But... Sendou can only attack
from two columns.
What the heck, Granny Glasses?!
That ain't what you were sayin' before!
I-I'm just saying the truth!
Nope!
Knowing Brother Aichi, I'm sure he'll do it!
I'm going to win this turn.
I'm going to release Kai from that darkness!
It's impossible.
Your attacks won't get through.
It looks like I've surpassed you!
Aichi, the darkness is
going to swallow you up!
Aichi, your full power has reached me.
Kai...
And I can say that I've surpassed you.
I won't lose! I'll win this fight
and return the Reversed Kai to normal!
Next time: Beyond the Bond!
Beyond the Bond
I'm shouldering everyone's feelings!
Right now, I've attained a height
far greater than you even think.
And what's waiting for
you is chaotic darkness.