[Episode 9]
Let's start!
Hello! We're Dreamers!
We were finally pushed to this point.
I hope you're the last one.
Oh, you startled me! Hello.
- Hello.
Why Jae Hyun?
Our album is out,
and it's called "I Couldn't Forget You."
- He's our frontman.
- Yes, I'm the frontman, Seo Joon Oh.
Yes, and I'm the bass player,
Choi Tae Ho. It's nice to meet you.
Joon Oh!
She was murdered.
I saw it myself.
So, who murdered Yoon So Hee?
No!
Seo Joon Oh.
Choi Tae Ho was right.
He killed her.
No way. This is wrong. This isn't right--
Can't you see that this is important?
And, he had an accomplice.
She knew what Seo Joon Oh was doing
but she covered it up, and helped him.
Who was it?
All you have to do is tell them
what you saw. We saw the same thing!
You saw Seo Joon Oh kill her.
What?
Secretary Tae. What are you saying?
That accomplice...
is right here.
What are you saying, Secretary Tae?
Wait... Let go! Secretary Tae--
Ra Bong Hee, she was his accomplice.
Secretary Tae. Secretary Tae!
We must expose the truth.
I killed Tae Ho. That's the truth.
If we... happen to get back...
Everything we saw and heard here...
Let's remember it for what it is.
I'm not sure if this is
the right time to tell you this...
But since you found out already...
This might be a good time to hear it.
What is this about?
Do you remember your DUI incident?
- Thank you.
- Sure!
Hey! Joon Oh, sit down and drink.
Okay! Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'll be right here.
Okay. Okay. Sit.
- Choi Tae Ho! Ma'am, it's Tae Ho!
- Hello.
It's Tae Ho! You can't take pictures!
You can't take pictures of Tae Ho.
He's come to pick me up.
Here we go!
That was probably after
Shin Jae Hyun died
and when you were a complete mess.
Even after you were acquitted...
This was a time when your incidents
were on the news
on a daily basis.
That's why I wrote that article about
your DUI without a second thought.
But a long time after that incident...
I received some information
about Shin Jae Hyun's incident.
What information? What went wrong?
That's why we went back and investigated
again, and during that process...
I found out something.
You got into an accident while driving
and the person who reported
your accident...
was Choi Tae Ho.
Yes.
Seo Joon Oh, you said,
"I drank, but I didn't drink and drive."
Is it true you drove under the influence?
I drank, but I didn't drink and drive.
You were telling the truth.
But...
Why are you telling me this now?
When people offer to help you...
Accept it.
Returning to your original place
is your right.
The truth is...
I don't know what's right.
I'm not even sure if that's a fact
that's for my well-being.
I'm going in to rest.
- Rest well.
- Yes, you too.
Let me speak to Secretary Tae alone.
What do you want to say to someone
who claims you were an accomplice?
I wasn't an accomplice!
And Seo Joon Oh's not a murderer either.
Secretary Tae knows this better than
anyone else! He must have a reason--
Are you saying
he was threatened by someone?
Are you asking because
you really don't know?
You have no fear, Ra Bong Hee.
The statements that we collected so far
all point to Seo Joon Oh as the murderer.
In other words, your testimony was false.
When many lies come together...
I guess that becomes the truth.
How are you going to refute
all of the statements?
They outnumber you,
so how can you prove your claim?
Now that we have this much evidence...
You would have nothing to say
if you were sent to the prosecution.
You don't know how serious
perjury is, do you?
Don't run wild.
Behave yourself until I call you.
This is not right!
The reason Seo Joon Oh
has to be the murderer
and I have to be his accomplice...
It's because you think
Seo Joon Oh is dead!
There's no way he is still alive...
He's easy to blame, and everyone
will easily forget this way!
I don't have evidence
to refute your claim.
But I'll make sure to find Seo Joon Oh!
I'll find him...
And I'll make sure
to show you that you're wrong.
Did it not go well?
You can't be exhausted already.
If you are, we'll end up
falling into their trap.
I won't be exhausted
until we find Seo Joon Oh.
He must also be...
trying his best to come back.
How can I be exhausted?
I'm still just fine.
I'm okay.
Are you all right?
Do you feel sick again?
You can't throw up here.
I'd have to clean it up.
Good work today.
- You have a very good friend.
- Pardon?
You were a lot more relaxed
after seeing your friend.
But... Tae Ho Hang.
You know you can't change
anything you said now, right?
The testimony you gave today
will be used in court as well.
In other words, no matter
what you saw or heard
- the truth starts here.
- I know that!
I can go now, right?
Is something bothering you?
We didn't hear anything else
about Seo Joon Oh, right?
Yes, but why are you asking
about Seo Joon Oh? He's dead.
If he's dead,
aren't you going to find his body?
Should I look into it?
I can call. But, there's
a time difference. If they're sleeping...
Why are you getting mad at me? Seriously.
She always takes it out on me.
You scared me! What's wrong?
Why were you so startled?
No, it's nothing. Why are you up
so early? You should sleep more.
Why? What were you doing?
It's just, everything's on the ground.
I'm sure it was just the wind.
Hey!
- Where did he go?
- What's wrong?
I saw someone run by!
Everything's on the ground too.
It's strange.
Go. There was noise. Go and see.
No. You go.
I don't want to.
Damn it.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Wait...
Wait.
- What is it, Ki Joon?
- Ji Ah, I heard a message.
- What are you saying? It wasn't working!
- I just had a signal.
- Oh!
- See? You heard it! It's not just me!
- Hey!
- Wow!
- Hey, I hear it!
Wait! Wait a minute! Let me listen!
- What is it?
- CEO Hwang, we heard a message.
- Seriously?
- Yes!
- It's working?
- Yeah!
- It wasn't working yesterday.
- It's not working.
- Pardon?
- Let me see.
- It's not working.
Oh! I hear it! I hear it!
Wow, I heard it!
Wow, I hear it too!
Hey, but why is it buzzing so much?
Hey, we can't get a very good signal
here, so let's go somewhere else.
CEO Hwang, you speak Chinese, right?
- Hey, take this and go that way!
- Hurry!
- Can we talk for a second?
- Pardon?
You said you heard something
last night, didn't you?
I've been getting
a strange feeling around here.
Oh, was that yesterday?
After I left?
Did you check
Choi Tae Ho's body, by any chance?
Did you confirm that he's dead?
Ch... Choi Tae Ho--
We could be mistaken,
so let's not tell anyone else.
Let's look for him, just the two of us.
Wh... What is it saying?
High seas warning is in effect,
and they're going home--
Hey, how can they go? Listen. Listen.
Hold it higher. Hold it really high.
Requesting help.
What... What did you say?
There is someone here
on this deserted island! (In Chinese)
We are from Korea's
Legend Entertainment company.
- Help!
- Hurry!
Hey, just listen to what they're saying!
We should listen to what they're saying!
Why do you keep talking?
- You should listen before you talk!
- But...
No! No! Translate! Translate right now!
Geez, what the hell are you doing?
- Hey, why are you screaming?
- Okay, it's connected.
- Be quiet!
- Talk!
- He just told me to stop--
- You have to talk! They're leaving!
- I can't do this!
- Requesting help! (In Chinese)
- Help!
- There are people here on this island.
Captain, we're going back
with a full load of fish today!
I know. We have a full load.
We really hit the jackpot today.
That's right. We're so lucky.
But when are we going home?
Be quiet for a second.
Why? What is it?  What's that?
There are people on this deserted island!
What?
What? They're saying there are people
on a deserted island, aren't they?
Save us! Can you hear us?
Hey, I'm going to look for something
with Journalist Kim.
You two shouldn't split up.
Stay together, got it?
I'll be nearby, so if anything happens,
scream loudly. Okay?
Wait, what are you looking for?
- I'll tell you later, Ji Ah.
- Let's go.
Return safely.
What the heck is this?
We have to leave when we get a message,
so where is he going?
Let's not stay together like this.
We don't know where the boat will dock,
so let's split up and keep in touch.
They might not have heard us.
I don't know if there's any point.
I like that idea. It's better than
missing the opportunity.
Let's leave this bastard out.
Ki Joon, let's split up.
That side is where the sun rises,
and that side is where the sun sets.
I like that. It's easy to comprehend.
Which way do you want to go,
Manager Jung?
It's a boat.
It is. It must be nice.
They get to have fun on a boat.
While we're stuck over here.
Why is the boat coming this way?
- A boat?
- Why is it coming this way?
The boat's coming this way!
The boat is coming for us. They're coming
this way to save us, aren't they?
I think they're coming to save us.
Hey.
Right? They're coming for us!
It's our boat, isn't it?
Hey, go up there!
We're here! Send help quickly!
(In Chinese)
Help! Help!
Don't let them leave!
There are people here
on this deserted island! (In Chinese)
on this deserted island!
Gosh, I'm worried about those three.
They're big in size,
but they can't do anything right.
- What if they lose the radio?
- Hey, no way.
You should have gone instead.
You would have been better.
But why aren't you telling me
where Joon Oh and Journalist Kim went?
They'll be back soon.
Be patient.
You must be thirsty.
I'll bring some water.
Thank you.
Gosh, who knew I would eat
mushrooms here? I'm all grown up now.
I could get married.
Oh, are you back?
Where did she go?
Ji Ah!
Ha Ji Ah!
No way.
- Ji Ah! Ji Ah!
- Bong Hee!
- They're inside, right?
- Wait, I'm looking for...
There's a boat.
The boat is here to save us!
- A boat?
- Joon Oh!
- Manager Jung!
- Where are they? Where's Ji Ah?
The thing is, I was just looking for her.
Where are Joon Oh and Journalist Kim?
The thing is, I think someone
was here this morning
but I have a feeling it was Choi Tae Ho.
- Let's find Ji Ah.
- Yes, hurry!
- Ji Ah!
- Ha Ji Ah!
- I'm going crazy! There's no time!
- What if the boat leaves?
- Pardon?
They could easily leave without us
because of this weather.
Oh, Seo Joon Oh!
Bong Hee! Take Joon Oh to the beach.
I'll look for Ji Ah for a little longer.
- Yes, sure!
- And...
Even if we're a little late, please
don't let the boat leave without us.
Yes. I got it, Manager Jung!
Hey! Hey! Wait!
Thank you! Thank you!
Who are you?
Did you hear my message?
We sent that message?
You were lucky today. We don't usually
come here because of the strong waves.
Hurry up! We have to leave because
we're on a high seas weather alert!
Thank you! Thank you!
Hurry up and tell the kids to come here!
- Why?
- They have to leave due to weather.
Please wait! Please wait! Please wait!
There are others. There are others.
- No, there's no time!
- Please wait. There are others.
We're going to live. We're going to live.
We're going to live! We're going to live!
- There's a boat?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Yes!
We have to stop the boat from leaving!
They could be late, so I told Manger Jung
I'd keep the boat from leaving! Let's go!
- Wh... What about Ji Ah?
- About Ji Ah...
Manager Jung is looking for her!
Let's go!
Then I'll find Ki Joon and Ji Ah.
You two can go and hold the boat, okay?
- No!
I'll find Manager Jung. You two
can go ahead, okay? Hurry! Hurry!
- I can find them faster. I'll go.
- No! No!
No. No. Hurry!
- Secretary Tae.
- A boat! A boat is here!
Yes, we know!
You do? Then what are you
doing here? The boat is trying to leave!
The side the sun rises on!
The boat is on that side!
Oh, the side where the sun rises. There's
a high seas weather alert, so go! Hurry!
- Still...
- Hurry!
What are you doing? We have to go!
We have to go if we want to live!
- We'll wait for you! Okay?
- Journalist Kim!
No, go without me! Go!
I'll catch up to you!
- I'll keep them from leaving!
- The side the sun rises on!
The side the sun rises on!
Choi Tae Ho!
Hey.
Are you crazy? Have you gone insane?
Ji Ah was your girlfriend, you punk!
Not anymore.
She's not my girlfriend.
Tae Ho, kill me instead.
Ji Ah didn't do anything wrong, did she?
Tae Ho.
She didn't do anything wrong.
But there's something I want.
I...
want to have a good life too.
So you all need to die.
Ji Ah!
Geez, where are they?
- Tell them to hurry!
- Please wait!
CEO Hwang! Over here! We're here!
They are our guys! They're with us!
Hurry! Hurry!
I'm sorry!
- Help them so they can get on.
- Thank you!
- Hurry up and get on!
- Get on!
- Ki Joon! Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Be careful!
- Ji Ah, are you all right?
- Yes...
Ki Joon! Ki Joon, are you okay? Ki Joon.
Ki Joon. Ki Joon. Are you all right?
Yeah, of course I am. Isn't it obvious?
Geez, I wish they could have
come earlier. I almost died.
The side the sun rises on.
Did they get to the boat?
They got to the boat! Let's get going!
Leave our belongings. Let's get going.
Go now. If we leave Tae Ho alone,
we don't know what else he'll do.
- Go now. I'll follow you!
- Be careful.
Ki Joon and Ji Ah aren't here yet!
Tell them to wait a little longer!
Look here. If we don't leave now,
it'll be dangerous!
- What did he say?
- We have to leave now!
Hurry up and pull up the anchor!
We were on this island for four months!
We were here for four months!
For four months,
no one came to this island!
We were cold and hungry,
and no one came to find us!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and pull up the anchor!
- No!
- Joon Oh!
- What are you doing to us?
- Seo Joon Oh, it's dangerous! Let go!
Joon Oh!
No! No...
No.
Joon Oh!
- CEO Hwang! CEO Hwang!
- They're here!
They're here! They're here!
- Over here!
- Come back!
- We're here!
Hurry!
- They're coming! They're coming!
- We're going to live!
- CEO Hwang!
- A little further!
Ji Ah, come here!
Hold on to the rope!
Thank you! Thank you!
Ki Joon, what happened to your face?
Tae Ho tried to kill both of us. Without
Journalist Kim, we would have died!
- Right there!
- Ki Joon!
Ki Joon, where's Journalist Kim?
He said he'll come after dealing
with Tae Ho. Get on! Bong Hee!
Yes. Seo Joon Oh, hurry!
Ki Joon, I'll find Journalist Kim.
- Joon Oh!
- Seo Joon Oh! No!
No, let go! No! Seo Joon Oh!
- Hey, Bong Hee!
- Seo Joon Oh!
Journalist Kim!
Journalist Kim...
Instead of evidence...
I wanted to testify on your behalf...
- Hey, wait...
- We're in trouble.
Can you get up? Come on.
Are you all right? Journalist Kim.
- I'm... I'm sorry.
- Hey, why are you sorry?
The person who gave me the information...
was Yoon So Hee.
She agreed to reveal everything
in an interview...
Hey, don't talk to much.
Journalist Kim, don't talk, okay?
But she kept changing her mind...
I got on the plane
so I could convince her.
Okay. I understand. I got it.
Wait a minute.
The reason why Yoon So Hee
changed her mind...
I think it was because of CEO Jang.
What?
I'll talk to you when I get back.
What else could it be? There's only
one thing we would talk about.
Pl... Please...
expose... the truth.
I'm... I'm sorry...
Journalist Kim.
Damn it!
We were here for four months.
Four whole months.
I beg you.
There's nothing on this island.
- Fine! But there's no time. Hurry up!
- Thank you! Thank you!
- He said he'll wait. I'm going.
- CEO Hwang, why are you going?
Hey, I'm the CEO. I have to go.
If I'm late... then leave without me.
- What?
- But you'd better come back for me!
- Hurry up!
- CEO Hwang! CEO Hwang!
- Joon Oh! Joon Oh! CEO Hwang, he's here!
- Joon Oh!
Hey, come on!
What were you thinking?
Seo Joon Oh! Get on!
Seo Joon Oh, hurry up! Hurry, please!
- We have to leave. Hurry!
- Joon Oh!
Joon Oh!
- Hurry.
- Joon Oh!
Please! Hurry!
Let's talk on the boat! Get on!
Joon Oh!
Do you feel better? Did you throw up?
Gosh, seriously.
I need you... to hit my back.
Oh, geez! Wow.
You said you did this in the military!
Hey, is that the same thing?
This is a foreign country, with different
water and fish! Everything's different!
You're hungry again? Yes, so am I.
That's why we're going
where we can find fish!
Stop whining like a three-year-old child!
Let's date. You and I.
I didn't have any feelings,
but Ji Ah didn't either?
Ji and I are dating now! It's day one!
She wants you to tell her if CEO Hwang
bothers you. She'll protect you.
I've never been on a boat.
Gosh! Turn that way!
- We ate the same thing.
- Talk facing that way.
Tripletail!
Rock Bream! Rock Bream! Rock Bream!
Salmon! Squid! Squid!
- What are you doing so early?
- Let's catch fish.
Tripletail? Squid? Salmon? Are there any?
I don't think I can eat any more
of the mackerel you catch.
- Hurry.
- You enjoyed it.
I keep burping.
Yes, that's right.
That's how it is in our line of work.
- Shall we get going then?
- Yes.
Please go on ahead.
- Thank you for today.
- Sure.
The mood of the special investigation
committee improved after one case.
All I did was treat my employees
to dinner for working so hard.
You must always see things
that I can't see.
You have to try to see it.
If you decide not to see it,
there's no way you'll see it.
I don't know. What is it
that I decided not to see?
I'm talking about
when I went to check So Hee's body.
I coincidentally saw Jang Do Pal
at the hospital in China.
Do you know who Jang Do Pal
was visiting at the time?
- Why is that important?
- Choi Tae Ho.
I thought you knew everything and thought
I was being nosy for nothing.
But I guess you didn't know.
Well, isn't that understandable?
They could have timed their return while
watching over Choi Tae Ho's condition.
Then why don't you ask
Jang Do Pal about it?
When I see his expression...
I'll be able to guess whether or not
you and Jang Do Pal...
are on the same team, don't you think?
Okay, pay attention!
From now on, Secretary Tae Ho Hang
will be the other CEO
of Legend Entertainment.
- Okay, applause!
- Applause!
Wait, what? I see.
Congratulations on your promotion.
- It's all thanks to you.
- Why is it thanks to me?
- Huh?
- It's because you did a good job.
Do you think so?
Okay.
Why did you tell them to come here?
You could have talked on the phone.
They found another survivor.
Should that be discussed over the phone?
- Do you know who it could be?
- Why are you asking me?
I'll ask one more time out of concern for
you. You're sure it isn't Joon Oh, right?
How many times do I have to tell you
that there's no way?
This time, they found two survivors.
If there are two, I can't leave it
to the guys. I'd better go there myself.
- I'll go with you.
- You'll only raise suspicion.
Prosecutor Yoon is already
out to get you.
CEO... I mean CEO Jang.
Do you remember Tae Ho's meeting
for his Chinese movie?
What if you said that appointment
was pushed to an earlier date?
That will work.
Wow. You're finally acting like a CEO.
It's possible they didn't return to Korea
right after being rescued.
They could be waiting for
the right time to return, just like me.
I'm just asking you to keep that in mind.
That's possible.
That accomplice is right here.
- Secretary Tae!
- Ra Bong Hee!
She was the accomplice.
When many lies come together,
I guess that becomes the truth.
How will you prove that this is a lie?
They outnumber you,
so how can you prove it?
Goodness. I'm here for soy sauce!
Did you see her daughter?
I heard that she's not in her right mind.
Go figure. I thought she looked pale
and absent-minded.
By the way, how do they plan on
finding other survivors through her?
That's what I'm saying!
That's why they didn't find any.
Who could they find with a girl
who's not in her right mind?
Gosh, it's too bad an unmarried girl
is in that kind of state.
It's because of her mother's fortune.
Things don't change!
Like mother like daughter!
You ignorant women!
Here you are, gossiping about others
because you have nothing better to do!
If you really have nothing to do,
go home and take a nap!
Why did you crawl out here?
Why are you making my daughter
into a mental case?
Are you crazy?
Pay me back for cleaning costs right now!
Fine. Fine! I'll give you money,
so go to the laundromat
and ask them to wash
your dirty mouths too!
This is why anything
that comes out of your mouths is trash!
Trash? Trash?
You'd better stay out of my sight
from now on!
If you don't, forget soy sauce.
I'll pickle you in salt and make you
into salted seafood!
You damned wenches...
How dare you talk about my daughter?
Wow, what a nice place.
- Prosecutor Yoon.
- Did you rest well for a few days?
I'm sorry for not being helpful to you.
Then stop being sorry,
and let's get back to work.
- Pardon?
- They found more survivors.
Survivors?
Who are they?
They requested personal protection,
so we only know there are two of them.
That's why I wanted to ask...
How about we go and see them in person?
Yes. Yes, I'll go no matter what.
The special investigation
committee doesn't know yet
and Jang Do Pal has guys
working for him in China
so he probably already heard the news.
We have to act quickly if we don't want
more witnesses stolen away from us.
But Prosecutor Yoon...
Out of those two survivors--
Um, I don't know
if this will be helpful...
But one of the two survivors
said they wanted you to visit them.
I think it might be Seo Joon Oh.
This time, I feel like it's Seo Joon Oh.
Yes, let's hope it is.
If Seo Joon Oh shows up,
we can flip this case around.
- Geez.
- Manager Jung, here.
Wait.
We can treat this when we get to
a hospital, so just hold on until then.
Geez, this is bothersome!
Wow, seriously. Are we really going home?
I didn't know this day would ever come.
Oh, everyone, what do you want to do
when you get home?
- We have to go to a hospital first.
- That's a given! After that.
What about you?
First, I want to eat delicious food.
- Like what?
- Braised short ribs.
My mom made
really good braised short ribs.
- I was born as an only son.
- Glutinous rice cakes?
No, you idiot.
We had one son for seven generations.
I was a precious child. That's why my mom
raised me with such good care.
But...
She doesn't know if her precious son
is alive or dead...
I can't imagine how worried she must be.
16... 17...
18... 19.
Seo Joon Oh. Oh!
Wow, seriously! Seo Joon Oh!
Wake up, Seo Joon Oh!
Are you all right? Huh? Gosh!
Hey, how many minutes?
Did I pass the four minute mark?
- Four minutes?
- Yeah.
22 seconds! You lasted for seven seconds
longer than last time! New record!
Geez, 22 seconds?
Hey, this is dangerous!
You almost died! The water is cold!
It would be good if I died.
I miss my mom.
What are you saying?
How would you see your mom if you died?
- My parents are in heaven.
- Pardon?
I have many siblings though!
Our Yeol, Tae Ho, and Ki Joon.
I consider Ji Ah a younger sister too.
Hey, forget this! Let's get back to work!
Pardon? Don't overdo it, Seo Joon Oh.
Hey, I can't let you feed me forever!
The artist is supposed to
feed his stylist. Follow me.
Wow.
- This is fascinating.
- What is?
I thought I would think about home
if I closed my eyes.
But I keep seeing that deserted island.
The shelter that we lived in together.
The beach.
The yard where we ate our meals.
Our So Hee.
Our Yeol.
Geez. I couldn't even thank
Journalist Kim.
If we didn't have the radio
he found, we wouldn't have been saved.
He also...
resolved the wrongful accusations
that were made against Joon Oh.
Geez.
- What was that?
- Are you all right?
They warned us about the weather.
I guess it's beginning.
This punk, why isn't he coming back?
Are you all right?
You'd better fix this first thing
when you get back.
Hey, hold it in.
Use your hands. Use your hands.
Helmsman. Please come back
to the captain's cabin. I repeat.
- Wh... What is he saying? Are we here?
- Helmsman, return to the cabin!
It sounds like he's looking for his crew.
Where are you? Come back here!
Helmsman, return to the cabin!
Wait, Ho Hang. Geez. Where are you going?
What are they doing?
They're making me so anxious!
- CEO Hwang.
- Where are you going?
I'm the only one who can speak to them.
I should see if I can help.
Find Secretary Tae. I don't know if he
fell into the water while throwing up.
Ki Joon, I'll look for Ho Hang.
Stay here, okay?
Don't come out. Stay here, got it?
- Be careful!
- He'll probably come back soon.
Ho Hang!
Are you all right?
Why did you come in here?
The currents are too strong!
I came to help you!
Then hold on to this for a moment.
- All you have to do is hold it steady!
- Okay!
Wow. What is going on here?
Ho Hang!
Where did that punk go?
- What did he say?
- He's asking where he went.
- Wait here.
- Bong Hee, where are you going?
Bong Hee!
- Geez, she doesn't listen.
- That scared me.
Seo Joon Oh!
Secretary Tae!
Ho Hang! Ho Hang!
What's wrong? Ho Hang!
Ho Hang! What are you doing?
Get up. Get up!
What's wrong? Are you okay? Wake up!
- Joon Oh.
- Are you okay? What is it?
I'm seasick.
Excuse me!
- It's Tae Ho!
- No!
No. Ho Hang, it's okay.
No! Don't look! It's okay. It's okay.
Ji Ah, wake up. Ji Ah, one minute.
Joon Oh, you're blocking the light.
Can you move?
Joon Oh, you're blocking the light!
Ki Joon! Ki Joon!
Ki Joon.
One person is still being treated,
and the other person has recovered
but they're postponing their return.
They get scared
when they hear anything about Korea.
But what's strange is that
they wanted to see Ra Bong Hee.
But you don't know
their identities yet, correct?
That's correct. Not yet.
Bong Hee!
Oh, Ji Ah. It's you.
What a relief that you're okay.
What about your injury?
Are you all right?
I was treated when I got here.
What a relief.
It's going to be okay,
now that we're all together.
But was it you...
who asked to see me, by any chance?
I did want to see you,
but the person who said that was...
Bong Hee! Bong Hee! Bong Hee! Bong Hee!
- It was hard for you, wasn't it?
- Yes.
I'm relieved to see that
you're both okay.
Oh, but I was wondering...
What about Seo Joon Oh?
You two were here for a long time.
Did you hear anything about him?
Bong Hee, don't you remember?
When we left that island...
Manager Jung! Seo--
Ki Joon... No...
Ki Joon! Ki Joon...
Put that knife down.
Ra Bong Hee!
Put that down.
I'm the one you want, isn't that right?
No, Joon Oh.
I'm going to kill everyone on this boat.
You and her...
I'm going to kill everyone here.
Mayday! Mayday! (In Chinese)
Oh, there's so much wind!
Requesting help!
Joon Oh!
Ji Ah. Ji Ah.
- No!
- Damn it!
Don't come... Don't come....
Don't come near me!
Don't come near me.
Don't. Don't.
When we were leaving that island,
Joon Oh...
Tae Ho stabbed him with the knife.
Right in front of you.
Seo Joon Oh, are you... are you okay?
Bong Hee.
You're okay, right?
I'm okay. What do we do?
That's all that matters.
If you're okay, that's all that matters.
No... No.
Look out! (In Chinese)
I'm sorry, Prosecutor Yoon.
I have to get going now. I'm sorry.
I know you'll think I'm crazy...
But for one last time,
I want to believe he's alive.
I got a call.
But his voice...
His voice...
It sounded like Seo Joon Oh.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
- I don't know why you're doing all this.
- You saved me.
They haven't been answering our calls
for over an hour!
Do you think I went through those
headaches, just to get their bodies?
Who died because of you?
It wasn't you, no matter what others say.
It's been a few days since those two
arrived. Didn't they contact you?
Choi Tae Ho, Tae Ho Hang, Jung Ki Joon,
and Ha Ji Ah all point to Seo Joon Oh.
Someone came to see you!
It's someone famous!