Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
[Episode 1]
Sir, you shouldn't get angry.
Acting like this won't bring the dead
back to life. So I'm saying--
No! I know they're still missing,
but I'm saying--
Damn it...
Sir. Hello?
Sir!
If they're missing, they're dead!
Your son is dead.
You won't see him ever again!
So... Stop crying and make some money!
Shit!
President! President!
President, you need to see this!
120 days after the incident, one of
the missing people has been found alive.
On the 24th of last month
at 7 p.m. in Huizhou, China
it was reported that Ms. Ra
who was a passenger
on the private plane, was found.
After Ms. Ra was found,
she was taken to a nearby hospital
and we are told
that her health is favorable.
Currently, China is questioning her
to find out what happened
during the plane crash.
After it was revealed that Legend
Entertainment's private plane crashed
- a survivor was found...
- When the investigation ends
- she will return to Korea.
- Right now
they are lighting candles of hope.
The fans who participated in a protest
against the search that ended in 45 days
made sure their voices
and objections were heard.
- The star never goes out.
- A survivor was found!
- What's going on?
- Teacher!
A survivor from
Legend Entertainment was found!
Oh my gosh! I can't believe it!
So Hee! Be quiet so I can hear!
So Hee... So Hee!
So Hee, I hope you're alive! So Hee!
You punks!
Lee Yeol, Seo Joon Oh,
Choi Tae Ho, Yoon So Hee...
Let go of me!
- Sir!
- Why isn't Tae Min here?
Tae Min is alive, right?
Right? Right? Right? Right? Right?
Don't change the channel.
That's not the issue!
After the kids went down with the plane
there's a survivor!
I don't care about the plane.
All that matters is this game!
- Gosh...
- You're back?
- The waves were strong today.
- You didn't catch anything?
They said they will use
all of their strength.
The survivor, Ms. Ra was a stylist
for the celebrity, Seo Joon Oh,
of Legend Entertainment.
She is planning to return to Korea
as soon as the investigation is over.
The team that confirmed
Ms. Ra was alive
was reorganized and the special
investigation committee has taken over.
And they asked China to cooperate
in the search for the other survivors.
Ms. Ra's--
Yeah, Lawyer Jo.
Please take care of something for me.
Have some water.
Geez, I do remember those times.
After the incident,
we were transferred for the search
but we didn't have the funds.
We searched right away, but we couldn't
even find the remains of the plane.
Well, we thought you were dead,
to be completely honest.
But, now that you're alive,
it has became very inconvenient for us.
- I have no room.
- Okay.
No room.
By the way, was it all true?
I'm talking about what you told
the Chinese police.
Yes.
- Are there any other survivors?
- Where were you all this time?
Please tell us about the crash!
How do you feel?
Do you know anything
about Lee Yeol and the others?
- Where are the others?
- Are they alive? What happened?
How is your health?
Bong Hee.
Mom.
Bong Hee!
Mom...
Bong Hee, you went through so much...
Gosh, thank you! Thank you so much!
Are you hurt?
You went through so much.
It must have been so hard.
Gosh, are you hurt?
- She can't remember!
- What?
I was able to get in touch
with someone in China
so I looked into what they
talked about in the investigation
and they said Ra Bong Hee
lost her memory.
They said it's a symptom
of post-traumatic stress.
You know how people lose their memory
when they go through too much shock?
They said Ra Bong Hee
is going through the same thing.
She recognizes her mom.
I don't know the details either
but they said she doesn't remember
what happened after the plane crashed.
They said she has short-term memory loss.
The doctor confirmed it.
I was wondering why the special committee
was secretive about it, but this is why.
Then are you saying we don't know
where they were and what happened?
Short-term memory loss
is similar to dementia
so she could suddenly get her memory back
or she could get parts of it back.
But they said no one can tell
when it will come back.
Just eat that.
Anyways, regarding this issue
the special investigation team is
working to recover her memory
so all we can do is wait.
Okay, I got it. Keep working at it.
- Thank you!
- Ra Bong Hee?
You know that the special investigation
committee is on this case, right?
I'm the chairman of the committee,
Jo Hee Kyung.
Thank you for being alive.
You must have gone through a lot.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay.
I heard everything from Investigator Oh.
He said you don't remember anything.
- Yes.
- So what do you think?
Do you feel relieved?
For the last four months,
where you lived
how you lived, who you lived with,
why you were saved alone...
The fact that you don't remember
could be a good thing for you.
We don't know what horrible
things you might have endured.
But Ra Bong Hee...
to us, that's not a good thing.
Do you understand?
The memory that you lost
is the only hope we have.
Those kids on the plane,
because of their unknown status
this country has been very noisy
for the last four months.
"The singer Lee Yeol was seen in China."
"Choi Tae Ho often visits a bar
in South America."
"This is a surprise event to celebrate
Legend Entertainment's 20th anniversary."
"They're alive, and they will
surprise us at their concert."
There are countless ridiculous
rumors going around.
We thought it was finally calming down...
And then you showed up.
You made things very complicated for us.
If you came back, you should have
brought facts, not chaos, Ra Bong Hee!
Try everything. Do whatever you can...
to get your memory back.
Get your memory back and tell us all
who lived and who died!
That's the only way this country
will find peace.
There's not much to patriotism.
You have to give our citizens
the answers to what they want to know.
That's what patriotism is, isn't it?
It was my first job.
It was my first day on the job.
And...
it was my first trip abroad.
That day...
was supposed to be...
the happiest day of my life.
So I thought...
Hello! I'm Seo Joon Oh's stylist.
- Oh, come this way.
- Okay.
[Dreamers' Joon Oh]
Geez...
- Hey, Joon!
- Where are you?
- Oh, I'm about to--
- Come here right now.
I already told you. You have 10 minutes.
Do you think I can get to Gunsan
from Seoul in 10 minutes?
- Anyways, I'll leave right now--
- 10 minutes.
- We came here to catch octopuses.
Yes! Yes! You're doing well.
Good! Good! It's fun to watch!
Seo Joon Oh! Come back here
if you're finished!
Joon Oh!
Hurry over! I planned
everything out for you. Come over!
Hurry up!
Yes, Manager Jung!
Hello, Bong Hee! We have to go somewhere
in 10 minutes. Where are you?
Oh, I'm in front of Star Cafe.
Geez, there are too many
of those in Gangnam.
You're at Manager Jung's shop, right?
We're in a hurry, so I'll go over there.
- Manager Jung--
- Wait for me there!
Oh, Manager Jung! Oh...
- Yes, like that! Yes!
- Roll over more!
- Good! Good!
- Joon Oh, are you okay?
- What do we do?
- Send a text for me. Where is he?
How far are you?
[I'm almost there.]
He said he's almost here.
Seo Joon Oh! If you sent your text,
come back here!
- I'll get through it.
- Do you want to take a break?
No!
Yes! I'm walking there now. Okay!
- Yeah, Joon!
- You have three minutes.
You should tell me what's going on--
Hello? Joon Oh.
How could you hang up on me?
I have two minutes now.
[Block this number?]
[Block calls.
Block messages.]
[Dreamers' Joon Oh]
Oh, Joon Oh!
You should look for it harder!
Look for the octopus!
I found one!
He should have caught it later!
It's not fun if it looks too easy!
Smile twice, and eat it in one bite!
Open your mouth wide! Open wide!
Yeah! Hurry up and eat it!
Why can't you make it look delicious?
- My phone.
- Sure.
What is he doing? Huh?
- The number you called...
- Damn it, he blocked me!
- is temporarily unavailable...
- He put me in the spam folder!
Are you finished? Get back in there.
Hurry up and get in there!
- Do it again! Do it again!
- The sun is going down!
- After I eat.
- Did we go overboard?
- Let's do it one more time!
- I think I crossed the line...
Wait, this won't solve anything!
Give me a bottle of Soju, please.
- He's so sensitive...
- You asked him to catch an octopus.
No, that's not it...
- Do you have anything else?
- No!
My contract ended ages ago...
[I fell for that buzzed feeling.]
Why were you so late?
I waited for a long time.
I'm sorry. I had something
I had to bring. I'm sorry.
That's okay. We're already late anyway.
Let's eat this and go slowly
as if we're on vacation.
- I thought you might like squid.
- Yes, I like squid.
- You brought your passport, right?
- Yes of course.
Here. The office took
a long time to make this.
I paid 40,000 or 50,000 won, so I thought
they'd make it for me right away.
- This must be your first trip abroad.
- Yes.
- Oh, I'll rip that for you.
- Yes, thank you.
Bong Hee, you don't seem that young
yet this is your first job,
and first trip abroad?
What did you do all your life?
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
I didn't do much, but this is
what I studied. I studied this field.
But I couldn't find a job, so I spent
a few years with my mom at home
and I came up to Seoul for this job
because you looked favorably upon me.
No, I didn't. No one else applied.
- Oh, I see.
- Did you hear about today's schedule?
- Yes, I heard.
- Yes, it's not much.
Joon Oh is shooting the "Gunsan
Octopus Special" of "Food Expedition."
We just have to help out with that,
and go to the airport right after.
For the "Legend Town Concert."
Yes, I understand.
Bong Hee, how much
do you know about Joon Oh?
Should I be honest?
What kind of person is Seo Joon Oh
in your opinion?
Um, he was the frontman of Dreamers.
- Eat this.
- Yes, thank you.
- He was a top star once.
- He was!
Now, he's having a hard time.
Because he drank under the influence
three years ago.
Let go of me! Where are you from?
I ate with your chief!
We went to the sauna, and drank!
We did everything!
I thought it would pass...
But he said something weird
as he came out of the police station.
Seo Joon Oh! Is it true you drove
under the influence?
I drank, but I didn't drink and drive.
Are you saying someone else drove?
Because of that incident,
all of his fans left him
and the reporters only said
bad things about him.
In the end... Dreamers split up.
I'm so sorry... My friends right here...
did nothing wrong.
I'm so very sorry.
Dreamers...
How could this have happened?
To our Chinese fans...
Hello, everyone!
Dreamers would like to say goodbye
to our beloved fans.
No, where are we going?
After the group split up,
every solo act failed big time.
It's 12! Gather around! Gather around!
Gather around!
- Five! Four! Three! Two! One!
Joon Oh, you're the best!
[98: "Ri-Gi-Ri-Gi-Dong", by Seo Joon Oh]
[Download Song]
[Download is complete. You can
find the song in the saved folder.]
I bought it.
After that, every drama
and variety show he did...
were all failures
so he's a complete--
Would you like an egg?
Oh, sure. That looks good. Thank you.
Our Joon Oh isn't that bad off.
Yes, of course.
He will reveal a new album soon
and he's respected in our company.
- He's still a Dreamer, no matter what.
- Yes.
The legendary thugs of music.
The frontman of Dreamers, Seo Joon Oh.
Wow, that was perfect timing.
[CEO Hwang Jae Gook]
It's our CEO.
This is the level that
Joon Oh is at in our company.
It's getting very tiring.
Yes, CEO Hwang!
Because of Joon Oh's schedule--
Manager Joon, you son of a bitch.
What did Joon Oh do this time?
What did he do to make
the broadcaster summon me? What?
Why should I be summoned
because of him? Why?
I'm with Joon Oh's stylist right now.
You're on speaker.
Joon Oh's stylist can hear everything.
- So what?
- I'm just letting you know.
CEO Hwang! Um, today...
Joon Oh is shooting in Gunsan
so we have hurry down there, and since
we're using the private plane tonight
can we use it for just a little bit?
Stop your bullshit! I'm hanging up!
Okay!
Manager Jung!
These sausages are really good.
You should have one too.
Please be careful and drive slowly.
You should look straight ahead
and drive safely.
We have no choice but to go slowly.
This van is used. It's locked so
we can't go over 80 kilometers per hour.
It's so that we can't speed.
[Stop for Children]
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
- Um, what's the matter?
- He said he won't do it!
- Why?
- How would I know that?
First, please get ready to shoot
and I'll try to convince him.
Solve it before it gets worse!
- I'm sorry.
Let's meet Choi Tae Joon, who is the star
of the upcoming mini series!
- Yes, hello, Choi Tae Joon!
- Yes, hello.
You're a lead in the upcoming mini
series. Please tell us your thoughts.
Yes, I'm very happy to act after
being active in a band for a long time.
Um, my role is very familiar to me
because it is a character
who plays the guitar.
So he plays the guitar romantically...
- Why are you wearing sunglasses indoors?
- It'll get in my eyes. It stings.
Let's do the show.
- After I finish this.
- It's unlimited. When will that be?
Until they stop refilling it.
It's not mannerly to waste food.
I'll eat here, so you can go do the show.
- No.
- Why not?
- It's different from when I was cast.
- What?
You said I would eat them,
not catch them!
- You need to catch them to eat them.
- You didn't tell me that.
You're supposed to catch
octopuses in the mud!
Ki Joon, I thought there were
no secrets between us. I'm disappointed.
Joon Oh, I didn't trick you. You catch
the octopus so you can eat it.
Whatever. I can't do the show,
so go and tell them.
- Hey, do the show--
- I can't! I don't want to!
Why do I have to fill in
for Choi Tae Ho all the time?
Who told you?
Byung Joo.
Joon Oh, you're Tae Ho's substitute,
but...
this is a good opportunity for us.
Let's become a permanent cast member
in the show and make a comeback, okay?
Hey, we don't need too much!
Let's make a good drama or a movie
- and do commercials--
- Stop it!
- Hey, do you know how hard it was?
Endure it! Make it work.
Endure it even if it's embarrassing.
It'll only get harder for you.
If you don't do this, what will you do?
Do you have anything? How will you live?
Seriously...
Ki Joon.
Okay! Let's do the show, okay?
I'll do it because I listen to you.
All I have to do is catch an octopus and
wave it in front of the camera, right?
But you know I'm stylish, right? I won't
do it if I don't like my outfit, okay?
- What are you saying?
- Who are you? Who are you?
I'm... Hello, I'm Ra Bong Hee--
I don't need your name. Bring me
the outfits you prepared. It's up to you.
It's up to you
if we "do this show" today or not.
I'm back! Yes, please have a look.
It's a simple and thick sweater.
It's made of spandex,
and if you match it with some blue--
It's too plain.
Next.
There aren't any...
These are dots, but in a military style.
It's popular, but it's the most basic--
It looks like it'll sting. Next.
This one.
You can match it with this Scottish
pattern to look like a hot fasionista.
- Seo Joon Oh?
- It looks like graph paper.
We don't have time, Joon Oh...
Gosh, I'm so tired...
Hey! Be careful!
Yes! I'm coming!
Seo Joon Oh, look at this while you eat.
This is striped shirt.
You can tie the bottom for
a university look. It's a campus look.
Joon Oh, only finished high school.
He took the GED...
I'm sorry.
Hey, why did you say that
to someone we just met?
Okay, this is a soft, wool knit.
It will show off your soft side
and sexy neck
- it will make your collarbone--
- It looks like an undershirt.
Don't you have any with five buttons?
I like horses.
Oh, that looks prickly, geez!
It's a knit, no it's a sweatshirt.
The panda is the main point.
The panda is lying down.
Is there a sweater with a panda
that's looking forward?
- Forward?
- He hates tails.
- He looks like a loser.
- Why do you think that?
- He's turning his back!
- He looks humble!
No, he has to look forward
with confidence.
What about this trench coat?
- Like an English gentleman--
- How could I wear this?
He has never been in England.
Is this only for people
who have been to England?
- Ouch!
- Oh, are you all right?
- Hey, this is seriously--
- It feels like silk.
- Your neck turned red!
- Should I call 911?
Found it!
It's too much.
Geez, we're in trouble. I don't like any
of the clothes. We should quit the show.
- Joon Oh.
- I don't like them. What do we do?
Tell the director for me, okay?
Oh, wait a minute!
This is something that is never
given for a sponsorship.
But I secretly borrowed it
from a friend to give to you.
They're sunglasses.
What's wrong with her?
Joon Oh, it looks like Bong Hee
doesn't know. Please be understanding.
Fire her.
Wait! Joon Oh! Wait! Oh no...
I'm sorry. I'll bring your clothes
as soon as possible, so please...
Why did you have to bring that
of all things? Tae Ho models those.
- Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh, you can't do this!
- Seo Joon Oh!
I didn't know! I really didn't know.
I'm sorry! It was a mistake!
Please forgive me just this once. Please?
Joon Oh, just this once...
Wait, don't be startled.
I'll remove them.
- Why are there octopuses in your pants?
- The director told me to do it.
Geez, that wasn't nice!
Why did he want them in here?
I'll bring you some clothes. Please
look at a few more, and reconsider.
Try it again.
- Can I do it for you? I'll help.
- Do it for me, then.
Please. I'll bring some more outfits...
Geez, you smell like fish.
I'll hold this for you.
Use your strength.
- Just wait--
- Wait, not like that--
- One, two, three--
- Wait, no--
Hey, not like that. You're holding
my feet. One, two, three!
Seo Joon Oh! I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I have to wash up and go
to the airport. Move. Close the door!
Joon Oh, this car is manual.
Our car was repossessed earlier today.
Hey, how much was it worth
that they just took it back?
I'm sorry. I won't do it again. If you
fire me, I have no other means to live!
Do you think driving is all
you need to do? It should be peaceful!
Please let me work! Please...
- Are you all right?
- Can you eat and live like this?
But, I'll really starve, Seo Joon Oh!
I'll work really hard!
No, Seo Joon Oh!
You can't go like this! I want this job!
Hey, why is a girl so strong?
Do you work out?
What does it matter how strong
you are? You need to have brains!
How can you do this? No!
You won't starve to death with this
strength of yours! Hey, help me out here!
This isn't something
you should ask for! Wake up!
- Hey, I'll use my strength.
- I want this job!
Hey, it's okay. I talked to him.
I talked to him. I talked to him...
Joon Oh. Joon Oh, stop the car.
Hey, stop the car. Hey!
Byung Joo! Hey!
- I need to scream for you listen...
- What are you doing?
Are you fooling around? Huh?
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry, this is really...
What's wrong? Tell me what's wrong.
Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
Why are you being like this? Huh?
Byung Joo!
Geez, I'm tired. Let's eat something
and rest before we go to the airport.
Yes, Joon Oh. Joon Oh, since we're here,
how about some octopus stew?
- Byung Joo.
- Yes?
I'm sorry.
- Byung Joo.
- I forgot what you did today...
Oh, it looks like you unblocked me.
- She said this is her first job.
- Who?
Bong Hee. This is her first job.
It's her first day,
and her first trip abroad.
It was a good day, so wouldn't it be
wrong to fire her for the first time too?
What is this?
Give me the keys! Let's switch cars.
There's no heater in this one.
Why hasn't it been fixed?
Where's the car?
It's over there.
Geez, aren't you going
to change the color?
You told me to leave it as it is!
You liked how pure it looked.
I'm leaving. See you at the airport!
- What are you doing? Come on!
- Okay!
- Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh--
- Hey, wait!
I don't know what his reason is,
but he said he's not firing you.
Really, Manager Jung?
I'm not fired?
Thank you! Thank you, Manager Jung!
Geez, what for? I'm going to talk
with the producer, so wait in the car.
Let's go the "Legend Town Concert"
in a private plane, okay?
Thank you! I'll work really hard!
Thank you, Manager Jung!
Wow, is the heater actually working?
Wow, it'll be a warm ride to the airport!
I'm already dripping with sweat, Joon Oh.
- Let me see.
- Pardon?
- Where's the sweat?
- Was it just my mood? I'm sorry.
- It felt like it...
- Just drive.
Hello, I'm Park Seul Gi.
I'm here where Legend Entertainment is
departing for their first concert abroad!
And the artists of Legend Entertainment
are just about to arrive--
It looks like Ha Ji Ah
is arriving right now!
Ji Ah, hello! Can you do an interview?
Yes! Oh, you have to leave?
Then please speak with us next time!
Okay, the former frontman
of Dreamers! It's Seo Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh! Have you been well?
- Hello.
- There are so many people...
- Oh, what? Have you--
I...
- Tae Ho!
- It's been a while.
Oh! How have you been, Tae Ho?
I know. This is your first concert
abroad! Are you ready for it?
This is our first concert abroad,
so we'll do a good job.
I'm worried for you.
Don't get hurt, okay?
- Yes
- I'm sorry.
- Tae Ho! Take care of your health!
- Let's talk again.
Yes, can you take me with you?
So Hee, your necklace is crooked.
Don't touch.
Move.
Yoon So Hee! Yoon So Hee!
Yoon So Hee...
Oh my! Oh my, hello, So Hee!
Have you been well? Are you ready?
- Do a good job while I'm gone.
- Sure.
And don't try to steal the company again.
I'll remember that.
It's a mistake the first time,
but not the second time. Okay?
- Yes, I got it, CEO Hwang.
- I'll be back.
Bong Hee! Please prepare comfortable
clothes for Joon Oh. He's uncomfortable.
- Yes, sure.
- Oh, and by the way...
- It's your first time on a plane, right?
- Yes, it's my first time.
I see. You know you're supposed
to take off your shoes on a plane, right?
- Please bring it to me when it's ready!
- Okay!
No way...
Wow, there's a place like this?
Excuse me... I should take off my shoes.
Manager Jung was right.
Wow, it's so spacious!
It smells nice.
Whoa... Wow... It's so pretty...
I'll talk to you when I get back.
What else could it be?
That's the only thing we'd about.
Anyway, I'll see you when I return.
It's So Hee.
Hello!
- Whose stylist are you?
- Oh, I'm Seo Joon Oh's stylist.
You're so screwed.
- Isn't it hard?
- No, it's fine so far.
Well...
Do you know what kind of person
Joon Oh is?
Pardon?
Oh. It's my first day, so I don't know.
Be careful of him.
Don't get on his bad side.
He's a scary person.
- Hey!
- Yes?
Why aren't you bringing my clothes?
I'm so uncomfortable.
Here.
- So Hee, it's been a while.
- Yeah, it has. How have you been?
Same old. I enjoyed your movie.
It's nice to see you succeed.
I have to continue to work hard
if I don't want to end up like you.
People like us don't know
when we'll be forgotten.
Oh, hey!
Give me my script.
Scene 87.
- What? Where are you going, So Hee?
- Oh, you should get ready.
Hey, you don't have a stylist. Where
would you go? Sit down. I'll be quick.
- Okay, I'll be here, then.
- I should change.
I'll be like you one day, right?
Don't worry! You'll be more
successful than I am.
So Hee.
How would you end up like me?
Don't worry. You won't be forgotten.
Why did you take off your shoes?
Follow me.
Manager Jung told me to take them off!
I'm... I'm coming!
Here it is.
- Pants.
- Yes. Here.
Why is he stripping
in front of me? We just met.
I wanted to change because my sweater
was itchy, so she brought turtlenecks?
I didn't ask her to bring me
uncomfortable clothes...
This is why I don't work with newbies.
Joon Oh, you're an angel. How will you
survive in this world by being kind?
I can see this being difficult.
Cheer up, Ra Bong Hee.
It hurts just to touch it.
How can I wear this if it hurts?
Do I have to change again?
[Mom, I'm on the plane.]
What is this? Is this stuck?
- Did you?
- No.
Ouch, this is prickly.
It hurts before I even put it on.
I'll have to change again!
Wait, Tae Ho.
Tae Ho, just a minute.
Wait. Oh! Ouch!
- You took photos, didn't you?
- Pardon?
You took pictures, didn't you?
No, I didn't. I was just...
watching you do things--
- Did she take pictures?
- I think so.
- Give it to me.
- No, I was texting my mom--
I really don't have pictures.
- Who are you?
- I'm Seo Joon Oh's stylist.
Joon Oh's stylist is Gyung Ran.
I'm not Gyung Ran.
I'm his new stylist.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
This collar hurts even more!
Joon Oh, is she your stylist?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
Oh, where did you...
Don't you have something like this?
You didn't take any. I'm sorry.
- Joon Oh, long time no see!
- Yeah.
Oh, what should we do?
Your skin is aging.
You should get it checked. Work hard!
Is she worrying about me or what?
Hey, do you have anything long like that?
This is the schedule. You have to wake up
at 7 a.m. to eat and go to the event.
What is this?
Oh, for this, the head of the department
asked for it himself.
- What is it?
- Not right now. You'll see later.
- When? After I'm dead?
- Why do you have to say it like that?
Oh, girls! Welcome! Welcome!
- Hey! Hey!
- Hello.
- Hey, how are you?
- Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down. Sit down.
Would you like something to drink?
- I would!
- Sure, what would you like?
- Coffee.
- Coffee?
- How about you girls?
- Don't give them anything!
They don't deserve it.
- Hey!
- You wench.
Oh! Ji Ah, wait a minute.
I made a drink that's just like you!
It's bittersweet like you.
- That's enough.
- Okay.
Joon Oh!
Okay, here... Why are you late?
Here, let me pour you a glass, Yeol.
Is it good?
CEO Hwang, please pour me
a glass as well.
Anyway, you prepared for a year.
It's time to sweep the music charts.
I'm working hard on it.
Joon Oh is preparing an album as well.
- Yes, I wrote many songs.
- Oh, really?
Can I listen to one of your new songs?
Sure, of course.
Okay, Tae Ho!
- How are you, Tae Ho?
- I'm a lead actor now.
Please change my stylist, CEO Hwang.
I heard you're friends with Jung Yoon Ki.
Do you want Yoon Ki as your stylist?
I'll do that. It's no big deal.
Now, if you secure your place
as a leading actor in the upcoming series
you can erase the dishonor
associated with you because of Dreamers.
Later on, when you stage your
comeback album, won't the fans love it?
CEO Hwang, I'm ready to play the song.
Okay! Let's listen!
Wow!
- That's our Jae Hyun.
- Wow, that was good.
Good work!
I... have something to say.
I don't think I can do this any longer.
This is similar to
that guy's song, isn't it?
- It won't be the title track, right?
- I'm thinking about it.
- Yeol.
- Joon Oh, I'm sorry.
But this is the least
we can do to remember Jae Hyun.
CEO Hwang... I'll be leaving now.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
Passengers, this is your pilot.
The plane is shaking due to turbulence.
- Please take your seats.
- Oh, it's shaking. Oh, my head...
Please fasten your seat belts.
- Oh, what?
- Wash them.
Pardon? But the plane is shaking...
Of course it is.
Have you never been on a plane?
- I haven't.
- Really?
- What should I wear?
- Oh, give it to me. How about this?
Hello.
- Ji Ah.
- Yeah?
- What is it?
- Don't take too many at a time.
Oh, I know.
- You seem to be everywhere.
- Oh, yes.
Manager Jung.
Shit. Hey, here.
Geez... Nothing goes
the way I want it to...
Joon Oh, I didn't do it
to hurt your feelings.
Then why did you do it?
Why did you make your song like that?
Yeol!
Just tell him already.
Tell him...
that you made the song to make Joon Oh
feel guilty for the rest of his life.
The clouds are becoming thicker.
- Have we stabilized?
- I think we should go up.
- Fly level 300.
Control, this is 079er.
Request climb to fly level 300
due to the wind.
Um, CEO Hwang. Please sit up
and put on your seat belt.
It's okay, there are no seat belts here!
What's going on? Oh! What's going on?
Oh! CEO Hwang!
Lightning! There's lightning!
So what?
It's okay. This plane won't crash.
It's a safe plane.
- Tae Ho, let's stop. You're drunk.
- Who's drunk?
Am I wrong? Why did we break up?
No.
Why were we forced to break up? Huh?
- Whose fault was it?
- Tae Ho, let's talk later.
No. So what?
What is it that you want to say?
I heard you followed us on the world tour
because you want to extend your contract.
And you're hanging on to this company
because you want to make an album.
Earlier, you talked about your own songs.
Do you think anyone can be a songwriter?
You sure have a strong will.
- You're being too harsh--
- No I'm not!
Don't you know what kind of person
that bastard is? He killed a man!
Jae Hyun was killed
by this son of a bitch!
I'm... having a really hard time.
It's so hard, that I could die.
Then die, you son of a bitch! Die!
Die. Okay?
We ask all passengers to stay in
their seats and fasten their seat belts.
Oh! Wow! Wow, CEO Hwang!
Please sit up! Please sit up!
Wow, seriously. We're not going to crash!
Oh! Oh! CEO Hwang! Please sit up.
Please put on your seat belt!
You're such a scaredy cat!
What are you doing here? Sit down.
- Hey, what's going on?
- What?
- Sit down!
- Hey, what's wrong with this plane?
Sit down! Hurry!
- What do we do?
- What's wrong?
This is why not everyone
can be on planes--
- Hey, grab something!
- We need seat belts!
- Hurry up and sit down!
- Sit down, you bastard!
- Stop overreacting. We're not crashing!
- Hold on tight!
- We're not going to crash!
- Hurry up and sit down!
- Ji Ah, don't sit. Hold on to something!
- I can't!
Shut up, you bitch! Don't sit and--
Listen to me!
Whoa, what's this?
Emergency positions!
Okay, crouch down, and curl up.
Is this your first time on a plane?
It's just turbulence.
Lower my body, and wrap my neck.
You should do it properly then.
Wrap your head and lower it.
Lower my body...
Hey! What are you doing?
Someone is in here! Please help!
- Hey!
- Hey, Ji Ah!
Ji Ah!
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Geez, is anyone here?
Sir, there's a fire.
There's a fire in the engine!
- CEO Hwang! CEO Hwang!
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
- Ji Ah!
- Crouch down... Crouch down!
Ji Ah. Ji Ah. Ji Ah.
Please.
This isn't the time for that.
Crouch down.
Yeah, I know! I know! Go over there.
I changed my password... to 2580!
CEO Hwang! Crouch down!
I know, you bastard! Stop it!
Ji Ah! Ji Ah. Open your eyes!
Ji Ah! Ji Ah.
- We're about to disengage!
- Check.
- Switch to level 2!
- Confirmed.
Done.
No! What do I do? Please save me!
We're going down.
Declare an emergency!
Roger! Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
Ji Ah! Ji Ah!
What the hell is this?
If this is a joke, stop it!
What is this? Ki Joon! I'm hurt!
Ji Ah!
I'm in here! Save me!
Save me!
Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
Joon Oh!
- What the hell is this?
- Joon Oh, are you okay?
Ji Ah!
Please wait here. I'll come back
after I check the situation.
Control, this is 079er.
We are in a dive. We are in a dive.
We're crashing, you bastards!
3000 feet!
So what did you say to Jae Hyun? How
could you? You should have comforted him.
- Ji Ah.
- Yeah?
Never mind.
- What is it?
- You'll meet a new manager tomorrow.
Why?
Is it because of the incident?
You're not wearing your seat belt again.
I told you to always wear it. Geez.
Wear it, even if it's bothersome.
I'm almost there.
Gosh, seriously.
Let's cheer up. Since we're all here.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Jae Hyun.
Ja... Ja... Jae Hyun.
Hey, Jae... Jae Hyun! Jae... Hey!
Hey! Jae Hyun!
Hey, Jae Hyun!
No! No!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
It is hard that people died...
And I felt pressure to survive.
I will reveal the truth.
It's not our job to manipulate the truth.
It will only complicate matters
if she recovers her memory.
Can you come with us?
Someone wants to meet you.
It seems like some
of her memory came back.
- Who lived and who died...
- We can live! We can be rescued!
How do you know if it's true, or if she's
pretending, or if she's hiding something?
What is this place?