Subtitles by DramaFever
Even if you think I'm crazy,
I have no choice.
There's only one way.
I'll turn myself in.
Wow, Seo Joon Oh.
It's so hard to see your face.
Since you came here yourself,
let's create a masterpiece together.
You still should have stopped him!
You were the one who didn't want
the prosecution to be involved.
But you just let him go?
If he went there without a plan,
it'll be over for him. What do we do?
It can only be Choi Tae Ho,
who left under an agreement.
He agreed to take care of it instead.
So that means
I need to split those two up?
It's your job to win Jang Do Pal
over to our side, Seo Joon Oh.
Geez, what is that on your head?
- You look good.
- Why did you want to see me?
Do you think it'll be okay
if we leave them alone like this?
Turn up the volume!
Have you been well?
I feel at ease because
I have nothing to worry about.
It's more like you're generous.
You're even in jail for Tae Ho.
If... you're trying to
get something out of me--
What about Tae Ho?
Does he come to visit you?
Do you even know
what Tae Ho is doing out there?
- Do I have to know that?
- Of course you should.
You should be curious if you confessed
to a crime in return for a favor.
But do you think Tae Ho
will do you that favor?
Even if you're willing
to get your hands dirty for Tae Ho
Tae Ho would never do that for you.
It seems like he already
forgot about your favor.
I'm not sure what you're saying.
I never asked for a favor--
CEO Hwang...
can speak now.
So? What do you want me to do about it?
I don't know why I'm listening to this.
Hey, what is he doing?
- Do you trust Choi Tae Ho that much?
- Let go!
- Go! Go! Hurry!
- Yes!
- What is this bastard doing?
- Hey, open the door!
Open up!
Open the door!
Don't move!
Take him away.
Seo Joon Oh, are you crazy?
What the hell were you doing?
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
You son of a bitch!
Are you playing with me?
No, I'm not.
- Do you trust Choi Tae Ho that much?
- Let go!
The underling you ordered to kill
CEO Hwang. You told Tae Ho to kill him.
But what do we do?
I saw Choi Tae Ho
and that underling being friendly.
You were tricked.
It's him.
This is the guy who tried to
inject poison into CEO Hwang.
That's right, Joon Oh. I saw that guy.
You once showed me a composite
of a guy and asked me if I knew him.
You said he caused CEO Hwang's accident
and that we needed to find him.
That guy got out of Tae Ho's van
and even bowed to him.
He acted as if he was Tae Ho's underling.
- What is this bastard doing?
- Hey, open up!
Open the door! Open up!
Don't move!
Turn myself in?
When did I say that?
You said you'd confess
if I let you see Jang Do Pal.
When did I say that?
I told you I'd confess?
Geez, seriously.
You're seriously crossing the line.
If you're going to act like this,
I want a trial!
You said you can lock me up
even if I don't confess! I'm leaving.
Hey, seriously! Damn it!
Hey! Get this bastard out of here!
Get him out of here!
I... I won't forgive you for this.
- Bong Hee!
- Hello.
You're here?
I heard Joon Oh turned himself in.
He didn't turn himself in...
He went in... instead of me.
The good news is...
we will get a trial,
regardless of Seo Joon Oh's confession.
Your statements all been neutralized,
so we needed a new angle.
This might be for the best.
Why are we hopeful about this trial?
Do you have something planned?
First, we have a reliable lawyer
on our side.
- You're a lawyer?
- Yes.
When did you become a lawyer?
Did you do it for Joon Oh?
No, it's not like that.
I've been preparing for a long time.
But I slowed down because of Seo Joon Oh
and then sped up thanks to him.
- Pardon?
- I'll tell you later.
- What does that mean?
- Anyway, congratulations.
Thank you.
Then, shall we plan for our trial?
I want to ask Hwang Jae Gook to be
our first witness, what do you think?
May I say something?
CEO Hwang hasn't fully recovered yet,
so will he be okay?
He's right.
He can't even speak properly yet.
But we should still give it a shot.
I'll ask CEO Hwang about it.
Yes. Yes. I understand.
He's on the line.
Sir, why is it so hard to contact you?
It seems like you're avoiding me.
Can't you tell from hearing my voice?
I'm in this state because I've been
using my voice to raise my ratings!
But I noticed that you often go to
Congressman Ahn's campaign rally.
Sir. Sir!
You can't treat me like this!
You were the one who asked me
to save the Equitable Party!
Excuse me?
Yes! No, that's okay!
Should I reschedule?
No. Let's go without him.
It's not my election anyway.
- Jo Hee Kyung!
Jo Hee Kyung of the Equitable Party!
Yes, hello! I'm on your side!
I'm Jo Hee Kyung!
What is this? Why are you being
so noisy in my restaurant? Get out!
Oh, you're working so hard.
It's nice to see that you're getting
a lot of business during a recession.
You sure know how
to smooth talk your way out of things.
Yes, I understand.
This is a hard time for all of us!
I will listen to your thoughts!
- If you give me a chance--
- Why would I give you a chance?
People in politics are all the same.
Even the special investigation committee.
You falsely claimed that a someone died!
You don't take anyone's life seriously
because you have power.
Imagine what will happen
if you win the election!
- About that--
- I don't care!
You're being noisy. Get out! Get out!
Gosh, after listening to the boss,
I think she should go into politics.
Hey, no thanks! I have better things
to do than to go into politics!
No thank you!
- She's such a good speaker.
- Politics aren't for everyone.
CEO Hwang, for Joon Oh's trial
they want you to be a witness.
Can you do that, CEO Hwang?
The weather is beautiful today.
Be careful!
What is it? Are you cold?
What's wrong? CEO Hwang! What's wrong?
CEO Hwang! CEO Hwang!
Yes. She resigned today.
Yes.
Turn off your phones.
The article will tell them everything.
There's no need to answer every call.
Yes.
Yeah, Prosecutor Lee.
News travels fast. You heard already...
Seo Joon Oh's trial?
He turned himself in?
He did.
You will be our witness
for the first trial, right?
Your words somehow
led us to a decisive trial.
This was your plan
so we couldn't possibly
find a better witness.
Wait, Prosecutor Yoon. Right now, I'm--
I'm telling you to clean up your
own mess! Act like an educated woman!
I expect you to be there.
I'll get everything prepared.
Wait.
That bastard...
He's suddenly making me feel competitive.
Um, Seo Joon Oh turned himself in?
That's what he says.
If he went to the prosecution himself
at a time like this...
doesn't that mean he surrendered?
You can take care of that for me, right?
Prosecutor Yoon gave Lee Jae Joon
evidence from Hwan Jae Gook's incident.
Get rid of him, and get rid
of anything that connects us.
You can do that, right?
I'll take care of it
as soon as I get out.
And as for your sentence...
I'll do whatever I can to shorten it.
The underling you ordered to kill CEO
Hwang. You told Choi Tae Ho to kill him.
But what do we do?
I saw Choi Tae Ho and that underling
being friendly with each other!
We're doing everything we can
to find Jang Do Pal's underling.
If we catch him before the second trial
Jang Do Pal will agree
to change his statement.
And by the way, Ra Bong Hee
is very worried about you.
"Seo Joon Oh, cheer up!"
That's what she wanted me to tell you,
but do I really have to do this?
I'm thankful. What did she say?
"Seo Joon Oh, cheer up!"
I swear that I will speak the truth, the
whole truth, and nothing but the truth
according to my own conscience
and if there is any falsehood
in my statement
I shall be punished for perjury.
Prosecutor, please question the witness.
During the Legend Entertainment
plane crash
did you spend four months on an island
near Huizhou China with the defendant?
Yes, that's correct.
You said you saw Yoon So Hee
being murdered
by the defendant, is that correct?
Yes.
Please tell us what you remember
from that incident.
That night...
I was worried about So Hee.
She had wandered off by herself
so I was looking for her.
But Seo Joon Oh suddenly approached her
from behind and strangled her.
He continued to strangle So Hee,
who was struggling for air
without any hesitation,
until the very end.
During your rescue...
You said he also attempted to kill
other survivors. Is that true?
Yes, that's true.
What was his reason?
It was...
We all knew that Seo Joon Oh
killed Yoon So Hee.
Objection!
His claim is subjective
and has no objective validity.
Sustained.
Lawyer, please question the witness.
Yes.
You said you witnessed the defendant
killing Yoon So Hee. Is that true?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Are you sure you saw it clearly?
It could have been dark or far away.
- Objection!
- Sustained.
I will change my question.
During the incident,
were you able to see very clearly?
Did you see, with your own two eyes
the defendant kill Yoon So Hee?
Yes.
Then during the incident,
what did the defendant do?
Was it like this?
Or like this? Against a wall?
No. I...
I didn't see exactly how he killed her.
You just told us
that you saw it clearly because
it wasn't dark or too far away.
But you suddenly don't remember?
[Autopsy Report]
Was there a glove on the deserted island?
- Why?
- She suffocated due to strangulation
but they found no evidence on the body.
I'm not sure.
- I don't remember.
- Figures.
It's not a pleasant memory.
Witness?
Please answer my question.
What did the defendant do?
At the time, I was in a state of shock
so I don't remember
exactly what happened.
It sounds like the defendant killed
Yoon So Hee in a very brutal way.
So you're saying,
you saw him kill Yoon So Hee
but you don't remember
how he killed her. Am I correct?
I apologize.
It was a very distressing time,
so I don't want to remember it.
How unfortunate.
Then while the defendant
was killing Yoon So Hee
what were you doing?
I already told you, I was in so much
shock that I couldn't move.
So let me get this straight.
You saw the defendant kill Yoon So Hee
but you didn't see how he killed her.
You don't remember because it was painful
but you couldn't do anything, right?
I will ask you one last question.
Are you sure the attacker was Seo Joon Oh
and Yoon So Hee was the victim?
- Objection!
- Sustained.
I'm not the only one, Tae Ho Hang
will confirm what I said.
When we were on that island,
Seo Joon Oh was a crazy murderer.
He told us he'd kill us if we didn't
listen! And we believed it.
You're saying you were scared to die
which was why you only watched as
Yoon So Hee died in front of you, right?
- Objection!
- Your Honor, that is all.
It'd be great if we can utilize his
presence as a witness to our advantage.
- How?
- If he accused you of being the murderer
but said something irrational,
or something like that.
If he's insisting he saw something
that he didn't see
it's only a matter of time until
things don't make sense.
- "Lies..."
- "Give birth to more lies."
That's what you want
to take advantage of, right?
Hwang Jae Gook needs complete rest
due to acute pneumonia.
Lawyer, please bring
your witness to the stand.
Your Honor, I would like to request
a new witness.
This witness wasn't
approved beforehand!
He is a very important witness. He was
the first to see Yoon So Hee's body!
We weren't sure if he could make it
due to his condition--
That's also why we cannot have confidence
in his statements!
This is the opinion of his family doctor.
Please confirm that he is capable
of being a witness in a court of law.
Lawyer, are you sure your witness
is well enough to testify?
Your Honor, I apologize.
The doctor confirmed that it was okay.
I...
He did nothing wrong.
Seo Joon Oh...
is innocent.
Seo Joon Oh tried his best...
to save everyone he could
until the very end.
Seo Joon Oh...
is innocent.
Prosecutor, is your second witness,
Jo Hee Kyung, absent?
Yes.
Since there are no more witnesses,
Case 2017-2916
the first trial of Yoon So Hee's
murder case is dismissed.
- Are you all right?
I saw Congresswoman Jo today.
Why did she just leave?
She was here?
Yes, I saw her in the hallway.
Why is everyone surprising me today?
Is it that hard
to put Seo Joon Oh in jail?
Is it that detrimental
if we're missing one witness?
You should go and see Jang Do Pal!
- Why would I see him?
- You haven't visited him lately, right?
It's possible he could decide
to testify for Seo Joon Oh.
Take my words seriously.
Prosecutor Yoon and Lawyer Jo
are looking for the culprit
so please be patient a little longer.
How is CEO Hwang doing?
He overworked himself today.
Secretary Tae called to say
he's all right now.
He said CEO Hwang
really wanted to come today.
Don't worry too much.
What about Jang Do Pal?
Prosecutor Yoon and Lawyer Jo
will see Jang Do Pal today too.
We're almost there,
so just hang on, Seo Joon Oh.
Okay.
CEO Jang.
It's been a long time, Tae Ho.
What do you mean? I was late because I
was waiting to bring you some good news.
Good news?
I... caught him.
- Really?
- He was in hiding.
I'll take care of him really soon...
so you can relax now.
He has no one to help him.
Where was he hiding?
Take my words seriously.
A few days ago, Jang Do Pal
and Seo Joon Oh met.
I think Jang Do Pal heard
something from Seo Joon Oh.
But I don't know what he said.
Well...
I'm sure he understands that it's over
as soon as someone finds him.
Anyway, I found him,
so you don't have to worry.
For your case,
I'll find an expensive lawyer
and prove that you're innocent.
Okay. Thanks.
I have one more good news to tell you.
You didn't know that CEO Hwang's
health deteriorated, did you?
I feel like it is divine intervention.
He's hanging on by a thread
so there's no way he'll wake up
and expose the truth about you.
So you don't have to worry.
Okay.
That's... good news.
Jang Do Pal.
Do you really want to miss
your last chance to live?
If you keep your mouth shut
and trust Tae Ho...
In the end, you will both be ruined.
I thought you had finally come to
a realization when you agreed to meet me
but I guess you still don't believe me.
That punk who tried to murder
Hwang Jae Gook was following your orders.
Even if we don't find him,
we can lock you up for good.
Do you know why?
It seems like...
CEO Jang found out
I kept you alive and hidden.
Because of that, he might testify
for Seo Joon Oh.
What should we do?
Should I have killed you
when I had the chance?
What if... I take care of Jang Do Pal?
Let's think of something.
- Is that true?
- Jang Do Pal is going to testify?
How? What got into him?
I guess he's ready to die.
Yesterday, CEO Hwang and Jang Do Pal met.
Do Pal.
I want to rip you into shreds.
But if you testify...
I'll request
favorable arrangements for you.
Testify for Joon Oh.
But what is Jang Do Pal going to say?
You told us before
that it will be hard to free Seo Joon Oh
from Choi Tae Ho's conspiracy charges.
Right after he was rescued,
Choi Tae Ho told Jang Do Pal
that he killed Yoon So Hee.
He agreed to testify to that tomorrow.
Wow, Joon Oh is going to be so happy!
Now, all we have to worry about
is getting Jang Do Pal
to the court room safely.
Choi Tae Ho probably knows by now
that Jang Do Pal is going to testify.
Yes, Prosecutor Lee.
Jang Do Pal will testify for Seo Joon Oh
tomorrow. Did you know?
If he testifies tomorrow,
you will lose this battle.
That will inconvenience me as well.
What are you going to do now?
Can you stop this from happening?
I guess he decided to testify in the end.
Seo Joon Oh.
I came because I was worried,
and I missed you.
It's been hard on you, hasn't it?
You've done a great job.
We just have to get through...
one more day.
It'll all be over tomorrow.
By tomorrow, we'll clear your charges,
and get you out of here.
Trust me.
- He still hasn't called, has he?
- No.
Bong Hee!
- Lawyer Jo.
- They just left.
What's wrong with them?
So?
There was an accident,
but I don't know the details--
I just need you to find out
Seo Joon Oh's location.
Lawyer Jo. Something's not right.
- I think something happened.
- I can't reach Prosecutor Yoon.
Pardon?
I'll look into it.
- They'll be here.
- Why aren't they here?
- They're not picking up, right?
- I can't contact the vehicles
and I don't know where they are.
What on earth is going on?
What can we do?
If Joon Oh and Jang Do Pal aren't here,
we can't have a trial.
- This won't do. Let's find them.
- No, you can't.
If we want to find them,
we need to be escorted by the police
but I think Lee Jae Joon
is stopping that from happening.
It's not easy.
- Yes, Prosecutor Yoon!
- I'm sorry.
What happened? We were worried
because we couldn't contact you.
I should have told you what was going on,
but Choi Tae Ho's guys got to me.
What about Seo Joon Oh?
We haven't found him yet.
They couldn't have gone very far.
I'll look for them. I'll call you later!
Yes.
Gosh, how long do we have to wait?
I'm going crazy.
Prosecutor Lee is stopping us from
doing anything, so we have no choice.
If we ask someone to find out their
location, I won't feel so frustrated.
I can't stand this. Wow, this is
the power of the prosecution, huh?
Oh.
There is one person who can help us.
I heard you decided to stand
as Seo Joon Oh's witness.
You didn't think I knew you were doing
other things behind my back, did you?
Even if I were doing other things,
or acting like an asshole...
You shouldn't treat me like this.
When Jae Hyun died...
I told you I couldn't stand it,
and that I would turn myself in...
but what did you say
after I said that so many times?
You told me you'd help me.
You said you'd take responsibility.
But, because of Jae Hyun,
whom I didn't even kill...
Since I was on that deserted island...
I wanted to live like other people...
so I lived while killing people.
But now...
you want to stab me in the back?
You can't do that.
If I'm going to die,
you're going to die with me.
Congresswoman Jo.
Bong Hee.
Congresswoman Jo lost her voice,
so she can't talk for very long.
I'm not here to hear what she has to say.
I'm here because I need your help.
Please help us.
You know exactly what happened
on that island.
- Bong Hee, she is no longer responsible.
- No.
She is responsible.
She is responsible, as the chairwoman
of the special investigation committee.
But not once did you act the part
in the special investigation committee.
If you had really
listened to us even once...
And supported us,
and stood on our side...
If you had done your job, even once!
Then we wouldn't be where we are today.
So how can you say
you're not responsible for this?
- You--
- That's why...
I'm giving you a chance.
I'm giving you once last chance...
to act like the chairwoman
of the special investigation committee.
What do you want to do?
Are you going to run away again?
Just like you've always done?
She knows how to talk.
Yes, how have you been, Director?
Oh, my voice? It's from my election
campaign. I'm embarrassed.
Well, I'm calling you because...
I have an urgent favor to ask you.
Yes.
I...
Because of you...
If it weren't for you...
I...
Tae Ho!
No! You can't do this anymore!
Just to hide your mistake...
Just to hide that...
Are you planning to run for the rest
of your life while killing people?
You son of a bitch!
Does that make you happy,
you son of a bitch?
When I didn't have to worry
about anyone else...
I was comfortable when we landed
on that deserted island!
That was when I was happy!
Let's end this.
Tae Ho.
You know...
I really want you to be happy.
We can't go back to how we were before.
But because I'm kind...
I will stay by your side.
Tae Ho.
Let's end this.
How did I become this person?
You worked hard, taking
my insults all this time.
Not at all. Please have
a relaxing vacation.
The people who made the wrong choice...
The people who regretted it afterward...
The people who tried to conceal
the truth with a lie, were punished
and everything finally
returned to normal.
Please come with me.
Let's go.
Let go. Let go!
Let's make it beautiful!
Don't frown like that!
Bong Hee, I have something to tell you,
but I don't know how to say it.
- Did I surprise you, Bong Hee?
- These are seagulls!
Smile. Smile.
- You look cute!
- Hey!
You can't do that!
Prosecutor, why are you so serious?
Hey, don't touch me!
Tae Ho!
Hey, Secretary Tae! Run after you finish
your work, you crazy child!
- What's your occupation?
- Manager.
Manager, right? Managers--
- Worry about yourself!
- Okay, Ji Ah.
That's why, I want to talk
about Bong Hee--
Is it Bong Hee or me?
You! I choose you! Yes!
Ji Ah, you can't do that! Ji Ah!
Even if we look happy,
we all have some pain inside us.
Why do you keep looking at people
like that? Even on the island!
How many people did he kill?
It's a secret?
I'm in a good mood,
and you're pretty too.
- Isn't she cute? Isn't she?
- She is!
CEO Hwang!
Hey, you punks! Don't touch
my hair! Hey, stop it!
- Why do you only get mad at me?
- Hey!
Hey, you punk.
Hey, Secretary Tae! That punk.
Why can't you get your act together?
Huh?
- Byung Joo!
- I'm sorry!
- What's wrong with you?
- I tripped on the tree.
- Put it back up!
- Stop that!
- Please go over there.
- Be careful!
What is it?
What is this?
- Ki Joon, I stepped in something!
- He stepped in poop!
Why is there poop up here?
It's manure, but it fell...
- It's dog crap.
- What? What's wrong?
- Did you fart?
- No!
- Bong Hee, who pooped?
- Oh!
- Joon Oh, it's poop.
- It is?
- He stepped in it!
- Hey!
Why would you poop there
when you could go to the bathroom?
- Joon Oh, when did you do that?
- I didn't poop!
How could you step in it? Did you step
on the land mine intentionally?
- Wait, the smell is spreading!
- Geez, I think I stepped in it.
Wait, no. It's not poop. It's not poop.
You'd better take care of that!
- Secretary Tae, he's so cute!
- That's all that matters!
We'll get going! Take care of that!
Why do you keep staring like that?
Get out of the way.
- Gosh, this smell.
- Why is there poop?
- I told you not to move your foot!
- Why?
- It smells.
- How could they leave because of this?
Wait! Your foot.
Stand still, Seo Joon Oh.
Stop!
- Geez.
- How did you step in poop?
They left? Why aren't you leaving?
How could I leave someone
who stepped in poop?
Geez. Why aren't you wearing
the necklace I got you?
I'm keeping it safe at home.
Don't just keep it safe. If you don't
use it, it's worth less than crap.
- Hey. Don't move.
- Hey, but...
Isn't it nice to be together again?
It reminds me of the deserted island.
I know. That was nice.
Bong Hee, there's something on your face.
Here?
No, lower.
- Where?
- Next to your lips.
Here.
- Wait, no--
- It's not coming off.
- What do we do? What else can we...
- There's another way.
And what's that? How do we erase it?
Well...
Let's see.
- Why are you closing your eyes?
- I did it for no reason.
- I guess it's bright out.
- It is. I'd better close them again.
What?
Geez! How could you tell me
about that now?
- Gosh, that smell.
- Hey.
Joon Oh, what do we do?
I was just told about this interview.
What interview?
Ji Ah had an interview scheduled
for today, but forgot.
- Hey, what about my face?
- You should have told me earlier!
We're having an interview
after I stepped in poop while painting?
The smell of poop won't be recorded
for broadcast.
Hello, I'm Seo Joon Oh.
Joon Oh stepped in poop!
I won't be able to star in a movie
for the time being--
Joon Oh stepped on a mine a while ago!
- Byung Joo, take this away!
- Wait. Yes.
You should remove this!
I am happy to greet you
on this broadcast. I will...
- When you commit a crime--
- Hey!
It ends up this way.
Please don't commit...
any crimes.
I know. It's okay.
What was it again? Ki Joon,
"Don't hate the crime, hate the person?"
Yeah, that's right.
They say, "Don't hate the crime,
hate the person."
Which camera should I look at?
- Bong Hee, are we on TV?
- Mom, we're on TV!
Hello! One, two, three!
- Hello!
What relationship?
PD, does everyone date after
being stranded on an island?
Well, we just take care of each other.
It's cold. Let's stop.
We dated, but we don't love each other.
Please don't ask about her dating life.
Please ask about her work.
- But I'm not working on anything.
- There are six movies on hold!
I feel bad. I should do better.
I will work a lot harder.
And we still haven't given up on Yeol.
We're still looking everywhere for him.
I learned from CEO Hwang,
to always work for our actors...
I'm a man who's not scared of anything--
That scared me! I'm sorry.
That scared me.
After I was dismissed...
I converted to a job
where I mentor high school students.
Please talk faster.
It's not fun. It's a business
relationship. Yes, I'm just learning.
You see, this man has great character,
and works really hard.
I'm a pretty good worker myself.
That's because I learned it from him.
At first, I graduated and worked
somewhere else
- and then my aunt called me...
- Your aunt?
Oh, Congresswoman Jo is my aunt,
but she...
left for a vacation.
- Byung Joo! Byung Joo!
- Yes?
- Jo Hee Kyung...
- Do you know me?
- The truth is, I like Bong Hee--
- Me?
- Oh.
You do?
- Please paint more actively.
- Yes.
Not with your mouth,
but with your actions.
Please show me.
- Stop it!
- Don't tell me to stop!
Ji Ah, what are you trying to express?
So this is the style that Ji Ah likes...
Oh! Oh!
That side is a little empty.
What do we do?
- Wow.
- This is amazing.
- Bong Hee.
- Yes?
- We're doomed.
- We are. I'm speechless.
I knew this was going to happen.
I didn't.
- What do we do?
- Should we start over?
- We can do it again!
- Look what you did!
Look, both sides are equal!
Both sides look good together.
- Let's paint over it!
- How?
You can do it.
We can do this!
Oh! Someone has to press the button.
- Timer! Three...
- Don't come here.
- Two! One!
- Get ready!
One, two, three!
[Thank you for watching "Missing Nine."]
Subtitles by DramaFever