Subtitles by DramaFever
You son of a bitch!
Why didn't you listen to me?
- Ji Ah, it'll be okay... Ji Ah...
- Okay... Okay...
You son of a bitch! You dumb bastard!
You bastard!
Stop it!
You son of a bitch.
Why do you keep making me
into the crazy one, you bastard?
Yeol!
I found the necklace your brother
gave you. You wanted to find this!
Right? So Hee, please.
No! Don't go down there!
No! Why are you doing this?
Come to your senses! You can't! No!
- Let go of me!
- Get yourself together!
Let go!
What's wrong? Bong Hee, what is it?
I remember everything.
It wasn't me!
I didn't kill her!
She's on the move.
Take me to Seocho-dong, please.
[Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young]
At 2 p.m., Chairwoman Jo Hee Kyung
of the special investigation committee
will announce some new findings.
A few days ago, one of the 46 people
who went missing, Actress Yoon So Hee...
According to Ra Bong Hee's statement...
The special investigation committee
was silent about Ra Bong Hee's statement
so the nation is very interested
in the announcement today.
One person involved--
Mister, please take me
to the Seoul Convention Center. Hurry.
In order to tell the truth, Yoon So Hee's
cause of death will be announced.
It's time.
Are we doing the right thing?
What would you know?
You just follow my orders.
Let's go.
[Episode 6]
Now, I will brief you on the daily record
related to the plane crash
of Legend Entertainment.
The special investigation committee
has been investigating the plane crash
and we rescued our first survivor
Ra Bong Hee, from Huizhou, China.
However, due to the trauma
from the plane crash
Ra Bong Hee experienced temporary
dissociative disorder and memory loss.
Seo Joon Oh, Lee Yeol,
Jung Ki Joon, Ha Ji Ah
Choi Tae Ho, Hwang Jae Gook,
Tae Ho Hang, and Yoon So Hee.
Besides the fact that she spent four
months on a deserted island with them
she was unable to remember
any other details.
And as a result, our investigation
became a little complicated.
Meanwhile, on the 17th of last month,
one of the 47 missing people...
Actress Yoon So Hee's body
was found in Huizhou, China.
[On the 17th of last month,
actress Yoon So Hee...]
She was murdered.
And on the 19th of last month,
through cooperation with China
a deserted island was found in China
where nine missing people were stranded.
Ra Bong Hee, who visited that island
to regain her memory...
[Miss Ra Bong Hee's memory...]
She said--
Um... They found another survivor.
Prosecutor Yoon. It wasn't me.
I regained...
all of my memory.
Ra Bong Hee, who visited that island
to regain her memory
is currently doing the best she can
to recover her lost memory.
That is all for our special announcement.
We will accept questions in writing.
Who's the survivor?
Hwang Jae Gook,
CEO of Legend Entertainment.
But there was an accident...
What's the problem?
After he was rescued, he was on his way
to questioning, but was in a car crash...
I'm sorry.
How long is this going to be dragged out?
Tell them to get him
to Korea as soon as possible.
And why is that girl here? Get her out
of here before the reporters get to her.
Are you certain?
- Yes.
- Then...
Who killed So Hee?
It's Ra Bong Hee!
- Did you really lose your memory?
- Do you remember who the killer was?
Please say something, Ra Bong Hee!
I'm sorry, we will announce it soon!
We'll contact you later!
- Please tell us!
- Okay, sure!
After I get things sorted, I'll bury you.
You son of a bitch!
You bastard!
Is he dead?
Dead? He just fainted.
- Let's go and get ready.
- Where?
We should go and find the kids.
I heard they're on the other island
shivering, waiting for us.
Right now?
Yes, right now. Why? Are you... scared?
No, I'm not scared. But I can't see
anything clearly right now.
If you can't see anything,
it's even worse for them.
If we're scared and tired,
they're even more... scared and tired.
Who'll save them if we don't?
They're probably starving and shivering.
It doesn't matter if we lose the boat,
and we end up living here forever.
People are more important.
I'll go even if I have cuts all over my
body. Even if my bones are broken.
I'll go no matter what.
To save our So Hee...
and our Bong Hee.
So Hee, are you okay?
Bong Hee, I'm sorry.
Blood! This won't do.
Let's go back to the beach, okay?
- Okay, get in.
- We won't all fit!
Who wants to come with me?
- I'll go.
- Okay. How about Ho Hang?
- Huh?
- Okay, you can come too.
CEO Hwang, please watch
Tae Ho while we're gone.
- I'll stay and comfort Tae Ho. Be safe.
- Mister, here.
- Ji Ah, don't get hurt.
- Okay. Be careful!
Okay! One, two, three!
Push from the back!
Okay! Get in! Get in! Get in!
Get in! Get in! Get in!
Geez!
- Wait!
- What are you doing?
Ji Ah, don't lose your cool
when we see Tae Ho, okay?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to kill him.
Here, get in! Hold this.
One, two, three!
One, two, one, two...
- One, two, one, two, one, two!
- Joon Oh!
- One, two!
- Are we good?
- We're good.
- It's okay, right?
- Yes.
So Hee!
- Over here!
- Over there!
Are... Are you all right?
Ye... Yeah... Your head--
No, it's okay. Geez, what a relief.
What's wrong with your face?
Why... Why are you by yourself?
Where's Ra Bong Hee?
- She went to find something for me.
- Geez, what did she go looking for?
You... You should have gone with her.
Ki Joon. Ki Joon, I'll look for her.
- Okay, be careful.
- Stay here, okay?
It's only been two days,
but it's so nice to see you!
- I'm so sorry! I'm sorry...
- It could have been worse.
- I'm sorry...
- Why are you sorry?
The fire. The fire. The fire.
It was scary, wasn't it?
You knew we were coming, didn't you?
Geez, what a relief. What a relief.
It's okay, we'll live.
- Who are you? Who are you?
- I'm the new stylist, Ra Bong Hee--
It's in your hands now,
whether we'll shoot today or not.
If you fire me,
I won't be able to support myself!
You won't starve to death
with this strength!
I told you not to eat it!
We're on a deserted island!
Are you crazy? Why did you eat it?
Why? Why? Ew, gross!
You're my stylist, and I'm your artist!
Who calls their artist crazy?
Do you want be fired?
Thank you for saving me.
You would have done the same for me.
I'll share the blame with you.
Hey, of course you should.
You're my stylist.
Don't worry. I'll hit him for you.
I'm sorry... for leaving you
behind by yourself.
What are you doing over here?
Seo Joon Oh.
Seo Joon Oh. Are you really Seo Joon Oh?
Are you okay? You're alive, right?
You're really Seo Joon Oh, right?
Blood... Blood... What do we do...
Are you hurt? What do we do?
Eat.
Hey, Ra Bong Hee.
Listen to me carefully.
Don't put other people's needs
in front of your own anymore.
Don't go into the water by yourself
just to save someone.
Don't do anything dangerous
for other people.
I'll take the risk.
I'll go into the water, and I'll do
the dangerous things, so...
Don't do anything.
Got it?
Yeah, I figured it was hard for you.
Let's go home. I'm hungry.
Let's do it together.
Stay right by my side.
You can do that, can't you?
Let's go.
Ki Joon, where?
Take a right, a left, and a right.
Come here. Joon Oh. Joon Oh. Joon Oh.
Hey, what are you saying?
The trees all look the same...
So Hee. Here.
You can have it.
This?
No way, this is precious to you.
How could I...
That necklace...
has a really special meaning.
My brother told me this necklace
was going to protect me.
Then it's more meaningful to you.
Take it.
No, you should have it.
You were the one
who protected me all along.
If it weren't for you,
I would have died already.
Anyway, you take it. It's a present!
So Hee!
- Wait for me!
- It wasn't that way! You liar!
- Why are you always lying?
- Hey, when did I lie?
Are you talking about that day
when you shot with the octopus?
Joon Oh, you were supposed to
catch the octopus in the mud...
- How do you... Look at this!
- You catch the octopus in the mud.
- Look at this! He's a total liar!
- You catch the octopus in the mud--
How do you catch an octopus in the mud?
- Joon Oh!
- CEO Hwang!
Oh, hey! Have you seen Yeol?
Seo Joon Oh, where's Yeol?
- What about him?
- We can't find Yeol.
- Excuse me?
- What are you talking about?
We think Choi Tae Ho did something.
We can't find either one.
- Joon Oh!
- Seo Joon Oh--
Tae Ho!
Yeol!
- Yeol!
- Manager Jung!
- Yes!
We shouldn't stay together.
Let's split up and look for them.
Then the three of us,
and the three of you?
You guys look over there! Be careful!
- Okay, be careful!
- Be careful.
- Yeol!
Tae Ho!
Yeol--
We're going to debut tomorrow.
How many years will we last?
If our first album flops, we're over.
How far are you thinking?
We won't become distant,
and break up, will we?
I hope that doesn't happen.
It won't happen. Why are you
worrying about useless things?
Just think about having
a good performance tomorrow.
Geez, I have no room!
This is what I think.
If we keep working together...
Yeol!
We'll become jealous of each other...
- We'll get worried...
- Choi Tae Ho!
We'll have secrets...
and we'll have misunderstandings...
We'll have fights...
and we'll resent each other.
Even when that happens...
Even if we grow apart...
and end up fighting in the mud...
Let's not doubt each other...
or pull out a knife.
Let's trust each other until the end.
Okay?
- Geez...
- What was that?
- Huh?
- What did you do?
- Huh? What?
- I smell...
Hey, what did you just do?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I think I ate too much for dinner.
Wait, what the heck did you eat?
Did you eat crap?
Hey, wait... What did you eat?
- I'm opening the window!
- Hey, wait! It's cold!
- Hey, it's cold!
- Hey.
How much did you eat?
Hey, you ate crap...
Wait, it smells. Geez...
Even if he was hungry, why did he...
Geez, we should remember
to feed him every day.
- Because it's our debut tomorrow--
- Geez!
- Stop it...
- What? What? What? What? What?
- It's crap.
- It's not... It's not crap...
Wow, seriously.
What? What? What? What do you want?
I think I have crap in my nose.
I must have been nervous.
That doesn't mean you should eat crap.
What should I do tomorrow?
This might happen tomorrow.
- Then go to the bathroom!
- What if I'm already on stage?
Then we should end the show quickly.
- You can't fart on stage.
- You can't.
Geez, we're actually going
to make our debut.
I can't help but think
it was Tae Ho, Joon Oh.
Where could he have gone after
he tied me and Ji Ah to that tree?
Seeing how Yeol disappeared...
So Manager Jung, you're saying...
You think Tae Ho did something to Yeol,
and packed his bags and fled out of fear.
Hey, no way!
Tae Ho and Yeol had a good relationship.
Unlike Tae Ho and Joon Oh.
I agree with what Manager Jung said.
Tae Ho is capable of much worse.
I normally don't talk
about my ex-boyfriends...
But I'll do it today.
Choi Tae Ho,
that bastard, is a piece of trash.
Our Yeol...
Choi Tae Ho definitely
did something to him.
What do we do about our poor Yeol?
No, we don't know yet.
I'll look for them.
Tae Ho and Yeol must be
somewhere on this island.
Even if it takes days or months,
I'll look for them.
Let's go together.
How can you cover
so much ground by yourself?
No. I'll look for them.
Even if we weren't acknowledged,
I'm still the frontman of Dreamers.
Who'll find them if I don't?
Ki Joon, please stay and take care
of the food and clothing.
- Hey, Seo Joon Oh, you punk.
- I can do it.
I have to do it.
Seo Joon Oh!
Yeah, what is it?
Are you leaving already?
Let me come with you.
No. You need to stay here. If you're
not here, everyone will really starve.
Um...
This. Eat this when you're hungry.
What is it?
- You took the bones out.
- You said you didn't know how.
Thanks. I'll enjoy it.
Go back to sleep.
Wait...
When you find Choi Tae Ho...
What do you plan to do?
What do you mean?
If Choi Tae Ho killed Lee Yeol...
And if that's why he ran away...
When that becomes clear...
What...
do you plan to do to him?
I don't know.
I'll probably be angry.
I'll probably think about whether
I should kill him or keep him alive.
Tae Ho!
Yeol!
That's why I won't think
about that right now.
If I think about that already...
If I think Yeol is dead...
and if I think Tae Ho killed him...
I don't think I'll try very hard
to find them.
I'll find them first.
And then I'll ask them...
what happened.
I'll ask them how we ended up
in this state.
That's what I'll ask first.
Make sure you bring them back.
Okay.
Thanks.
Wow, we were out in that blood bath,
but she can't remember it?
Wow, she can't be like that! She should
remember of all people! She should!
What really... happened on that island?
Our CEO Hwang is sleeping so peacefully.
Isn't he being too disrespectful?
Well... Such accidents don't happen
with any kind of warning.
I didn't know you'd take me
seriously, Doctor.
That was just my frustration talking.
I'm so frustrated.
Please contact me if he wakes up.
Chairwoman Jo.
If... he happens to pass away
what should we do then?
Then you should call his family, not me!
Oh, yes--
Oh. Yes. Yes, the thing is, Minister.
I'm sorry about announcing it
without consulting you first, but...
Gosh, how would I know that? I didn't
ask her to lose her memory, Minister.
No, I'm not defying you...
Pardon? The attacker
who killed Yoon So Hee?
Well, that's what I'm the most
curious about--
He... Hello? He...
Damn it!
If he was going to just talk at me,
he should have written a letter instead!
What did he say?
He wants to know why Ra Bong Hee lost
her memory and who killed Yoon So Hee!
If I knew that,
would I be here like this?
That crazy bastard. Does he think
he's Sejong the Great or something?
I can't deal with this.
Oh, it's Investigator Oh.
I'm not in a good mood. If it's not
good news, don't tell me anything.
What?
Are you serious?
Ra Bong Hee remembers everything?
- You said it call came back.
- Yes.
Why are you telling me that now?
She just remembered, so I... I'm sorry.
How much did you get out of her?
You know the singer, Lee Yeol?
She said he went missing.
That's what we secured so far.
That good-looking kid went missing?
Yes. He went missing,
but she said Choi Tae Ho was to blame.
Choi Tae Ho?
Choi Tae Ho...
That kid who was in that drama?
- Yes.
- Why would he? Why Lee Yeol?
No, forget it.
Yoon So Hee. Does she remember
who killed Yoon So Hee?
Yes. She remembers it clearly.
Okay. Then keep going
with what you were doing.
This isn't a variety show anymore,
it's a documentary. Got it?
Yes. A documentary. I understand.
Chairwoman Jo just arrived.
That's why... from now on
you must tell us everything
very accurately.
Do you understand, Ra Bong Hee?
Yes.
Then please continue where you left off.
From the point when Choi Tae Ho
and Lee Yeol went missing
to the point where you tell us
who killed Yoon So Hee.
Please tell us the truth,
without leaving anything out.
Nice! Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
- Okay!
- I'm good now.
- My turn?
- Wow, that was good. Come here.
- Ouch!
- You're so stiff.
Hey, you're so stiff.
You're stiff everywhere.
Hey!
- Pardon?
- What are you doing?
Why is a manger rubbing
an actress's shoulders?
No, that's not it.
Ji Ah helped me move something earlier
and her shoulders seemed stiff,
so I was massaging them for her.
It looks like you've forgotten
after being here for so long.
I'm the CEO of your company.
The groups Chiming and Blue Angel
went missing after the crash.
We don't know if our Yeol
is alive or dead.
And Choi Tae Ho is responsible
for that! I'm your CEO.
Our Ji Ah, whom you're massaging,
and our weak little So Hee!
These two girls are all I have left.
You shouldn't be massaging each other.
Especially when we get out, got it?
- We weren't flirting or anything--
- Got it?
Yes, I understand what you're saying.
I'll be careful from now on. I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about? When I think
about it, something's off.
What's wrong with Ki Joon and me?
Why can't we make physical contact?
We're getting along just fine so far.
Listen to what this wench...
Hey, don't you know the risks of rumors
spreading about an actress and manager?
You're better off with Tae Ho.
At least he has a higher rank.
I'm sorry. I will be more careful.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Why do you keep apologizing?
Stay still for a second! Stay still...
CEO Hwang, who has a lower rank?
Is Ki Joon a lower rank?
How is he...
Hey, I'm not that great either!
Why are you being so sensitive?
I told you, no. Got it?
You shouldn't be acting like this.
Don't do it. Listen to your CEO.
- I'll rebel if you tell me not to do it.
- Don't do it.
I really hate it when someone tells me
what to do and what not to do.
What did you just tell me not to do?
Don't do anything with
Manager Jung. Don't do it.
- Ki Joon, do you want to go out?
- What?
We see each other every day.
Go out where? We're out right now.
Hey, why can't you understand me?
Let's date. You and I.
You want to... date? You want us to date?
Why? Don't you want to?
No, it's not that...
I just don't understand...
this situation--
Do you want to or not?
Answer me right now.
I think I understand it now.
Let's date, sure. Let's date.
Let's date. Let's date! Let's date!
We're dating now! It's our first day!
There's not much to it!
I'll stay by her side, comfort--
Hey, that's enough. Ki Joon is
my boyfriend now. Okay?
Ji Ah. Ji Ah!
Should I rebel even more?
You'd better not do it.
You'd better not date... Manager Jung.
Then I will.
Tae Ho.
I did it.
And CEO Hwang, don't mention
that bastard, Choi Tae Ho, ever again.
Okay?
Ji Ah!
She's crazy.
Hey! Come back here!
Why are you running away? Hey!
Why are you running away?
You son of a bitch! Why are you running?
Why are you running away? Huh?
Tae Ho! Yeol... Where's Yeol? Where's--
I don't know!
Tae Ho!
Where is he? You son of a bitch!
Hey, Tae Ho!
Let go!
Come here!
Yeol... Yeol! Where's Yeol, you bastard?
He's dead? Huh? No, right?
He's not dead, right, Tae Ho?
He's not!
You didn't do something to him,
did you? Tell me! No, right?
Tell me it's not true!
Tell me it's not true,
you son of a bitch!
Tell me it's not true!
It was an accident.
I really... had no intention
of killing him, Joon Oh.
Yeol tricked me
and devised a scheme behind my back.
That's why I did it.
If Yeol had listened to me
and had left the boat alone
none of this would have happened.
We need to survive!
No...
We can't die here, Joon Oh.
You, Yeol, and CEO Hwang...
Why are you taking it out on me?
We can't die here, Joon Oh...
We won't become distant
and break up, will we?
Even if we grow apart...
And end up fighting in the mud...
Let's not doubt each other
or pull out a knife.
Let's trust each other until the end.
Joon Oh!
Joon Oh, no! Wait a second!
Joon Oh! I didn't do it on purpose!
Joon Oh...
- Manager Jung.
- Yeah, Bong Hee. Come here.
- What did Ji Ah say?
- She said you shouldn't worry.
- And?
- She said she's sorry.
And... And...
She said she did it without any emotion.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, really.
Oh, I didn't have any feelings,
but Ji Ah didn't either?
Oh...
In your opinion, did it look like
Ji Ah didn't have any feelings?
I didn't have a good view
so I couldn't tell
if there were any emotions.
- I'm sorry, Manager Jung.
- No. No. Why are you sorry?
Hey, anyway, what a relief! I would have
felt bad for Ji Ah if I was the only one!
- What a relief. That's good.
- What a relief.
What a relief.
Did Ji Ah say anything else?
Yes! She wants you to tell her when CEO
Hwang bothers you. She'll protect you.
- She'll protect me?
- Yes.
Bong Hee, isn't that something guys
usually tell their girlfriends?
Um... Normally, that's true.
Even for kissing...
The guy usually is the instigator.
Then... what does that make me?
Wait, many girls initiate
the first kiss these days...
Bong Hee, have you ever initiated a kiss?
- Oh! No, I haven't!
- No? I haven't either.
Then... have you ever felt embarrassed
when you didn't do anything
or felt like you were stripped naked
when you didn't say anything?
No, I've never felt like that.
Oh, me either.
I'm okay.
- Cheer up.
- It's okay. It's okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay! I'm fine.
Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
What happened out there?
Are you hurt? Are you all right?
- Blood! You're bleeding! You got hurt?
- Hey, what is this?
Don't deny it. You're bleeding so much.
Gosh... What do we do...
Hey, get over here!
Choi Tae Ho.
You son of a bitch!
Get up.
Hey!
What did you do to Yeol?
What did you do to Yeol? Where is he?
Where is he? Tell me! Tell me now!
What happened? Did you kill him?
Did you kill him?
What is it?
Where is he? Why won't you say anything?
What did you do? What did you do to Yeol?
Where's Yeol? What did you do to him?
Even if they curse at you,
suffer through it.
If they hit you, stand there and take it.
Endure all of it by yourself.
They have the right to do it.
And...
You'll pay for the sin you committed.
For Yeol...
Always feel sorry...
And live with that guilt for the rest
of your life, you son of a bitch.
Joon Oh.
I know what you're saying
but are you really okay...
living here with Tae Ho?
We can't just leave him to die.
Tae Ho will die too
if he continues to live alone.
I don't know why you're looking out
for that bastard, Choi Tae Ho, but--
- I'm not looking out for him, Ji Ah--
- Listen to me.
You said he killed Yeol.
You said you heard him admit it.
That's right, Joon Oh. If we think about
Yeol, keeping Tae Ho here isn't right.
So should we kill him?
Should we?
Should we leave him
out there alone to die?
What?
Is that what we...
Is that what we really want? Huh?
Tae Ho was wrong... No, he did
something that was unforgivable. I know!
I know, and it's driving me crazy! But...
But, that doesn't mean
we should let another person die.
We're not that cruel, are we?
What if Tae Ho volunteers to leave?
- What?
- If he says he'll leave on his own...
That means we can let him go, doesn't it?
That wouldn't be our fault.
I'm just saying.
Just in case something like that happens.
Why did you want to see me?
I have a request.
Say it.
Can you leave?
What?
I don't want to stay here with you.
You killed a man.
- So Hee.
- You remember what I said, don't you?
- How will you send a rescue team?
- If we look, it's possible.
How can I trust you?
I saw what you did.
- What did you see?
- Should I say it right now?
I know what kind of person you are.
That's why, if I tell everyone
about what I saw
you won't be able to stay here.
But you know that already, right?
So Hee.
- I don't know what you're saying.
- Stop playing dumb.
You know it, and I know it.
So what are you going to do now?
Are you staying or leaving?
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
You're staying, huh? Okay, fine.
Then I'll make you leave.
So Hee.
If you tell them, we'll all die.
I won't be the only one who gets hurt.
- I know.
- You'll get hurt too.
Do you know what you're doing?
Let's all live together.
Don't get any strange ideas.
Let's just all live together, okay?
Tae Ho, let's just...
Let's just die together.
If we don't, I think the others
will get hurt because of you.
It's so hard to live.
Ch... Choi Tae Ho killed Yoon So Hee?
Yes.
Wait, are you saying everyone knew
Choi Tae Ho killed Yoon So Hee
and continued to live together?
At first...
We thought it was suicide.
So Hee!
So Hee...
So Hee was having a really hard time
and in the end...
There was something Secretary Tae said.
So Hee said she was having a tough time
and that she wanted to die...
And then she suddenly walked out,
so I just thought...
I just thought she was going for a walk
to calm herself down.
Why are you saying this now, Punk?
And then?
You thought it was suicide...
How did you find out
that Choi Tae Ho killed Yoon So Hee?
The truth is...
Secretary Tae was a witness.
Who's there?
So Hee.
So Hee!
Be quiet if you don't want to die.
He said Choi Tae Ho threatened him.
If he told other people
about what he saw...
I'll kill you too.
You... You'll get hurt before then!
We outnumber you...
Did I say I was going to touch
the others? I'm only going to kill you.
After I kill you,
I might as well die with you.
So, Ho Hang...
Let's not die together.
Let's think about
living together instead.
Honestly, compared to So Hee...
I'm more useful to the group.
You're saying...
Secretary Tae only said
Yoon So Hee committed suicide
to conceal Choi Tae Ho's murder.
We have enough information
to be certain that it was Choi Tae Ho?
Yes.
Let's get ready to announce it.
It's going to be very noisy
for the next few days.
Yes, this is--
Very good. Let's keep going.
After Yoon So Hee died, what happened--
Stop! Stop, right now!
They found another survivor.
He's arriving in Korea now!
Um...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
- Who's that person?
- Reporter Kim. He was on our plane.
- The patient at the Chinese hospital--
- Did you find out?
Was Yoon So Hee there too?
You know, don't you? I feel like
you know why Yoon So Hee died.
That day, was anything else
weird about So Hee?
That's why we should know! Do you think
someone could have killed her?
- Don't say that.
- Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you, you son of a bitch?
Look at this! Why was he on our plane?
You killed her. Isn't it wrong to kill
someone and pretend you're innocent?