Subtitles by DramaFever
Yes, Manager Jung.
We're in trouble, Bong Hee!
Tae Ho is headed your way!
- Pardon?
- Get Joon Oh out of there!
We must fix it no matter what.
I need to know what information
is on this phone.
I want to know what's on this phone,
that everyone wants so badly.
I need to be the first to know.
I'll put it where you told me to.
Then get going.
I'll be right behind you.
Yes.
No way.
You're alive?
You can't be alive.
I'm not alive, Tae Ho.
That's why I'm at peace.
[Episode 13]
You did a good job, Seo Joon Oh.
You restrained yourself well.
Look where you're going.
Okay.
How did it go?
Did you find the cell phone?
No, it wasn't there.
And since Tae Ho left with nothing,
Congresswoman Jo must have it.
And by the way...
I ran into Tae Ho.
That happened
a lot sooner than we expected.
It looks like we'll be busier
starting tomorrow.
Joon Oh is alive?
What do you mean?
- He's alive.
- Tell me the details!
Seo Joon Oh is alive.
Is it that easy for you to say
that Seo Joon Oh is alive?
Don't raise your voice at me.
It won't hide the fact that
you've been trying to push me aside.
What do you mean?
That was because...
I heard Ki Joon and Ji Ah were there
so I was afraid your presence
would raise suspicions.
Why would I ever push you aside?
How can I expect to make movies
by myself?
If I wanted to push you aside,
why did I help you?
Ever since I crawled into
that fire pit to save you
- we became a team.
- That's why...
That's why I don't understand.
Tae Ho.
You still don't trust me?
Did you find out...
where the cell phone is?
It's unclear.
I'll have to keep looking for it.
When you find out where it is,
make sure you let me know.
I'll decide if I should trust you or not
by watching your future actions.
Okay?
In the meantime,
I'm going to search for Seo Joon Oh...
so round up the guys.
Okay. Let's do that.
While we're at it, we'll send him to
the prosecution and prove your innocence
and we'll get rid of that cell phone
so that we won't be dragged around
ever again.
We'll be spotlessly clean.
Okay?
The sky is so dark in Seoul.
The night sky on the deserted island
was so bright.
- The stars could have poured down on us.
- Yeah.
Do you remember that?
When things were difficult
on the deserted island
I looked at the stars in the sky...
and was comforted.
I know, right?
When we were on that island
I was only thinking about
how to eat and survive.
When I think about that... Bong Hee.
I felt more at ease
when we were on that island.
Oh, that's right. I should
give this to you before I forget.
When I was in trouble,
this reminded me of you.
That's why... I bought it.
You can have it.
What is this?
It's pretty valuable,
but you can have it.
What is it though? You should tell me so
I can decide if I should take it or not.
Hey, I bought it because
it reminded me of you, so just take it.
But, before I--
Hey, seriously!
Forget it then!
- Hey, Seo Joon Oh, why--
- Geez.
Hey, why are you using your strength
again? You agreed not to do that.
I only grabbed you lightly, but...
Here. Take it.
Geez, you're so strong.
Yeah, Mom. Did you sleep well?
Of course I did. How about you?
Yeah, I slept well too. Isn't it hard
traveling up to Seoul so often?
Hey, not at all! It's not hard for me.
The bus takes me everywhere.
No, it's hard on you.
I'll go down there from now on.
Oh, sure. It's been sunny these days
so I'm busy with work anyway.
- Don't forget to eat, okay?
- Go back to sleep. Okay.
What's wrong, Seo Joon Oh? What is it?
Hey! Come here! Hey!
Hey! Hurry... Geez!
- What if they break it?
- We can fix it later. Let's go.
Those guys are looking at us,
aren't they?
Yes, they're making it pretty obvious.
It looks like they're curious
about where Seo Joon Oh is.
They're monitoring a prosecutor?
Those punks...
They have some nerve.
- Hello!
- Yes!
Jung Ki Joon!
Hello.
Why did it have to be our Ji Ah?
Manager Jung, haven't you looked after
Ji Ah since she was in middle school?
Do you really want to do this with Ji Ah?
Why does our Ji Ah have to get mixed up
with you and suffer like this--
Mother, that's not it...
Stay away from our Ji Ah.
Ji Ah is all I have left.
Listen carefully, Manager Jung.
Ji Ah has been the head of our family,
ever since her brother died.
She's a kind daughter who only cares
about her mother and her work.
I thought she was finally about to bloom
so I can't watch her crumble because
of the rumors about your relationship.
If Ji Ah is that precious to you,
stop selling her out.
Don't you feel sorry that she's still
working so hard after barely surviving?
She's a kind daughter?
Who does that benefit?
What's the use of working so hard?
She doesn't even get 10 won of her salary
because she's a kind daughter?
Mother.
If you're sincerely worried about Ji Ah
please stop using her, and let her go.
Because of the money
you mooched off her company
Ji Ah has to work until she's 60.
Do you understand that?
Who are you to tell us what to do?
I spent so much money on her
to make her into who she is
so why can't I take some of it back?
Ji Ah.
- Mom, come here.
- Yeah, okay.
Ji Ah, did you hear
what Manager Jung said to me?
- I did, so stop.
- Okay.
Yes, CEO Jang.
Yes.
Joon Oh is back.
Joon Oh?
Do you mean our Joon Oh, who died?
Stop the act. I saw Joon Oh last night.
I didn't call you here
to hear your answer.
You'd hate for others to get hurt,
just to save Joon Oh, wouldn't you?
You saw Ji Ah's mother today.
It hasn't been long,
but she came back to take more money.
That woman won't stop
until her daughter dies.
That's why you and Ji Ah
had better figure out where you stand.
Do you really think
CEO Hwang was in an accident?
Don't be scared. I won't kill you.
I'm going to kill Ji Ah.
Does Ji Ah know why you gave up
being a doctor?
Oh, that's right.
She doesn't have to know.
Since Ji Ah is going to die soon.
I'm only going to kill Ji Ah.
Don't forget your promise
to take responsibility for Ji Ah,
if I kept her alive.
I told you multiple times
that I remember.
And Joon Oh has feelings too, so if
I went back, would he even accept me?
After what I did to him...
Even if he would accept you,
do you have any interest in going back?
Why are you twisting things like this?
Then can you show it to me?
Show me how you really feel.
Ji Ah!
Ki Joon. Later. Let's talk later.
I have an interview to go to.
Oh, you have an interview?
- Get going then.
- Okay.
[Seo Joon Oh]
I'm here.
Prosecutor Yoon! Over here! Over here!
Hello!
Get up, Seo Joon Oh. We should give them
our chairs. They're our guests. Get up.
Here, please sit here! Please sit.
Yes. Yes. Okay.
How did you find this place?
This was the best place we could find
that was free and had no people around.
Seo Joon Oh can't be seen by anyone,
as you already know.
Thanks to you, I feel like we're camping
during work hours. How nice.
I see that Jung Ki Joon isn't here.
We don't have to worry about him
for the time being.
Instead, this is my manager.
He's my small and compact spy.
Please say hello.
I've already met Prosecutor Yoon.
I'm Byung Joo.
- You're working hard.
- Let's begin, Lawyer Jo.
Oh, sure.
We compared what you told us,
with the findings from our investigation
and tried to determine
what's on Yoon So Hee's phone.
So Hee said she had proof
that Shin Jae Hyun didn't commit suicide
but she kept changing her story.
That's why Journalist Kim
looked into it himself.
I'm sorry. I can't make it.
Hello! Long time no see.
- I'm here to ask about Shin Jae Hyun.
- That case is closed.
But no matter how hard he searched,
other than So Hee's word
there was no other proof
that it wasn't a simple suicide.
- Hello.
[Myungsung Report - Kim Ki Hwan]
But then an anonymous source
shared decisive photographic evidence.
When he had to start at square one,
he probably thought the way we did.
If the culprits disguised
Shin Jae Hyun's death as a suicide
by making it look like he jumped...
Jae Hyun!
Let's talk.
Choi Tae Ho went to see Shin Jae Hyun...
I'm almost there.
There was someone else who helped him
with his crime and alibi.
Now that we're all here,
let's hear what he has to say.
At the time, the police said there were
CCTVs at the front and back doors.
They reported that both cameras
were broken
but Journalist Kim obtained
CCTV images from the front door camera.
I looked into it, and the back door
CCTV was broken
and was left alone for quite some time
but the front door CCTV was only missing
the footage from
the time of the accident.
It wasn't broken.
If Jang Do Pal
was Choi Tae Ho's accomplice
he would have used the back door
instead of the crowded front door,
when he was leaving.
And then he bribed the security guard
to erase the front door CCTV footage.
The security guard who was bribed,
quit his job right after the incident
and we still haven't been able
to contact him.
- This weekend--
- No. No. No.
We're now wondering if Jang Do Pal
pushed Shin Jae Hyun's body.
And we're also wondering
what is on that cell phone.
Tae Ho...
was cast by Jang Do Pal.
He couldn't sing, but CEO Jang liked him
because he had star qualities.
If it was for Tae Ho, Jang Do Pal
would have run over to help him.
Journalist Kim also said Jang Do Pal
threatened So Hee
so we can be certain about that.
And...
I'll talk to you when I get back.
What else could it be?
There's only one thing we'd talk about.
- And?
- Pardon?
Never mind. Please eat.
Huh? Joon Oh,
she said she can meet us now.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Who are you talking about?
She said she could see us right away,
but what time is it now?
We've only waited for 10 minutes.
Let's wait.
She said she'd come so she will.
But Seo Joon Oh,
you've never met Lee Se Mi before?
After Jae Hyun's incident,
I didn't get along with So Hee
so I don't know anyone on her staff.
Anyway, I'll ask the questions,
so just stay like this.
Cover your eyes, cover your mouth,
and just listen, okay?
Fine.
Oh, she's here. I'll be back.
Hello! Hello! I've heard a lot
about you. Isn't it cold? Drink this.
I warmed up this coffee because
it's cold out. It's warm. Have some.
It's okay. Have some. It's delicious.
Se Mi, you worked for Ji Ah,
but transferred to So Hee's team, right?
- Was it for a year?
- Yeah, about a year.
Wait.
Did you call me here to talk about
Yoon So Hee, and not Ji Ah?
Wait, where are you going? Have
some coffee. Please talk to us. Don't go.
Right. It's okay! It's okay!
Just for a little bit. I'm right here!
I can't hear anything.
Se Mi worked as So Hee's stylist
for the longest time.
Other stylists changed their numbers
and can't be contacted.
- It was difficult to find her.
- Gosh, thank you.
Why don't you tell her about So Hee?
It's okay. Let it out. Let it all out.
What's the use now?
Well, it's hard working as a stylist.
I know because I tried it briefly.
Some actors can be picky or sensitive.
Was So Hee a sensitive person as well?
You know,
she was pretty weird to be honest.
- Hey, where did you put my phone?
- Your phone?
- Yeah, my cell phone.
- Don't you have it?
I gave it to you before my shoot!
I told you to take care of it
better than you take care of yourself!
Move.
So Hee! Oh my!
At first, I just assumed
she was addicted to her cell phone.
But she was moody and indecisive
all the time.
I was about to go insane
from being around her.
I was tight on money from my student debt
so if CEO Jang hadn't given me a bonus,
I would have quit right away.
Don't think doing
what you did to Jae Hyun.
I already have my insurance.
If something happens to me,
we're all going to die.
And on top of that,
she treated CEO Jang so badly.
I was amazed that
CEO Jang took it.
- Hey, no way!
- No, it makes sense.
It's more likely that she was threatened.
How could she have threatened CEO Jang?
No.
I thought CEO Jang did everything
because he adored So Hee...
but now that I think about it,
So Hee was controlling CEO Jang.
- What are you doing?
- Wait.
[Standard Contract for Movie Actors
Yoon So Hee]
Now, you're even stabbing
your own family member in the back.
Hey, how could you do this? Huh?
Ji Ah, please give it to her
just this once.
The director wants So Hee.
What can we do?
You said he created that character
for me.
First, you sent my stylist to her team
and now she's taking my roles?
So Hee.
What weakness did you find in
CEO Jang that you became such a star?
Are you happy?
On the day we got on the plane,
I heard So Hee talking to Jang Do Pal.
- What did she say?
- "Let's talk about it when I get back."
But could it have been
about Shin Jae Hyun?
But it didn't sound like
she was being pushed around.
If So Hee wanted to threaten Jang Do Pal
she needed evidence about Jae Hyun's
death. Did she really have it?
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho are
going crazy looking for So Hee's phone
so wouldn't that mean her phone
contains evidence?
How did So Hee get that evidence?
Gosh, when did you become so naive?
- Wait, is your stab wound okay?
- It was up here.
- Joon Oh!
- Yeah?
I don't have to meet Tae Ho today.
He said Ki Joon is with him,
so he doesn't need me.
- What does that mean?
- I'm not sure
but Tae Ho and Ki Joon were together
all day. It's not like they're married...
Why are they together?
I'm sure they have their reasons.
- Eat this.
- Yes, I need to eat.
Take all of it.
Let me know as soon as you find out
where it is.
Remember, I have to see it
before CEO Jang does.
Tae Ho, where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Ki Joon.
If you keep agonizing over it,
Joon Oh and Ji Ah will both die.
Don't try anything weird.
Okay.
I heard the news yesterday.
I heard Choi Tae Ho went through
Investigator Oh's car.
He must have acted without thinking
because he was in a rush. I apologize.
Why is everyone acting this way?
Are you looking for that cell phone
as well, by any chance?
Congresswoman Jo,
I guess you haven't seen it yet.
Why are you smiling like that?
It's nothing. It might be better
that you don't find out.
You made the right choice not to check.
What's on that cell phone
that made you so anxious?
All you have to do is give us
the cell phone.
If you give it to me
I'll take care of it myself.
Then you won't have to worry,
and you won't be harmed.
However, if this leaks out...
What if it does?
I can respectfully tell you that
we will all be in danger.
After how far you've come
there's no need to inconvenience
yourself before the election.
What could possibly be on that phone,
that would harm me as well?
Wouldn't it better
if we end this case completely?
If you agree, please give it to me
without asking any questions.
I promise you
we won't put you in harm's way.
I will think about it.
Remember that it's out for repair.
Yes.
Then I'll wait for your call.
Goodbye.
What was that about?
Tell them to fix it quickly.
Now, I'm so curious I might go insane.
I understand.
She said the cell phone is out
for repair. Find out where it is.
Yes.
- This...
- Eat this.
This...
This is much better than
any average video call.
And the sound...
What does this look like?
- A speaker.
- Oh, you know!
The sound quality is really great.
Let's try it out.
Isn't it nice?
Doesn't it look like a microphone?
Oh, it does.
- It's unexpected.
- Oh.
It's Investigator Oh.
- Hello?
- Bong Hee.
- Did you call me?
- I have a question for you.
You received lost items from the deserted
island not too long ago, didn't you?
There was a cell phone.
It was So Hee's cell phone.
Bong Hee, how do you know that?
Um, where is it?
That's a secret. It's out for repair.
But, is that why you called me?
Why are you interested in it?
Because it was So Hee's cell phone.
I wanted to check something.
Thank you, Investigator Oh.
- Hey, where do they fix cell phones?
- Cell phones?
She hung up without asking how I'm doing.
Fine, I see how it is.
[The cell phone is repaired.
Please pick it up.]
Fine. Fine...
I asked around, and near
Jo Hee Kyung's election headquarters
there are three repair shops that are
known to fix broken cell phones.
It's probably at one of those shops,
so how about you go there first?
Yes, they just arrived. Please come here.
Let's go inside.
What is this?
Who are those people?
I should know why we're here.
We need to catch Seo Joon Oh
and find the cell phone.
Why would Joon Oh come here?
Tae Ho.
So... So, what can I do?
You just have to stay by my side.
Okay.
- This is...
- It's number 103 on the third floor.
- Search everywhere, got it?
- Yes.
What are you doing?
I was texting Byung Joo.
[If you find out where it is...]
I was asking him to let us know
if he finds out where the cell phone is.
Let's go.
- Sir, where are you going?
- We're here to find the cell phone.
Cell phone? Where?
- It's not here either.
- What is this?
- Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
- Bong Hee.
Lawyer Jo found out the location
from the special investigation team.
I'll send you the location via text.
Hurry over there. I'm on my way.
Really?
- Look carefully.
- Yes.
- Tae Ho! Tae Ho! Tae Ho!
- Hey, there they are!
They found out where the cell phone is.
It looks like CEO Jang is on his way.
[Ki Joon, CEO Jang is
on his way to get the phone.]
Geez, the person who dropped it off
should pick it up.
Oh, this is so bothersome.
Hello, you said the cell phone was ready.
I just finished the repair.
- But how did you know?
- You texted me.
I did?
Who are you? Who are you guys?
- Hand it over.
- What?
What are you doing?
Get him.
These people! Let go! Who are you people?
Hey, who are you?
Let go!
Good work.
Ouch, Congresswoman Jo.
We're in trouble. The cell phone...
- Look.
- Yes, I see him.
- Let's follow him.
- Yes.
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
Bong Hee.
I'm near the center and following
Jang Do Pal's car. Follow me.
I have a feeling
he's going to Legend Entertainment.
A man by the name of Journalist Kim
was on the island.
But that man...
had CCTV footage of me in Jae Hyun's
apartment on the night he died.
The footage that you told me you erased.
- What?
- You...
released those photos, didn't you?
What are you saying?
Why would I have done that?
I didn't think you had any reason
to do that at the time...
but because these things keep happening,
I'm starting to think you did it.
I'm sure that cell phone...
will tell me why you did that.
Hey, what are you doing?
- This son of a bitch!
- Hey, Choi Tae Ho. Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
What are you doing? Catch him!
You dumb bastards.
What are you doing? Follow him!
Find that cell phone! Hurry!
- He couldn't have gone far!
- Geez!
[Audio]
Tae Ho. Do you... want to live?
Yes.
I want to live.
Okay. You should.
I'll save you.
Okay. I got it.
CEO Hwang and the kids are coming.
Get out of here.
I'll take care of this.
- After I go outside...
- Take a lap around the block in a taxi.
You need to arrive when
the others arrive to avoid suspicion.
What? Do you want to die with him?
All you did was open your mouth
and stress me out.
Who knew you would be
so much help to me?
Close your eyes.
Let's send you off.
Sa... Save me...
Jae Hyun.
- Save me...
- Jae Hyun! Jae Hyun...
Save me...
Let's send you off.
Die! Die!
Die!
He could have lived.
What have I been doing?
What is this?
It's a knife!
[Jung Ki Joon]
Where are you?
Okay.
There he is!
Are you all right?
What are you doing here?
- Do it.
- No.
Do it!
- No!
- Do it!
- You have to pretend you didn't see me!
- I'm sure they know already--
- You still have to pretend.
That's how we can both stay safe.
Listen to Tae Ho for now.
You have to refrain from doing anything,
so that we both stay safe.
This is the only way we can both survive.
This is how we can help each other.
I'm with him, just like you told me
to be, but I don't know if this is right.
He's looking all over for you.
Where are we going?
Where do you think we're going?
You're his guardian, right?
Wait a minute!
Really?
Seo Joon Oh found Choi Tae Ho.
- Yeah, I'll go there right away.
- Right away?
I should hurry.
Geez, it's so late. Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Is that a trending phrase?
Why are you always sorry?
What are you going to do?
They ganged up on me...
- How are you going to find it?
- Are you looking for this?
The murderer wasn't Seo Joon Oh,
it was Choi Tae Ho.
Jung Ki Joon, do you know
what you're doing right now?
I do.
I'm prepared to receive my punishment.
I lied, but I think it's time for me
to tell the truth.
Yoon So Hee's murderer was Choi Tae Ho,
not Seo Joon Oh.
And Ha Ji Ah wanted to tell the truth,
but because of me
because I wanted to take Choi Tae Ho's
side, she had no choice but to lie
so please take that into consideration.
What are you staring at?
How did you get here, Seo Joon Oh?
You're asking me what I was thinking
to come back, aren't you?
Is that... how it sounds?
Prosecutor Yoon told me to see you first.
You haven't heard yet, have you?
Please listen.
Tae Ho, do you... want to live?
This won't change much.
- I got it, you can go home.
- Okay.
By the way, why are you doing this now?
It's up to you whether or not
you want to be honest
but do you think this will
change anything?
It's hard to believe that you're doing
this for your own conscience.
It's not like Seo Joon Oh
suddenly showed up.
I'm just saying
what I should have said earlier.
It's not because Seo Joon Oh's alive.
[My So Hee]
He's dead.
Choi Tae Ho.
Sa... Save me...
- Jae Hyun. Jae Hyun...
- Save me...
Let's send you off.
In one shot...
Die! Die!
[My So Hee]
[Incoming Calls
My So Hee]
[My So Hee
Today, 10:48 p.m.]
Yoon So Hee.
This is what really happened
when Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal
killed Shin Jae Hyun four years ago.
And those two...
disguised it as a suicide.
- And Yoon So Hee recorded this?
- Yes.
And I think So Hee was killed
because of this.
I could have gone straight
to the prosecution...
but there is one reason...
why I came here first.
As the chairwoman of the special
investigation committee of this case
please save me, Seo Joon Oh,
the last survivor.
Please tell everyone
that I am alive, and that I've returned.
And to prove my innocence...
It's not like I did anything wrong
but I'll talk about it
at the press conference.
I know it's not the right time
to bring this up...
But when the special investigation
committee wrapped things up
we received a call from China asking us
to collect a body. Do you remember?
They told us about the bodies we missed,
and Journalist Kim's location.
Now that Seo Joon Oh has come back
I think...
Seo Joon Oh made that call.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
When the contents of that phone
are released, it'll be a huge blow.
- We have to block it.
- So Hee's phone will be taken too.
If you came alone without evidence,
you won't change much.
She blamed you for killing him
when she knew the truth?
I can't stand this.
I killed your bandmate.
How can I expect forgiveness?
I kept him alive because he couldn't
talk. I have to kill him before he talks.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I have to turn myself in.