Subtitles by DramaFever
So Hee said she was having a hard time,
and that she wanted to die.
And then she just walked away...
If you thought it was suicide
how did you find out
that Choi Tae Ho killed Yoon So Hee?
The truth is...
Secretary Tae was a witness.
Oh! So Hee!
He said Choi Tae Ho threatened him.
If he told anyone what he saw...
I'll kill you too.
So Secretary Tae lied to everyone
and said Yoon So Hee committed suicide.
To conceal Choi Tae Ho's murder.
It looks like it'll be quite noisy
for the next few days.
Yes, this is--
Let's continue.
- After Yoon So Hee died, what happened--
- Stop! Stop right now!
They found another survivor.
He's landing in Korea right now!
That's why I'm asking, who's the survivor
that you're not telling me about?
What? Hey!
Are you looking down on us?
This is the chairwoman
of the special investigation committee.
You still cannot enter. Please go back.
- What are you saying--
- Investigator Oh.
Let's wait and see
what they're up to behind our backs.
Bong Hee. You're hoping
it's Seo Joon Oh, aren't you?
I... I think it's Seo Joon Oh.
That's Seo Joon Oh's manager.
[Episode 7]
Hey, you must have gone through a lot.
Oh, they're here too.
The survivor who came back...
is the murderer.
Let's go.
Move!
Choi Tae Ho.
I'm Jo Hee Kyung
of the special investigation committee.
Where have you been?
Did you know you came back
at the most unbelievable time?
- I'm not sure what you mean.
- It's true.
Shall we hug as a congratulatory gesture
for your safe return?
I heard you killed Yoon So Hee.
We'll see each other again soon.
I think everyone is still very shocked.
After what happened to So Hee and Yeol...
They must be scared. People who were
by their side started disappearing.
"We might never get rescued.
We might end up living here forever."
That's probably what they're thinking.
It's normal to be scared right now.
That's true. It's normal.
So we should work even harder
to get out of here safe and sound.
Seo Joon Oh, you should be careful too--
Seo Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
What are you doing in there?
Hey, do you think I'm here
because I want to be?
Your words sadden me at times. Last time,
you asked me why I stepped on a mine.
You might as well ask me why I was born!
Here, grab my hand. Come on!
Huh?
Thorns! They're thorns!
Why are there thorns?
Hey, why are these here?
Thorns! Thorns! Thorns!
Those aren't thorns. Those are bones.
Give them to me.
There should be more down there.
Look for more.
It's a cow.
- Thorns!
- They're bones. Hand them over.
What kind of bones are they?
- It's a rabbit.
- Pardon?
Wow, Ki Joon said the rabbits here
are huge, but they were this big?
Wow, what did the rabbits eat
to grow so big?
Hey, this isn't a rabbit.
These bones should go here.
No, it's a rabbit. It's a scary rabbit--
It's not.
The way I see it, I think it's a pig.
- What?
- I know because I love pig feet.
I'm certain this was a pig.
This is a pig's foot. Its front leg.
The front legs are the most tasty. You
know that right? They're so good.
- The back legs are better.
- The front legs! You don't know!
Anyway, why are there pig bones here?
Well, I'm sure it fell into the hole,
they way you did.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It fell when it was passing by.
- Probably.
- Let's stand guard.
- Here?
Let's stand guard
until another pig falls in!
If we catch a pig, can we eat meat!
That's right! We can!
Let's stop eating seafood!
Everyone is out of energy!
- They'll gain so much energy from this!
- They will! They will!
Do you know why corporate employees
always go out to eat meat?
I've... never worked for a corporation.
Seo Joon Oh, give me my first paycheck
when we get back to Seoul.
Okay? I want my first paycheck.
Okay. I'll think about your rate
when we get back.
- Today, I'll catch you a pig!
- Really? Sounds good!
Life is so hard. Gosh...
- Hey, Ha Ji Ah!
- Yeah?
- What's that smell?
- That's not important. Stop that.
Stop what?
You know what I'm talking about!
Stop acting on impulse
in front of CEO Hwang.
When was I acting? Why?
Why else? Even if it was a joke,
do you know how precious your lips are?
And the other person's feelings...
She told you not to feel burdened.
She feels sorry. She didn't mean it.
I didn't mean it,
but Ji Ah said she didn't either?
Anyway, don't do it.
- Ki Joon, I--
- Don't. You shouldn't joke like that.
If you joke like that one more time...
I'll really date you.
Bullshit.
Do you know how scary I am?
You can't handle me. I'm a real man!
I don't give up either.
It's scary just thinking about it,
isn't it? That's why you should stop.
Ouch, that hurts. That hurt a lot.
Anyway, don't joke around
about things like that!
I guess we'll just date then.
Seo Joon Oh.
Did we do a good job with our camouflage?
Hey. When I served my military service
there was a time when I was undercover
in an area with many trees.
My squad commander peed on me
thinking I was a tree.
That makes no sense. How could
someone mistake a person for a tree?
That's how well I was hidden!
A neighboring platoon hammered a nail
into me to set up their barracks.
Men don't... Ouch! It stings! It stings!
- What's wrong? Seo Joon Oh!
- My neck! Something's on my neck!
Take a look. Ouch, that stings.
Leaves got in, didn't they?
Gosh, you startled me! Gosh.
I almost died.
By the way, are all men like that?
Do they all lie
when they talk about the military?
Yeah. They all lie.
It's cold now that the sun's setting.
Go back. I'll stay here.
Where would I go? I'm not leaving.
I'm going to stay here.
Why? You look uneasy.
Well... It's because of
what you said before.
You told me not to do anything alone,
and stick by your side.
I'm just doing what you told me to do.
Well, it's not like
I'm from the Joseon Dynasty.
I can't just stick to you and scream,
"Help! Save me! Feed me!"
Hey, that's not my thing.
I can't do that.
So let's do everything together.
Let's look out for each other like this.
You can look after me,
while I look after you.
Now that it's night, it's getting cold.
You can ask me for help, to save you,
and to feed you.
I'll do everything by myself,
so don't disappear.
Don't leave my sight.
After the plane crashed, you were
the first person I saw when I woke up.
If you disappear...
or if something happens to you...
It'll be really hard for me.
That's why...
I don't want you to look out for me.
I'll look out for you.
Until we get out of here.
- Oh!
- Oh my gosh!
Oh! It's a pig! We have to catch it!
Where is it? Catch it!
No! Do... Don't throw that!
Please don't throw that! No...
- How's CEO Hwang?
- He's surviving one day at a time.
Who knew he'd live
after the car was crushed like that?
But they said it's almost impossible
that he'll wake up
so don't be too anxious.
But I am.
I am anxious.
CEO Jang, you haven't done
anything right so far.
Hey.
Am I wrong? You couldn't take care of
Ra Bong Hee, so she's back in Korea.
- I didn't know. I didn't know!
- Is that all you can say?
What would you have done
if she hadn't lost her memory?
The chairwoman of the special
investigation committee told me...
She said...
she knows I killed Yoon So Hee.
How does she know that?
Did Ra Bong Hee get her memory back?
I'll take care of it.
People in politics are all the same.
Let's shake up the playing board.
Shake it up.
The people who were on that island...
They all have to die.
That includes...
Ra Bong Hee.
Let's hold a press conference.
Let's hold a press conference tomorrow
and expose the fact that
Choi Tae Ho killed Yoon So Hee.
- Can you do it?
- Pardon?
Can you do the press conference?
You said you're certain.
Oh. Yes, I'm certain.
I'll do the press conference.
Okay, secure the location,
and find a good hair salon for her.
- Um, Chairwoman Jo.
- Yeah?
- Isn't it too soon?
- What do you mean?
Choi Tae Ho just came back, but if we
make him into a murderer right away--
Investigator Oh. How long ago
did Yoon So Hee die?
- It has been three months, hasn't it?
- Yes.
Criminal cases, should be
centered around the victim.
That's why, it's not important to us
that Choi Tae Ho returned today.
It's more important that
Yoon So Hee died three months ago.
Let's be respectful to the deceased,
Investigator Oh.
I understand.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
[Choi Tae Ho's Top Secret Return]
Yes.
It's me, ma'am. You're quite busy
these days, aren't you?
Yes, what else is new?
You're busy too, aren't you?
Since we're both busy,
I'll just get straight to business.
That would be nice.
It's about the person Ra Bong Hee
said was the murderer.
Who was it?
Prosecutor Yoon, you must be curious
about a lot of things.
Wait a day longer.
You'll find out soon enough.
Who do you think you're trying to trick?
You arrogant punk...
- Prosecutor Yoon.
- Yes?
It's about what you asked me last time.
About the patient
in the Chinese hospital.
Yes. Did you find out
who was in that room?
According to our source
from that hospital...
Prosecutor Yoon, the thing is...
Who is it that you can't tell me?
Is it the president of Korea?
It was Choi Tae Ho.
Who?
Choi Tae Ho.
Then are you saying Choi Tae Ho
intentionally delayed his return?
Is that what you're saying,
Detective Lee?
- Why?
- I'm not sure why yet.
Nice to meet you. Are you Chairwoman Jo
of the special investigation committee?
Yes, but...
Oh, you must be that CEO
of Legend Entertainment. Jang...
Yes. I'm Jang Do Pal.
Oh, yes. Yes. Jang Do Pal.
I remember you.
But, what brings you here?
Our Tae Ho wanted to meet
with you in person.
Why does he want to meet me?
Let's get going. I'll escort you
to a comfortable location.
I told you we'd see each other again soon
but I didn't know
I'd see you again quite so soon.
Are you here to turn yourself in?
It wasn't me, Chairwoman Jo.
You have the wrong information.
I didn't kill her.
Then who was it? Who killed
Yoon So Hee on that island?
I didn't know there were
other people so close by.
I should have looked around sooner. Geez.
- Were you here alone all this time?
- Yes.
Wow. You're very skilled!
He did a good job making this.
When I opened my eyes,
the remains of the plane were right there
so I packed up everything from
the plane and found a place to live.
- Can I eat this?
- Yes, go ahead.
Thank you.
Geez, after living day to day...
- It's been a few months now, hasn't it?
- I think so.
The weather has been unpredictable,
and it's getting colder.
It must have been hard by yourself.
Just when I thought I was going to die,
I ran into you two!
That's a relief.
- A pig would have been better.
- Pardon?
Did you hear? Anyway, we normally
wouldn't have come out this far.
We were all lucky.
Anyway, nice to meet you, Seo Joon Oh.
I'm Kim Ki Hwan, an entertainment
journalist at Myungsung Report.
Oh. You're a journalist.
I knew you looked familiar.
Have you interviewed me?
Oh, I remember interviewing
Yeol and Choi Tae Ho.
Seo Joon Oh! Look at this! Look!
It's a radio, isn't it?
- Hey, no, it's not...
- No, it's a radio.
- Did you not serve?
- I served my time!
It is a radio!
Does it work?
Wow. Where did you find this?
- Give it to me.
- It's heavy, be careful.
Someone from the military
must have been here.
I was walking by and found it.
Does it get a signal?
Well, it looks like soldiers were here
too. Didn't you find anything like this?
- We didn't find anything special here.
- Does it work?
Hey! If someone can fix this,
it could work. Who knows?
Secretary Tae! He went
to a technical high school!
- Really?
- Seriously?
- He might be able to look at it!
- He's in there. Call him out.
Oh, but didn't he skip our last meal?
I'll get him something--
Hey, leave him alone!
How many days has it been?
Okay.
Do you even know what you're doing?
What's wrong with Secretary Tae?
Did something happen?
Oh, he's just not feeling well.
He's not?
Choi Tae Ho is alive too?
- It's broken.
- This doesn't work.
Let's ask Secretary Tae.
Choi Tae Ho?
Who are you?
I'll be living with you from now on.
Please look after me.
You didn't tell me who you are yet.
Oh... I was a journalist.
But does that really matter here? Call me
whatever you like. "Older Bro" is fine.
"Excuse me" is fine too.
He's a journalist?
- Really?
- Yes, I'm telling you!
Hey, no way!
He's not dating her!
That actor is dating a singer!
Hey, I know who he is. He's my friend.
- Really?
- Didn't you know?
- Wow, really?
- No way. No way.
No, really! During a live broadcast...
Joon Oh. Let's talk for a second.
You were totally fooled.
Were you fooled all your life?
You're too much.
Who's that person?
He said he's Journalist Kim.
He was on the same plane. Why?
Are you letting just anyone join us here?
Who do you think he is?
Hey, he would have died if we'd left him
alone. How could I leave him there?
In what way does that person look like
he's about to die?
Is this your first time meeting
a feisty journalist? What's up with you?
Do you actually believe
he's a journalist?
What if he's not? Why would that matter?
Gosh, this man. Get up! Get up! Get up!
I bet this doesn't hurt
because you're fat.
Ho Hang, something bad could happen.
You'll collapse!
- Ho Hang!
- I'm okay.
Mister, this is your last chance.
If you don't eat, that's it.
Let's get up. Okay. Please open wide.
- Eat.
- Open wide.
I'll eat it myself.
I'll eat this by myself, so go out there
and do what you need to do.
- Okay. Eat.
- We'll get out of here no matter what...
But please forget about it already.
You weren't the one who killed So Hee.
- Ji Ah.
- You did nothing wrong.
- Geez, seriously. Ho Hang!
- I'll eat.
Eat, okay? Forget it, let's go.
Make sure you eat, Secretary Tae.
Don't eat it then!
You should have let it slide.
Did you have to say that?
I don't know. I'm pissed off. Is he the
only one suffering after So Hee's death?
We're having a harder time.
Even if you're pissed off...
He needs to eat.
You always say everything that's
on your mind without thinking.
Are you talking about Yoon So Hee?
Was Yoon So Hee with you too?
She died a few days ago.
Wait, why? I mean... How?
She committed suicide.
Suicide?
CEO Hwang scolded Secretary Tae for not
saying anything to So Hee as she left.
CEO Hwang said Secretary Tae
killed So Hee.
That's why he's acting like that.
He won't eat and has no energy.
Because he feels guilty.
Ho Hang.
Did you stay in here all day again?
Yeah.
Go outside and see some
sunlight tomorrow.
Don't stay inside too much.
Don't forget your meals either.
Everyone is worried about you.
Yeah... I will.
Good night, Ho Hang.
Choi Tae Ho, you know, don't you?
I feel like you know...
why Yoon So Hee died.
She must have been scared.
Scared? Of you?
No.
Of this island.
Where should I put this?
You can put it over there.
Oh, these are cooking so well.
I'll help you cook these.
- No, that's okay.
- No, I can do it.
About what you said yesterday...
About Yoon So Hee.
Oh, yes.
Why do you think it was suicide?
Because we saw her dead body.
But when someone commits suicide,
there should be signs, don't you think?
Someone should have suspected
that she would. Something like that.
Can someone decide to commit suicide
overnight?
Think about it carefully. Think about
how she acted before she died.
Is it ready?
- I'll finish it.
- Give it to me. Yes.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
- It's burning. I'll do it--
- Let go! I'll do it.
Don't block the wind. Go.
That day...
Is there anyone else who thought
So Hee acted strangely?
Mister, you said you talked to
So Hee that night.
Was anything else strange
about So Hee that night?
- What are you saying all of a sudden?
- It's not all of a sudden.
It's been bothering me
for quite some time.
She told me she wanted to return to Seoul
together. But she died the next day.
And she committed suicide.
Does that make sense?
Does anyone else know anything?
Did I bring up something unnecessary?
We're all thinking the same thing!
I too...
have been frustrated all day long.
I'm upset, but what can we do?
What can we do? There's no solution.
I feel sorry for So Hee too.
That's why we need to find out.
If it wasn't suicide...
Don't you think someone
could have killed Yoon So Hee?
Who would have killed So Hee?
Don't say things like that.
Damn it!
What are you doing here?
Go inside if you're finished.
- Why did you bring that up?
- Geez, you scared me!
Why did bring that up all of a sudden
just to make everyone anxious?
I didn't bring up anything pointless.
I probably know a lot more
about Yoon So Hee than you do.
You have to believe me.
Don't trust... Choi Tae Ho.
He's a dangerous man.
He probably killed Yoon So Hee too.
Who the hell are you?
Come out.
Come out, you son of a bitch!
Who the hell are you? What the hell
is this, you son of a bitch?
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Let go. Let go! Look at this. Look at it!
I told you, didn't I? This bastard is up
to something. We have to kick him out!
Why would he have boarded our plane
with this? Why did he follow us here?
Let me see!
Who is this?
Jae Hyun and So Hee!
Are these yours?
Wait, why do you have these...
That was the first article I wrote.
Shin Jae Hyun's suicide incident.
I told you, didn't I? I know more
about Yoon So Hee than you do.
I got to know Yoon So Hee after that.
These two were secretly dating.
This is what Choi Tae Ho said.
He said he didn't kill Yoon So Hee.
He asked me to believe him instead.
- But Ra Bong Hee said Choi Tae Ho--
- What job are we here to do?
Pardon?
What is our job as the special
investigation committee for that crash?
No, forget that.
What job should we be doing?
We should investigate
and reveal the truth--
The truth?
How are we supposed to know the truth?
What are you trying to say?
It's his word against hers.
Whose side should we take,
so that we'll get fewer insults?
He probably killed Yoon So Hee too.
It was an accident...
I really... didn't mean
to kill him, Joon Oh.
We need to survive!
You, Yeol, and CEO Hwang...
Why are you doing this to me?
We can't just die here, Joon Oh.
Geez, you scared me.
You should indicate
your presence next time.
Who the hell are you?
- Huh? I told you I'm a journalist.
- Stop joking around.
Why did you come here
and bring up Jae Hyun and So Hee?
Why are you confusing everyone?
Geez, what confusion?
If you don't want everyone to be
confused, why don't you just tell them?
This man is seriously...
Tell them what?
What should I tell everyone?
That you killed her.
Isn't it wrong to play innocent
after killing someone like that?
You're a real actor now, huh?
Your acting skills have improved.
You crazy bastard.
Whom did I kill?
We'll find out who the crazy one is...
later on, right?
Move.
Why are you all doing this to me?
I don't know why you're looking out
for that bastard, Choi Tae Ho...
But you said he killed Yeol.
You said you heard him admit to it.
That's right, Joon Oh. If we think about
Yeol, it's not right to keep Tae Ho here.
Then should we kill him?
What if Tae Ho volunteers to leave on
his own? Then we can let him go, right?
That wouldn't be our fault.
Seo Joon Oh.
About this afternoon...
Your mind is pretty chaotic
because of Choi Tae Ho, isn't it?
Yeah, well, you know...
Talk to me if you're struggling
with anything.
Tae Ho, that punk...
If I made up my mind to trust him...
I should continue to trust him
until the end.
But I've been overwhelmed
with many thoughts these days.
After I brought him here...
I shouldn't be like this.
I have a lot to think about.
When you have too much to think about,
being active is the best solution.
I saw a whole field of mushrooms
in the woods a few days ago.
Let's all go tomorrow and pick mushrooms.
Make Choi Tae Ho do all the work
so that he doesn't cause trouble.
As if he would do all the work.
Hey, he's just like me.
He doesn't use his body.
Well, then... we'll just leave him here.
- Then why would we tell him?
- It's basic manners to ask him.
- Let's go.
- It snowed a lot in the woods.
We'll look at the snow,
and pick mushrooms. It'll be fun.
- There are mushrooms?
- Yes!
There are so many! You'll be surprised!
- Should we all go together?
- Yes.
Okay. Let's go.
Hey, Secretary Tae.
Are you really not going to get up?
Let's go! It'll feel like we're hiking,
and it'll refresh our moods!
CEO Hwang. I'll rest, just today.
- Journalist Kim, get up! Let's go!
- Please let me stay.
I feel so happy
after a good night's sleep.
They're not coming!
You should come with us.
It'll be just the two of you here.
Don't worry about Secretary Tae.
I'll make sure he eats.
Please take care of him.
Ho Hang, I brought you water.
- Let's go, CEO Hwang.
- Sure.
Geez, these shameless punks.
I'm only letting it go this time!
- I think we should take all of this.
- Will this be enough?
- Let's go!
- Oh.
What about Journalist Kim
and Secretary Tae?
Secretary Tae isn't well, so Journalist
Kim will look after him. Let's go.
It's a good idea to go on a field trip
for some fresh air. Bong Hee is smart.
- Ji Ah, let's go!
- Follow us with this.
Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
- We'll be back!
- Rest well!
How could there be mushrooms
in a field covered in snow?
No, CEO Hwang! When I came last time,
there were so many!
- I'm sure they're dead by now!
- They were nearby. Wait a minute.
- There's so much snow.
- Let's go! Hey, let's go.
- Hey, you said there were lots!
- Oh, here they are!
Mushrooms! Look! I found them!
See? They're under the trees!
- Wow, that's amazing!
- They're good to eat.
- Oh, here they are!
- It tastes like beef.
- Wow!
- CEO Hwang!
- They're here!
- Whoa!
- Where did you find them?
If you dig under the snow
next to the trees, you'll find them.
Oh, they're here.
They're here! They're here!
- Let's look for more!
- Wow, I can't believe this.
Are they delicious?
Give me the bag. Hey, there are
mushrooms here. Look for them.
Hey, let's grill these like meat!
Oh, it's so cold! Seo Joon Oh!
Okay. You did well.
Gosh, it got in my ear! CEO Hwang!
I mean Manager Jung!
- Geez!
- That was embarrassing!
- Why don't you listen to me?
- Pick some mushrooms!
Come here! Hey.
Hey, look for mushrooms.
Look for mushrooms already.
Stop it! Stop it... What are you doing?
Let's try here.
Seo Joon Oh!
Oh, it's so cold!
Let's hurry up so we can go back!
There are many over there too...
- Ra Bong Hee.
- Yes?
Where's Choi Tae Ho?
Huh? Oh!
Wait, he was nearby just a minute ago.
- I'll go look for him.
- Wait. Let's go together.
No, I'm sure he just
went to go to the bathroom
Take care of the others, okay?
Where did he go?
Secretary Tae!
The fish is ready!
Where did he go?
What? Why are you back already?
Where are you going?
The problem is... your big mouth.
Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh!
- What?
Why are you out here? Huh?
- Choi Tae Ho... That bastard...
- Wh... What?
Choi Tae Ho! He's killing Journalist Kim!
Geez, Journalist Kim.
You should have died in the crash.
But you survived...
You should have just lived quietly!
Why do you have to open
your mouth all the time?
How much do you know?
How much do you really know?
Wait...
Where are you going?
Where are you going in the middle
of our conversation? Huh?
Journalist Kim.
You talked so well in front of
the others. Why can't you talk now?
Talk to me. Talk.
Bong Hee! Bong Hee, look at this.
Bong Hee. Ta-da!
Hey, I paid a lot of money
for this back in the day.
Hey, this is a designer brand!
- It's pretty.
- Try it on.
Gosh, your arms are stuck. Take a look.
Bong Hee.
I'm on your team,
and so is everyone else.
That's why, Bong Hee...
Don't be scared or afraid...
Tell them exactly what you saw
and experienced on that island.
Think about those people
who are precious to you.
The people who could
still be alive... or dead.
That would be the courteous thing
to do for those people. Okay, Bong Hee?
The citizens are still demanding
that the truth be revealed...
Yes, Investigator Oh.
Hello, did you leave yet, by any chance?
Yes. I think I'm almost there.
Oh, well... The situation
has changed quite a bit.
Hey, shouldn't this say "accident?"
Check it again!
I think you should go back home for now.
Pardon?
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I was told to tell you
not to come here right now.
- Investigator--
- They formally requested that we wait.
We will talk to Reporter Choi Jeong Ah
at the scene.
The press conference is about to start.
Through the survivors' testimony,
the special investigation committee
has promised to reveal the truth
about Yoon So Hee's death.
It is predicted that Yoon So Hee's case
as well as information about
the other survivors will be revealed
so it is capturing a lot of attention.
What are you doing?
Huh?
What the hell are you doing?
Journalist Kim, look at me.
Look at me. Get up.
Look at me. Wake up. Look at me!
Journalist Kim!
Hey! Hey, what's wrong with him?
- Journalist Kim!
- What happened to him?
- Take a look at him.
- Please wake up!
There's a pulse, but he needs to wake up
so we can check his condition.
- Can you bring me a towel and water?
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Mister! What do we do?
That bastard did this, didn't he?
This wasn't an accident! He was trying
to kill him! Does he kill out of habit?
Ki Joon, he has to wake up.
I have to ask him something, okay?
Okay. Okay.
You have to believe me.
Don't trust... Choi Tae Ho.
He's a dangerous man.
He probably killed Yoon So Hee too.
Why did you do it?
That son of a bitch started it.
He was meddling in everything,
and annoyed the hell out of me--
Do you kill people who annoy you,
you son of a bitch?
He didn't die. If he didn't die,
there's no problem, right?
No. You tried to kill him.
- I was just trying to scare him.
- No! You tried to kill him.
But you failed because of me.
No.
I said you're wrong.
Why do you keep doubting me?
You did it to So Hee too!
What? What did he do to So Hee?
Tae Ho...
did it to So Hee too.
I saw it all.
That's bullshit!
What? What... did you see?
This bastard...
This bastard killed So Hee!
And disguised it as suicide!
I saw it all!
He said... he'd kill me if I told anyone.
Did you...
really kill So Hee?
Is that guy crazy?
Hey, what's with you guys?
Do you believe him? Do you believe
what that crazy bastard is saying?
He's not just crazy,
he's completely insane!
Hurry up and tell the truth!
Stop this bullshit and tell the truth!
No! I'm not lying!
I saw it! I saw... I saw him kill So Hee!
I don't lie! I really saw it!
He killed So Hee.
Tae Ho.
CEO Hwang.
CEO Hwang,
why are you being like this too?
Why did you do it, you bastard?
Are you crazy?
Yeol... You killed Yeol.
And you killed So Hee too.
Why did you kill those innocent kids,
you bastard?
I told you it wasn't me!
Your friends!
Those poor and innocent...
younger friends of yours...
How could you kill them,
you son of a bitch? Huh?
You son of a bitch! Damn it!
You damned son of a bitch!
Shit!
Now, we will listen
to the testimony of Choi Tae Ho
who is a survivor of
the Legend Entertainment plane crash.
This is regarding Yoon So Hee's murder,
which was a mystery during his absence.
Please listen to the testimony of
Choi Tae Ho, who was a decisive witness.
- If she shows up, don't let her in.
- Sure.
Everything I'm about to tell you...
is all true...
and I witnessed all of it myself.
That person...
was always a threatening person to us.
That's why Yoon So Hee...
always called him a murderer.
And he...
tried to kill all of us.
Chairwoman Jo.
We're... doing the right thing, right?
Wait, Miss! No, stop.
- Mister, what?
- Hey, go home!
- Hey, block her! Block her!
- Why are you doing this?
- Hey, where are you trying to go--
- Hey!
This is illegal. Don't you know that?
Hey, who are you?
We're from the western
district prosecutor's office.
- You go.
- Don't push.
- Who are you?
- Um, we're...
We're here for an internship
with a security company.
- Yes!
Are you interested
in a prosecution investigation too?
Maybe not that.
- We had many experiences already.
- I'm going to the washroom!
He wanted survive by himself...
So he tried to kill us,
when we were in the lifeboat with him.
It was because... we knew the truth.
To that person, we were...
people who needed to die.
Who was that person? Please tell us.
That murderer was...
Seo Joon Oh.
It was Seo Joon Oh.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
Are you someone I can trust?
I came to help you,
but I'm troubling you instead.
What do you mean you're here to help me?
Whose testimony is right?
Ra Bong Hee or Choi Tae Ho?
He's not in a good state.
- Shin Jae Hyun was murdered.
- It's all in the past. Why now?
Seo Joon Oh and I will reveal the truth.
Stop looking for Seo Joon Oh, he's dead.
Think about your own future.
If I told you someone went to his house
before he died, would you believe me?
Tell me! Why do I have to keep
you alive? Tell me!