Subtitles by DramaFever
I know you probably think I'm crazy,
but I still have to go.
I got a call.
Bong Hee. It's me, Joon Oh.
Seo Joon Oh.
Don't put yourself in danger
for other people.
I'll make the sacrifices.
I'll go into the water,
and I'll do the dangerous tasks, so...
Just stay by my side.
Seo Joon Oh.
Who... are you?
Do you know me?
Got you! I've always
wanted to try that on someone!
Seo Joon Oh, you scared me!
Come inside.
Grandpa. (In Chinese)
This is the girl I told you about.
- Hello.
Du Du.
Come in.
- Rest in here.
- Okay.
- Yes, hello?
- Did you see Seo Joon Oh?
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
Wow, you finally found him.
Congratulations. Thanks to you...
I opened Shin Jae Hyun's case again.
We'll talk about it when you return.
You two must have a lot to talk about,
so I'll let you go.
Give me a call any time you need my help.
Yes.
[Legend Entertainment
Group Memorial Service]
[What Are The Chances
Of Finding Additional Survivors?]
[Choi Tae Ho:
"Seo Joon Oh Killed Yoon So Hee."]
[Actress Ha Ji Ah,
What Happened On That Deserted Island?]
[Journalist Kim Was Mentioned
In The Final Announcement. Who Was He?]
[Lee Yeol?]
- Geez, it's cold, isn't it?
- Where did you go?
I'll show you.
That's right. I just got a call
from Prosecutor Yoon.
Who? Oh, So Hee's older brother?
Yes. He took care of me very well
while you were gone.
Really? You're hungry, aren't you?
Yes. What is all this?
By the way, can you really
roam about like this?
What about your injury?
Are you okay?
Of course I'm not!
I'm straining myself just for you.
Hearing you talk like that reassures me
that it's really you.
I wasn't so sure before.
You're really alive, Seo Joon Oh.
I bet you kept looking for me,
thinking I was dead.
Why would I have looked for you
if I thought you were dead?
I looked for you because
I thought you were alive.
I didn't think you were dead
but other people kept telling me
that you died
so it was hard to believe,
and I had a hard time with that.
That's how I felt.
But...
Who saved you?
The grandpa you met earlier.
He was fishing by the ocean,
and he saw me on the beach.
Hello? Are you all right? (In Chinese)
It turned out
that he was the neighborhood doctor.
At first, I wasn't sure
if he was trying to save me or kill me.
But he wasn't a complete quack.
It was for the best.
If I had gone to a big hospital...
I would have turned out like CEO Hwang.
That's why, no matter
how hard I searched for you
I couldn't find anything.
Hey, I heard news about you,
and I continued to search for you.
Look at this.
The internet is slow in this neighborhood
so it took forever to print out
even one page.
But, Seo Joon Oh,
how did you know my number?
That was my first day,
so I hadn't given you my number.
Artists are supposed to memorize
the phone numbers of the entire staff.
Do you think we're stars for no reason?
I guess that's how celebrities are.
Yes, hello? Yes, who is this?
Why are you speaking informally to me?
Yes, that's right. This is Byung Joo.
Oh, Joon Oh! Joon Oh! I'm sorry,
it's so great to hear your voice!
It's so nice to hear your voice!
Where are you calling from?
You were in China?
There's a lot of pork in China.
You didn't eat any pork?
You had sweet and sour pork?
When are you coming back?
Bong Hee's phone number?
By the way, Seo Joon Oh.
I was really lonely while you were gone.
People I thought I knew on the island...
After coming back to reality...
They weren't the people I thought I knew.
You told me not to do anything,
and just stay by your side.
But you left me alone.
I didn't even know
if you were alive or dead
so all I could do was wait.
I almost gave up too.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
For the position of CEO of Legend
Entertainment, which is currently vacant
we have nominated CEO Jang Do Pal.
For the past five months, he has rescued
the survivors who were missing
and took on a large role
in normalizing the company.
He has also given his best effort
to improve the company's reputation
after it was tarnished
due to many rumors.
We cannot leave Hwang Jae Gook's
position empty any longer
yet he is still absent.
This is why I recommend CEO Jang Do Pal
to be promoted from a temporary CEO
to the permanent CEO of this company.
Now, let's take a vote.
He has been approved.
Thank you.
Control your expression.
Aren't you controlling your expression
too well?
It doesn't look like
you're controlling it. You look sincere.
Smile.
CEO Jang. Congratulations
on formally becoming the CEO.
We should have a company dinner
on a night like this.
Are Tae Ho and Ji Ah working?
- Tae Ho's shooting a movie.
- Ji Ah's at a meeting for her movie.
Those punks sure are unlucky.
It's not like they'll starve
if they don't come.
Tell Ji Ah to drop by my office tomorrow.
It could be difficult because
she'll be filming an outdoor commercial.
Tell her to come by when she's finished.
Is it going to take all day?
Yes.
CEO Jang, you said you were going to
visit the hospital today. Are you going?
Has CEO Hwang's condition improved?
- Well, not really.
- Then there's no use in visiting.
You can go and nurse him
so that problems don't arise.
- If he gets better, let me know.
- Yes, I understand.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
[Journalist Kim Was Mentioned
In The Final Announcement. Who Is He?]
When we were leaving that island
Journalist Kim told me something.
The person who gave me the information,
was Yoon So Hee.
The reason So Hee didn't say anything
when she knew
who caused Jae Hyun's death...
The reason why Yoon So Hee
changed her mind...
was because of CEO Jang.
Him.
It was because of Jang Do Pal.
- CEO Jang Do Pal?
- Yeah.
On the day of Jae Hyun's death...
Tae Ho arrived late, and while
we were walking into Jae Hyun's house
Jae Hyun fell.
If Tae Ho killed Jae Hyun
and came out to cover up his crime...
that means someone else
pushed him off the roof.
Then are you saying...
Jang Do Pal was the one
who helped Choi Tae Ho?
Yeah.
I don't know how Journalist Kim
found CCTV footage of Tae Ho
but during the investigation, they said
the footage was being inspected.
I'm certain Jang Do Pal
had something to do with it.
And I'm sure Tae Ho wasn't
thinking clearly enough at the time.
And at the time...
I thought Jae Hyun committed suicide
because of me
which is why no one, including me,
thought it could have been a murder.
CEO Hwang and I stopped the autopsy
for that reason.
We didn't want to kill him twice.
Jang Do Pal
even bribed the hospital
that Manager Jung and Ji Ah were in
and tried to kill all of us.
What? Why are you telling me this now?
We just found each other.
That's right. Were you hurt?
No. I'm a fighter.
- But Seo Joon Oh.
- Yeah?
When we return to Seoul, how will we
deal with Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal?
No one's on our side.
What do you mean? You're on our side.
Everyone thinks I'm dead.
If I go back,
Ki Joon, Ho Hang, and Ji Ah...
can all be persuaded.
I'll take care of everything,
so don't worry.
You've suffered enough because of me.
Cheers.
But how will we return to Seoul?
The prosecution is investigating
your case right now
so they're probably going to
put you in handcuffs as soon as we land.
So...
Please draw us a picture. (In Chinese)
No. Yes! Yes! Yes!
A three-way intersection out front?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
There will be a red light?
Okay! Okay! Okay!
I get it now.
Wow, there are hundreds of those.
Oh, wait! Excuse me! (In Chinese)
This place, you can go this way.
Turn left, go straight
and then turn right.
And then go upstairs and then downstairs.
Thank you.
What did he say?
Oh, Seo Joon Oh, the red light!
If we see the light, turn right--
Turn right when we see the light.
No, we came this way,
so we have to that way!
If I look at it from here, it's this way.
South and north.
From here, it's this way--
If we look here,
the full moon is in the sky--
Wait, hey. Then you don't even need
a map! You're looking down on Grandpa!
Just like how the moon is fixed,
the cardinal points are fixed too.
Wow, seriously. Listen to this girl.
- West is our non-dominant hand.
- Our right hand is our dominant hand.
You're confusing me now. Did we use
a spoon to eat on the deserted island?
Excuse me, what do you use to eat?
- In India, they eat with their right--
- They do--
- You're in trouble if you use your left.
- Does that mean--
Grandpa told us that
when our backs face the red light...
Hey, don't do that! Seriously!
You said you eat with your right hand...
Excuse me!
Seo Joon Oh, this way. Our dominant hand.
This is where we can
take the boat to Korea, right?
Yes, that's right.
- It is, right?
- Yes, it is.
You're sure this is the place, right?
He said it is.
Seo Joon Oh, this place feels strange.
- No.
- What? There's nothing here.
We're walking into the dark again.
You passed the physical examination.
Oh, you're the perfect size!
You will arrive in Incheon
tomorrow afternoon.
- 500 yuan.
- I paid already.
- Did you receive it?
- Yes, I did.
We're going to get you there in the box.
We won't be held liable for anything.
- 500 yuan.
- I said I paid already.
- Did you receive it?
- Yes, I did.
- Please sign here.
- Oh! Wait.
You can't sign without thinking.
How can you trust him?
It's always like this for illegal acts.
- Is it always like this?
- Hey, it is. It's always like this.
- Should I stamp all of it?
- Use five fingers.
Wait, why are you stamping everything?
Why do you need this? Stop stamping!
It's always like this on this continent.
Are we finished?
- 500 yuan.
- I said I paid already!
- Did you receive it?
- Yes, I did.
He received my payment!
Here's a clipper. Give me a nail clipping
and two strands of hair.
Hey, wait! Why are you giving that to
them? What are they going to do with it?
In Chinese movies, they always do this.
Wait, why do you need
his nail clippings and hair?
- Why do you talk so much?
- Geez. Here.
- 500 yuan.
- I paid already!
- Did you receive it?
- He did! He received it!
You're finished.
I don't think this is right, Seo Joon Oh.
I'm anxious. Don't you watch the news?
I don't watch the news.
There's no guarantee that
those people will take you to Seoul.
It doesn't seem like they have a permit.
If they had a legal permit,
would they smuggle people over?
I'll give Prosecutor Yoon a call.
There must be another way.
There isn't! There's no time either.
Hey, aren't you leaning on
So Hee's brother too much?
People should do
what they can on their own
and only ask for help
if they really need it.
You can't even take out the bones in your
fish. How will you enter Korea illegally?
I'm worried, Seo Joon Oh.
- Bong Hee.
- Yes?
What's our goal?
We should get back to Korea, right?
- Yes.
- We should go and see people, right?
- We should fix everything, right?
- Yes.
- Then this is nothing! Don't worry!
Here. Get in!
Pardon? Why?
We can't go to the airport together
because I'm wanted. Let's split up here.
They said I'll arrive in a day,
so I'll see you tomorrow.
How can I go alone?
I can't. I'm too anxious.
- Hey! Come here. Get in.
- I'm worried--
Geez, seriously. Hey! Who am I?
I survived a plane crash, stepped
on a mine, and survived the high seas.
- Does this make sense?
- No.
There's someone else
who doesn't make sense.
We have to catch him.
Don't worry.
Call me when you're about to leave.
I'll wait for you there.
- Okay.
- Take care of yourself.
Okay! Don't worry! Go on. Get in!
- Go!
- Take care of yourself, Seo Joon Oh.
Go!
We'll face plenty more hardships
going forward. That's why...
This is nothing in comparison.
I can endure all of it.
I'll be okay.
I wonder how much time has passed.
It's so dark in here
that the inside of this container
is frozen in dimness.
No one is willing to speak first.
At a time like this,
an introduction is much needed.
Hello! I'm a Korean singer, Seo Joon Oh.
(In Chinese)
I shouldn't have done that.
It's been a while
since I've been so embarrassed.
Okay, I'll break the ice
with the person next to me.
Hello. My name
is Seo Joon Oh. (In Chinese)
Don't ask any questions,
if you want to live. Got it?
You're Korean!
Don't ask any questions.
Wh... What?
Don't ask any questions!
Geez, there's always someone.
I'll just sleep.
- Don't ask--
- I don't want to know anything.
I'm not curious at all. You have a knife.
Geez, I'll just sleep.
I wonder how much time has passed now.
I'm thirsty.
Oh, is he doing card tricks?
Don't ask any questions.
I wasn't asking you.
Um, is that magic?
Whoa! How did you do that?
Wow, amazing.
What are you doing?
You're putting it inside?
No way. You must be kidding.
Whoa!
How did that get in there?
How did you do that?
Fascinating. Fascinating.
- Don't ask any questions.
- Geez!
Excuse me.
You must pay me because you watched.
It's about money.
Wow, it's awesome! (In Chinese)
In this small space,
where there's no fresh air
they're juggling fire.
Hey, stop it! That's enough!
- Please pay up.
- Yes, you must pay us!
Geez, it's for money again.
Okay, pay up. Find the white ball.
Where could the ball be? Let's see.
Okay! Okay. Where could it be? Find it!
- Here!
- I want to know!
- No!
You put it right there!
They're swindling each other for money.
Geez, how pathetic.
What is that?
Oh, this is a drawing
my daughter gave me.
I'm looking at it because
I miss my daughter so much.
Mister, is there anyone you miss?
Someone I miss?
Don't ask any questions.
Should I kill him?
He was the one who asked me a question.
Someone I miss.
- Oh my goodness!
- Geez.
Gosh, why hasn't he called?
I'm going crazy here.
I wonder how much time has passed.
I woke up to the sound of someone crying.
Mister, why are you crying?
Don't ask any questions.
Where did your knife go?
You were swindled, weren't you?
Hey, why would you...
Mister, what's wrong?
Where are you cards?
Mister, where's your daughter's drawing?
You were swindled, weren't you?
Your torches too?
I couldn't hold it in any longer.
This person, seriously. You...
Mister.
I challenge you.
Plane crash, land mine, high seas...
No one is as lucky as I am.
Everything I have.
I have nothing to lose.
I'm Seo Joon Oh.
Oh, excuse me. Um, wait...
Oh! These are Seo Joon Oh's clothes.
This is...
Wait, excuse me. Have you seen
a skinny Korean man with yellow hair?
His name is Seo Joon Oh.
Have you seen him?
- Don't ask any questions.
- Let's go!
Seo Joon Oh.
What happened?
- Hey, it's nothing.
- Pardon?
Wait, where are your clothes?
What happened to you, Seo Joon Oh?
I was swindled.
Oh, what's that smell?
- Bong Hee.
- Gosh! That smell!
It's coming from this bag.
- What's wrong?
- Wait a minute.
Hey, lend me your scarf.
- Why are you running away?
- I'll give it to you. Stay there.
- Hurry.
- Here.
Gosh, something's rotting.
- Is it cashmere?
- Yes, it's soft, isn't it?
Okay. Let's go and wash up.
I'll find you clothes in the meantime.
Let's go.
- What happened?
- Hey, stop it.
- Hey, I can see!
- Hey!
- Wait, I'll cover it for you!
- Hey, stop it! You're bothering me!
But I can see everything!
I can see your butt!
I can't do this. I won't.
This is a role
that Tae Ho recommended you for.
- Why don't you want to do it?
- This was So Hee's role.
So Hee recommended him too.
- So? What's wrong with that?
- I'm sure you don't care, but I do.
I don't want to be her replacement,
and why would I do a melodrama with you?
If you're so particular and picky,
how will you ever reach the top?
You didn't purposely push
So Hee out of her role.
You're just taking a lead role because
she's dead and gone. What's wrong--
Hey, Ji Ah! Do this movie!
Hey, So Hee really wanted to do movies,
and asked to meet directors
by begging CEO Jang
and even threatening him.
CEO Tae. Stop saying crazy things.
Yes, I apologize.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Tell her not to do it.
But Ji Ah.
People can always change their minds,
so think about it.
Your mom should stop mooching
off the company.
That bastard.
Anyway, I can't do it. I won't do it.
I'm making myself very clear.
I won't do it. I'm leaving.
- I'll find a good project--
- Ji Ah.
You haven't seen the tabloids yet,
have you?
Tabloids?
Go and look at them
when you get a chance.
- Ji Ah--
- Manger Jung.
- Let's talk.
- Sure.
- You don't seem to get along these days.
- What do you mean by that?
I'm not as closed-minded as you think.
Whether you date, or move in together,
I don't care.
We're not dating.
When we were on the island...
Are the tabloids about...
[Four Months Pregnant?]
What is this article saying?
- Am I pregnant?
- That's ridiculous.
You promised you wouldn't
do anything to Ji Ah.
You promised.
You were acting so slowly, that..
I thought you forgot about that promise.
Maybe I didn't make it clear enough.
Maybe that was my bad.
Okay, now...
How about...
you control Ji Ah better?
Before a bigger problem arises.
Yeah. What?
Lost items?
I found it! (In Chinese)
I found it!
Hurry up and find them! We have to
find them before the sun goes down!
They said these are items
they didn't find last time.
There were clothes and cellphones
left behind.
Wait. A cellphone?
I mean...
I asked for a meeting with the directors.
Why haven't I been contacted yet?
Aren't you neglecting me too much?
This isn't what we agreed to!
- Did you search the computer?
- Yes, I didn't find anything.
Yeah, Ji Ah. You said you were
with So Hee after the crash, right?
Yes, why do you ask?
Okay, then. You know the cellphone
that was waved in the air for help?
Whose phone was it?
- Why are you bringing that up all of a--
- Answer my question!
Why is he yelling?
There's light.
It was So Hee's. Why?
Okay.
- Yeah, where's the cellphone?
- I don't know.
They were already collected
and landed in Korea.
Then whose hands did it fall into?
Please look favorably upon me.
Let's turn things around.
Oh, hello. I'm Jo Hee Kyung.
Please look favorably upon me.
- Oh my, you're working hard.
- Oh, Chairwoman Jo!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Oh my. I know a lot
about traditional markets.
I've loved traditional markets
since I was very young.
When I was little,
I used to go to the market with my mother
and those were such great memories!
I still remember!
Please try this.
- Oh, it's delicious!
- Is it?
This too. Please try this too.
This is very delicious.
Try the fish cakes! Try this too!
It looks like you love market food!
Jo Hee Kyung! Jo Hee Kyung! Jo Hee Kyung!
- Jo Hee Kyung!
- Thank you!
Congresswoman Jo.
Why did you plan out
our schedule this way?
Why are we going to all the markets? It's
not like we're a on a hunt for good food.
- Yes--
- I ate too much rice soup.
And, why are they still calling me
Chairwoman Jo?
The special investigation committee
ended ages ago.
I understand, Chairwoman...
No, Congresswoman Jo.
What? The survivors' lost items?
[Lost Items]
Yes.
Yes, I'll bring it over.
Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
- You finally look more human.
- Bong Hee.
Why do you always give me turtlenecks?
- You are so stubborn.
- They look good on you.
- You're really obsessed with these.
- Here, be quiet.
Keep your hat on.
You can't be seen by anyone.
There are so many other things
besides turtlenecks...
- Seo Joon Oh, why are you empty-handed?
- What?
- Where's the scarf I lent you earlier?
- I threw it out. It smelled. I'm sorry.
We have a lot to talk about,
so shall we relocate?
I'm sorry,
but I have something to take care of.
It's more important than
clearing myself from the false charges.
- What is it?
- I'll tell you when I return.
I'll be back.
Bong Hee. Um. Lend me 10,000 won.
Sure.
Prosecutor Yoon. 10,000 won, please.
- Yes, 10,000 won.
- Oh.
[Secret]
- When are you going to tell me?
- Weren't you sleeping?
I'm waiting for you
to decide to tell me yourself.
What do you mean?
CEO Jang threatened you
to change your statement, didn't he?
You said you wouldn't do it,
so why did you suddenly change your mind?
Was it because of me?
Did CEO Jang use me to threaten you?
- It's not like that.
- Then what is it?
I'm not scared about the tabloids,
so let's just tell the truth!
Why aren't you scared of the tabloids?
You should be! You're an actress!
Your image is your life if you're
an actress! You should be scared!
After what we went through on that island
"Pregnancy On The Deserted Island"
is a top search. This is upsetting me.
That's because CEO Jang--
Do the movie if you want
the rumors to go away.
You have to take on a project
for them to quiet down.
Tae Ho's image is good right now
so if you display good chemistry
in this melodrama, it'll help you too.
So let's not think right now,
and just get through this.
Until the world calms down...
Let's just...
do our job quietly.
Does it look like I was shot in the head?
Don't you feel like we owe Joon Oh?
Oh, that's right.
We no longer have any right
to feel apologetic.
We really betrayed him.
You don't have to feel that way.
I'll be the son of a bitch
for both of us.
I don't think I can continue traveling
with you right now. What should we do?
Do you want to get out? Or should I?
What are you saying? We're in Gunsan!
If we get out right now,
we'll be roadkill!
All I did was choose a path
for our survival.
Since Joon Oh is no longer here.
Ji Ah didn't know anything about this
so all she has to do
is firmly walk along that path.
That's all I wish for.
- Yes, please go ahead.
- Yes.
I'll push you.
- I'll push you.
- Okay!
It's easier if I push you, isn't it?
Do you always drive so safely?
This isn't my car. It's not my car.
Ouch, my legs.
Go back safely!
Geez, what is all over the ground?
Trust, love, and friendship
are all on the ground.
Oh! What's that smell?
It smells very familiar!
It's the smell of a traitor.
Joon Oh.
Hi.
Come here.
Come here!
Come here! Come here! Come here!
Byung Joo, come here!
Come here, Byung Joo. It's me!
- Step on it! Go!
- But it's Joon Oh!
- It's Joon Oh, but let's go!
- I understand!
I talked to him already, so just drive!
Go this way!
- Reverse! Reverse!
- Come here!
Hurry! Drive to the right!
Hey! Come here! Come here!
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't push my arm! Open the window!
- Joon Oh could have gotten hurt!
- Hey, choose!
Is it Ki Joon or me?
Byung Joo! What are you doing?
Spin the wheel this way!
Where are you trying to go?
Reverse to the left!
- Joon Oh, tell us if we have room.
- More.
- Hey, Byung Joo! The other way!
- The other way?
No, go forward first. I don't think
you can drive. Open the door.
Joon Oh! Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh!
- Come here. Ki Joon!
Hey! Hey, get out! Get out! Get out!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please go!
- Mister, who are you?
- I'm in a difficult situation--
That's your problem!
How dare you just jump into my cab?
Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
Joon Oh, are you all right?
- How are you?
- Hey, I'm fine.
- Joon Oh!
- Hey, wait.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
We're here! But... Mister! Mister!
Why did you get into my cab?
Oh, but still...
This is my house. Get out!
My house is right here! Get out!
- Hurry up and get out!
- Thank you.
I told you to get out! Geez, seriously!
I thought I was going to die!
Thank you. Thank you.
- Close the door!
- Yes, I will.
- You have to close the door!
- Wait.
- What? Are you hiding?
- I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
He's a beginner,
so we might have to help him get out.
Seriously, these people.
Why can't anyone drive?
Reverse! Reverse all the way!
Damn it!
Come here!
Joon Oh, are you all right?
Geez, why are you going
so fast on a bike?
You're okay. You're okay.
Are you okay? Be more careful!
Hey!
Wow! They still have these?
I want to play!
Ki Joon! Let's play this game!
Wow, they still have these machines?
- This is for girls. Give me 1000 won.
- Wait. Wait.
Ma'am, can I get some change?
I'll kill you!
- How much is one portion?
- 2,000 won.
- Give me half for 1,000 won.
- No.
- Please give me half!
Since when are you so strict?
- Can I get one portion?
- Yes.
- This is amazing!
- These are the best rice cakes.
- Where did these rice cakes come from?
- They're chewy. They're wheat cakes.
- Chew it. They're rice cakes.
- Try this.
Rice cakes are more expensive!
Wheat cakes are bad for eczema!
- This is itchy, isn't it?
- Isn't that why you're wearing it?
I'm only eating rice cakes
because this is itchy.
So if I eat wheat cakes,
I can't wear any clothes?
- Why are you arguing?
- We're not arguing! We're adults!
- Why would we fight?
- We're so close.
I'm dying here.
Is it okay to leave
the two of them alone?
Seo Joon Oh shouldn't
expose his identity right now.
Of course. Seo Joon Oh told me.
He said, when he comes back,
he can persuade
Manager Jung, Ji Ah,
and Secretary Jung to come around.
He said he was going to do that.
I know it won't be easy.
But just like how he acted on the island
and when we were coming back to Korea...
I'm certain he will bring everything
back to normal in his own way.
I truly believe that he'll do it.
Geez, I'm going to wash up!
I'm going to wash up, so wait out here.
Pay for me, and wait out here, got it?
Ki Joon.
I've been thinking...
I think you were right
about the rice cakes.
You've always been right...
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
- Hey, what about your injury?
- It's just a scar now. It's fine.
Oh, it healed well.
But it still hurts when I raise my arm.
I asked you why you did it.
I told you I'm sorry.
- Hey, can you roam around like this?
- No.
You can't. The prosecution
is searching for you.
So what? Are you going to report me?
I can't. How could I report you,
even if I'm a son of a bitch?
Don't tell anyone that you saw me today.
Why? What is it this time?
What are you planning to do?
What else? Now that I'm back,
I'm going to flip everything around.
Wow, these people are really shameless.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho.
Hey, Tae Ho, that bastard.
Did you see that bastard cry?
- Hey, he's a good actor!
- He's good.
- What do you mean he's good?
- He's good! He's better than you.
You saw. He can cry out of the blue.
He's really good.
Don't underestimate CEO Jang and Tae Ho.
They have a lot more power
and it's been too long, so there's
no evidence either. Will you be okay?
Of course I won't. It'll be exhausting.
But I can't just stay still
and do nothing.
They think they can do whatever they
want, when they're only in entertainment.
Geez, they think if time passes
and the evidence is destroyed
their crimes disappear too.
What can I do?
What about Jae Hyun's murder?
I need to do this, even if I won't
be okay. I need to do it.
I should at least hope to resolve it.
What else can I do?
- See?
- Joon Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. No matter what the case is,
I can't take your side right now.
It just ended up this way.
I'm really... sorry. Geez.
Hey, you said you would believe me...
and be on my side,
when no one else believes me.
Look at this.
You just say whatever you want
and hear whatever you want.
Geez.
Hey.
If you were going to be sorry,
you shouldn't have done what you did!
Why do you keep apologizing?
I'm really so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Ki Joon, the door code to your house
is still the same. 0831. My birthday.
- How do you know that?
- I was there earlier.
- Why would you do that?
- Because I came back late. Sorry.
Do you think you can just go into
anyone's house because it's late?
Well, it was really late.
Why do you live like that?
Is that how you were raised?
- I learned it from you--
- Hey, I taught you better.
- But it was so late--
- That doesn't mean you can sleep there.
But... I bought you that house.
- Really?
- I bought it for you.
- You're sorry, aren't you?
- About what?
You're sorry, aren't you?
Don't do that. Don't do that!
You're the only person
with different colored socks.
- Please have some fruit!
- Oh, yes.
Yes, here you go.
- Thank you.
- Yes, here you go.
Have a seat.
By the way...
- Who's Seo Joon Oh?
- Oh that?
Mom, over here. The one in red.
Oh, it's him.
My mom doesn't watch TV.
That's okay, right?
This is Seo Joon Oh.
I heard a lot about
how you've been helping our Bong Hee.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, no problem.
Please continue to look after her
in the future.
Thank you.
Please have some fruit, and let me know
if there's anything you need.
- Yes.
- Please eat.
Thank you, Mother.
Oh! "Mother? Mother..."
Mom.
- Yes, please sit.
- Yes, please sit down.
Wow, it's good.
Yes, please have some.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
How does it feel to be back in Korea?
It must be a whole new feeling.
It doesn't feel that special.
Regarding what you had to resolve today,
did it go well?
Yes, I guess so.
- Joon Oh.
- Yeah?
- Are you in a bad mood?
- No!
Please don't mind us.
Please eat. Please eat.
Why aren't you offering me any?
It must feel awkward
because we've never met before.
What should we do? We can't feel awkward
if we want to work well together.
I'm sure it'll get better.
Joon Oh, what's wrong? You're making
them uncomfortable. Smile.
I just have bad memories
about government authorities.
You are probably aware.
I guess this kind of interaction...
is a little awkward for me.
That's right. You're aware, aren't you?
That's understandable.
Is this funny to you?
What's wrong with you?
This is our first meeting,
so I'm sure it'll get better.
I'll try my best to speak
casually with you first.
Oh, is that how you sound
when you speak casually?
Seo Joon Oh, what do you mean?
He's speaking in his casual tone
right now.
If he speaks casually with you,
you can do the same.
That doesn't mean
you can be rude to him though.
Lawyer Jo,
should we give them a briefing?
Oh, sure.
- Get going.
- Yes.
We found out about this while we were
reinvestigating Shin Jae Hyun's case.
Yoon So Hee, who testified at the time
there was record of her statement saying
that she had evidence that it was murder.
We asked the police officer
who was responsible for this case
and he said So Hee
did give that statement
but she ultimately insisted
that Seo Joon Oh was the murderer
so her statements were inconsistent.
So Hee was probably threatened
by Jang Do Pal.
That's why she changed her story.
Because she knew
about Jae Hyun's murder...
In the end...
That's why, in order to find out
the truth about So Hee's death
we must catch the murderer
who killed Shin Jae Hyun.
And that's how
we can clear your charges as well.
But we don't have any witness statements
or any decisive evidence,
so we're in a frustrating situation.
The truth is,
I've been looking into something myself.
A package will land in Korea
very shortly.
The lost items that were found
on the deserted island.
In with that stuff,
I found something that looked familiar.
Go faster.
These are the pictures I received.
Seo Joon Oh.
Isn't this the cellphone
that Ji Ah was waving in the cave?
It was really dark that night.
Wasn't it black?
This was So Hee's cellphone.
Pardon?
How do you know that?
She stubbornly only used
this cellphone for many years.
It was very dirty,
and it broke many times
but she insisted on keeping this one,
without even changing the case.
It didn't suit her image as an actress,
so I offered to buy her a new one
but she said she liked that
it felt familiar in her hands.
- Deputy Kim. Can you check it out?
- Oh, sure.
Hm, send this to the other offices.
Yeah. Bring it here for now.
- It's not here.
- What do you mean?
I'm here because you said it was here!
It's not here. Someone picked it up.
Who are you?
- Congresswoman Jo.
- Yeah?
The lost items from the deserted island
have arrived. What should I do with them?
Our team dispersed,
so they weren't sure where to send them
which is why I told them
to bring the items here.
- Investigator Oh.
- Yes.
Do I still look like a chairwoman to you?
Don't ask me that,
just get rid of them! Burn them!
I have enough to worry about already.
I apologize.
You still call me
"Investigator Oh" too...
Let's find that cellphone!
Let's bring it back here!
Okay.
Let's find it.
[Lost Items]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
This situation is a lot more serious
than you think.
I'm suspicious of Jo Hee Kyung's room.
Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal's guys
are here.
Did you already take care of the items
that she told you to burn?
It's clear they're avoiding something.
What's inside that everyone is after?
I'd better find out first.
We're in trouble, Bong Hee!
Tae Ho went that way!
No way.