I want to live.
You should.
I'll save you.
Get out of here. I'll take care of this.
And after I leave?
Take a taxi around the block.
You have to arrive when the others arrive
to avoid suspicion.
- Save... Save me...
- Jae Hyun. Jae Hyun...
Sa... Save...
Let's send you off. In one shot.
Die! Die!
This is what really happened
when Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal
killed Shin Jae Hyun four years ago.
And those two...
disguised it as a suicide.
- And Yoon So Hee recorded it?
- Yes.
And I think So Hee was killed
because of this.
I could have gone straight
to the prosecution
but there is one reason...
why I came here first.
As the chairwoman of the special
investigation committee of this case
please save me, Seo Joon Oh,
the last survivor.
Please tell everyone
that I am alive, and that I've returned.
And to prove my innocence...
It's not like I did anything wrong...
but I'll talk about it
at the press conference.
What an unlucky year we've had.
Can I get you some water?
Do you think water will fix this?
This might not be the best time
to tell you this...
What are you trying to say?
When we wrapped up
the special investigation committee
we got a call asking us to collect
a body. Do you remember?
They told us about the bodies we missed,
and Journalist Kim's location.
- And they asked us to collect them.
- So what?
Now that Seo Joon Oh has come back...
I think Seo Joon Oh made that call.
So what do you want me to do?
Should I thank him for a job well done?
If he had killed them,
he wouldn't have made that call.
It's important to make
a political judgment. It is...
But now that this has happened,
I want to request...
that you rethink this one more time,
in a cool-headed manner.
I'm sorry if I crossed the line.
I'll get you some water, Congresswoman Jo.
[Episode 14]
Please, no flash.
How is Choi Tae Ho doing?
Was he really stabbed?
- Please tell us your thoughts.
- How is he?
You should have listened to me.
If you had listened,
this wouldn't have happened.
Why did you do it?
Why... did you kill Jae Hyun?
Why do you think I did it?
It was all for you, of course.
Should I have let him live
after he heard what we said?
I... just did what I had to do.
What you had to do was to kill a person?
I'm tearing up.
You killed a person for me.
Let's get things straight, Tae Ho.
This happened
because I was dealing with the mess you
made when you thought you'd killed him.
Do you know that?
But still...
You shouldn't have killed him.
If you hadn't,
my life could have been different.
Do you really believe that?
You're so naive.
Please get rid of the reporters
and make sure the medical staff
stays quiet.
- I'm going to leave tomorrow.
- Okay.
I'll do that.
Oh, right.
About that cell phone...
What are you going to do about it?
Hey, Choi Tae Ho.
What the hell are you doing?
Get those police cars out of here!
How did you get my number?
I know everything you know.
I know you sent them to catch me.
But you idiot...
If they catch me, they'll find So Hee's
phone too. Think before you act.
I'll find it.
I'll find it myself.
Okay, then. Get some rest.
- Hello!
- Please look here!
Please pose for the photos!
Get out.
Deputy CEO Jang, I don't think
I can do this any longer.
I have to turn myself in,
Deputy CEO Jang.
I can't live like this anymore.
Get a hold of yourself, Choi Tae Ho!
It was an accident.
Do you want to ruin your life
because of a little accident?
It only takes a second to ruin your life.
Are you aware what state Joon Oh is in?
Joon Oh and Jae Hyun ended up that way
because it was their fate.
If you close your eyes for a moment,
it'll all be over.
Why are you making a fuss over this?
I want you to do as I say
for the time being. Do you understand?
Then...
Do I have to live with this guilt...
for the rest of my life?
I don't think I can do that,
Deputy CEO Jang.
If you weren't prepared for this
you shouldn't have asked for my help.
It's too late now.
We've already crossed the line.
Tae Ho.
In life, people do things
that are much worse than this.
You'll learn soon enough.
- How have you been?
- I've been well.
Your fans are waiting.
Do you have any good news?
I'm preparing for my next project,
and I'm also exercising.
Please say something to your fans.
Geez, what was that?
Yes, um...
Murderer.
Do you think you can erase
what you've done?
Ki Joon, why are you out here?
- Did the broadcast go well?
- Yeah.
- Let's talk.
- About what?
Let's go.
Geez, the weather is so nice.
Ji Ah.
I'm sorry for how I've acted.
I didn't tell you what was going on.
You must have been frustrated.
Today, I'll tell you everything
I've been keeping from you.
Don't tell me.
Let's not worry about it.
And I already know
what you're going to say.
How would you know that?
CEO Jang threatened you with the fact
that my mom mooched off of him, right?
And I'm sure you tried to protect me
behind my back.
Ji Ah.
How do you catch on so quickly?
Hey, let me ask you a question.
Do you feel like...
I interfere too much in your life?
Do you feel burdened because of it?
No.
Because I knew why
you were acting that way
I felt bad for you more than anything.
You didn't have to do that.
What do you mean you knew
why I was acting that way?
I'm not dumb.
I know what happened between you
and my brother.
How do you know that?
You came to my brother's funeral,
didn't you?
I heard you were an army doctor.
How could I have not known
when you cried more than we did?
So you knew...
You knew.
Hey, why didn't you say anything?
Didn't you hate me?
I didn't think it was your fault.
I just thought my brother died
while serving in the army.
It wasn't anyone's fault.
I just accepted that it was his fate.
That's what I thought.
How could a middle school student forgive
me when she lost her older brother?
How could you forgive me
when I killed your brother?
You didn't kill anyone.
It's not like you did it on purpose.
You just tried to save him.
And not everyone apologizes
the way you have.
You threw away your career, you cared
for me, and took my mom's insults.
And you did it for a long time.
Your apology was more than enough.
That's why I was able to forgive you.
So let's stop talking about this!
Why are we still talking about this?
Stop it, okay?
Stop.
Gosh, it's really cold out.
I might catch a cold.
My nose is running.
Ki Joon, it's cold, isn't it?
I'll get going.
Yeah, Ki Joon.
Did you talk to her?
Yeah, me too.
When are you coming?
Bong Hee wanted to eat together
at her house. I don't know.
Okay, come soon. Okay.
Hey, not bad.
Oh!
Damn it, no one saw!
It only took one try!
Wow, this is actually possible.
Please grab it. Please grab it.
Please wait. Geez.
- What is this?
- Isn't it cute?
It's so cute! Here.
- Do you want to try it?
- Of course.
- 500 won.
- Sure.
It's your money.
- One more.
- Geez, so greedy.
- Let's do this!
- This one looks easy.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Okay. I got it! I got it! I got it!
- You got it.
- I got it! It's mine.
Geez.
- See? It's not that easy.
- I should have gotten it. 500 won.
- Try this one.
- Let's go.
You got it.
I can get this one. It's in the bag.
I'm stupid if I miss this.
Here we go!
You got it. Wow, this game is well-made!
What a great machine.
Geez.
Gosh, they're so cute.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
But Seo Joon Oh, this is my first time
getting stuffed animals as a gift.
- This is your first time?
- Yes.
Wow, you've had so many new experiences
since we met. You were lucky to meet me.
I know. I've had so many new experiences
since I met you.
- You should be thankful.
- I am.
Today, I learned that you are capable
of doing things.
Hey, stars need to be good at everything.
It's not that easy.
Right, you were a star, weren't you?
I almost forgot.
- Why would you forget that?
- They're so cute.
Thank you, Joon Oh.
Joon Oh?
Wait, So Hee recorded it? When?
She knew,
yet she still called you a murderer?
- Hey, Ji Ah...
- What?
I think...
there were too many things I didn't know
about our So Hee.
It's possible that a part of me
could have been suspicious
of So Hee from the beginning
but I might have been in denial.
We felt the same way.
And she was sensitive to begin with
so I just thought she was shocked
after Jae Hyun died.
I'm sure she never intended to use
her recording. It just happened that way.
She even tried to report it
multiple times.
But the way she treated Joon Oh...
So Hee wasn't like that before.
She liked and respected Joon Oh.
She wasn't the type of person
who could have done that when she knew.
Now that you mention it, I think
So Hee wanted to say something once.
When Joon Oh was a complete wreck...
I visited Joon Oh's place a few times
to help him clean up.
Joon Oh.
I drank today too.
And then I somehow ended up here.
I'm sorry, Joon Oh.
I know you did nothing wrong.
I know it wasn't you.
But if I don't do this...
I don't think I can bear it.
I don't think I can keep living.
Don't forgive me, Joon Oh.
Because she was accepting bribes
from Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
she was probably in denial.
The more tortured and guilty she felt
the more she
would have wanted to deny it.
It's a common occurrence that I see
in my investigations.
It wasn't anyone else...
but it was our So Hee who did that.
I'm sorry, Seo Joon Oh.
I want to apologize on So Hee's behalf.
Hey, no need for that.
Prosecutor Yoon, it's all in the past.
Hey, let's catch Jang Do Pal and
Choi Tae Ho. How many victims are there?
There's me, So Hee, Journalist Kim, and
CEO Hwang. Who knows what else he'll do?
We shouldn't relax
until the press conference is over.
That's right. We'll go
and testify correctly this time.
- We will.
- Geez.
I feel so much better
now that all the secrets are out.
Joon Oh, you can trust us.
We're not afraid of anything anymore.
- You need to be afraid of me.
- Really?
After the press conference,
we'll wait with a police team
so that Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
can't escape.
If we just expose the contents
of that cell phone
it'll cause an uproar.
Okay! Cheers to that.
- Cheers!
Oh, how about we move CEO Hwang
to a different room?
I feel like we'll be more at ease if we
move him so that he remains safe.
What will we say to Secretary Tae?
He still hasn't come around yet.
Even if we move him, once Secretary Tae
tells them, it's all over.
CEO Hwang! CEO...
Whoa, he opened his eyes!
Jae Gook! Jae Gook!
He opened his eyes!
He opened his eyes! He...
Honey, do you recognize me? Honey!
He moved! He opened his eyes!
Mrs. Hwang, he...
What do we do now?
- I'll call the doctor.
- Okay.
CEO Hwang, do you recognize me?
It's me, Ho Hang!
Jae Gook. Yes, Jae Gook.
If you recognize me...
blink your eyes, just once.
He opened his eyes!
Wow! He opened his eyes!
What do I do? Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it's Secretary Tae.
Yeah, what is it?
Manager Jung!
What? What's the matter?
You're scaring me. What is it?
- Who is it?
- Did something happen to CEO Hwang?
Yeah, Ji Ah. Manager Jung.
CEO Hwang.
The doctor said
he's remembering things, but slowly.
CEO Hwang, do you recognize us?
CEO Hwang, it's me, Ji Ah.
CEO Hwang.
Joon Oh.
Yeah.
What? Hwang Jae Gook woke up?
Hello.
- Hello.
- Is CEO Jang inside?
- Yes.
How conscious is he? Can he talk?
He woke up,
but he can't talk or move yet.
- How long until he talks?
- I haven't asked the doctor yet.
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Did you go there to say hello?
We can't let him say a word.
I only kept him alive
because he couldn't talk.
When it looks like he's about to talk,
we have to kill him. Got it?
Ask the doctor right away.
Why aren't you going inside?
I... I came to say hello to CEO Jang
but it seems like he's still busy,
so I'm going to leave. Bye.
You're here?
Why didn't you pick me up
from the hospital?
Something came up.
Is it true CEO Hwang woke up?
Where did you hear that?
I just found out.
What are you going to do?
What else can we do?
He'll tell everyone I tried to kill him
as soon as he opens his mouth.
We need to kill him.
[Yoon So Hee Murder Investigation]
We're already in the middle
of investigating this case.
Geez, look how thick it is.
You've done a lot of research.
[Shin Jae Hyun Murder Investigation]
What is this?
These are documents for Shin Jae Hyun's
death. The one that was called a suicide.
Please look into this case first.
It will give you clues
about Yoon So Hee's case.
Why are you trying to mess around
with a case that's already closed?
The statements were consistent and
the culprit was identified, so it's over.
Are you trying to give me extra work
because it looks like I'm slacking?
Did you try to investigate
Yoon So Hee's case properly?
I did, but it wasn't different from the
special investigation committee's report.
That's why I'm asking you...
Why do I have to disregard
the consistent statements
and investigate this all over again?
You're aware that Seo Joon Oh
has returned?
I heard, but I haven't seen him myself.
I should see him for myself--
As someone who sent the police to
Ra Bong Hee's house to catch Seo Joon Oh
that's a lame excuse.
Fine, if you came here
without Seo Joon Oh or any evidence,
you won't change much.
Do you have another plan?
Please wait until the press conference
tomorrow.
Everything will be exposed tomorrow.
From what I've heard,
the culprit in Hwang Jae Gook's death
is the same man who is responsible
for Shin Jae Hyun's death.
I will send you the evidence soon
so you should consider where you stand,
if you don't want to humiliate yourself.
- Thank you!
Please vote for Jo Hee Kyung!
Congresswoman Jo, can we take a picture?
Thank you.
Here. One, two, three!
- Thank you! I hope you win!
- Yes, thank you!
Good luck!
Yes, that's right. Yes.
Yes, not at all. Yes.
What on earth is the problem?
Jung Ki Joon changed his statement,
and Hwang Jae Gook's case could be murder
yet you don't think there's a problem?
How the hell did your team investigate
and create such a mess?
Hey, it's not like we even have
a license to investigate.
We did our share, so the rest is up to
you! Why are you taking it out on us?
As a former chairwoman who is trying
to join the national assembly
you shouldn't talk
so carelessly about this.
Will you be able to face your voters
after Seo Joon Oh speaks to the press?
Ma'am, you must help us wrap up this case
if you want me to do
what you asked me to do.
How dare this district attorney
order around someone so stubborn?
Doesn't he have anyone else?
By the way, earlier...
He called you,
and asked you to call him back.
Please give this to me.
I can do it for you.
I should take these off.
CEO Hwang! He's smiling.
- Put those there.
- Yeah?
Wait, at a time like this...
- One, two, three!
- Smile! Smile!
He smiled!
Ji Ah, can you empty this?
- Wash it too.
- Okay.
Aren't you cold?
Good luck. Good luck!
- Throw it out?
- Good luck! I don't know either.
- Let's eat.
- Yeah, wait.
- Ji Ah, would you like a drink?
- Yes.
- Orange, grape or tomato?
- Tomato!
Tomato and grape...
The grape is for Ji Ah.
Sir, during Hwang Jae Gook's accident
a witness saw someone
touching the equipment.
They said he spoke in language
that was not Chinese
and when we got a composite sketch
- he looked familiar.
- Do you know him?
You'll recognize him too.
Jang Do Pal's guy?
Who are you? (In Chinese)
I took care of it.
Jang Do Pal...
- has a sloppy side.
- I know.
Take this, and print out the photos
from the hospital he bribed
so that we can target both Jang Do Pal
and Choi Tae Ho at tomorrow's conference.
Yes, I will do that.
Seo Joon Oh wants to hold
a press conference.
Did you know?
At that press conference...
he wants to play the recording.
You'll want to stop that from happening,
won't you, Choi Tae Ho?
Of course.
If this incident from the past
is talked about, it'll ruin my image.
If that happens, the help you've given me
will all have been in vain.
I can't let that happen.
I knew we'd be on the same page.
Can you do it? Can you stop Seo Joon Oh
from holding the press conference?
I have no choice.
I want to live in peace, you see.
Great! Isn't it great that we moved?
How nice is this?
CEO Hwang will be more comfortable,
and recover quickly.
Right, CEO Hwang?
Thank you so much
for taking care of my husband.
People kept saying the plane crash
was his fault
so it has been hard
for me and our children.
Because you were by his side
on the island, and you're still here now
the misunderstanding has been resolved.
Thank you so much.
It's time to pick up the kids
from school. I'll be back.
- Please stay for as long as you like.
- Yes.
- Travel safely!
- Goodbye!
- Are you all right?
- I'm sorry.
My skirt. You shouldn't sit on it.
- No problem.
I'm also...
very thankful to you.
I thought you would resist until the end.
Have you come to your senses?
- Hey, we were just as bad.
- Do you think so?
We understand your position.
You had no other choice,
for CEO Hwang's sake.
You must have struggled a lot
by yourself.
Let's look after CEO Hwang together
from now on.
I know you had your reasons, so it'll be
hard for you to open up right away.
We all understand that.
But I'm sure you understand
our side as well.
If something happens to CEO Hwang,
call me right away.
You can do that,
even without opening up to me, right?
You can.
Yeah.
Until CEO Hwang fully recovers
we have to take turns watching
Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal.
Okay?
- Answer him.
- Okay?
Yeah. Yes, I understand.
Yes. Yes, Tae Ho.
Yes, I understand. Yes.
Who was that? Tae Ho?
Is he out of the hospital already?
Yes, he told me to pick him up.
Figures, he's probably looking for the
cell phone, so he has no time to spare.
- Go.
- Yes, sure.
And don't make it obvious
that you were with us.
Don't worry. You can trust me.
- I'll get going! Yes.
- Goodbye! Yes.
CEO Hwang, take care.
I feel anxious no matter what he does.
Seo Joon Oh is speaking
at a press conference tomorrow.
I'll go to the press conference first,
and look for the cell phone.
Of course. We need to stop him.
- I found out where Hwang Jae Gook is.
- Okay.
Then go there
during the press conference tomorrow
- and kill him.
- Yes.
[Byung Joo]
Choi Tae Ho will go straight to the press
conference tomorrow to find the phone.
Have you heard anything
from Jo Hee Kyung's team yet?
No, they just said they'll see us
at the press conference tomorrow.
She's not that easy to deal with.
You can't let your guard down, okay?
If she doesn't help us,
we can do it ourselves.
Okay.
Drive safely!
Geez, it'll be fine, right?
It's going to be fine.
Geez, I wish it weren't tomorrow,
but the day after tomorrow.
It has to go well.
It will go well. It will.
It has to.
Don't worry.
It will go well.
- Tilt it this way, and to the center--
- Lift it up!
Move it to the right! To the right.
To the right. To the right.
- Move that to the right too.
- Testing. Testing, one, two, one, two.
Joon Oh! Have you left yet?
Take care of the phone.
Get there safely,
and prove your innocence. Good luck!
Oh, you scared me! You scared me...
You're here? Let's go.
No, I'll drive myself today.
Go home.
Tae Ho, I'll drive you!
Tae Ho! I'll drive you!
Today will go as planned, right?
I hope so. Has Seo Joon Oh
left his house yet?
Yes, he probably has.
Yes, Seo Joon Oh. Where are you?
If I'd known I was going to leave
so early, I would have gone with you.
I thought I was supposed to go
as late as possible so no one sees me.
Ki Joon, why did you call me at 4 a.m.?
Hey, on an important day like this,
we should be prepared.
Bong Hee! He doesn't normally get up,
but he got up today after one call!
He must be pretty nervous too!
I'm not nervous. Hey, where are you?
We're on our way too.
See you soon.
Who are you? Stop! Who are you?
No! No! Stop it!
Who are you? Who are you?
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
Don't come in!
Stop it! Seriously!
CEO Hwang! CEO Hwang! Stop it! Help us!
Help us! Help us! Stop!
You crazy bastards!
Help us! Help!
I told you I'm the only one
who can protect you and CEO Hwang.
Why don't you believe me?
Tae Ho.
What...
What is it that you want?
Make a call.
Hello?
Yeah, Ho Hang. Whose number is this?
Joon Oh...
Someone... is trying to kill CEO Hwang.
The number is unavailable--
He's still not answering?
No, neither of them is picking up.
- I'm anxious, Prosecutor Yoon.
- It'll be okay.
- Bong Hee, I'm sorry I'm late.
- Ji Ah.
Where are Joon Oh and Ki Joon?
What? What happened? Huh?
What is it? What happened?
I'm sorry.
I called you because I was scared
when he disappeared for his checkup.
- Geez, seriously.
- You scared us!
I was really scared. I'm sorry.
Geez, why hasn't he updated me yet?
What the hell happened to him?
- Hello, you're here.
- Hello.
It's ready.
Bong Hee, I thought Joon Oh was coming.
I know.
He hasn't called me either.
What is this? He's not getting out?
You're driving over here?
You're not getting out,
you're driving over here?
You're driving? You're driving?
[Press Conference For Plane Crash
Survivor, Seo Joon Oh]
I think something is wrong.
In order to expose the truth
about a tragic murder
that took place a few years ago
I've come to speak to you
in Seo Joon Oh's place.
I don't think I can wait. I'll be back.
Mister, are you almost done?
Mister, I asked you
if you're almost done.
I'm talking to you...
Mister. Are you hard of hearing?
- What's this?
- What? I'm Ki Joon.
You're a smart one. Look behind you.
- Hey, take better care of this.
- You're so smart.
Joon Oh! I'm here! Get in!
Why would I get in? Why the hell...
- You're in danger, get in!
- It wasn't dangerous at all!
Geez, seriously. Why did you run it over?
- That...
- Why did you drive so fast?
- I was going to save you from danger!
- What are you going to do now?
It's broken. What do we do?
I messed up everything!
- What are you going to do?
- I'll fix it.
Wow, seriously! What are you going to do?
Geez, these idiots.
Hey, what do we do? Geez!
This is why people need to have brains!
Yes.
Please turn on the radio.
The press conference
I told you about earlier.
Turn up the volume.
This is about Shin Jae Hyun's death
four years ago.
It was revealed that it wasn't a suicide.
It was murder
that was disguised as a suicide.
You're useful for once.
Close your eyes,
so I can send you off.
Sa... Save me... Save me...
Yes, I'll send you off in one shot.
No way.
Do you think I'll be doomed
without you?
Let go... Let go!
Is he dead?
Deputy CEO Jang, if we take him
to the hospital--
Then...
Take him.
Or, I'll turn myself in.
If I turn myself in, they could say
it was accidental death.
I'm sure... that's possible.
But...
Your life as a celebrity will be over.
[My So Hee]
No...
Tae Ho, do you really want to live?
Yes.
I want to live.
Choi Tae Ho.
Okay. You should live.
I'll save you.
Close your eyes,
so I can send you off.
- Sa... Save me...
- Jae Hyun. Jae Hyun...
Save me...
Let's send you off in one shot.
In one shot! Die! Die!
It was an obvious murder
that was devised secretly and elaborately
as a result of a man's ambition.
Who's voice did we just hear
in the recording?
Did we also hear the voice
of his accomplice in the recording?
CEO Jang! CEO Jang, we're in trouble.
Take a look at this.
- What's all the fuss about?
- Take a look.
[Press Conference
For Plane Crash Survivor]
Shin Jae Hyun's case was disguised
as a suicide four years ago
by CEO Jang of Legend Entertainment--
Jang Do Pal.
[Arrest Warrant]
His accomplice was Choi Tae Ho.
The murder was plotted by these two men.
That is why
I'm here to formally request
the investigation be reopened.
Tae Ho is going to try to take the cell
phone and stop the press conference.
So we will transfer the audio files
to Bong Hee's phone
and I'll stop Tae Ho
from going to the press conference.
- What do you think?
- What is he saying?
- I get it.
- Stop lying.
Ji Ah,
I have So Hee's cell phone, right?
So Tae Ho is going to try to take the
cell phone to stop the press conference.
Are you going to the press conference?
Tae Ho is going to try to stop us from
holding the press conference tomorrow.
And what do we need for the press
conference? We need those audio files.
We will transfer those files
to Bong Hee's phone
and I'll stop Tae Ho
from being able to do anything.
I'm confused now.
Then just do as I say.
For this plan, Byung Joo...
- Byung Joo.
- Why did you hit me? I'm sorry.
- So...
- I'm sorry.
Byung Joo, you need to convince
Tae Ho that I have the phone, okay?
[Joon Oh! Have you left yet?
Take care of the phone.]
- Oh, you scared me! Geez.
- I'll drive myself. Go home.
I'll drive you! If you go alone,
I'll be worried about you!
And Ho Hang, do what you always do.
Pretend to be scared
pretend to be deceived,
and pretend to be obedient.
Hey, I wasn't pretending.
- That's how I sound when I'm scared.
- Then do that.
That's how he sounds.
I'm really sorry.
I was so scared.
That's why I called you.
I know. I know.
- Then you should have called earlier!
- It's a relief though.
And when you follow them...
- I know, I planned it.
- Yes. I'll trust you with that.
- What about me?
- Bong Hee, take care of the audio files.
And Ji Ah, since this is important...
- Don't do anything.
- What?
- You can do that, right?
- Can you do that?
- It won't be easy.
- Good luck.
- Wait--
- And Ki Joon will come with me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
The plan is to get Jang Do Pal
with these files
and to nail Choi Tae Ho
as his accomplice.
If we use the suspicion
around the conspiracy strategically
we'll be able to nail Choi Tae Ho
for his other crimes as well.
Okay.
What does that mean?
They're going to catch Tae Ho too...
Never mind, don't do anything.
- It's dangerous!
- Geez, it's not dangerous!
It was dangerous, I'm telling you!
Yes, Tae Ho just left.
He's leaving through Gate Three.
Yes, I got it.
Subtitles by DramaFever