Subtitles by DramaFever
That person...
was always...
a threatening person to us.
That's why Yoon So Hee...
always called him a murderer.
And he...
tried to kill all of us.
He wanted to survive by himself...
So he tried to kill us,
when we were in the lifeboat with him.
It was because... we knew the truth.
To that person, we were...
people who needed to die.
Who was that person? Please tell us.
That murderer was...
Seo Joon Oh.
It was Seo Joon Oh.
Is Seo Joon Oh still alive?
Why did he kill Yoon So Hee?
- Were you at the scene?
- Hey!
It's not true, Prosecutor Yoon.
It's not true!
I'm so sorry.
For not being able save
the colleagues I loved...
And for coming back by myself...
I'm truly sorry.
No! It wasn't Seo Joon Oh,
Prosecutor Yoon!
Bong Hee. Let's talk outside.
If you do this,
it'll only make things difficult for you.
Regarding your questions,
we will return to answer them
once we complete
the additional investigation.
Choi Tae Ho! Choi Tae Ho!
- Choi Tae Ho!
- Please answer us!
She got through.
I apologize.
[Episode 8]
Let go! Let go of me!
Was that why you tried
to stop me from coming here?
If so, I won't wait around foolishly
any longer.
Where's Choi Tae Ho?
Where's Chairwoman Jo?
Bong Hee.
Do you think anything will change
if you see them?
You said you understood.
So you should get your act together!
The survivor who is here is Choi Tae Ho.
Not Seo Joon Oh. He's dead!
I think Jang Do Pal sent those guys
to block her.
I think Jang Do Pal and Chairwoman Jo
are in on it together.
Figure out Choi Tae Ho's movements.
I'll call you later.
You're not coming with us?
I have something I have to check.
You worked hard today.
Please give us a call!
Geez, I thought my eyes
were going to run out of tears.
Good work today, Tae Ho.
I know you're still emotional
but can I ask you something?
What happened to Joon Oh?
I'm talking about Lee Juno of
Seo Taeji and Boys. Don't misunderstand.
You see, I was a  bag fan
when I was little.
I used to walk home from school
while listening to "Come Back Home."
I had hoped I would meet Lee Juno
once I became a manager
but I don't know when I'll get
that chance.
I'll get back to work. I'm sorry.
- Damn it.
- Get out. Get out!
Get out, you bastard!
Get out, Choi Tae Ho!
Get out. Get out!
Get out, you son of a bitch!
Get out, Choi Tae Ho! Get out! Get out!
Choi Tae Ho. It looks like everyone
believes you right now, doesn't it?
But everyone will end up finding out
what kind of bastard you really are
and what shit you did.
Seo Joon Oh and I will make sure of it.
Stop fooling around and listen to me.
This isn't a deserted island, it's Seoul.
Do you think people will
believe what you say?
Stop looking for Seo Joon Oh, he's dead.
Focus on your own future.
He's not dead! He's not dead.
Seo Joon Oh's not dead! He's alive.
I saw his dead body.
When Seo Joon Oh died, I...
Never mind. Forget it.
Let's go, Byung Joo!
Are you all right?
- Yes.
- I have a question, Ra Bong Hee.
Are you...
someone I can trust?
I'm sorry, Prosecutor Yoon.
Right now...
All I can tell you,
is that you have to believe me.
But, Prosecutor Yoon,
you're So Hee's older brother.
That's why you need to know the truth.
The person who killed So Hee...
wasn't Seo Joon Oh.
It was Choi Tae Ho.
Okay. Can you wipe his face?
What are we going to do with him?
Let's wait a little longer.
What are we waiting for,
and for how much longer?
We should either kill him
or kick him out.
Let's wait for Journalist Kim
to wake up...
And see what he has to say
before we decide, Ji Ah.
I need to know something.
Why did he kill So Hee...
And what did he hear,
that made him go crazy?
It's hard for you, isn't it?
I'm okay.
I just feel like they're not the people
I thought they were.
Not just Tae Ho, the other people too.
I don't know if they changed
from being here...
Or if they were always like that,
and I just didn't know.
If by any chance...
Journalist Kim doesn't wake up...
What will you do then?
If he never wakes up,
and you can't ask him what he knows...
What will you do?
Hey, Joon Oh.
Go inside and get some sleep.
Geez.
Joon Oh!
Journalist Kim is awake.
- Wait out here.
- Pardon?
What is it?
Did Journalist Kim wake up?
Yeah. But he wants to speak
to Joon Oh alone. Just a moment.
- Are... Are you all right?
- Yes.
I came to help you, but I ended up
causing you trouble instead.
What do you mean you came to help me?
I received some information.
About Shin Jae Hyun's death.
That's all in the past,
so why bring it up now?
Shin Jae Hyun didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
If I told you he had another guest
at his house...
besides you, before he died...
Would you believe me?
If that were true, it would have been
revealed in the police investigation.
Who gave you that information?
And how did they know?
You must have many questions,
but this is all you need to know.
Yoon So Hee's death,
and Shin Jae Hyun's murder...
are connected.
As is the reason
why Choi Tae Ho tried to kill me.
In... Instead of saying these things...
Do you have any evidence?
If I show you the evidence,
will you believe me?
Ji Ah.
Can you get me some water?
I'm thirsty.
What is this son of a bitch saying?
Here you go, you son of a bitch.
Are you hiding something from me?
What are you saying?
If you are, just tell me.
Can't you just tell me?
I'll look into it then.
Wait.
- Okay.
- What about Tae Ho?
Yes, he just came out.
That crazy bastard. This isn't
the time for this. He has no patience.
Oh my, Prosecutor Yoon!
You waited for a long time, didn't you?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Jang Do Pal of Legend Entertainment.
We've met before, haven't we? But...
You're not very punctual.
Oh no.
I forgot I took up
a lot of your precious time.
If you haven't had lunch yet,
let's go eat.
It's my treat because I was late--
Let's skip all that.
Let me meet your friend instead.
Excuse me?
Choi Tae Ho.
I'm here today to see your friend.
Is it because he's a top star and
a national hero? I couldn't reach him.
Oh, I see. You should have
given me some notice.
Our Tae Ho isn't feeling so well
right now.
- Byung Joo, water.
- We don't have any.
He just got an IV, and went home to rest.
Is that so?
There are many people wanting to see
him these days, so he's been strained.
I'm so sorry. What do we do?
He can't avoid me forever.
If you respond this way, it always
ends up as a bigger problem later on.
Who's avoiding you?
Come on, Prosecutor Yoon.
We'll contact you soon--
Answer my call next time.
It won't be a call asking you
if you're doing well.
- I won't see you out, Prosecutor Yoon.
- Oh!
Why did you keep Choi Tae Ho hidden?
What are you saying?
You know. You were in China
before coming back to Korea.
Was he that ill?
Okay, start with your right foot.
Like this.
Tae Ho! You can't do this here!
- You have to wake up! Tae Ho!
- Where are we?
- We're in front of the company.
- Okay.
- Walk straight, Tae Ho!
- Okay, leave me alone!
Geez, CEO Jang told you not to let
anyone see you so drunk!
- Please walk like you're sober.
- What are you saying?
Why are you acting like Yoon So Hee? Huh?
Geez, kids who aren't worth anything...
need to be taught a lesson
to wake the hell up.
Whoa! Tae Ho! Ouch... Tae Ho!
Tae Ho, get ahold of yourself!
You can't sleep here, Tae Ho!
What's going on here?
Tae Ho, you can't do this here.
Tae Ho!
Please give that to Choi Tae Ho.
Who... who are you?
If you tell him Yoon So Hee's older
brother wants to see him, he'll get it.
[Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young]
Tae Ho.
Choi Tae Ho!
I told you... it's too early to pop open
a champagne bottle, didn't I?
You should have been more careful!
Yeah.
What?
A survivor?
Did you get his testimony?
Who's right? Ra Bong Hee or Choi Tae Ho?
I'm not sure. They said
they didn't get a proper answer.
- What does that mean?
- He's not in very good shape.
No, don't worry.
It must have been hard for you.
Wow, seriously.
Are you all right?
- Are you?
- Um...
I... will be protected, right?
Of course. Nothing will happen
to you while you're here.
There's no need to worry.
No one can find out...
that I'm here.
No one must know that I'm here.
If I'm caught... it'll be over for me.
It'll be over.
Did something happen to you
before you got here?
No way. I can't talk to anyone
unless it's CEO Hwang.
Send him to a hospital.
Yes, I will send him to the hospital
where Hwang Jae Gook--
That's not what I'm saying!
Does he seem normal to you?
How could he of all people be a witness
and appear at a time like this?
The state that he's in
is quite unfortunate, but--
Let's watch over him as he recovers.
We can discuss what to do with him.
Chairwoman Jo.
You don't think Choi Tae Ho's testimony
will be sabotaged by Tae Ho Hang, do you?
We have to make sure that doesn't happen.
Yes.
I just got the call. We'll be able
to meet with them tomorrow.
Secretary Tae was the only witness
who saw So Hee's murder.
He will surely testify on our side.
As you said...
I'm curious about
what that sole witness will say.
I can't wait to find out.
Bye.
So Hee was the one
who tied my hair for me.
I wonder if this still has any juice.
It's been decades,
but it looks just fine to me.
Anyway... What will Joon Oh do?
- What about him?
- I overheard something.
About Jae Hyun...
- It might not have been suicide.
- Is that what Journalist Kim said?
Yes.
That's why Joon Oh left to check
Journalist Kim's belongings.
Hey, if it wasn't suicide...
Does that mean...
someone killed Jae Hyun?
Tae Oh! Tae Oh!
Ho Hang, you really know how to talk.
Save me... Save me, CEO Hwang!
Where did Joon Oh go?
Murderer!
How could he come here
after killing someone?
It's Seo Joon Oh!
Is that Seo Joon Oh? He's so shameless!
He's a total animal.
How could he come here?
He's so shameless.
That's Seo Joon Oh, isn't it?
Wow, is he even human?
Are you really giving this to me?
Of course!
I received it with your song.
You're trying to overwork me forever
after giving this to me, aren't you?
Wow, you got smarter.
Of course! Until we die.
Geez, I want to...
I want to debut too!
You'd better. You'll debut.
Just wait a little longer.
Right now, I have enough
on my own plate.
I'll make sure to help you
so that you can do what you want.
I'm going to hold you
to that promise, okay?
Of course!
Yo! Dreamers won an award!
- Yeah!
- Shin Jae Hyun!
If you can't hold on to Jae Hyun,
Dreamers is over. That's it.
Jae Hyun listens to you.
Try to convince him.
Why don't we take this chance to let
Jae Hyun debut or go to another company?
Why do you want to let talent rot away?
It's not like we can
depend on Jae Hyun forever.
I'm begging you, please?
It will happen when it's time.
Tell him to wait.
Hold on to him. Don't let him go!
You really don't trust me?
I asked you to wait a little longer.
I said I'll help you become
an independent artist.
If you just leave like this,
it'll ruin everything!
Aren't you bothered that you
waited all this time for nothing?
Then for you... how much longer
is just a little longer?
Until the third album?
Until the next concert? Or...
Until the awards ceremony?
Joon Oh. It's been seven years.
Joon Oh.
In the end,
you're just like everyone else.
You pretend that you care about me
but in the end, it's all about
Dreamers, am I right?
In the immediate future,
you're waiting for Tae Ho's replacement.
In the end... all you can think about
is your album!
So what do you want me to do? Huh?
That's why...
It's getting too hard for me.
It's so difficult, I want to die.
Then die, you son of a bitch!
Then die.
If you can't endure this, just die.
How can you do this to me?
You said... You said
I was part of Dreamers too!
[Our Jae Hyun]
The number you have dialed
is unavailable--
Joon Oh. Why are you out here?
Did you see Jae Hyun? Where is he?
Did you hear anything from him?
- Is he upstairs?
- Yes.
- Can't you reach him?
- I talked to him for a little bit.
I told you to convince him nicely.
Did something happen?
Why... Why is everyone here?
Why? Why? Why?
What... What are we doing here?
Hey.
- What is it?
- Jae Hyun wanted to talk to us.
Okay, since we're all here,
let's listen to what he has to say.
[A Mysterious Murder,
Who's The Murderer?]
[The Wrongful Death Of A Trainee.
Is This How He'll Be Forgotten?]
Jae... Jae... Jae Hyun.
Hey, Jae... Jae Hyun! Jae... Jae... Hey!
Hey! Jae Hyun!
No!
He's still there?
Yes. He is.
It's been over 30 minutes already.
Tell him to take it easy.
Gosh, this waiting is tiring me out!
Yes, I'm getting tired too,
and I'm hungry... No, never mind.
Hurry up and wake up already!
Hurry! What are you doing here like this?
Please wake up...
Excuse me. Tae Ho Hang, the time--
Please go away!
CEO Hwang. I'm so scared!
Geez, you've been here long enough!
Hwang Jae Gook has gotten
a lot better lately!
Wow, seriously. Yes! I know!
- You have no idea what's happening!
- Yes! Okay! Calm down! Calm down!
Please calm down! I understand,
but we're a little busy!
Jae Hyun!
[The Unfortunate Suicide Of A Trainee]
Tae Ho.
Why did you do it?
Joon Oh.
I'm having a really hard time right now.
Joon Oh. In the end,
this is how far we came.
I really hope you're the last one.
All of this is too hard for me.
Hey, do you think we'll fail
without you? Huh?
- Wait!
- Hey, let go!
911. Jae Hyun. Jae Hyun, hold on.
I'll call an ambulance. Jae Hyun!
Please circle around the block.
Jae Hyun... How could you?
Jae Hyun...
Why Jae Hyun?
Why are you so worried about him?
He was already dead! Falling off
a building didn't change anything!
Why?
Joon Oh... Joon Oh... What do we do
about Joon Oh? Joon Oh.
Huh? Secretary Tae.
- Joon Oh. What do we about Joon Oh?
- Wh... What's the matter?
Tae Ho.
Tae Ho...
Should I go with you?
No, I'll go by myself.
Chairwoman Jo. Ra Bong Hee is here.
Ra Bong...
Why is she here?
Did someone call her?
I'm not sure. She's out front.
Let her in.
I don't think anyone asked you
to come here today.
No. I chose to come here.
I heard Secretary Tae is here.
I want to hear his testimony.
You can't just show up here
because you want to.
Then who is allowed to listen to it?
Do we have to share
the same opinion to be here?
Fine. If you want to join us...
If you were to join us,
what is it that you want?
If today's testimony goes sideways,
tell everyone that it wasn't Seo Joon Oh.
Please fix the situation so that
he's no longer framed as a criminal.
Aren't you getting ahead of yourself?
We don't know anything yet.
Let's wait and see.
Let's see what happens.
You don't have to be nervous. All you
have to do is tell us what you know.
What's wrong?
- Are... Are you all right?
- Yes.
No! Wait! What's wrong? Is it coming out?
Wait. Wa--
You can't do that in here! You can't!
Do you think you can swallow it?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Not here!
Don't do that here! No!
- Are you okay?
- Please give me some time.
I know you're feeling sick,
but we're tight on time--
Damn it! You won't even
give me time to vomit?
What is that?
I'll be out soon! Wait!
Geez, seriously!
What the hell are you... Huh? Huh?
What is this? Where did he go?
Who are you? Let go!
What is this? Damn it...
Geez!
There.
Geez, what is this? Seriously.
That isn't it!
Tae Ho Hang, let's go--
Tae Ho Hang! Geez, there's a lot.
Where is he?
What do you mean by that?
How could he just disappear?
I'm not sure either. He was vomiting.
I was stuck to him like glue...
Find him! Find him and bring him here!
Chairwoman Jo, what's going on?
Who disappeared?
Save me! Save me! Save me!
Please! Save me!
Help!
Prosecutor Yoon,
I have a favor to ask you.
Please find Tae Ho Hang.
Tae Ho! Tae Ho, save me!
Save me! Save me...
You're alive, huh?
I'm so happy to see you like this.
Gosh, why hasn't Ki Joon come back yet?
Did something happen to him?
Gosh, I'm so anxious.
Joon Oh!
Tell me.
Why do I have to save you?
Tell me!
Just let go.
Live.
Don't let go... Live!
You really don't listen, do you?
Hold on!
Do you think I'll fail without you? Huh?
No!
Ki Joon.
He's not there. He wasn't where
Journalist Kim told me to check.
- He wasn't there?
- I'll check the woods.
No, don't do that. Sit.
It's dangerous out there.
Geez!
What took so long?
Secretary Tae.
Why are you searching someone
else's car? Should I report this or what?
Oh, Prosecutor Yoon.
- You know where Choi Tae Ho is, right?
- Pardon?
- Where is he right now?
- Why are you looking for Tae Ho?
Where is Tae Ho right now?
He's scheduled to work right now.
Is there a problem?
Secretary Tae. Are you okay?
Where were you?
I looked everywhere for you.
Oh.
A friend. I met with a friend of mine.
I suddenly remembered I had plans.
You met a friend,
right after you went to the bathroom?
I can begin my testimony now, right?
Secretary Tae.
It's true that nothing happened, right?
- Yes.
- Let's begin! Hurry.
Um, please give honest testimony.
- Sure.
- Make sure you tell them what you saw.
It's true that Yoon So Hee was murdered.
I saw it.
Are you saying you witnessed
the murder yourself?
Yes.
Okay, then. Who murdered Yoon So Hee?
You know already.
Seo Joon Oh.
Choi Tae Ho was right.
He killed her.
No way. This is wrong. This isn't right--
Be quiet! Can't you see
that this is important?
No way.
And, there's something else
I want to say.
He had an accomplice.
She knew what Seo Joon Oh was doing,
but she covered it up, and helped him.
Who was that person?
All you have to do is tell them
what you saw, okay?
You saw it!
You saw Seo Joon Oh kill her.
What?
Ho Hang.
This is Seoul.
We're not on a deserted island anymore.
We... saw the same thing, didn't we?
Secretary Tae, what are you saying?
That accomplice...
is right here.
What are you saying, Secretary Tae?
- Let go! Secretary Tae!
- Ra Bong Hee!
- She was his accomplice.
- Secretary Tae... Secretary Tae!
- Oh, Ki Joon.
- Oh, did you find him? No?
Geez, I'm tired.
He's nowhere to be found.
Geez, seriously.
I get scared at night.
No!
I...
I should go back, right?
They're all waiting for you.
You can definitely go back.
That's where you're supposed to be.
You have a place there.
Let's go.
- Hey!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Are you all right? Huh?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I heard everything from Journalist Kim.
I was the one who sent you
to convince Jae Hyun.
I made you do what I was supposed to do.
I'm sorry. I have no right to be the CEO.
I...
I killed Tae Ho.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't save him.
- Oh...
- I'm sorry.
That's okay, Joon Oh.
Why do I feel like this
when people are dying?
I'm so calm.
I shouldn't be so calm.
My own kids keep dying.
Joon Oh.
Don't blame yourself too much.
We know you didn't do it on purpose.
Hey, you should apply some medicine.
Joon Oh. We don't think
it was your fault.
You know that, right?
Why aren't you answering me?
If you think it's your fault again,
you're dead.
And...
I'm sorry.
- For what?
- Just because.
I don't think I ever
apologized to you before.
That's why you should
say it more often from now on.
Joon Oh. No matter what happened,
it's more important that you came back.
That's right. You're important to us.
I don't care about anything else.
- Don't say that.
- Why not?
I should. I should say more.
It's not just us,
many other people think...
Jae Hyun died because of you.
Tae Ho didn't just frame you,
he messed up your life.
We should reveal who the murderers are,
and who they killed, don't you think?
We should expose the truth.
I killed Tae Ho.
That's the truth too.
When we... get back...
If we get back...
Help me so that I can get
the punishment I deserve.
That's why none of you...
should do anything for me.
The things that happened here...
The things we saw and heard here...
Let's remember them for what they are.
Geez.
Oh! Secretary Tae!
Um, um... He... Hello? Um...
It's a boat.
It is. They're so lucky.
They get to have fun on a boat.
While we're stuck over here.
Why is the boat coming this way?
Why is it coming this way?
I think it's coming to save us!
Wow! They're coming! Wow!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
They found another survivor.
They found two this time.
Someone heard some noise.
I'm getting a weird feeling.
Did you find Choi Tae Ho's body?
Did you check?
- Hurry up and follow me!
- I'll wait for you, okay?
No, go! Hurry up and go!
- You shouldn't forget.
- Ji Ah!
I don't know what happened.
Where did it all go wrong?
- No! No, it's dangerous! No!
- You can't go!
No! No...