Subtitles by DramaFever
We found out when we were
reinvestigating Shin Jae Hyun's case.
Yoon So Hee, who testified at the time
there was record of her statement saying
that she had evidence that it was murder.
Look at this. Look at it!
It started then. I've known Yoon So Hee
since they were secretly dating.
We asked the police officer
who was responsible for this case
and he said So Hee
did give that statement
but she ultimately insisted
that Seo Joon Oh was the murderer
so her statements were inconsistent.
You can't forget him.
You killed Jae Hyun.
We'll die anyway!
Whether we starve to death or someone
kills us, we're going to die here!
So Hee was probably
threatened by Jang Do Pal.
That's why she changed her story.
Because she knew
about Jae Hyun's murder...
In the end...
That's why, in order to find out
the truth about So Hee's death
we must catch the murderer
who killed Shin Jae Hyun.
That's how we can clear
your false charges as well.
A package will land in Korea
very shortly.
The lost items that were found
on the deserted island.
In with that stuff,
I found something that looked familiar.
These are the pictures I received.
Seo Joon Oh.
Isn't this the cell phone that Ji Ah
was waving in the cave?
This was So Hee's cell phone.
- It's no longer here.
- I'm here because you said it was here!
It's not here. Someone picked it up.
The lost items from the deserted island
have arrived. What should we do?
Do I still look like Chairwoman Jo
to you?
Don't ask me that.
Get rid of them! Burn them!
Let's find that cell phone.
Let's bring it back here!
Okay.
Let's find it.
[Lost Articles]
Beloved citizens of Seowon!
I'm your candidate, Jo Hee Kyung!
- We must change everything--
- Jo Hee Kyung! Jo Hee Kyung!
Everything must change!
Thank you! Yes! Yes! Thank you! Oh.
Oh my. Oh my! Grandmother!
Yes, thank you.
- Yes, please vote for me.
- Yes. Yes. Yes.
- Oh! You're here!
- Yes. Yes.
Yes, thank you. Yes.
I love these vegetable side dishes,
especially bellflower root.
These aren't bellflower root.
These are chicken feet!
Do you eat these as side dishes as well?
Of course! They're delicious!
Here you go, please try some.
- No, that's okay.
- They're delicious!
- Oh, Congresswoman Jo, please use this.
- Oh, no. It's okay!
Let's take a picture together! Oh my!
Here. Here.
Oh! Oh my! Oh my! What do we do?
- Yes, please get some rest.
- Oh, yes. You worked hard today.
Gosh, I could die.
Have you been well, ma'am?
Oh my, who is this?
It's been a long time.
You must be busy
preparing for your election.
Oh, you know. An extra body
wouldn't be enough at this point.
But, I'm sure you're not calling me
to cheer me on.
Okay, what is this about?
Your team should have gotten
a package. Did you receive it?
A package? What package?
You know, the lost items that
the survivors used on the island.
It should have arrived by now.
Lost items?
I'm not sure about any lost items.
I haven't received anything like that.
You'll receive it soon. I know
because I tracked the package.
Wait, Prosecutor Yoon. It's been
so long since that case closed...
And, our team dispersed,
so it might not even come here.
Your team dispersed,
but the case isn't closed yet.
Wait, does that package contain
something that belonged to Yoon So Hee?
Don't you understand how rude it is
to act like I have something of yours?
If you look in the package,
you will find a white cell phone.
That's all I want to see.
It was So Hee's.
Hey, Prosecutor Yoon.
I have to get back out there
for my campaign
so I'll call you back after I check.
Gosh, what is this about?
The number you have dialed
is unavailable--
This case is still holding me back,
even after the team dispersed.
Geez, why isn't anything working out?
Yes, what happened last night?
The items that she told you to burn...
Did you burn them already?
Did you actually burn them already?
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Open the trunk!
Why did you have to do
exactly as you were told?
They were actually going to burn
everything because I told them to?
Well, you told me not to talk
about it again, so...
He said this was Yoon So Hee's.
- I guess she liked antique things.
- What do you mean?
That is a really old model.
It's not turning on.
He's probably going to be here soon.
We need to know what's on it,
before he arrives.
Let me see.
Because this is such an old model,
unless the battery is dead
I don't know if it can be fixed.
Who should we bring this to?
Bong Hee, I'm on my way
to meet Jo Hee Kyung.
I think it'll be best if I meet
with her on my own first.
Where are you two?
Oh, there's somewhere we need to go.
Is Bong Hee busy with something?
Why are you answering her phone?
- Bong Hee is driving right now.
- Turn right.
My license is suspended,
as you probably know.
Prosecutor Yoon, we're on our way
to meet Byung Joo--
We can't meet you.
No, we'll be there soon!
Please find the cell phone! Good luck!
You too!
- Bong Hee, why aren't you turning right?
- Yes, right.
- Please make a U-turn.
- Make a U-turn up there.
- A U-turn?
- Who are they? Do you know them?
Yeah, prepare the cars.
Tell everyone to gather.
We're going to Seowon.
You there. Who are you?
Geez.
It's me. CEO Jang, can you see me?
- How long have you been there?
- It's not that. There's so much dust!
You see, I have germophobia. I was
going to clean while you are away.
People say, the right hand should work
so that the left hand doesn't notice.
That's what I'm doing. I'm actually
on the small side, but you saw me.
Geez, the left hand caught me.
I was caught.
Wait.
Yes?
Byung Joo.
It's okay.
After Tae Ho finishes his work today
make him loosen up and enjoy his night.
Whether you drink together, or play games
- do whatever.
- But why?
Why are you asking questions?
Just do as you're told.
But if I suggest this out of the blue
he'll scold me again.
He always curses at me, you see.
He's been working so hard
so you can just tell him
that I told him to take a break today.
There's that method, isn't there?
Thank you, CEO Jang.
Don't leave Tae Ho alone
until he goes home
- and then keep an eye on him.
- Yes.
And don't tell Tae Ho about
what we just talked about.
- Yes.
- If anything happens...
Call me right away.
Yes. Don't worry, CEO Jang.
While I was in America,
my name was "Mark."
Your source of income
is under my control.
- Yes.
- Remember that.
- Why Seowon?
- I'm not sure either.
But Jang Do Pal just rushed out
with his guys.
But Prosecutor Yoon said
Jo Hee Kyung's district is Seowon.
Is that why Jang Do Pal went there?
Yes, but it's strange that Jang Do Pal
told me not to tell Choi Tae Ho.
Is it because Choi Tae Ho could worry?
But that only happens between
married couples who worry--
Hey, who cares?
Anyway, Byung Joo, we're counting on you.
Tell me everything that Jang Do Pal
and Choi Tae Ho talk about. I told you.
You're small and compact,
so no one can see you.
That's the most important advantage
for a spy.
But, I don't think
I'm as small as we thought.
- What are you saying?
- I was seen earlier.
- Who saw you?
- Jang Do Pal. I was taken aback.
He was probably mistaken!
Make yourself smaller! Try it out.
Try it! Byung Joo, where are you?
Byung Joo, where are you?
- Byung Joo! Have you seen him?
- I can't see him!
- Byung Joo!
- Here I am!
You scared me! See?
Okay. If it means you will return
I will do my best to make myself smaller.
Wait.
What's that?
- It's time to pick up Choi Tae Ho.
- Get out.
Yes.
- Bong Hee, see you later.
- Eat this.
Try to make yourself really small!
Hey, you'd better not buy me a hamburger
with bacon in it next time!
Be careful!
Are you worried?
Byung Joo is half the size he was before.
He must have been on a diet.
I really can't see him. He'll be fine.
He'll be okay, right?
Yes, very good!
Yes, nice!
Yes.
Okay, look this way!
Yes, very good!
I'll check something before we resume!
Ji Ah, water.
Give me that.
Ji Ah.
It looks like Ki Joon is misunderstanding
but he should know how to differentiate
personal life from work.
I'll talk to CEO Jang
and find you another manager.
I'm just thinking of you.
Give us a moment.
- You want me to change managers?
- Yeah.
You damned son of a bitch.
Do you know how much harm you
caused me already, you son of a bitch?
You have no right to talk after
killing people, you bastard. Shut up.
Lost items?
A cell phone?
[I can't take your side]
[I'm letting you know just in case...]
Why are you out here already?
Are you finished?
If you were going to act like this,
why did you let me work with him?
If you're having a hard time now,
how will you endure the movie?
What do you mean?
You left because you got mad
while watching our commercial shoot.
- Oh, that's not it...
- Then why did you leave?
What were you thinking about all day?
I can't express all of my feelings to you
because I want to protect you.
What am I saying? Let's go in.
Ki Joon.
You seem to have a lot of secrets
these days.
What kind of secrets could I have?
It's just that, these days...
It's because I'm so frustrated.
Geez, I'm so frustrated.
Excuse me!
Oh, what do we do? What do we do?
What's wrong?
- You can't go inside. Please wait here.
- Why? Why?
You can't go inside.
- Mrs. Hwang, what's the matter?
- I don't know! All of a sudden...
It looks like he has gotten through
the critical stage.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Let's talk outside.
- Yes.
CEO Hwang.
You were in critical condition.
But, you made it through.
Please, continue to hold on.
Don't give up, okay?
Don't leave me here by myself.
In order to save you...
I even betrayed Joon Oh.
He... He promised
not to hurt you anymore...
That's why I sold my soul to the devil.
I'm sorry.
CEO Hwang, if you leave like this,
I'll really be a bad guy.
CEO Hwang. Jae Gook. Don't give up.
You'll wake up, won't you?
You're going to wake up, right? Please.
Ho Hang. The doctor said he's all right.
Don't worry.
Mrs. Hwang. You must have been
shocked. Thank goodness...
If...
Mrs. Hwang, just a moment.
Hey, stop it already!
Be quiet! What if someone sees you?
Keep your hat on! Lift this up too.
Geez, how far up? Lift it. Lift it.
Is that good? Is that good? How's that?
- Cover your eyes. Very nice.
- Hey, is this the right hospital?
It is. I've visited before.
- There's Secretary Tae. He came out.
- Where?
Hey, why aren't you stopping me?
Look at me. Okay, there.
That was strange.
I saw Joon Oh. It was definitely Joon Oh.
What the heck?
Joon Oh.
- Why aren't you stopping me?
- I didn't know you were going.
Wow, seriously.
Oh! Whoa! He's a ghost! He's a ghost!
Whoa! Whoa!
Ghost! No, there's no ghost!
Wow! That scared me.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
Hello?
You've gotten weaker.
Our CEO Hwang.
Hold on for a little longer.
I'll catch them...
And expose the truth.
Seo Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
Mrs. Hwang is coming. Hurry!
Tae Ho. Tae Ho?
Is there anything you want to do today?
Why?
I knew you would ask me why,
so I asked CEO Jang about it.
CEO Jang said you've been working
really hard recently
so he told me to take you out drinking,
or play games with you at your house.
Why would I drink with you?
And, play games with me?
Does it look like I have no one
to play games with besides you?
Just take me home.
Okay.
[Choi Tae Ho is home.]
What are you doing here
in broad daylight?
- Are you guarding my house for robbers?
- No...
Then... are you spying on me?
No.
- Did CEO Jang tell you to do this?
- No.
[Choi Tae Ho is home.
Oh no, we're in trouble...]
Put that phone down and drive.
Geez, seriously.
If I want to survive,
whose side do I need to take? Seriously.
I'm so conflicted.
Choi Tae Ho or Jang Do Pal?
Geez, I'm so conflicted.
Whose side should I take?
Oh! Take this.
Why don't you offer him some tea?
- Yes, what kind of tea would you like?
- That's okay. Thank you.
- Congresswoman Jo.
- I'm fine too!
Oh.
Did you look for the package?
Oh, that? I was informed about it.
I received it...
But it was evidence
that should be sent to the prosecution.
It's not something I can just give you.
You know that.
You're saying...
You won't let me look at an item
that belonged to my deceased sister?
Ma'am.
Are you really going to act like this?
I want to show it to you too.
Look here, former chairwoman
of the special investigation committee!
You weren't even interested in those
items until I told you about them!
You didn't know it was So Hee's phone,
or where those items came from!
But now that I want to see it, it's
suddenly evidence for the prosecution?
Why are you trying so hard
when you already know how things work?
It's quite unfortunate,
but there's nothing I can do for you.
As you can see, this was a short break
from my election campaign.
You've never lost a loved one, have you?
To me, that cell phone...
is the only item that my sister
left behind.
Her will could be on that phone,
and the truth could be on it as well.
And the person who will expose the truth,
the person who must see the evidence
is not the prosecution,
it's Yoon So Hee's brother.
It's me, Yoon Tae Young.
What kind of place do you think this is?
This isn't the special investigation
base! This is my election headquarters!
Do I really need to listen
to everything you say while we're here?
Even if you don't show it to me,
there are other ways.
I'll make myself clear.
You made a mistake today.
Why did you do that?
I thought you intended
to show him Yoon So Hee's phone.
Last night, the CEO
of Legend Entertainment came to customs
and demanded that we tell them
where the lost items went.
I thought you should know.
Just leave it.
Let's wait and see for a little longer.
Geez, she's strange. She doesn't need
those items and they are important to us.
Does she think we won't see them
if she doesn't let us?
There are many people
going in and out of her headquarters
so I'm pretty sure it isn't there.
Let's go to the hotel. There's a place
where she rests between appearances.
Yes. Go to the hotel.
Okay. We'll head that way.
Is there another way, Seo Joon Oh?
Bong Hee, the only way is for you
to drive faster.
I'm driving fast already!
If you're going to be like this,
I'll take a taxi. Give me 10,000 won.
CEO Jang. Yes, it's Byung Joo.
Tae Ho is on his way over there
right now.
Yes, I thought you should know.
That's why I called.
Tae Ho, what brings you here?
Why?
Am I somewhere I shouldn't be?
Hey, no way.
It's just that I told you to rest,
for your own good, but here you are.
You wanted me to rest
but had someone watching me?
That doesn't make any sense.
So?
Is there something
I'm not supposed to find out?
Wait outside.
Tae Ho.
The lost items from
the deserted island arrived.
Inside one of those boxes...
is So Hee's cell phone.
It's in Jo Hee Kyung's hands right now.
But...
Why are you telling me this now?
I didn't tell you because I wasn't sure
if there was any evidence in those boxes.
And because it's Jo Hee Kyung,
I feel cautious about jumping in.
I was going to check first--
Now that I know about it,
let's check together.
Whether there's something in there
or not, I have to know.
Sure. For me, it's always reassuring
to have you around.
Jae Hyun!
Let's talk.
You already know.
What else is there to talk about?
This won't change my mind.
You were doing so well. What's wrong?
Dreamers has just started to do well.
If you help us a little more--
Then, should I work in the background
behind your success
and... live as a shadow?
Jae Hyun.
Is it because you need money?
If it is, I'll talk to CEO Hwang--
Hey, you!
Do you think I'm a money-hungry gangster?
If you're going to give me that
bullshit, go. I don't want to hear it.
Tell me what you want.
I'll give you anything, if you stay.
Who do you think you are?
You don't even know how to sing,
so how can you help me?
Instead of wasting your time
holding on to me
go and practice your singing.
That will be more helpful to you.
- You're speaking too carelessly.
- No.
If I compare this to how you treated me,
I'm not being careless at all.
What did I do that was so wrong?
Didn't I treat you well,
if all you did was lend me your voice?
All I did was lend you a voice?
Fine.
This voice will quietly disappear.
So I wish you all the best
in your future.
I'll be watching to see how well you do.
Do you feel like you can say anything
because I praised you?
Do you think I'll be doomed without you?
Let go! Let go! Let go!
I just want the best for us.
I'm sorry, okay? Jae Hyun.
- Geez, seriously!
- I stopped gently.
Let's go.
Whoa.
Hey! What are you doing?
Yes, I'm coming! I'm coming, Seo Joon Oh!
- Hey.
- Yes?
- What's with you? What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
Why are you putting on makeup?
We're entering a hotel,
but I look so tacky and untidy...
Hey, who cares?
We're just going to a hotel.
- Is this your first time?
- Yes.
Wow, that's so like you.
You did so many things
for the first time after meeting me.
You were lucky to meet a good artist.
I let you go on a plane
and took you to a hotel.
You should be thankful to me, okay?
Give that to me.
- What are you doing?
- Come here.
- No, that's okay--
- Come here so we can go!
Like this. Pucker up.
More!
You messed it up, didn't you?
You rubbed it all over, didn't you?
No, you look pretty.
- Pardon?
- You look pretty.
Wait for me, Seo Joon Oh!
- Bong Hee, where are you?
- We're in front of the hotel.
We're going inside right now.
Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal's guys
are scattered around the hotel.
This goes for Seo Joon Oh too,
but if he sees you
he'll get suspicious,
so be careful not to get caught.
I'll go upstairs and reserve a room.
You should take off your shoes
when you enter a hotel.
- What are you doing? Take them off!
- Okay, I'm taking them off.
I'm not stupid, you know!
Happy? Huh?
Hey, you were really rude.
What do you mean, "Happy? Happy?"
Hurry up, Seo Joon Oh!
Wow, seriously!
15th floor. Go!
Hey, this is your first time
in a hotel elevator, isn't it?
There are people like that. Go! Go! Go!
15th floor!
Oh, does it detect sound?
It's not working.
- 15th!
- 15!
15th... 15th floor.
Wait!
Oh.
Oh! Aren't you Choi Tae Ho? I'm a huge
fan! Please give me your autograph.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Since Jang Do Pal
and Choi Tae Ho are on the move
I am certain
they're after So Hee's phone.
I'm not sure exactly
what is on that phone
but it's clear there's something
that they're trying to hide.
Earlier, Byung Joo said Jang Do Pal was
coming here behind Choi Tae Ho's back.
- He thought it was strange.
- Is that so?
I can't be on your side,
but I'm telling you this, just in case.
Jang Do Pal asked Ji Ah
whose phone it was.
He seems to be sensitive about So Hee's
things because of Choi Tae Ho.
I'm letting you know in case this can be
helpful in clearing your false charges.
No need to thank me.
There's no need to refuse my thanks.
I'm already here to find that cell phone.
Wow, you've gotten slow.
If you're that slow,
I don't think you can work with me.
I hope you live happily ever after
with Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho.
You told me not to talk to you,
but why are you roaming about like that?
[Traitorous Jung Ki Joon]
- What?
- Yeah, Joon Oh. Where are you?
Why do you want to know?
Where are you?
- I'm at the Seoul Plaza Hotel.
- Where?
You know, that one time
after we finished work
there was pizza here,
so we ate four pizzas.
Are you following Jo Hee Kyung?
Are you alone?
Since you betrayed me, I'm always alone.
Hey, what if Jang Do Pal and
Choi Tae Ho find you? Get out!
But I'm not that scared for some reason.
Why aren't you scared?
Joon Oh. This situation
is a lot more serious than you think.
Those guys move in groups!
Anyway, I don't have a good feeling
about this, so get out. It's dangerous.
Get out of there--
Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
- No!
- Joon Oh!
What's wrong? What is it?
Ji Ah, I'm sorry, you have to go
by yourself today. It's an emergency!
- I'll call you! I'm sorry!
- Ki Joon!
Taxi! I'm sorry!
Ki Joon! Ki Joon! Ki Joon! Damn it!
Follow them!
Everything is A-OK.
He's using the slang term.
Oh, he said everything's okay.
- Tell him to keep watch anyway.
- Yes.
"Be on the lookout."
You're saying, Jo Hee Kyung's room,
and her election headquarters
those two rooms are suspicious, right?
Yes. Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
probably already know that.
All we have to do is get to them
before they do.
Prosecutor Yoon, stay at the headquarters
while Bong Hee and I search her room.
You must be careful.
Their side is on the move too.
Don't worry. The two of us
will search for it carefully.
From now on, it's all about timing.
During the afternoon,
when she's campaigning, is your best bet.
In that time period,
please search her room.
Okay! Let's do that! Let's go!
But, Seo Joon Oh.
You must be very careful.
Don't worry. We'll do whatever it takes
to bring her phone back.
I'll throw these out.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
Jo Hee Kyung! Jo Hee Kyung!
[Jo Hee Kyung's Campaign Schedule]
Go.
Key! Key!
Hey, why did you throw it?
Like this, here... Come here.
- I can't focus.
- Bong Hee, you have to learn this.
I threw it like this,
but it was hit by the wind...
Put it back! Put it back! Put it back!
Seo Joon Oh. Our dominant hand.
From our dominant side, this way.
Can you see up there?
Check Jo Hee Kyung's room first.
Oh my!
Wow, why are you in such a dark place?
Hey, because you're here
this place seems a little brighter.
I brought you coffee
so you don't get tired!
How long have you been here?
I saw you at a hair salon. Wait,
no I didn't. Wait! Where are you going?
- We must go!
- You should take your coffee!
Oh no. Joon Oh's up there.
Why aren't you answering?
Hey, there's nothing here.
- That was close. There's nothing, right?
- I don't think it's in here.
- You're phone's ringing.
- Oh, it is. It's mine.
It's Byung Joo.
Hello?
What do we do, Seo Joon Oh?
You should have put it on vibrate.
Is it on vibrate?
No, I can't see,
so I can't put it on vibrate.
- Did you hear something?
- No.
Someone could show up at any time,
so let's start.
- Yes.
That bastard bought new shoes.
Open it.
Hey, Tae Ho.
Here you go.
What brings you here, Ki Joon?
Ji Ah agreed to do the movie.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- What brings you here?
- What about you?
- I was passing by--
- How long have you been here?
Have you been here a while?
Well yes, I took a good look around--
- Did you see him then?
- Who?
If you saw anyone, tell me who they were.
Who exactly have you seen?
Have you seen my friend...
wait, who?
- Could it be Joon...
- Oh?
- Seo.
- Joon.
Oh.
- Joon Oh.
- You know Joon Oh?
Are you here to meet Joon Oh?
- Have you seen him?
- Something terrible has happened.
Tae Ho just went up to Joon Oh's room.
- I'm going to lose my mind.
- Hey.
Joon Oh's here?
What? You don't want me to?
No, I've got nothing to lose.
Make a decision before I change my mind.
What are you doing here?
- Let's talk outside.
- Huh? Why?
This visit is quite sudden.
What's so urgent that you came here?
- It's urgent.
- Yeah, it is.
First you didn't want to do it
at all, and now it's urgent?
I said it was urgent.
It's urgent.
Tell me if you don't want me to do it
so I can tell CEO Jang.
Never mind. Do the movie.
I forgive you of your sins.
Get me a pizza from the pizzeria
across from the hotel when you leave.
No bacon.
We're good now, right?
Wow.
I thought I was going to die
in that cramped space.
- Here.
- I thought I stopped breathing.
Open it for me.
[Traitorous Jung Ki Joon]
I decline.
I figured it out.
I think it was Investigator Oh.
I will place this where you asked.
Go on ahead. I'll follow a bit later.
Yes, ma'am.
Now we're going to track Tae Ho.
It's only us.
If one of you loses Tae Ho,
you'll die by my hands.
Jung Ki Joon was here.
I think Jang Do Pal has also
caught on to what's going on.
That means we need to be
one step ahead of them.
I'll take care of Jang Do Pal.
You two keep an eye on Investigator Oh.
- Understood.
- All right.
Get a move on
so we don't lose him.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, it's me.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Goodness, bosses!
Goodness. Boss! Boss!
I bought drinks, though!
Investigator Oh.
- He's leaving.
- Leaving.
- He's leaving! Shouldn't we go?
- Not yet.
- I think we have to go.
- We wait for the light.
- Wait, no!
The light hasn't turned!
We have to follow him
so we don't lose him!
Not yet, Bong Hee!
- He's gone.
- Go, go, go, go!
- Don't.
- We have to go now.
- Stay calm.
- D.
- We're already too late.
- P, R, N, D.
- Let's go.
- I'm going.
- Do I turn on the brakes?
- Just go.
- I'm going.
- Bong Hee, let's go.
- Bong Hee.
I'm going. I'm going.
[CEO Jang Do Pal]
Hello?
Tae Ho is with you, isn't he?
Yes.
Don't answer, just listen.
I understand.
Don't leave the hotel.
Keep Tae Ho there for one hour.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Who was that?
An acquaintance.
Do you want to grab a bite to eat?
We could talk about the movie.
Tae Ho...
Those men...
Get out.
- Why do you keep veering left?
- I'm not veering left!
Just follow the car
ahead of us, Bong Hee!
Che bella cosa...
Cchiu' bello, oi ne'.
- Why are you driving so slowly?
- I'm driving pretty fast.
He hasn't caught on, has he?
- Oh there... what do we do?
- Seriously!
He just took the right exit.
- What do we do?
- Do something.
- Make a U-turn.
- A U-turn?
Hurry! Stay left
so you can veer right.
All right.
Whoa!
- It's because we're so slow.
- But I'm driving so fast!
- He appeared out of nowhere.
- Okay, veer right now.
- Oh no!
- Why is this guy trying to get in here?
Why is this guy trying
to butt into this lane?
What? What's wrong?
Behind us.
Wait a second. Hold on.
Given the situation, I don't think
you should keep driving straight.
- You won't make a U-turn?
- I haven't done that before.
So you're just
going to keep driving straight?
I'll just... keep going, I guess.
What is with that car?
What's going on?
He keeps tailgating us.
License plates 0704
and 0124, pull over!
Pull over, 0704 and 0124!
How fast were you going
that you got pulled over?
Looks like you were caught
speeding too, CEO Jang.
Oh, Seo Joon Oh. That car!
- Is that it?
- Yes, it is! Yes, we found it!
See, our paths crossed again
because I kept driving straight.
What in the world is he doing?
We're following him.
It's because I drove fast.
- Stay strong.
- I think that's the hardest thing to do.
Don't smile too much, Bong Hee.
- Why not?
- Because we're tailing him.
That's right.
What's wrong with me?
Oh, sol... oh.
Oh, this won't do.
Oh. Okay, stay quiet.
Keep it together.
All right now.
Oh, he's over there.
He's headed that way.
It's a rest stop.
That's a gas station.
- I'm saying it's both.
- Oh, I see.
Don't turn on the headlights!
Why turn on the headlights
when we're tailing him?
How can you just
take the wheel like that?
- You startled me!
- Slowly veer right.
You startled me!
- Welcome.
- Yes.
- How much?
- 20 liters. 20 liters.
All right.
- Where is your restroom?
- It's over there.
Oh!
He's headed for the restroom.
[Do not throw out trash in the
restroom. We sell trash bags.]
Here we go.
Seo Joon Oh.
I'll buy us some time,
so you go and search his car.
How do you expect to buy us some time?
Best of luck!
Hey.
She can't be serious.
Che bella cosa...
Cchiu' bello, oi ne'.
How disgusting.
O sole mio...
What the? It's locked?
This can't be happening.
Oh, come on.
Excuse me!
[Restroom Out of Order]
Is something wrong with this door?
Is anybody out there?
Save me!
[Restroom Out of Order]
Gosh.
[Legend Entertainment: Private Items]
Yes. Are you on your way?
Yes, I just arrived.
Yes, ma'am.
You must get it fixed.
I have to know what's on this phone.
I have to know what's on it to understand
why everyone wants me to hand it over.
I think I need to be
the first one to know.
I will place this where you've asked.
Go on ahead. I'll follow a bit later.
Yes, ma'am.
- Yes, Manager Jung?
- Something awful has happened!
Tae Ho is headed in your direction!
- What?
- Get out of there! Hurry!
Unbelievable.
You're alive?
You can't be alive.
I'm not alive, Tae Ho.
So I'm at peace.
Subtitles by DramaFever