Bong Hee! Bong Hee! Bong Hee!
- It was hard for you, wasn't it?
- Yes.
I'm relieved to see that
you're both okay.
But, I was wondering...
What about Seo Joon Oh?
I heard you were here for a long time
did you hear anything about him?
Bong Hee, don't you remember?
When we were leaving the island...
Tae Ho stabbed Joon Oh with a knife.
Right in front of you.
[Episode 10]
It's because you asked to see her.
I guess she was expecting to see Joon Oh.
I know. I wouldn't have said that
if I had known she didn't remember.
You said you are Prosecutor Yoon, right?
So Hee's older brother.
Yes.
Our Bong Hee is a really pure person.
It was her first day on the job,
and her first trip abroad.
But I stopped Joon Oh from firing her
that day, and we ended up on that island.
Bong Hee did all the dirty work
while we were on the island.
Oh, do you know how many times
she saved So Hee's life?
It's true. If So Hee were still alive...
She would have been
the most thankful to Bong Hee.
I guess she couldn't say that herself.
I didn't know.
I don't know about anyone else,
but I thought you should know.
That way, you can help Bong Hee.
It'll be hard for her to go back
in this state, won't it?
Oh, just a moment.
Yes, ma'am.
Prosecutor Yoon.
Are you in China
with Ra Bong Hee, by any chance?
Yes.
Then, it's true that you're meeting
with the survivors.
I didn't tell you because
this was a personal matter
but I guess you heard.
You're meeting survivors I haven't met.
Didn't you think I would hear about it?
Who are you? Are you
the special investigation committee?
If I were, I wouldn't have met them.
What do you mean?
How severely did you neglect
the safety of the survivors
that they can't trust you, even when you
promise them personal protection?
They're so scared
that they only trust Ra Bong Hee.
That's why I came here with her.
Ra Bong Hee, that girl...
She's still under investigation.
The prosecution will ask for her
due to conspiracy suspicions
but you've taken her abroad without
our permission. How dare you?
Whether those charges will end
with an acquittal or a sentence...
We'll only know once we look into it.
Weren't you only interested in
finding Yoon So Hee's murderer?
Why are you protecting her?
You were out to get her not too long ago.
Back then, I thought Bong Hee was the
bad one, but I realized that's not true.
The bad side can be found somewhere else.
The truth is, we came here because
we wanted to hear Seo Joon Oh's story.
Why are you laughing like that?
What? Are you underestimating us?
So, did you see him?
It ended the way you wanted it to.
I don't know what you're saying.
What I want is for Ra Bong Hee
to return as soon as possible.
I want her to stay quietly under
my jurisdiction until we are finished.
So don't delude her with lies, just bring
her back while I'm asking nicely, got it?
So, who are the two survivors?
Are you asking me that question?
Finding out who they are is your job!
You didn't even know Ra Bong Hee
got away! What the hell are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's do our work properly.
Let's do the work we're supposed to do!
Don't let anyone get their hands
on our work!
- Yes.
- Regarding the two remaining survivors
do whatever you can to get them here.
Tell them we'll do much more than
personal protection, and get them here!
Yes, I understand.
After we deal with those two survivors,
let's wrap this up.
Gosh, I'm getting so sick of this.
I don't think I can do it anymore.
- Hello?
- Is this Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young?
Yes, who is this?
I have evidence regarding
Yoon So Hee's murder.
Geez, how did Ki Joon do this
in 10 seconds?
How did he step on all these lines?
- Seo Joon Oh.
- Yeah?
- Let me join.
- Hey, this isn't a place for you.
I have to do this in 10 seconds.
No, I'm not talking about that.
- Then what?
- I thought about it carefully.
Your family is up in heaven
and you have so many siblings...
So I'll...
I'll be the rock you can lean on.
What?
You know, I'll cook a warm meal for you
if you're ever starving.
If you are struggling with
no place to sleep, I'll help you out.
If no one else takes your side,
I'll take your side.
And, if no one else believes you...
I'll believe you no matter what.
Hey, why do you trust me so much?
They say real trust
is when you trust what you can't see.
I want to try it too!
What do you mean? How can you
trust something you can't see?
Anyway, you promised me! Don't change
your mind when we get back to Seoul.
- You want to try it?
- Yes.
You died. You have to step on the lines.
The lines? No, in our neighborhood,
you have to avoid the lines.
No, not here.
Do I have to step on the lines like this?
You died. You only have 10 seconds.
- How can I finish in 10 seconds? No way!
- Ki Joon did it.
Seriously?
- You didn't touch the lines!
- I don't have to touch them here.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- Didn't I do it?
- That was my rock.
- You should use your rock.
- My rock?
- Bong Hee.
No, just lie down.
Why am I lying here like this?
Just lie down, Bong Hee.
Prosecutor Yoon postponed your flight,
so you don't need to rush.
You can't erase your memories
all at once, so take it slow, Bong Hee.
We heard what's going on in Korea.
Tae Ho, that bastard. Making Joon Oh
into a murderer wasn't enough
so he's going around
acting like a national hero.
It must have been very hard for you.
You didn't have any help.
Oh, have you heard anything
about Ho Hang?
Secretary Tae came back to Korea.
Then why aren't there
any articles about it?
He requested personal protection
so the special investigation committee
didn't officially announce it.
But he already gave his statement.
Right now...
He's probably with Choi Tae Ho.
Wow, I'm going crazy here.
I can't understand it.
He must have been scared
after hearing about CEO Hwang.
Now that Joon Oh's not here,
this is Tae Ho's world.
Wow, Choi Tae Ho,
that tenacious son of a bitch.
That bastard was involved in
CEO Hwang's accident too.
- Calm down. Stop talking about him.
- How can I calm down?
He made you like this, coaxed Ho Hang,
did this to Bong Hee...
And Joon Oh...
This is all because of Choi Tae Ho.
How much longer
do we have to worry about him?
Ji Ah wanted to go back,
but I stopped her.
CEO Hwang's accident
didn't seem like a coincidence.
So, what do you plan on doing now?
If it weren't for Ki Joon's injury,
I would have flipped out already.
We should go.
Even though Joon Oh's not here, there are
things we need to do, so we should go.
We need to help to you, since
you've been dealing with this alone.
So you don't need to worry too much.
When we go back,
you won't be alone anymore.
Secretary Tae is also acting like that
because he has no one to lean on.
He'll come around if we go
and persuade him.
We need to go back and clear
the false charges against Joon Oh.
And we need to make Tae Ho
pay for his crimes.
You'll really do that?
Seo Joon Oh...
I don't want him
to wrongfully suffer anymore
because of crimes he didn't commit.
I'm begging you.
Don't worry, Bong Hee.
I have somewhere I need to go.
Bong Hee, can you wait here?
What's going on?
Someone called me to say he has
evidence regarding So Hee's murder.
So I need to meet him to see what it is.
- Then I'm coming with you.
- Hey, where are you going?
I came all the way here to expose
the truth. I can't just lie here all day.
- Wait...
- Oh, Bong Hee.
I'm sorry I can't disclose
the patient's room number
or any personal information. (In Chinese)
- What did he say?
- This is a private hospital.
He can't reveal any personal information
about the patients here.
Let's act like nothing happened.
(In Chinese)
The guys will take care of everything.
Do you need to stay? You could be seen.
I should see it in person.
I'll take care of it.
Please go ahead and go back.
Okay. If that's what you want.
Oh. Tae Ho.
It's almost over. Let's end it well.
I think it would be best
for you to stay here.
We don't even know what the evidence is,
so there's no need for you to go.
- I'll check with Lawyer Jo.
- But Prosecutor Yoon...
I'll be back soon. Go inside.
Move! Move! (In Chinese)
Oh no!
You dumbass! We're not here
to kill people today!
Dumbass! Dumbass!
Dumbass! Dumbass! Dumbass!
Get out of the way. Hurry! Hurry!
The mission is to catch
these people alive.
Our main purpose today
is to capture these two guys.
If they don't cooperate,
you can kill them.
Dead or alive.
You idiot! You're a doctor!
What are you doing?
You can't the hospital doors.
You can't lock the doors!
Hey!
Let's move.
Don't move!
What are you doing?
You can't do this here!
Get lost!
Who are you? What's going on?
I'll take care of it.
It's nothing. Go on.
Hey! Move aside.
Wait!
Ji Ah! Ki Joon! You're in danger!
You have to get out of here!
- What is it?
- They're looking for you with pictures.
Get out of the hospital
while I buy some time.
- Pictures? Why?
- Wait, what about you?
They don't recognize me.
Be careful! Hurry up! Be careful, Ji Ah!
I'm pretty sure this is the location
you were looking for.
Move! Get out of the way! (In Chinese)
Who are these people?
- Who are you?
- Hello.
Thank you!
Stop!
- Stop!
- Crap!
Stop right there!
She's here too?
What is this? Move! (In Chinese)
- Stop right there!
- Over there!
Catch them! Catch them! Move!
I found them!
That's me, you son of a bitch!
It's because you're prettier in person.
Get her! (In Chinese)
Bring it on!
Ouch, that hurts. Ouch! That hurts!
That hurt!
Are you all right?
Lawyer Jo, hurry and call the hospital.
We'd better get back there.
We lost them.
Ki Joon, what do we do?
Ji Ah, I think this hospital was bribed.
I think it'll be better
if you go and look for help.
What are you saying? What about you?
We'll stand out if we're together,
and I'll slow you down.
I'll hide here, so go--
What are you saying?
Didn't you see them?
Do you think they'll let you live?
Stop the bullshit.
Ji Ah. Ji Ah.
Pay attention and listen to me.
That's why
I'm asking you to find help.
You have to find people who can help us
if we want to live.
I'm sending you because I want to live.
Bong Hee is being chased out there.
If we waste time, we'll all die.
Why are you so scared? We escaped
that desolate, deserted island!
No.
You saved me multiple times
so it's my turn to save you.
Wait.
Come on.
What's going on? (In Chinese)
Stop! Stop!
Okay!
Move!
Ki Joon, let's go!
The number you have dialed is--
- Prosecutor Yoon, they're not answering.
- Are we almost at the hospital?
We're almost there.
Does it make sense
that we can't contact the hospital?
Do your job! This is your job!
Stop making stupid excuses,
and get over there right now!
- Geez, he's so out of it.
- What is it? Is there a problem?
He said the hospital hasn't been
answering for an hour! That's nonsense!
I already told him to go there because
he can't check anything over the phone.
How severely did you neglect
the safety of the survivors
that they can't trust you,
even when you offer personal protection?
They're so scared
that they only trust Ra Bong Hee.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho.
Check if those guys
are in China right now.
Yes, I'm on it.
Let's stop, Ra Bong Hee.
Do we have a reason to fight,
now that Joon Oh's not around?
You son of a bitch.
But Seo Joon Oh...
trusted you until the end.
You're not listening to me again.
You know how to punch.
Is it fun to play like this?
Let's stop now, okay?
This is fun.
Prosecutor Yoon!
Prosecutor Yoon, Ji Ah and Manager Jung
are in danger. We have to save them!
Hurry.
Wait. What happened here?
Where... Where did they go?
Where did they go?
Strange men were looking for
Ji Ah and Manager Jung with photos.
Choi Tae Ho was here too!
Where did they go?
Prosecutor, let's get out of here.
Excuse me.
Lawyer Jo. What's going on?
What are they saying?
They said nothing happened.
They said there was no intrusion,
and no injured patients.
They're playing innocent,
saying they have no idea.
But Manager Jung and Ji Ah
are nowhere to be seen
and people stormed in here,
and I was the one who made this mess.
What happened?
There are no CCTV's
in this hospital either.
The way I see it, the doctor is lying.
I think the hospital was bribed.
Hey! Hey! That's her! (In Chinese)
She's the one who caused such
a scene in our hospital.
Officers, arrest her!
They said you caused all of this mess,
and that we should arrest you!
- Arrest her! (In Chinese)
- Arrest her! Arrest her!
Prosecutor Yoon.
They wouldn't have paid off the hospital
without planning to kill.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho have them
for sure. We have to find them!
Oh, Chairwoman Jo!
To what do I owe this honor?
The connection isn't very good.
Are you somewhere far away?
Oh, yes. It's just for business.
Your business...
isn't related to our survivors, isn't it?
- I don't know what you mean.
- I mean...
If you touch a single hair
on their heads, you'll die!
Chairwoman Jo, you're being quite harsh.
I think you're deluding yourself.
Just because I listened to you once
do you think we're on the same side?
No way! They're my guests,
and I'm the host!
Do you think I went through all that for
five months just to receive their bodies?
How dare you butt into my work
without any fear?
We're taking different paths,
but I thought we had the same goal.
You're talking strangely.
I'm a little hurt.
We don't have the same destination,
just because we crossed paths.
Let's not drag this on,
let's settle this.
You'd better escort those kids
back to Korea in good condition.
Bring them back safe and sound.
CEO Jang, they're here.
Ji Ah!
Manager Jung! It's been a long time.
Wow, Ji Ah lost so much weight.
Hey, what is Manager Jung wearing?
You should have let him change.
Geez, you went through a lot.
First, why don't you sit down?
Sit down. Sit down.
Geez, it must have been hard.
I bet you didn't eat properly. Eat this.
Ji Ah, eat. You lost too much weight.
Your complexion isn't good either.
It's okay! Eat. Go on and eat.
Manager Jung. Let's talk for a moment.
Ki Joon.
- I'll be right back, okay?
- Wait.
It's okay. Eat.
Ji Ah, order anything you want.
Bring her everything she wants.
It must have been hard. But you know...
It was really hard for me too.
While you were away,
everything became a mess at the company.
And on top of that, do you know
how much money Ji Ah's mom took
as compensation from our company?
If we want to earn that back,
we have to put Ji Ah in a movie
or move her around.
We have to do something.
So?
Let's say...
Joon Oh is the murderer.
Oh, Ji Ah! Did you eat a lot?
Oh, you ate so much.
Eat more, okay? Eat slowly.
Manager Jung, you should eat too.
Okay, let's go outside.
Eat lots!
Ki Joon, I'm sorry.
I ate your food too.
It was just too delicious.
Why are you crying?
I didn't leave you anything.
Ji Ah!
Manager Jung!
Seo Joon Oh,
what would you have done?
Manager Jung! Ji Ah!
Just like when Yeol
and Choi Tae Ho disappeared
you searched until you found them.
Seo Joon Oh, were you afraid too?
Were you scared
that there was nothing you could do?
That you were already too late?
I'm a little scared.
Please watch over me.
Until I can find them...
So that Manager Jung and Ji Ah
remain unharmed.
[Personnel Appointment Notice]
What is this?
Why am I being transferred
to the Changwon Prosecutor's Office?
- Sit down. Sit down so we can talk.
- Tell me why!
Wow, here you are getting angry
at others for your own mistakes.
I already warned you. I told you not to
let your sister's case get in the way!
I was never careless about my duties
because of my sister.
Are you sure? If you weren't, why
did you take sick leave to go to China?
Is it normal to fall behind on work,
while you're solving your sister's case?
- District Attorney!
- You've done enough.
Even if it's your sister,
we have no other choice.
That case has been turned over
to Lee Jae Joon, so he'll wrap it up.
Take your hands off that case
and go somewhere for some fresh air.
Do you think this will make me stop?
This is not enough to stop me.
I've done dirtier
and more petty things than this.
This is nothing.
I'm going to work on my sister's case
even after my transfer.
And I will make sure to expose the truth.
[Missed Call - Ra Bong Hee]
I'm going along with it
because you told me to.
But I still don't know
why you're doing this.
Ji Ah, you told me.
You said I saved you
on that deserted island
so you'll save me this time.
What does that have to do with anything?
This is how you're going to save me.
Believe it.
Trust me and do as I say, just this once.
Don't ask me any questions either.
Didn't you see Ki Joon and Ji Ah?
They just left.
But, I didn't see them.
Didn't they call you?
It's been a few days since their return.
That's strange. Why didn't they call you?
CEO Hwang.
Please wake up.
You have to wake up.
Please help me.
This is it, but they're not coming out.
They'll come out this time, right?
Don't you think they will?
This is the last announcement.
Ha Ji Ah and Jung Ki Joon
are coming out today too, right?
Yeah, probably. They'll probably
come out with Tae Ho Hang.
But will their statements have any
credibility? How much should we trust?
Wait.
Can you come back later?
Well, do we really
have to do all of that?
Ra Bong Hee, that girl...
Let's just leave her out.
Well, she was our first survivor
and if we consider how much
she helped in the rescue operation...
Yes, okay then.
I didn't leave her out to make you happy.
I know that. I appreciate
your political judgment.
Let's wrap things up.
Yes.
- Ji Ah.
- Bong Hee.
I've been trying to reach you
all this time!
I was so worried.
I thought something happened.
I'm sorry, Bong Hee.
Bong Hee.
I'm sorry.
- I'll get going.
- Ji Ah.
Bong Hee.
Manager Jung, how do you feel?
Are you hurt?
- Did you come by yourself?
- Oh, yes.
- Um, Manager Jung--
- I'm sorry, Bong Hee.
Pardon? What are you sorry about?
Manager Jung.
I know a few words won't make
a big difference in our current situation
but if we roll over
without saying anything...
There will be too may things
we'll feel sorry for.
That's why, I'd like you to speak up.
Even if no one's listening,
please say something.
I'm begging you.
[The Last Announcement -
Legend Entertainment Plane Crash]
They're here!
Let's say... Joon Oh is the murderer.
- CEO Jang--
- He's dead anyway.
We should survive, right?
You judged me incorrectly.
You want to use our poor Joon Oh
just to make money?
For the sake of your money...
You want to use our poor Ji Ah,
who has lived a tough life all this time?
You're a cool guy, just as I thought!
You're cool.
That's why I prepared this.
There's nothing you can't
get your hands on in China.
Do you think...
CEO Hwang was really in an accident?
You don't need to be scared.
I won't kill you.
I'm going to kill Ji Ah.
Do you think Ji Ah knows
why you gave up on becoming a doctor?
Oh, I guess she doesn't have to know.
Ji Ah's going to die soon anyway.
I'm only going to kill Ji Ah.
The special investigation committee
will now begin our final announcement
regarding the Legend Entertainment
plane crash.
A total of 47 passengers
were on that private plane.
We will brief you on 12 of those people
after excluding 35 people
who are still currently missing.
We followed the testimony of Ra Bong Hee,
who was our first survivor
and found the deserted island where nine
survivors were stranded for four months.
And in a recent search, we found bodies
we did not discover in our first search.
Pilot Park Seok Tae,
Co-Pilot Nam Soo Cheol
and Journalist Kim Ki Hwan
of Myungsung Report.
We recovered a total of three bodies.
Therefore, including Actress Yoon So Hee,
who was discovered near Huizhou, China
four people are confirmed to be dead.
Excluding these four and Ra Bong Hee,
out of the seven survivors...
Choi Tae Ho, Tae Ho Hang,
Jung Ki Joon, and Ha Ji Ah.
These four returned to Korea safely.
The former CEO of Legend Entertainment,
Hwang Jae Gook
is currently in a vegetative state after
a sudden accident after his return.
It is assumed that the singer, Lee Yeol,
went missing on the deserted island.
And regarding Seo Joon Oh, who is the
leading suspect in Yoon So Hee's murder
his status is still unclear.
Are you saying that you're certain
Seo Joon Oh is the murderer?
- Do you know how he killed her?
- Please tell us something!
Choi Tae Ho was the first
to point at Seo Joon Oh as the suspect.
CEO Tae Ho Hang
of Legend Entertainment...
Who killed Yoon So Hee?
It was Seo Joon Oh.
Choi Tae Ho was right.
He killed her.
Manager Jung Ki Joon of Legend
Entertainment, and actress Ha Ji Ah
all pointed at Seo Joon Oh
as the murderer in their statements.
Excluding Ra Bong Hee, whose statement
lacks credibility due to her condition
the statements we've gathered so far
are all consistent.
Besides the witnesses' statements,
do you have any other evidence?
Can you tell us what your stance is
since you were very involved
in the first half?
Under such close quarters
after the plane crash
Seo Joon Oh killed Yoon So Hee,
he had frequent conflicts with her
and on the way back, on the rescue boat
Seo Joon Oh, who threatened other
survivors in order to conceal his crimes
suffered an injury...
And we believe that he died.
So did you find Seo Joon Oh's body?
Through a transparent investigation
we hope to uncover the truth about
Yoon So Hee's murder as soon as possible.
We concluded that there are no more
substantive truths to be uncovered
so we will wrap up our investigation
related to the plane crash
and disperse.
Regarding the tragic disaster that caused
many heartaches in the last few months
we would like to express our condolences
to the victims and their families.
Choi Tae Ho, how do you feel?
Please tell us!
Bong Hee, I'm sorry.
I think this is our reality.
Geez, I'm in pain...
Geez...
- It's morning.
- Ki Joon, I'm glad we didn't drink this.
Hey, don't talk to me. I can't hear you.
Hey, I'm telling you.
It's good that we didn't drink these.
That's because you drank and drove.
No. My image would have suffered
if I had drunk these last night.
- Hey, seriously. You don't need these.
- Hey, get rid of those.
Let that guy know that Ki Joon
is seriously pissed off! Tell him!
Hey, I'm so angry! I wouldn't drink that
if they gave me 100 boxes.
- I bought these at the store.
- Good job.
Ki Joon, I bought these at the store.
If we drink these, we can drink alcohol.
If you drink these,
you will never get drunk.
Hey, what's that smell?
It smells like it rotted.
The design and color is the same as the
one you drank last night. You have these.
I bought them because
I wanted to sober up.
You want to sober up? Geez, seriously.
Stop drinking that.
- You're finished.
- Hey, let go.
- Hey, why are you being like that?
- Let me finish this.
Hey, why are you drinking?
You drank too much!
Geez, let go! I'm going to drink it!
Hey, let go!
When are you going to stop this?
Do you think Jae Hyun will
come back to life if you act like this?
- I killed him, didn't I?
- Who? Who told you that?
Ki Joon.
I killed him, didn't I?
Hey, I know you.
I know you, and you didn't do it.
No matter what they say,
it wasn't you, okay?
If anyone talks shit about you,
I'll deal with it for you!
Hey.
You're Seo Joon Oh,
the frontman of Dreamers.
This won't bring you down, right?
It doesn't matter what other people say.
I believe in you.
Let's drink again sometime.
Who is it?
Hello!
Bong Hee! You have a visitor!
It's someone famous!
This place...
reminds me of that deserted island.
Your life here isn't so different
from our life on that island.
How did you find me here?
- Get lost.
- Back then...
It was really hard for us.
But I realized that it wasn't all bad.
I realized many things
from that experience.
When I think about those times,
there's nothing I can't endure.
- Nothing is difficult here.
- Stop the bullshit and get lost.
Ra Bong Hee. The same goes for you.
Killing you will take no effort.
I'm going to escape again anyway.
I'll do the same thing
I did to Seo Joon Oh.
So, just live the way you live now.
In that state where
you don't know anything
and you don't know
how to do anything...
Live just like that.
Mom.
Let's forget everything, Bong Hee.
You did everything you could.
Let's forget everything...
and live like nothing happened,
just like before.
Let's pretend nothing happened.
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
There's something I have to give you.
I think I should return it to you now.
Sure. Travel safely.
Hello?
Hello? Please speak.
Who is this?
I'm sorry, Prosecutor Yoon.
What do you mean?
I have to leave.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I know you'll think I'm crazy,
but I need to go.
For the very last time,
I want to believe that he's alive.
I got a call.
Bong Hee. It's me, Joon Oh.
Seo Joon Oh.
His voice...
It sounded like Seo Joon Oh.
Seo Joon Oh.
Who are you? (In Chinese)
Who... are you?
Do you know me?
Got you! I've always
wanted to try that on someone!
Seo Joon Oh, you scared me!
Bong Hee. Let's go back to Seoul.
Subtitles by DramaFever