Subtitles by DramaFever
A few months ago, the celebrities
of Legend Entertainment...
Their private plane crashed
and went missing...
One survivor has been found.
She can't remember
anything after the plane crash.
The memory that you can't access
is the only hope we have.
I told you not to eat that!
We're on a deserted island!
What did you just say?
Is it because of your sister?
Do you think she's alive?
Are you okay?
I will reveal the truth. Helping
the victims in the name of law is my job.
Hey, Yeol. Hey, Yeol!
Have you ever thought that
we might end up dying on this island?
If I tell you everything
I remember in detail...
The people who might be alive or dead...
Will you be able to save them?
[Missing Nine]
The light from the cellphone...
The survivor that you, Seo Joon Oh,
and Lee Yeol risked your safety to save.
Who was that person?
Do you remember?
You must remember, Ra Bong Hee.
Who was it?
Joon Oh.
Ji Ah!
Who was it, and did that person
live or die on that island?
Do you... remember that?
That person...
I definitely...
No! Don't go!
I definitely saw her...
You saw her. Who was it?
Help me... Save me...
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Who's there? St... Stay here.
Our safe house has been found.
How the hell did they find us here?
Oh! What are you doing? Oh! Ouch!
Please let me go!
Wait! Wait! Just a second!
Are they here to watch?
Duck! Duck!
Let's stay hidden from the reporters.
Why should I? I did nothing wr--
Ra Bong Hee!
Are there any other survivors?
Go! Go! Hey, get out of here!
Where do you think you are?
Look over here please!
Move! Get out of here!
What is it? What's going on?
What?
- What is this?
- Open it.
All of a sudden?
This is your first project,
so I wanted to get you something.
- Oh!
- Don't think about losing this one.
Ta-da! Our couple rings!
- What's wrong?
- Tae Young, I should be dating. Take it.
- Why does that matter?
- No.
This would suit you right now.
Wear it for the shoot, okay?
Thank you. I'll wear it well!
I'm going now!
He said she was found under a cliff...
But it wasn't the plane crash...
He thinks someone killed her.
Please ask him how long it'll take.
How long will it take? (In Chinese)
We will prepare the car.
He said they'll get the car ready,
and that it'll take a bit.
I'm the president of
Legend Entertainment, Jang Do Pal.
There are rumors going around
that this accident
was fabricated by Legend Entertainment.
Does that make any sense?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
If the nation finds out about this,
they'll go crazy.
- Okay.
- Excuse me!
Sorry.
Oh, you're here.
We looked everywhere for you.
Oh, sorry.
Um, can you look into
who's in that room?
- What is this about?
- It's not a big deal...
But look into it. Please.
Sure.
[Episode 3]
I'll start over from scratch.
Oh! I caught it!
I caught it!
We're going to eat you now, okay?
But what am I supposed to do
when you're so cute...
If you don't leave in three seconds,
I'll really eat you.
Or I'll hit you with this stick.
There's no time to think.
I could just catch you like this,
but instead, I waited for hours...
I'm really going to eat you.
Go, or I'll really eat you.
I'll hit you. Really hard.
You'll bleed...
I'll eat you after the count of three.
One, two, three!
Okay, I'm going to eat you.
Hey! You can't even catch that?
All you have to do is scoop it up!
You told me to gather them
so you can fish them out!
You said you did all of this in the navy!
Is that the same thing, you punk?
This is a different country! The water's
different, everything's different!
Geez! Damn it!
I'm sorry. I didn't think it through.
We're abroad, aren't we?
If it weren't for my brother...
If he hadn't saved me
from carbon monoxide poisoning!
- I should have died back then!
- My mom told me to never say that.
My grandmother didn't see a point
in living and wanted to die
but she passed away
while eating rice cakes.
A sticky rice cake. A big one.
Grandmother, are you doing well?
I'm hungry!
I brought food!
- Oh!
- It's meat, isn't it?
It's meat! Meat! You worked hard! Meat!
Meat! It's meat, right? Meat!
I went to catch a rabbit, but there was
a predator. So I brought coconuts.
- Shouldn't you have caught the predator?
- It wasn't as easy as I thought.
Just for today, let's just eat the
coconuts. They're fresh from the tree.
I tried some, and it's pretty good.
Let's just eat these for today.
I want to roast them.
If we roast them,
they might taste like meat.
Let's roast them.
Milk should come out of them.
Geez, it's still a coconut
even after roasting it.
No. It tastes more fishy
after roasting it.
Geez, I'll really catch
a rabbit tomorrow.
You've said "tomorrow" every day
since the day before yesterday!
Geez, let's bear through it.
Everyone's dead, so we should be
thankful to be alive. Let's endure it.
But Ki Joon, do you really think
they're all dead?
We would have seen them
if they were alive.
This island seems pretty big.
Don't you think someone might live here?
Don't be crazy, just eat.
Eat the coconuts.
Hey, don't you smell something roasting?
- We're roasting coconuts.
- Not that. Not that.
You say some weird stuff sometimes
and it scares me...
- I smell someone cooking beef.
- Where do you smell...
It smells like someone's cooking beef.
Wait, what is this? It smells like the
Korean restaurant next to our company.
Wow, I smell it. It smells so good!
Tae Ho?
- Choi Tae Ho?
- Tae Ho!
You're alive!
You're alive? Tae Ho!
Tae Ho.
Tae Ho!
- Hey, Punk!
- What?
I'm your CEO, you punk!
I heard this from a younger schoolmate
who is now a police officer.
He talked about the missing, Seo Joon Oh.
A member of "Dreamers."
- He has a unique background.
- What is it?
When Shin Jae Hyun died,
he was investigated by the police.
Who's that?
Was it "Dreamers?" He's their frontman.
There was a suicide case. A man
in his 20s, named Shin Jae Hyun.
I think he's being investigated
because of that.
Should I look into it?
- Targeted investigations are boring.
- Oh, okay. I understand.
But, Prosecutor Yoon.
It's probably one of them, right?
Well, we don't know
who's dead and who's alive
but of the other people who lived
with your sister on that island...
One of those people probably...
- killed her?
- Um, yes. Yes.
Why are you being so careful? We're
close enough that you can just say it.
But still...
I'm going to take a nap.
Wake me up when we arrive.
Okay.
- You're okay, right?
- What do you mean?
You're smiling...
I'm not okay at all.
I'm really angry.
- Well, do you like the tea?
- It's not bad.
I will apologize if our people crossed
the line the other day.
Gosh, it was just because
the reporters came in so unexpectedly--
Ra Bong Hee, that girl...
I heard she lost her memory.
Is that why you were holding on
to Ra Bong Hee and keeping her quiet?
Because people would insult you if they
knew the only survivor lost her memory?
No, that's not exactly true--
If I reveal this to everyone,
what do you think will happen?
I think the people
will find this pretty entertaining.
Are you having fun?
I wonder what you find so entertaining.
This situation.
Isn't it fun, Chairman Jo?
What's your name?
Seo Dong Min.
Okay, Reporter Seo.
Reporter Seo...
Do you happen to know
what I'm here to do?
Just because I'm the chairwoman
of the special investigation committee
people think finding out the truth
and revealing it to everyone
is my job.
But that's not my job.
My job
is to make the people
forget this as soon as possible.
To make them forget about the dead stars
so they can return to their normal lives.
That's my real job.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I don't know. I'm not really sure.
I'm not in this position
to entertain a bastard like you.
If you're going to cross your legs
and laugh like an idiot...
You should do it with matters
that you can handle...
In front of people you can handle.
Look at me closely.
What kind of person do you think I am?
Do you think you can handle me? Do you?
Her condition seems to have improved,
by the looks of her CT.
But she still can't remember?
Yes. It seems like her memory
still comes and goes.
If I look at this from a medical point
of view, she should remember.
She should remember everything.
All signs of
encephalomeningitis are gone.
Is it you?
Then are you saying...
Ra Bong Hee remembers everything,
but she's pretending not to?
Is that what you're saying?
Who are you?
I'm... Ha Ji Ah's mother.
Did our Ji Ah... survive?
Did she die?
I... I... I'm not sure.
I'm sorry.
Don't be like that. Answer me.
Is our Ji Ah alive or dead?
Did you see her body? No, right? Right?
Please let go of me.
Our Ji Ah has to be alive!
If our Ji Ah died...
If she doesn't come back...
Then our entire family
will starve to death!
Why are you doing this? Please let go!
This is what I have to say.
This situation doesn't make any sense
from a medical point of view.
Doctor.
I have a favor to ask you.
Please keep this a secret
from Chairman Jo--
- Let go!
- I'm sure you saw. Why don't you know?
You're tricking me, aren't you.
Did you do something to her?
- Did you do something?
- I don't know!
- What are you doing? Move!
- Let go. Let go!
Please stop this! Let's go.
I know what you guys are up to!
I'll find out the truth! And...
I'll find our Ji Ah myself!
Instead of finding
a useless person like you...
Our Ji Ah...
The Ji Ah that everyone loves...
I'll... I'll find her, you bastards!
- Ji Ah...
- Let's go.
- They're coming out!
Geez, why are they here again?
Get out of here!
Let's go.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Ra Bong Hee?
Jae Hyun.
So Hee.
Do you... trust people?
Don't trust anyone.
You'll be abandoned.
Just like me.
Here. Have some.
What is this?
It smells bad, but it tastes okay.
There's more over there. Help yourself.
Isn't it good?
It's not good enough to want more.
This wench must not be so hungry...
We're probably the only people
who survived, right?
- You're worried about Tae Ho, right?
- I should worry. He's my boyfriend.
Ji Ah.
I'm not saying this
to comfort you, but...
Tae Ho is probably alive.
We found Yeol.
Figures. I thought you were dead too.
How can you say that so easily--
What a load of bullshit.
Did you think I was alive?
I got it, you wench.
Hey, your fans know
how rude you are, right?
Of course. Are you kidding? They always
ask me to curse when they see me.
They think it's sexy.
Anyway, be careful not to get hurt.
If Ki Joon finds out you're hurt...
Do you think...
Ki Joon is alive?
Let's hope he is.
Yeah. Let's hope he is.
Until we see Ki Joon and Tae Ho again...
Take care of yourself.
You don't have your medicine.
What are you two doing?
Oh.
You're smiling?
Can you smile
when we're all about to die here?
Um... Then, should I cry?
You must be relaxed
if you can joke around like that.
Hey.
I guess you already
forgot about Jae Hyun.
Hey, Yoon So Hee. How can you say that?
So Hee. I still remember Jae Hyun.
I haven't forgotten him for
a single moment. I don't want to, either.
You can't forget.
You're the one who killed Jae Hyun.
You could kill someone else.
Since this is a deserted island.
You can joke and get along right now
because we have the food and resources.
But what happens when we run out?
What happens when it's cold, we have no
food, and it's hard to survive ourselves?
- Hey.
- Do you think you'll be smiling then?
- Yoon So Hee.
- People kill others so they can live.
I saw it all.
What the hell did you see?
You're going to die anyway...
You'll die anyway...
You've done it once before.
Hey, since we found the others,
fish is good...
But shouldn't we feed them something?
Like tuna...
Fried eggs might be difficult...
We should just feed them fish.
Hey, be careful!
So Hee! Don't go any further! It's deep!
- What's with her?
- So Hee! What are you doing?
Joon Oh. Joon Oh. Joon Oh.
So Hee's acting strange.
- So Hee!
- Hey!
Joon Oh!
Hey, Yoon So Hee!
So Hee! So Hee!
Hey!
???
Let go. Let go! Let go!
Come out!
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
It's so good, I'm tearing up.
I wanted to eat fish so badly,
so we were over there...
Wow, seriously. How long
has it been since we ate fish?
If I'm on a deserted island with you,
I think I can live!
You're good at acting. You're good
at singing. You're good at everything!
Eat lots, CEO Hwang. I'll catch
a bigger one for you tomorrow.
Manager Jung, aren't you eating?
Did you lose your appetite after all the
coconuts? Eat! You have to eat to live!
Try some.
CEO Hwang, I've been thinking...
And I think we should head out
to find the kids.
- Let go!
- Come on! So Hee! Please!
Let go!
Why are you doing this? I want to die
because I don't want to live anymore.
You're acting crazy! So Hee, please!
I'm going to die. I'm going to die...
We're going to die here anyway!
Whether we starve or someone kills us,
we're going to die here anyway!
Who's going to kill you, huh?
Who said they were going to kill you?
Don't scream! You're scaring her!
That's because
she's not making any sense!
So Hee. We're... all in the same boat.
If we live, we'll live together,
and if we die--
No. We're not going to die. We won't die.
We're going to survive and get out
of here. We really will, okay?
I told you I saw it...
We're all going to die here.
They'll kill for their own survival...
What did you see? Yoon So Hee,
what did you see? Huh?
Joon Oh!
Hey. Hey, what's wrong with her? Huh?
I think she was cut by sea moss.
What do we do? Ji Ah, are you okay?
- Let's see. Let's see.
- Hey, it's nothing--
Let me see! It won't stop bleeding!
Ji Ah, where's your medicine?
Where's the medicine Ki Joon gave you?
- Ji Ah.
- Yeah?
Don't take too many at once.
I don't have it.
I lost it in the plane crash.
What? Why won't the bleeding stop?
Ji Ah, are you sick?
Don't look at me like that.
It's not fatal.
What do you mean you won't die?
You'll die if you bleed out!
You stubborn jerk.
Why did you wear a short skirt?
You can't even swim, so why did you go?
What are you going to do, huh?
What do we... Hey. Hey, is there
anything that stops bleeding?
Pardon?
How would I know that? I'm a stylist.
Geez, what do we do...
Geez...
We can't do that.
We should stay here
and wait to be rescued.
We're not even sure if they're alive.
You want to stay here
by yourself?
No. We should all stay here.
It's obvious they're dead,
so why should we suffer for them?
- They could still be alive.
- They're all dead.
It's been a week since the crash.
How could anyone be alive?
You're alive. We miraculously
survived too. So why not anyone else?
Aren't you worried about your girlfriend?
You're not worried about Ji Ah?
Are you dating Ji Ah? Since when?
It hasn't been long. Around three months.
The duration doesn't matter.
You're dating her because you love her.
Dating doesn't necessarily mean love.
Do you even know that Ji Ah is sick?
Ji Ah's sick? Why don't I know anything
about what happens in my own company?
Ji Ah! Ji Ah!
Ji Ah's medicine.
Ji Ah doesn't have her medicine.
Damn it!
Ji Ah will die without her medicine.
Ji Ah... needs her medicine to live.
I have a few more bottles in my bag,
so I'll go now!
Don't do this.
I feel like a real patient.
It's not your fault that you're sick.
But it's wrong if you to hide it.
Okay, keep talking.
When I was young, I got injured
while hiking with my grandmother.
And my grandmother stopped
the bleeding with some kind of grass.
What grass? What kind of grass?
I don't remember the name.
But I might recognize it if I see it.
Do you think...
we can find it in the forest?
We can only hope.
We need to find it. We should try.
Okay? Get ready. Let's go.
I'll come with you! Three is better
than two. I'm coming too.
Stay here.
So Hee, I'm sure you understand
our current situation.
We have to go into the woods.
That means it'll just be
you and Ji Ah out here.
You have to take care of Ji Ah.
Look at me, okay? Look at me.
Answer me. Look at me. Okay?
Answer me!
Hey, Yoon So Hee.
No! No...
No...
You...
You killed him...
Hey, are you the only one?
Are you the only one suffering?
I'm having a hard time too!
It's so difficult, I could die!
What can we do?
She got hurt while trying to save you!
You should take responsibility!
What if we can't stop the bleeding?
Yoon So Hee, look at me.
Look at me, and talk!
Answer me!
I'll talk to her.
Stay out of this, Seo Joon Oh.
So Hee, you understand
what's going on, right?
We have to go into the woods.
We have to find medicine
to stop Ji Ah's bleeding.
While we look for the medicine,
we need you to take care of her.
Can you do that for us?
If we give up, Ji Ah will die.
You don't want her to die either, right?
We're...
going to die here anyway.
This is a deserted island.
You're right.
Honestly, we could die here. We might
not get rescued and end up dying.
But...
I'm going to live.
I won't lose hope and give up,
and I won't run away out of fear.
I'm going to live until the end! I will
struggle until I crack all of my nails.
And if that's still not good enough...
Then I will die.
That's why, So Hee...
Let's clench our fists
and push through it together.
Let's trust each other,
and protect each other, okay?
Who are you?
Why isn't Chairman Jo coming...
Oh, she won't be coming.
I'm Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young of
the western district prosecutor's office.
I'm also Yoon So Hee's older brother.
Do you trust people?
I have to. It's lonely if I don't.
You can go, then.
Thank you, So Hee. I believe in you.
Wait!
Why is Yoon So Hee's older brother
looking for me...
My sister...
died. To be more exact...
She was murdered on that island.
I had a necklace my brother gave me.
He gave it to me as a present
when I got my first pay check.
But I lost it in the woods.
If you happen to see it...
Can you bring it back for me?
Sure. I'll do that.
The necklace
that you're wearing right now...
That's the necklace
I gave to my sister as a present.
Judging from the fact that
you're wearing my sister's necklace...
I'm guessing you had
a special relationship on that island.
Do you remember who it was...
who killed my sister?
She was my one and only younger sister...
And I haven't done much for her
as her older brother.
She was the kind of girl,
who needed a lot more
than I was able to give her.
Our So Hee...
That's why, Bong Hee...
It must be hard for you...
It must be hard to remember...
But do you think
you can trust me and follow me?
I will help you.
I'll help you recover your memory.
- Is this it?
- No. No.
- Hey, give us more details!
- It looked like this.
- It was really tall.
- How tall?
- This isn't it?
- It wasn't this wide.
- You said there were fruit.
- No, not fruit...
- Hey, how long was it, then?
- It was really long.
- It's long?
- It's sharp.
- Long and sharp?
- What's long and sharp around here?
- What else? What color?
- It looks like a saw.
A saw?
Manager Jung, are we going the right way?
I don't know. We should just keep going.
- Don't you think we strayed too much?
- No.
Joon Oh!
Hey!
Hey, it looks like
it's going to keep raining.
Let's find it quickly and go back.
Yeol, I can't picture it with words.
- Draw it for us. That'll be quicker.
- Hey, yeah. Draw it.
Okay, look. This is the grass.
The grass looks like a saw.
I don't know if it's a fruit or flower,
but it looks like a sea squirt.
- Sea squirt?
"Sea squirt..."
You're using the wrong vowel.
"Sea... sea... squirt."
The words "sea" and "squirt"
share the same vowels.
We're talking about the seafood.
Like the sea creature!
It's a homophone for "arf" and "dog."
He used the right vowel. He's right.
- Really?
- Anyway, you get the idea, right?
Let's split up to look for it.
Hey, do you really understand?
Am I the weird one here?
Just look for a sea squirt
and a saw combined.
That will be faster.
Ji Ah!
Joon Oh!
Manager Jung. Manager Jung.
It's raining too much.
Let's come back when it stops.
It hasn't been long since we departed...
If you're leaving, go by yourself.
I want to keep searching.
- Hey, how do we go back--
- Ji Ah!
We don't know the way back!
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Ji Ah!
If we get lost without food,
we'll be doomed!
- Are we going back to get the fish?
- Yeah, let's go. Let's go.
- Do you only think about food?
- Let's go. Hurry up!
Why did we come out in the first place?
Just do what I say, you punk!
- Ji Ah!
- Hurry! Hurry!
Is this it?
Hey, what is a saw and a sea squirt?
A sea squirt and a saw?
I'm sorry.
Ji Ah!
Oh! That scared me! That scared me!
That scared me! That scared me so much!
Wow, that scared me!
Wow, that scared me! Hey!
You scared me!
You scared the shit out of me!
You did that on purpose
didn't you? You...
Hey, I'm busy right now. Tomorrow...
Tomorrow, I'll really... You scared me!
Joon Oh! Bong Hee!
- There's a boulder!
- A boulder!
There's a boulder here! Joon Oh!
Geez, these things are always hiding
in places like this.
Did I step on one?
This sounds weird.
This is a landmine...
- Seo Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
- This landmine...
Did you find it?
We have to pick it and go!
I found the plant, but...
Don't babble nonsense and tell me
where it is! We have to find it and go!
We found it, but I stepped on a mine...
Why does it matter if you stepped
on a centipede? Where's the plant?
Not a centipede. I stepped on a mine--
Of course there are centipedes
on the ground!
Not a centipede!
I stepped on a mine! A landmine!
It'll blow us up! There's no centipede.
I said I stepped on a mine...
Why is there a landmine here?
You... You stepped on...
- You're crazy! You're crazy!
- Seriously!
- Take your foot off!
- Wait! Hey! Hey!
- You can't handle this alone!
- No, the thing is...
- I can't take my foot off of it!
- I'll do it for you!
Why would you? Wait! Wait!
It's not something you should touch!
Wow, seriously.
I mean, why is there... Hey.
Geez.
Hey. Hey, are we going the right way?
We're going the right way. Follow me.
Hey, I didn't see this tree earlier!
Geez, I'm right, CEO Hwang!
Just follow me.
I'm good with directions!
Why do you keep blabbing away?
Let's hurry up and go!
- A sn...
- Pardon?
A sn...
You're hungry again? Yes, I'm hungry too.
That's why we're going
where the fish are, okay?
So stop please complaining!
Are you a three-year-old?
- A snake!
- Pardon?
It's... a... snake...
Go on without me.
Where would I go without you?
Go back and take care of Ji Ah.
I think the plant we're looking for
is that one, so take it and go.
Um... Then what about you?
Go back and save Ji Ah.
I'll take care of this myself.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
I never even imagined this...
Wow, I can't take my foot off--
Seo Joon Oh, I'll be back.
Just be patient. Okay?
Okay.
- Hurry up and go.
- Okay.
Hurry up and go!
I'll go now.
Go!
She left so quickly.
She only contemplated things
for 10 seconds.
I just... had to grab it and go.
What did I do that was so wrong?
After the plane crash...
After all I did to survive!
My legs hurt! Wow!
Geez, I thought I took my foot off...
Why is this in the middle of nowhere?
I was wrong.
If I think about it carefully...
I should have caught the octopus!
The octopus! The octopus!
I didn't appreciate the work
that was given to me...
Ji Ah!
Joon Oh!
Yeol!
Oh!
What do we do?
I'm hurt. You should go without me.
If you go that way, you'll find the tree.
- Go.
- What are you saying, you punk?
I'll... I'll save you!
Just like how you saved me!
I'll save you, you punk.
Hold on.
I told you to go.
Who are you? Are you a native?
Are you really a native?
Wow! Hey!
Hey, this isn't a deserted island!
People live here!
CEO Hwang, follow her. Go...
- and live.
- What are you saying, you punk?
We're going together!
Miss, he...
Oh, I'm speaking Korean.
Snake! Snake! Snake!
The poison is... Okay?
Yes, so you're saying a snake bit
his chest and it's spreading.
Yeah! Wow, she understands!
You speak Korean really well.
Are you an overseas Korean
or an international student?
Oh. Hello, CEO Hwang. I'm Seo Joon Oh's
new stylist, Ra Bong Hee.
A stylist?
I have to take a dump.
Geez, I have to take a dump.
How should I do it?
I should reposition myself.
Joon Oh?
Ki Joon!
- Joon Oh!
- Ki Joon!
Joon Oh!
- Joon Oh. Joon Oh!
- No. Wait!
You're alive!
You're alive! You're alive!
- No, wait. Seriously!
- You're alive!
- You're alive! You're alive...
- Ki Joon, are you okay? What happened?
- I thought you were dead!
- What happened?
You're alive!
Joon Oh's alive!
Where were you?
- I stepped on a mine!
- Good job.
- A mine. I stepped on a mine.
- What?
- A mine.
A mine.
Help me. My legs feel numb
and I have to take a dump.
What did you step on?
I stepped on a mine.
- Where are you going?
- Did you poop?
No, not yet. I can't move...
- Isn't that your poop?
- No, that's mud.
- What are you doing?
- Just stay still! I'll do it!
No! Don't! What are you doing?
- Joon Oh, this is a mine.
- I told you it was!
- I'm so upset...
- I have to poop but I'm on a mine!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Hey, you can't do that!
Don't make me move! Don't make
me move! Don't make me move!
Stop talking! I'm trying
to handle this! Stay still.
- I didn't move.
- Don't move! Don't move!
Wait, no...
What?
- It's a mine.
- Geez, I told you it was!
Please hold on! We're almost there!
Even if we get there, can we do anything?
Yes, we can remove
the poison with a knife
and use fire to stop the bleeding.
You should just be a stylist.
Why are you talking about this so easily?
It's no use. I was bitten near my chest.
It'll spread quickly.
It's over for me. Go on without me.
What are you saying?
I told you I'm going to save you!
Wait, this punk...
It's been long enough for the poison to
have spread already. Why are you okay?
Her condition seems worse than yours!
I'm a hopeless cause. Go on without me.
That's the right thing to do...
Why?
What is it?
Joon Oh, I specialized in this
in the navy.
This landmine is really old!
It's older than 70 or 80 years!
Okay, I'm ready.
Tell me what it is. What is it?
- Take your feet off.
- Damn it!
There's higher possibility
it won't explode, so...
This man must be crazy! Who would
do that after stepping on a mine?
- Hey, I was a soldier--
- How would you know about mines?
It's 70 or 80 percent likely
that it won't explode!
That leaves 20 to 30 percent!
What if it explodes?
You'll probably get hurt.
You probably will.
You'll bleed a lot too.
Probably, right?
It'll probably hurt a lot.
Just because this isn't your problem...
Well, then...
Try your best to dismantle it.
Joon Oh...
A soldier doesn't
know how to dismantle a mine.
Just try your best! I was able to do
everything when I was a soldier.
You're really strange.
Anyway, since I was a soldier,
I'll try my best to dismantle it.
When I count to three,
we'll switch, and you can run away. Okay?
Then you have to make it clear when
you count to three. Not "one... two..."
But count like--
Hey, don't do it so carelessly!
You should run after "three,"
who runs after "two?"
Everyone does that!
- You're trying to push me off again.
- No, I'm exhausted.
- Ki Joon, is this shampoo?
- Hey, is this the time for that?
- This is shampoo...
- Why are you so strange?
I don't know how I worked
with you for all these years.
- Ki Joon.
- What?
- Hey, what is it?
This is Ji Ah's, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- This isn't the time to be helping me.
If you go that way, you'll see the beach.
When you see the beach--
When you see it, you'll see
the shelter I made! Ji Ah is in there!
Give her the medicine! Okay, Ki Joon?
Ji Ah!
Please... Ji Ah!
Wait... Ji Ah!
So Hee, are you okay?
CEO Hwang, please help!
Oh, wait.
Wait, Ji Ah... Help Ji Ah...
Wait... Ji... Ji Ah!
Ji Ah, come here!
No! Here we go...
What... What's wrong with her?
I'll take care of Ji Ah.
Please help him over there.
Oh, shit.
- Get up. Get up.
- CEO Hwang. It's over for me.
- Go on without me.
- Stop saying that, you son of a bitch!
Get up!
No... No!
So Hee! Please hold this for me!
No! Wait!
- Ki Joon, what are you doing?
- Tae Ho!
They're alive. They're alive.
Joon Oh and Ji Ah are alive.
- So Hee!
So Hee! No!
So Hee! Hey! Hey!
- So Hee, are you okay?
- So Hee, what's wrong?
What do we do?
Hey, come over here! Tae Ho, come here!
Ji Ah!
Ji Ah! Ji Ah. Ji Ah Ji Ah.
Hey, over here. So Hee, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
When did this start?
What's wrong with Ji Ah? Ji Ah. Ha Ji Ah!
Hey, you seem to be fine!
How many fingers?
Three...
You're okay! Ji Ah and So Hee
are in trouble! Get up! Okay?
I...
Bong Hee, I'll take care of Ji Ah.
Can you look after So Hee?
Sure.
- Ji Ah!
- So Hee, are you okay?
Ji Ah, open your mouth.
Ji Ah, open. Open. Open.
Just take one. Okay.
Okay, here.
Thank you for saving me.
You would have done the same for me.
But I'm still thankful.
I won't forget it.
Don't forget it. Cherish this memory.
- I'll be back!
- Where are you going?
Hey! Where are you going?
Oh, how refreshing.
Is it fall already?
The necklace belongs to...
They found the island...
that you were on.
Subtitles by DramaFever