Subtitles by DramaFever
Ra Bong Hee...
you're relaxing at the beach.
Your family... your loved ones...
and other familiar faces are all there.
Everyone you love...
is welcoming you.
Okay, Mom.
Ra Bong Hee... You feel comfortable.
You're in a place...
where you can spend your entire life
with your loved ones.
Let's go.
[Episode 4]
Ra Bong Hee.
You walk into the woods,
with the people you love.
Ra Bong Hee, you're not scared at all.
Because your loved ones
are by your side to protect you.
And then you approach a door.
Ra Bong Hee, you are afraid.
However, your loved ones
are by your side to protect you.
So you build up the courage
and slowly, walk...
through that door.
Bong Hee!
Joon Oh!
Over here!
Geez, I'm so hungry,
that I'm hearing things now.
Geez, my legs hurt...
Over here!
Joon Oh!
Yeol?
Wow, this place...
A ghost could pop out of nowhere.
Wow.
Yeol, can you hear my voice?
Yeol, I stepped on a landmine--
Whoa!
Who's out here in the middle of the night
making ghost sounds?
What if a ghost really pops out?
Do you know who I am?
After the plane crash...
I have one foot on a landmine!
Who--
Wow, amazing.
The landmine didn't explode.
Wait.
Ki Joon was right.
This is old.
Wow, this is... Damn it!
Why are you crying?
Oh...
I must have hit you in the eye.
Does it hurt?
I thought you were a ghost. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, for leaving you here alone.
Hey, why are you sorry? I told you to go.
What are you sorry about? Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
Hey, why are you crying?
My hands are dirty.
Stop, okay?
Stop crying. Geez. Okay?
Geez, come here.
There, there. Don't cry.
Okay? Stop. Geez...
There, there...
You're a nice girl, right? Don't cry.
Here. There, there. There, there.
Stop.
Over here!
Joon Oh!
That's Yeol, right?
- Let's go.
- Hey!
- Yeol, grab this.
- Grab it and wrap it around your waist.
Can you do that?
- Hold on tight!
- Tell me when you're ready!
Pull this, okay?
- I'm ready!
- Okay. One, two, three!
Two.
A little more!
Ow my arm!
Be... Be careful of your arm!
- Yeol, are you okay?
- Yeol, look at me.
Joon Oh, are you okay? Are you hurt?
What is this...
It's so deep.
It's so deep. Are you really okay?
What about Ji Ah? What happened to Ji Ah?
You're alive. I knew it.
How could I die and leave you here alone?
That's okay. Don't move. Just lie down.
Were you the one who saved me?
If not me, who would take care of you?
My boyfriend is pretty cool.
You're awake? Tae Ho,
CEO Hwang asked us to gather for a talk.
Geez, don't you think you slept too much?
Your complexion looks great.
I'll be back. Rest here.
Geez, why did you go off and get hurt?
You make me so angry.
Hey, do you think I wanted to get hurt?
Thanks.
- For what?
- What do you think...
Don't get hurt. Don't get hurt...
- Rest, okay?
- Okay.
Gosh.
What is this? Is he giving this to me,
or did he drop it?
Hey, I can't believe we're all alive.
It feels like a dream.
But, no matter how much I think about it
I don't think our lives here
will end easily.
Manager Jung,
I'm not really going to die, am I?
I told you it wasn't a poisonous snake.
You're alive right now, so...
You're okay.
What should we do
if we want to get out of here alive?
What else can we do?
We have no choice
but to wait here to be rescued.
We're all wondering if we should
rely on being rescued right now.
Tae Ho, we should wait to be rescued,
but not here.
There's no shelter when it rains
and if something like this happens again,
we'll be in trouble.
So what are you trying to say?
What do you want to do?
Let's go into the woods!
I stepped on a landmine
in the woods today.
Ki Joon, you saw it, right?
Ra Bong Hee saw it too.
Anyway, what does
a landmine on an island mean?
It means other people, or soldiers
once lived on this island.
Even the hole that Yeol fell into,
was made by people.
The hole was hidden with wood,
which means a person made it!
The place where those people lived...
The place where they ate and slept...
That's what we have to find.
That's how we can survive.
We can just build
another dwelling out here!
I don't think we should leave the beach.
If we are too far away from the beach,
we won't get rescued.
How can they save people
they can't even see?
We can get a rescue signal
from inside the woods.
The weather is cray here,
and it's getting colder too.
We have a patient, so we
have to find a warmer and safer place.
Why didn't you change after suffering?
Do you need to suffer some more?
I understand that you go all out
when you have an idea
but out of all lies you could have come
up with, a landmine? Try to be rational!
Seo Joon Oh really stepped on a mine.
It didn't explode--
Why don't you stay out of this?
I'm talking here.
- Why are you taking it out on Bong Hee?
- Hey, what was that?
Oh, I guess you got close after
being on a deserted island together.
Excuse me, is Joon Oh really good to you?
He should treat us better. I guess
he's only good to irrelevant people.
Tae Ho, what's wrong? Why do you
only act like that with Joon Oh?
Who's the bastard who killed Jae Hyun
and screwed up "Dreamers"?
That same bastard is acting arrogant,
so would you have anything nice to say?
That's enough.
You're the same as before!
If you want to be doomed and die,
do it yourself.
Do you know how hard it was
to recover my career back then?
That's enough, you punk.
After that day, I decided to never
believe you again. I made up my mind...
So if you're going to leave,
leave by yourself, you son of a bitch.
Choi Tae Ho, aren't you
being too harsh? He's still--
I told you to stop, Choi Tae Ho!
I'll just say one more thing. Joon Oh.
I'm begging you.
Don't try to do anything from now on.
When you take the lead,
you mess up everything.
Jae Hyun and "Dreamers"
were both screwed over because
you took the lead. Am I wrong?
Stop it, you bastards!
Why are you bringing that up again?
"Jae Hyun! Jae Hyun! Jae Hyun! Jae Hyun!"
Stop talking about Jae Hyun already!
We are supposed to think about how
we are going to survive, you bastards!
We should do everything
we can to survive!
Tae Ho is right. He's...
He's right about everything.
But please listen
to my opinion this time.
I'm saying this so we can all live.
It's not so I can survive alone.
We need to go into the woods
and find a safe place if we want to live.
If we don't stay together...
It'll be harder for us to survive.
Let's take a vote. Let's take a vote!
Let's vote
and we'll do what the majority votes for.
We'll all go, or we'll all stay.
Choi Tae Ho, what do you think?
- Do what you want.
- You little...
- What do you think?
- Yes, let's do that.
Okay.
Okay!
"I want to stay here." Raise your hands!
What are you doing?
Hey, let's not go on an adventure.
It's me, Manager Jung, and So Hee.
It's the four of us.
Out of all people,
what's your reason, Yeol?
I want to follow Joon Oh.
Because he's our team's leader.
Joon Oh's stylist.
- Yes.
- What's your reason?
I think we should look for traces of
other people if we want to live longer.
You son of a bitch,
why didn't you raise your hand?
I... get cold really easily.
This place isn't right. The sea breeze
is really intense here, so it's too cold.
I should have abandoned
this son of a bitch.
Then...
One, two, three, four. We're tied.
What do we do? Seriously!
Ji Ah hasn't voted yet.
I'll go and ask her.
Okay, ask Ji Ah!
We will all go if Ji Ah says yes,
and stay if she wants to stay.
You heard, right?
Yeah. I heard.
What do you want to do?
- You want to stay here, right?
- You heard, so you should know.
What about you?
Ji Ah, what do you want to do?
Ji Ah will probably do
what Choi Tae Ho wants to do, right?
You don't know
what kind of girl Ji Ah is, do you?
Ji Ah is a girl who wrote
her own contract at the age of 14.
There's no one else in this company
who's as confident as she is.
- Tae Ho.
- Yeah?
- You know I like you a lot, right?
- Of course I do.
But Tae Ho...
I don't want to stay here.
I want to follow Joon Oh.
Hey, Ji Ah. If you follow Joon Oh--
Don't try to talk me out of it.
We don't need to have the same opinions
just because we love each other, do we?
Let's make our own decisions, Tae Ho.
Pack your bags.
We can leave tomorrow morning.
Pack our bags?
Damn it! Hey, if there are landmines,
what else could be out there?
Are you worried?
Are you worried that
you'll drag everyone in there
and get all the blame
if we don't find anything?
Who cares about that?
If we search but can't find anything...
I'll share the blame with you.
Hey, I'm saying
I'll take the insults with you.
Hey, of course you should.
You're my stylist.
Hey, if Tae Ho tries to beat me up...
Can you throw the first punch for me?
Tae Ho's a really good fighter.
He even learned kickboxing...
Geez, there's nothing
I can't say to you anymore...
Don't worry. I'll hit him for you.
Even if you tell me
not to be, I'm worried.
Get some sleep.
We have to wake up early tomorrow.
Wait, Seo Joon Oh.
I'm not sure if I can ask you this...
But what happened
between you and Jae Hyun?
- Let's go big!
- Thank you!
Hey, for our cake...
- Jae Hyun will be our representative.
- Sounds good!
- We should do it together!
- Shin Jae Hyun!
Shin Jae Hyun! Shin Jae Hyun!
Shin Jae Hyun!
- Shin Jae Hyun! Shin Jae Hyun!
One year! One year!
One year! One year! One year!
What do we do? Is he really mad?
- Are you okay?
- Jae Hyun, are you okay?
Hey, that's right! That's our Jae Hyun!
Shin Jae Hyun! Shin Jae Hyun!
Shin Jae Hyun!
It's... It's too hard for me.
It's so difficult, I could die.
Then die, you son of a bitch! Die!
No...
No! Don't go, please...
You killed him.
I killed Jae Hyun.
I killed him.
You are on a path lined with flowers,
brightly lit from the warm sun.
When you walk through the next door...
A very large tree is waiting for you.
You are unable to understand
the tree's message
just yet.
The windy hills...
are beautiful, but it's a weary path.
Ra Bong Hee.
You discover a gift
that will take you to the truth.
Ra Bong Hee, what is the gift...
that you discovered?
What did you find, Ra Bong Hee?
A necklace.
Why did you find a necklace?
I don't know, it's just...
It's just there...
Do you remember who owns...
that necklace?
Yes.
I know.
The necklace...
The necklace belongs to...
They found the island that you were on.
Bong Hee, are you ready?
Why is your face lacking color?
Are you sick?
No, I didn't sleep very well.
No wonder...
Why are you going on a plane again?
It's okay, Mom.
Bong Hee, try this on.
Let's bring some life to your face.
What do you think? Does it suit me?
Yeah. You're so pretty, Bong Hee.
I don't normally dress up. But when I do,
I look pretty because I take after you.
My daughter...
You'd better take care of yourself
on this trip.
Don't worry.
This is your second trip abroad.
It's not easy
to send you away or to trust you.
Chairwoman Jo, aren't you...
coming with me?
There's no guarantee that you'll
recover more of your memory if I'm there.
Investigator Oh
will take good care of you.
So you'd better regain
all of your memory.
When you wake up from a nice nap,
we'll be there.
Wherever we are in the ocean,
it all looks the same
but do you remember anything
now that we're almost there?
Oh, that island that we see over there
is the island you were on!
We're going there now!
Do you see it?
[Hwang Jae Gook, Tae Ho Hang,
Jung Ki Joon, Choi Tae Ho, Ha Ji Ah]
[Yoon So Hee, Lee Yeol, Seo Joon Oh,
and Ra Bong Hee won't give up.]
- I really like it here, though!
- Hey, it's cold here.
Come on.
What are you doing? Let's go!
Okay, I'm coming!
You can follow me!
[Seo Joon Oh]
We're almost there!
You know where you're going, right?
Where are we headed?
We're almost there!
Just a little longer!
- Ji Ah, are you okay?
- We were already here!
Hey, don't get mad! Come on!
Didn't we just come from there?
We're here!
- He said we're here! He said we're here!
- Where?
Do you even know where we're going?
What the hell are you doing?
- Where are you going?
- Are you joking? Are you fooling around?
- We're here.
- Hey, you sound like a mom!
- Where are you going now?
- Where are you going?
- This isn't it!
- We're here!
- We were here already!
- No, we weren't.
He keeps saying, "We're here,
we're here." Where is he now? Hey!
Oh, what do we do?
Where... Where were you?
Let's just go! I don't know
why we keep following him!
- We'll just end up coming back here.
- He came back!
- When did you get here?
- We were here the whole time.
- You were here this whole time?
- Yeah.
We found it. Right?
It's really here.
Hey! Wow! You punk!
- Did you know this was here?
- I didn't know.
Wow!
Let's go inside!
Can we live here?
Hey, we should be thankful for this!
- Be careful!
- Wow...
- Wow!
- Hey, did you know this was here?
- I didn't know.
- Hey, here...
- It's not bad!
- Hey, Ra Bong Hee!
- Yes, I'm coming!
I think something
might be inside. Go inside.
Hey, this thing...
It's deep! Go inside!
- Go inside.
- It's so deep. I would have been doomed.
- I could have died.
- Which ones?
This one and that one.
- This?
- Yeah, this one and that one.
Hey, stop it. It's not like
you've ever worked before...
Hey! Hey! Everyone, gather around!
We should have a meeting.
What are you talking about?
- Ji Ah, wait. You're hurt...
- No.
- Share opinions and have arguments!
- That's how we should work!
- Let's do this again...
- Is this a corner?
- Get yourself together!
- No!
- Let go!
My younger sister... died.
To be more exact,
she was murdered on that island.
Do you remember who it was...
who killed my sister?
Ra Bong Hee!
What are you doing here?
Did you remember something?
No... No.
Then, why do you look like that?
Are you sick?
No. I'm fine.
Okay. I'm sorry for making you wait.
What did you want to talk to me about?
I... thought about this
for a long time...
But I thought you should know,
so I brought it here.
What is that?
Do you really not remember anything?
- I'm sorry.
- We just wasted money...
Where are you headed?
- Home.
- We'll give you a ride.
[Prosecutor Yoon]
Aren't you going to answer?
Go ahead and answer it.
No. It's not important.
I'll go home by myself.
No. No. We have to take you home.
This way.
Geez, what is it this time?
Yes, Chairman Jo!
Right now?
Why so suddenly?
Excuse me?
Doctor Park left this here.
He said this is the recording from
Ra Bong Hee's hypnosis session.
Investigator Oh,
did you step out during that session?
Oh, I left for just a moment
when they found the island.
He said this was recorded then.
Listen to it.
Okay.
Do you remember who owns...
that necklace?
Yes. I know.
I heard you visited that island.
Please give me a call.
That necklace belongs to...
So Hee.
Yoon So Hee.
Ra Bong Hee.
Why do you have Yoon So Hee's necklace?
I... I...
I... killed her.
No!
I killed Yoon So Hee.
What are we going to do now?
Ra Bong Hee, that girl...
Will we make her into a survivor,
or a murderer?
We don't have clear evidence
that she murdered--
Investigator Oh!
I'm talking about evidence.
I'm asking you
what will work in our favor
making her into a survivor or a murderer?
Are you asking for
a politically favorable decision?
Yes, a political decision!
The citizens of this nation pay for our
salaries with taxes, so we can do that.
Is she a survivor or a murderer? Huh?
What is it going to be?
Should we give Ra Bong Hee
a ride in a flower palanquin...
or a police car?
- Look at this!
- What is it?
It's a suitcase! A suitcase...
- Oh! I think that's mine!
- Pardon?
- Wow! Where did you find this?
- I found it by the rocks at the beach.
- Wow!
- My shoes!
Wow, my shoes! Wow!
Wow! My shoes!
I didn't see this
when I was there last time.
I think it was swept onto shore by the
waves. I think there are a few more...
Would anyone be willing
to swim out there with me?
Look. We don't know
how long we'll be here
so if we find some more suitcases,
it'll be a huge help to us.
If they might be helpful,
we should find them.
Who would like to come with me?
Why are you looking at me?
- We have to do it, right?
- You're the one who said we should.
We must do it.
- We can succeed, right?
- We have to.
Everyone is putting their faith in us.
Hey, don't worry, okay?
Trust me. Let's go!
Hey! Hey! Go slowly, okay?
You're going overboard! Hey!
Hey, the currents are strong over there!
Hey! Hey! Slow down!
Ra Bong Hee!
Oh, geez.
Let's go!
Geez, the currents are no joke! Right?
Clothes!
What is this? Ramen! Ramen! Wow!
Hey!
- Not the tuna!
- Just one.
- We should share with everyone.
No.
Wow, look at this.
Let's go and find one more.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
- Is this kimchi?
- Yes!
Should we eat just one piece each?
I don't like kimchi, though.
Here, I'll give you the big one.
I'll be right there!
It's really ripe.
I'm coming! Hey, don't go too far!
I'll be there soon!
- Where are you?
- Over here! Over here!
I told you we should go together...
Oh! There are a lot more clothes! Hey,
it looks like we can stay warm, right?
Yes.
Let's see. Hey.
Hey, take a break.
No, it's better
if we get it all over with.
Hey, take a break.
You don't look so good.
Everyone's waiting.
Hey, tell them to wait! They're just
sitting around sucking their thumbs.
Hey, put this on, okay?
Here. Okay? Wear this. I'll be back...
Rest here, okay?
- Let's go together--
- Hey! It's okay.
Stay here. Okay?
It's dangerous though...
Hey! Hey, wait... Wait...
- Pardon?
- Wait...
- Another break?
- Yeah, let's rest for a little bit.
Gosh, you only found one suitcase
in two hours. Why are you so tired?
Hey, the currents
are different from Korea.
Hey, how did you retrieve five suitcases
in those strong currents?
The currents will only get worse.
It'll be impossible for everyone else,
and it'll get harder for me too.
The undertow could kill us if we
aren't careful when we go into the water.
Hey, how do you know all of that?
Were you a diver?
Yes, I was. My mother is a diver.
Oh, really?
Gosh, I'll be the only one to swim from
now on. It's dangerous for everyone else.
Hey, stop working.
Why are you the one to step up
every time something happens?
I don't want to be a useless person
on this island too.
That's all.
- Let's go.
- Okay!
- What is all this?
- Can we wear these?
- Oh, this is Joon Oh's!
- This is mine.
Hey, if you can't open it,
just wear some of mine.
None of them will fit me.
Hey, all you have to do is
put one of these over your head...
So Hee, did you find your clothes?
Hey, aren't you... going to change?
After I finish this.
Why is there so much fabric?
It looks like they were stage props.
- Aren't you cold?
- It's still bearable for me.
Yeol! What do you think?
- Won't you be cold?
- Ji Ah, that's not yours!
This...
This is mine.
- What? This is mine!
- No, it's mine.
- Hey, this is for women!
- I said it was mine.
You must be crazy!
Wow, I'm speechless.
Geez, this is too small.
It used to fit...
This is small. Hey, for you.
Do you want to wear it? Go ahead.
Wear it while I ask you nicely.
Seo Joon Oh...
- Do you want to die?
- I have to give it to Ji Ah. She's sick.
- Ji Ah has clothes.
- She's sick! Wait.
Try it on and see if it fits or not.
Gosh!
Just wear it.
Ji Ah, you weren't sleeping?
How could I sleep with you two
running back and forth? I woke up.
- I'm sorry.
- Let me sleep.
- But Ji Ah, you're sick. You should--
- I'll get better if you wear this. Go!
- Ji Ah--
- Goodnight.
Joon Oh.
Okay.
Ouch, my shoulders...
Where did everyone go?
- Are you awake?
- Manager Jung, where is--
- We have a crisis.
- Pardon?
Geez, I'm going crazy...
What... What... What happened here?
I don't know.
It couldn't have been one of us.
Then who did it? Does that mean
someone else is on this island?
If they were other survivors, they
would have just eaten the food and left.
Then who could it be?
- Joon Oh!
- Yeah!
- Geez, I'm going crazy.
- What?
- Some of the clothes are gone too.
It's certain now.
There are...
other people on this island.
[Prosecutor Yoon]
I'm sorry.
Bong Hee, let's eat.
The number you have dialed
is unavailable--
Sir?
I looked into it...
and the vibe in the special
investigation committee isn't so good.
Oh. What do you mean?
Well, I heard they're not contacting
anyone outside of the committee.
And they turned off
all the briefing routes.
I think...  they found something strange.
Like what?
A few days ago, Ra Bong Hee
received hypnosis therapy.
- Chairman Jo.
- Later.
- Oh, and make sure no one comes in.
- Oh, yes. I understand.
But after Chairman Jo
met with the doctor in charge
they said the vibe wasn't good,
and the look in her eyes changed.
They say she makes
a lot of strange phone calls.
Strange phone calls?
A murderer, or a survivor
which one do you like better?
Gosh, seriously.
What's wrong? You have seniority
for making such political decisions.
Then, can you tell me at what hospital
Ra Bong Hee received the hypnosis?
Yes.
- We can find out, right?
- Of course, yes.
Just in case something like this
happens again, let's stand guard.
It's too dangerous
for one person do it, so in pairs. Okay?
Sure... Who wants to go first?
- I'll go first.
- Sure, sounds good.
Who else...
- Bong Hee, would you like to join me?
- Pardon?
Me?
Don't do it!
Sure... I'll do it. Okay...
It's settled then. Let's start right now.
Let's go.
Hey, guard the place with a bat.
There could be wild savages out there.
Okay, let's decide
who'll go next tomorrow.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cookies...
Two.
Excuse me.
There's something I'm curious about...
Why... did you pick me?
I mean...
I don't think I ever upset you in any way
but you picked me all of a sudden.
I don't like seeing you
with Joon Oh all the time.
That's why.
Do you hate Seo Joon Oh that much?
It sounded like this is because
of a man named Jae Hyun...
And I don't know
the whole story... I don't...
But you were once like brothers
in the same group...
So I don't know why you have to...
Did you know that Joon Oh killed a man?
I killed Jae Hyun.
I killed him.
But that was just emotional.
He didn't actually kill him.
I guess you don't know
Seo Joon Oh very well yet.
You'll understand
after you spend more time with him.
You'll see how Joon Oh kills people.
What was that? Who was it? Huh? Hey!
Come here!
This bastard.
Wait! Seo Joon Oh! What happened?
Did you see him?
I don't know. He disappeared.
Hey, Tae Ho!
Who are you?
Doomed. It was doomed.
What?
The plane you were on was doomed.
Then why did you steal from us?
You could have just shown up.
Why did you go behind our backs?
Tae Ho! Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
I'm over here!
Do you want to live?
If you want to live, listen to me.
I don't know about them,
but I can save your life.
I can help you get out of here!
- What the hell are you saying?
- Hey!
Choi Tae Ho!
Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
If you want to live, listen to me.
First, send them away.
- Hey, Tae Ho!
- Tae Ho!
Did something happen? Hey!
He must be nearby...
Hey!
Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
Talk.
How can I survive?
There's a lifeboat.
On the beach near here.
A lifeboat?
Yes, a lifeboat.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
But...
It only holds four people.
That's why I was watching you guys.
I was looking for people
to escape this island with.
If we take that boat...
Can we really get out of here?
- Is it safe enough?
- Of course.
It was on the plane in case of a crash.
Two people.
If we get two more people...
We can get out of here.
If we find two more people...
We don't have to stay in this shithole.
Do you understand?
We can live.
Two people.
You're saying
we need two more people, right?
Who do you have in mind?
People who can be helpful, of course.
Is that Tae Ho?
- Hey! You!
- What is this?
Are you okay?
- Where were you?
- Don't worry.
You should have said something
before going!
I'm okay.
I got lost because it's nighttime.
It's dangerous.
Let's stay together, okay?
How could you just leave like that?
You have to be careful.
Let's go together next time.
It's dangerous.
Aren't you cold?
Is the chair comfortable enough?
Yes.
May I ask you what you've been
having a hard time with?
My younger sister died.
Not too long ago.
To be more exact, she was murdered.
But when it came my to feelings...
I was sad at first,
but I calmed down over time.
Am I weird?
The same goes for physical wounds.
They fade slowly, over time.
I'll ask you again, Doctor.
Am I the weird one?
My younger sister's name
was Yoon So Hee.
I'm Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young, of
the western district prosecutor's office.
I've found the right place
for a consultation, right?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
A person who is dirty enough,
and selfish enough...
- I'm coming too.
- People like that? You're not like that.
Hey, be careful.
Take care of your health.
I'm bothered by what So Hee said.
It sounded like she wasn't coming back.
If you really killed my sister,
I'll put everything on the line...
- Do you want to die here?
- and send you to jail.
- Tae Ho killed someone.
- What happened on that island?
Ra Bong Hee wants to send someone.
That person's still alive?