Subtitles by DramaFever
We're going down!
I'm in here! Please save me!
- Declare an emergency!
- Roger!
Mayday! Mayday!
Joon Oh! Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
What the hell is this?
Ji Ah!
Wait here. I'll come back
after I check the situation.
Control, this is 079er. We are in a dive!
We're crashing, you bastards!
Mom, can I stop doing this?
There's no need for your daughter
to be a diver just because you are.
- You can stop, then.
- Really?
Wait, why did you give up so quickly?
I never expected you
to live a life like mine.
People should do
what they want to do in life.
Then why did you make me go into
the water and make me do this every day?
This is all I can do for you.
I'm unable to leave my child
an inheritance to live on
so teaching my child how to eat and live
is the least I can do as a mother.
Do what you want to do,
and come back if it's too hard.
I'll always be here.
Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh, wake up!
Seo Joon Oh!
Seo Joon Oh! Wake up! Seo Joon Oh!
Seo Joon Oh.
No! Seo Joon Oh, please wake up!
Seo Joon Oh!
Are you awake, Seo Joon Oh?
The others... Huh?
Seo Joon Oh!
Seo Joon Oh! No! Seo Joon Oh, wake up!
Wake up! Please!
There's water.
Oh! No, you can't! Don't touch that!
You can't drink this yet.
Why? What's going on?
Where did you come from?
Where are we? Huh?
Hey, why can't I drink that?
Hey, why?
Hey, where the heck are we? Huh?
Hey! I'm asking you where we are!
Your actions tell me you're okay.
Wait here for a little bit.
And just in case, don't touch that.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey! Hey! What...
Did our plane crash?
But... But I'm... I'm okay!
What is this? Is... Is this the engine?
Ouch, that's hot!
Ki Joon! Ye... Yeol! Hey, Ji Ah!
My phone... Hey, where...
Hey! Hey!
Shit!
What do we do...
What do I do, Mom?
[Episode 2]
According to the doctor
her memory has been compromised
temporarily, due to encephalomeningitis.
Anyway, we will try everything
to recover her memory--
Investigator Oh, about her...
Don't you think she's too calm?
She can clearly express
her emotions and opinions
and her clear speech tells me
she didn't go through that much hardship.
She's much too calm.
Anyway, whether it's medicine
or hypnosis, do everything you can.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go.
- Be careful!
- Yes! I'm coming!
Hurry up. Go.
Ra Bong Hee!
Geez, can you come with us for a moment?
There's someone who wants to meet you.
Who is...
- It'll just be a moment.
- Please come this way.
- Why are you doing this?
- Hey! You'll know when you get there.
- Who are you--
- Hey! Don't fighting back!
Geez, this girl!
Who the hell are you?
Damn it... Who are you?
Yes... We're... Um, who are we?
Who the hell are you?
Oh, we're... here to explore
the mud flat.
Oh... Yes, we heard that the octopuses
are good these days, so we're...
- Bong Hee!
- Hey, catch her!
- Stop right there!
- Bong Hee!
- Go!
- Hurry up!
- Follow her!
- Excuse me!
Wait!
My jacket!
- What the hell are you saying?
- That's why I'm here!
Hey, you son of a bitch! Hey, come here!
Hey, you bastards! Come here!
Seo Joon Oh!
Hey... Hey, let's go!
- Let's... Let's go!
- Hurry!
So?
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Here you go, Sir.
Bong Hee. Are you all right?
Yes.
Why did our plane crash? Why?
Damn it! Shit!
The plane couldn't even handle that?
This plane was so expensive!
Why... Why can't I drink that?
Nice!
Why isn't anyone here?
Hey, what? Is this all yours?
Give it to me. Give it to me!
I'll buy some for you when we get back.
Give it to me!
I told you to give it to me!
Wait, why are you acting like this?
I told you not to eat that!
We're on a deserted island!
I was just...
What did you just say?
This is a deserted island. Everyone died,
and we're on the only ones alive.
That's all we have left to eat!
What did you say? Huh?
Hey, we're on a deserted island?
The plane crashed,
and now it's just the two of us?
Have you gone to that side?
What about the others?
Did you look for them?
What about Ki Joon, Ji Ah, Yeol, and
Tae Ho? Did you go all the way to end?
There's a hidden camera, isn't there?
I should have known earlier.
You're not a newbie stylist.
You're a rookie actress, right?
Where's the camera? Huh?
What about the others?
What happened to the others?
Before all of this...
They were family.
We worked together for many years.
There are rumors going around
that this incident...
was fabricated by Legend Entertainment!
Does that make any sense?
After the only survivor of the crash,
Ra Bong Hee, returned
the families of Legend Entertainment
have been pressing for the truth
in order to find out
if the rest of the missing are alive.
The fan clubs for those who are
still missing gathered at 10 a.m.
and through the question and answer
period with Seo Joon Oh's stylist, Ms. Ra
they pressed for the truth
to be revealed.
For the purpose of the ones
who are still missing we ask Ra Bong Hee
for her testimony of what she remembers.
If we follow the fan clubs'
joint statements
there are no statements from
the authorities involved in this case
so many malicious rumors
are going around...
A deserted island!
She regained some of her memory, and
she said she was on a deserted island!
- Is she certain?
- Yes. She is.
Bring Ra Bong Hee
to Yeomchang-dong right now.
Sure.
Why can't you do it?
Tae Young, this case
came down to us from the top!
If we take care of this well, you and I--
There's something else
I must do. I'm sorry.
Is it because of your sister?
If rumors start--
I will work hard to prevent any problems.
I have Lawyer Jo as well.
Do you think your sister is still alive?
- I can only hope.
- And if not?
After you throw away
your opportunities for success
and hang on to this case, if your
sister is dead, what will you do then?
Whether my sister is alive...
or dead, I will have to do my job.
And what do you think your job is?
The truth. I will reveal the truth.
It's my job to help the victims in
the name of law. That's your job as well.
It's not our job...
to manipulate the truth,
like we did for this case.
So the plane crashed,
and only the two of you survived?
So, Seo Joon and Ra Bong Hee,
just the two of you.
Yes.
Don't believe everything
she says. Get confirmation.
Get more out of her! Ask her for details.
I don't know
how you'll feel about this...
But how did it feel after
you knew you were on a deserted island?
You don't believe me, do you?
I'm a girl who can't remember
what happened
for the last four months.
It's strange that I suddenly
remembered a part of it.
And it's also strange
that I survived the plane crash.
So you're wondering
if I'm telling the truth or not...
And asking me trick questions.
No, I'm...
I don't remember everything...
about what happened to them.
But...
If I tell you everything
that I do remember...
I saw and felt in detail...
Will you believe me?
Will you believe me...
And for those people
who might be dead or alive...
For those people...
Can you go save them?
If... If you can...
I'll do everything you ask
to regain my memory.
So...
So, please...
Please don't abandon those people.
Here we go.
Let's accept it.
One day...
I wondered why it had to happen to me...
Out of all the people...
Why did this happen to me?
I was full of resentment.
This is for encephalomeningitis.
It might help with your memory.
And on another day... I felt pain...
because people died.
And on a different day...
I was thankful that I was even alive.
I felt desperation
because I wanted to live.
Hey! It's... It's a boat!
Hey, it's a boat!
Over here! Over here! Over...
Hey. Hey. Hey! Hey! Hey!
Over here! Over here!
Good job! Good job!
- I think we'll survive!
- Over here! Save us!
Go! Go!
We experienced hundreds
of different feelings
and moods every day.
Our bodies got injured...
And our hearts got sick...
- Oh, are you hurt? Let's see!
- It hurts.
Hey, this won't open!
It was as if we were waiting to die...
as we endured it sluggishly, day by day.
But we saw something.
What was it?
Hope.
10... 15...
20... 25!
- You didn't see his body, right?
- I didn't.
He was saved. In 25 days.
- We can live too!
- We can! We can live!
We can survive! We can survive!
We can survive!
We're going home! We're going home!
Home! Home!
No matter what it takes,
we're going home!
- Home! Home!
- We're going home!
After seeing hope
right in front of our eyes
a thought crossed my mind.
"Let's survive for now."
"If we stay alive for now..."
"someone will surely come to save us."
Did you think about
looking for other survivors?
We tried looking for them...
- Seo Joon Oh, why did you come out?
- Hey, let's stop for today.
Is it because the grass is prickly?
No, I'm hungry. We should eat
if we're going to move around.
- You ate bread this morning.
- Hey, let's live.
No, we can't stop!
Let's look for a little longer!
Ask her how they lived
during those four months.
I'll ask you a detailed question.
How... did you survive?
There were no people...
And because there were no people,
there were no houses.
And because there were no houses,
there was no light.
If you were in a place like that
for four months...
How do you think you would have lived?
Is that a weapon?
Oh, be careful.
Gosh, take off your gloves!
No. No. Wrap it around the big tree.
- This one?
- With your fingers!
- It stings.
- I'll do it. Move.
Then you should have done it
from the start!
Three! Yes! That's right! Yes!
- One, two...
- Three!
- Use your strength!
- I'm holding it up! Three!
- Three!
- Four!
One...
- Pull it one more time!
- A little more! This way!
Left or right? I can't see!
Lift it higher.
When will you do this side?
If we go near the grass, the grass
is getting water from somewhere.
So if we plug this in,
drops over water will come out.
Oh, it's coming out! Look!
It's coming out! See?
It is.
We should drink it next year.
We don't have to ration for 25 days
if we've already been here
for a few days, right?
This won't work.
For our remaining days, I'll just
drink this. You can have the rest. Okay?
And for food, I don't eat much.
I'll just have this, and you have
a lot here, so I'll take this too, okay?
Put it down.
How many rations?
Her statements have been good
for the last few days
so what should we do now?
Make a call to China for me.
Yes, around Huizhou, China
where Ra Bong Hee was found
there are 143 islands.
Out of those, we are assuming
97 islands are uninhabited.
We requested that they contact us if any
trace of human life or a body is found.
How long did they say it'll take?
I'm... I'm not sure, so people who know--
How long will it take
to search those 97 islands?
We asked the specialists
to start the search as soon as--
I don't want to hear that they'll try
their best and that they'll work hard!
Tell me the facts. The facts, okay?
The... The truth is... So...
If we have to mark all 97 islands
and recruit people to search
the surrounding water
it'll take around three months.
It looks like I'll be fired
in the meantime.
- Where is Ra Bong Hee right now?
- She's at home in Namhae Island.
- Did you give her security guards?
- Yes.
Tell them to protect her
so that the reporters can't get to her!
If the media finds out about her
memory loss, they'll press us harder.
Yes, I'll tell them.
You can continue with
our investigation in Yeomchang-dong.
Continue to record it and send it to me.
Yeah, Lawyer Jo.
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon,
they found your sister.
They found your sister
in Huizhou, China.
But...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Where in China?
I'll bring back lots of fish!
- What are you doing?
- Isn't it obvious?
You don't have to do that.
People who look will see it.
Here's your lunch.
Hey, wait!
- Give me some more.
- No.
Hey, I'm working! Give me a little more.
No one asked you to do this.
I better not eat it.
Excuse me. Sir.
- Your barbecue is ready.
- Huh?
Would you like some wine, Sir?
What is this? Pineapple...
Pizza!
Excuse me, would you like
some barbecue, Sir?
- I don't really like pork.
- Okay. Okay.
Here's some spicy seafood noodle soup!
- Oh!
- Have some!
- Bonjour.
- Hey, Byung Joo!
Do you like shrimp?
This is why I have you, Byung Joo! Hey!
Thank you! Sausages.
Wake up. Excuse me.
Is it delicious?
Why are you eating this right now?
You're crazy! You're crazy!
You're crazy! Huh? You're crazy!
Why are you eating this?
- No, it wasn't me!
- Gosh, really.
Are you crazy? Are you?
Why did you eat this? Why? Why? Why?
It wasn't me! It wasn't!
I was dreaming about eating.
Gosh, that's gross!
- I... I'm burping because I'm hungry.
- You're got to be kidding me.
I was running all over this island and
saving this food so that we can live!
What do we do if you eat it all?
I told you I was dreaming!
Would I have eaten this in my right mind?
You're crazy! You're crazy!
You ate all this to save yourself!
Hey!
This girl... Hey!
Are you going to keep
talking to me like that? Huh? Crazy?
You're my stylist and I'm your artist!
What stylist calls her artist crazy?
Do you want to be fired?
Hey, if we're saved like that Alden guy
I'll send boxes of these to your house.
So be careful what you say.
If not, I'll really fire you, got it?
Yes.
Since I already...
I'm sorry. I didn't burp. I'm sorry.
What will you do now? Huh?
I ate everything.
I ate everything. There's some honey,
but the food is gone. What will you do?
What else can we do?
We have to hunt.
Who are you?
Make a fire.
I'll find food for us to eat.
How can I make a fire without a lighter?
I'm asking you because we don't have
one. Would I have asked if we had one?
Make one for us!
Hey, what are you going to catch?
How do I make a fire?
Geez, I should have gone
on "Law of the Jungle."
Damn it. I knew it wouldn't work.
- Where did you get that?
- I found it.
What are you doing?
I'm making a fire.
I'm making a fire with the lens.
That is just glass!
It won't start a fire.
You need a convex mirror
to make a fire. That won't work.
Hey, why are you telling me
that now? I've been here for hours!
Because I just saw you. Anyway,
make a fire. I'll catch some fish.
- This is a present.
- How...
It's a present!
Oh, I got one!
Wow! That scared me!
Geez, that scared me.
I almost caused a fire.
I was the one
who set this all up earlier today.
Hey, what did you do for a living?
There's nothing you can't do.
It's not that there's nothing I can't do,
but there are many things you can't do.
And can you stop calling me "Hey"?
I have a name. Ra Bong Hee.
- Fine, Ra Bong Hee.
- This looks good.
Hey, the way I see it,
I think a deserted island suits you.
You were born to live here.
I can't just starve to death
after what we did to survive.
I should make it work
until we're rescued.
- It looks delicious.
- Here.
- What?
- Eat it. It's ready.
- Just like this?
- Yes!
- I can't take the bones out.
- Pardon?
I choked on a fish bone when
I was little, so I can't do it anymore.
Take out the bones for me.
Wait, then what is it
that you can actually do?
Geez, it looks like you forgot already.
Hey, do you really want to be fi--
Hey, do I really have to say
the same thing over and over again?
Do you really have to make me
into an indecent and petty person
by making my heart ache
as I keep threatening to fire you?
I'm exhausted!
Sure. Okay, fine.
Hey, eat some while you take out
the bones. When you're eating fish
it's more delicious
if you eat it like that.
Here, okay? Here, you have some.
And I'll have some too.
- Isn't it good?
- Wow, it's so good!
Hey, we should have eaten this
from the beginning.
We shouldn't have eaten snacks...
- Hey, eat this.
- Okay.
Bones.
Let's cook them all.
Wake up. Seo Joon Oh!
- What?
- Hurry up! Come out here.
Where are we going?
- What? Is something there?
- There are sounds...
- Where?
- Listen carefully.
- What is it?
- Over there. Over there.
- You can hear it, right?
- I think we heard it wrong.
No! No way!
Over there.
Damn it.
Seo Joon Oh, do you see that?
Seo Joon Oh, do you see it? Seo Joon...
- Seo Joon Oh, what are you doing?
- I'm farsighted. I can see better. Wait.
Stop it!
Let's move in on the count of three.
Yeol. Hey. Hey. Yeol!
Ye... Ye... Hey, Yeol!
Hey, Yeol!
One, two...
Here you go.
That's it. Like that.
Let's drink some more. Open wider.
Oh, you're awake?
How's your arm? Oh...
It's okay thanks to you.
That's a relief. Oh, sit down.
I was making porridge.
There's nothing but fish and clams here.
It's almost ready.
It looks good. You can eat it with...
Oh, drink it with that hand.
Thank you.
By the way, there's something
I'm curious about.
How did you not die?
- Are you okay? Oh, I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
Oh, it came out weird, didn't it?
What I meant was...
How did you survive
and get all the way over here?
And how did you know we were here?
That's what I wanted to ask.
Um, after the plane crashed...
and I woke up...
I thought I was the only survivor.
I waited for days
hoping that a rescue team would come.
But then I saw a light last night.
Oh, that light. We were cooking
and eating fish last night.
Do you think they'll come for us?
To save us?
Over there,
it seemed like A-L-D-E-N was here.
I don't know exactly
what country he was from
but I think he was here a long time ago.
He lived on this island for 25 days.
I think he was rescued.
Haven't you thought that
we might end up dying on this island?
Right now, the chances
that they won't come are pretty high.
Why do you think that, Lee Yeol?
I saw him.
Alden.
Is that...
really true?
If people found this island
and came here even once
the people that I saw...
They would have been collected.
Because they're human bodies.
Geez, it's cold. You're awake?
- Joon Oh!
- Yeah.
Geez, I couldn't sleep
because of the two of you talking.
What about food?
Did you eat something?
Hey, is that enough? Huh?
You should eat fish. Fish.
We have a lot of fish.
Hey, let's cook a few more
of the fish from yesterday.
Don't we have any left?
Oh, that's right, we ate all of them.
Hey, then go and catch some more fish.
Hey, you're going to make
my heart ache again...
Hey, if you keep acting like this,
I'll fire you when we get back to Seoul!
Okay, fire me.
Fire me, you son of a bitch.
Fire me. If you're lucky enough
to escape this island, fire me!
But you...
won't be able to get out of here.
Neither of us will be able
to escape this place!
- Hey, what... Hey, are you crazy? Ouch!
- You horrible bastard...
- Let go. Hey, let go.
- You son of a bitch!
- You can catch your own fish!
- I won't eat them.
You son of a bitch!
Joon Oh! Joon Oh! Joon Oh!
Joon Oh. Joon Oh. Joon Oh, get up.
What?
Light.
A person.
It's a person!
Hey. Hey. Hey!
Where do you think.... Hey.
I bet they're not here
to rescue us, right?
Joon Oh, they could be
like us. Survivors.
Joon Oh, they could be people
we know! I'll be right back.
Yeol! Yeol! Hey, where do you
think you're going? Hey!
Hey, Yeol!
Where is it?
Let's go that way!
I think it was around here somewhere.
Let's split up. If you find someone
or if something happens, scream loudly.
Okay.
Excuse me! Is anyone out there?
Here!
Please help!
Bong Hee!
Please help me!
Please save me!
You should have been more careful!
Geez, come on.
There's something I'm curious about.
When you first saw that light...
Why did you run towards it
without looking back?
Did you do it to help another survivor?
Is that way?
I didn't go to help anyone...
To be honest, I wanted to be helped.
No matter who it was
or where they were on that island...
I thought they would be
better off than we were.
I completely understand how you felt.
Yes, I think I would have
felt the same way.
Are you on a date?
Stop the useless chatter
and ask her who that survivor was!
Yes... Yes, Oh... Yes. Um...
So, Ra Bong Hee.
The light from that cellphone.
The survivor that you found
by putting yourself in danger.
Who was it?
Do you remember? Do you?
It's so cold.
You scared me.
Thank you for saving me.
You would have done the same for me.
But I'm still thankful.
I won't forget it.
Don't forget it, okay?
Cherish this memory.
- Joon Oh!
- Earlier...
- Yeol.
- Bong Hee!
Are you okay? What happened?
- I tripped.
- Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
- That's why you two shouldn't have...
- Let's go. It's cold.
You must remember, Ra Bong Hee.
Who was that person?
Who was that person
and are they still alive
or did they die on that island?
The thing is...
Do you remember?
That person...
No!
I definitely...
I definitely saw that person.
Who was it that you saw?
I saw her face...
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
Joon Oh...
- Ji Ah!
Ji Ah! Ji Ah. Ji Ah.
Wh... Wh... What happened?
Where were you?
Why did you leave me alone?
Ji Ah, are you hurt?
- Don't cry. Don't cry.
- Hey, how did you survive all this time?
Hey, were you alone all this time?
Were you alone?
No, I was with someone.
They found the body under a cliff.
(In Chinese)
But the crash wasn't
the cause of death. It was murder.
He said she was found at the bottom of
a cliff. But it wasn't the plane crash...
But he thinks someone killed her.
I stayed here after the plane crash
and this is where we met.
- What's so weird about that?
- Just follow me.
- She's anxious and won't eat anything.
- After all that happened...
She tried to kill herself a few days ago.
Why?
She said she wants do die.
She said she's miserable here.
What is his relationship to her?
(In Chinese)
He wants to know their relationship.
Tell him she was his younger sister.
Are you okay?
From a medical point of view
she should remember everything.
Are you saying...
Ra Bong Hee remembers everything,
but she's pretending she can't?
Is that what you're saying?
This is all I have to say.
From a medical perspective,
this situation doesn't make any sense!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
It seems like you were
close on the island.
- You know what's going on, right?
- Do you remember who it was
who killed her?
He kills others so he can live. He can
do it again. We're on a deserted island.
If they find out, it'll stir up a mess.
- Are you sick?
- It's not a fatal illness.
What's not fatal?
We don't know who's alive or not...
Do you think everyone else died?
- Tae Ho?
- You were alive!
Whether we starve or we're killed,
we're going to die here anyway!
- So Hee's strange.
- Hey, Yoon So Hee!
He's Seo Joon Oh,
a former Dreamers member.
He has a unique theory.