This is about Shin Jae Hyun's death
four years ago.
It was not a suicide.
It was murder
that was disguised as a suicide.
You're useful for once.
Let's send you off. In one shot.
Sa... Save me... Save me...
Let's send you off in one shot.
No way.
Shin Jae Hyun's case was disguised
as a suicide four years ago...
Jang Do Pal.
[Arrest Warrant]
His accomplice was Choi Tae Ho.
These two planned their crimes...
which is why I am here
to request the investigation be reopened.
- It's dangerous!
- Geez, no it's not!
I'm telling you it was!
Yes, Tae Ho just left.
Gate Three. Yes, I understand.
The owner of the cell phone
that recorded this murder
became a murder target
for Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal.
That was Yoon So Hee.
I want to request a rigorous
investigation into Yoon So Hee's murder.
How did Yoon So Hee record the incident?
So are you saying Seo Joon Oh
is unrelated to this incident?
Will Seo Joon Oh speak
at this press conference?
We caught Choi Tae Ho!
We caught him as he tried to escape.
Okay.
The police caught Choi Tae Ho.
That's enough. You should leave
a little room for our investigation.
Through a fair investigation
by the prosecution
I am urging them to work hard so that
they don't victimize an innocent person.
That is all for today's press conference.
[Episode 15]
Wow, Ji Ah. Thank you.
Thank you for not doing anything!
- Ji Ah did so much by doing nothing!
- She did.
But why do I feel so weird?
We were so worried that we couldn't
reach you and Manager Jung.
By the way, are you sure
Tae Ho was caught?
Why do you keep asking? Are you sad?
Why would I be sad?
I just can't believe it.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
were both caught
so starting tomorrow, you must take over
Legend Entertainment, Deputy CEO Tae.
- I'm leaving.
- Hey, I didn't want this position.
And why is it my responsibility?
Now that CEO Hwang has woken up,
he should take responsibility for it.
Isn't that right, CEO Hwang?
Joon Oh, a guy like this can't be a spy.
He should be the spy.
He was such a great actor, that I thought
he was on Jang Do Pal's side.
Hey, you really don't get me.
Do you know how difficult it was?
I'm not so sure.
I wish every day was like this.
I'm a little anxious because too many
good things are happening at once.
Hey, you don't have to be anxious.
We still have one important thing
left to do.
Clearing the false charges
against Joon Oh?
Joon Oh, don't worry.
This time, we will tell the truth,
and prepare a red carpet for you
so you can walk on it with light feet.
Should I dress up for this?
Prepare something for me.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm a lawyer from Choi In Park Law Firm.
Legend Entertainment's lawyer
is already working for Jang Do Pal
which is why Tae Ho found another
lawyer. He's looking for a way out.
We must tie him to the conspiracy.
And make sure Choi Tae Ho
doesn't get off.
Of course.
What are you going in here?
What? Am I not allowed to be here?
You're not affiliated with us anymore and
this case isn't under your jurisdiction.
You're overstepping your authority
by acting like this.
Think whatever you like.
But you'd better start investigating
the witnesses' statements tomorrow.
What about Seo Joon Oh?
- I need to see Seo Joon Oh first.
- Get the statements first.
Seo Joon Oh needs to come in
before I collect their statements.
When is Seo Joon Oh coming?
After you carry out the statement
investigation in a reasonable manner--
Reasonable? How can you talk so
carelessly as a man in the same field?
We only halted his indictment
because Seo Joon Oh wasn't here.
We'll start once he shows up!
That's why...
You'd better tell Seo Joon Oh to show up.
You don't think the stay of proceedings
on Seo Joon Oh's case
was without a reason, do you?
You will also be charged
with concealing a criminal.
You shouldn't demand it so confidently.
I dare you.
You have more to lose than I do,
so I have nothing to fear anymore.
You said you'll investigate properly
so lock up Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho.
You'll have to act properly
now that so many people are watching.
- Lawyer Jo.
- Yes.
Here is the evidence for Hwang Jae Gook's
incident. It's someone under Jang Do Pal
but Choi Tae Ho was involved
in this incident as well.
Please keep that in mind.
Let's go.
[Hwang Jae Gook
Murder Instigation Evidence]
Geez, what was our relationship
in our past lives
that we got involved in two cases?
Two murder cases.
You talked with your lawyer for a while.
What did you conclude?
Jang Do Pal has been
consistently playing dumb.
He's the real criminal,
so of course he has nothing to say.
And what about you?
Prosecutor,
I know this is a lot to ask...
but can I see CEO Jang?
Why would I let you do that?
Are you going to see your accomplice
and plot something else?
I want to reduce your workload.
So please let me see him, just once.
Wow, Yoon Tae Young
has really done it this time.
I shouldn't have played along.
Isn't he a prosecutor too?
How could he do this to his own family?
Listen well. Nothing has changed.
Our investigation was fair,
and the criminal is Seo Joon Oh.
- Defend our side.
- Yes.
Yoon Tae Young, that bastard.
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
We're in front of Bong Hee's house.
But there are many police officers here.
I know it'll be uncomfortable,
but hide out for a few days.
Lee Jae Joon is desperately
trying to find you.
But you can't go in until
Choi Tae Ho is locked up for good.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
were really caught, right?
Yes, you can sleep comfortably tonight.
How can I sleep comfortably
when I'm in hiding? Okay, I'll try.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey, we predicted this would happen.
We should hide so they can't see us.
Why? You don't have to suffer with me.
You can go inside and rest.
Again? You told me to stay by your side,
yet you want me to go home alone?
Hey, why do we both have to suffer?
It's better that you rest well.
What if you were me?
Would you go home alone?
Of course not.
I'm too responsible to do that.
See? I would feel uncomfortable
either way, so there's no difference.
We've come this far,
let's suffer for a little bit longer.
And, you'd be really bored without me.
I know, but I don't want
everyone to suffer because of me.
- Enough!
- Son of a bitch?
- Enough! Enough! Enough!
Enough. Enough. Stop saying weird things
and just cheer up.
Okay?
- Cheer up! Okay?
- Geez.
- Huh?
- Okay. Geez.
Let's do this!
Yeah. Yeah, Reporter Park.
Let's not do this
before the election, okay?
No, don't do that. Not again!
You should know better than to do that!
Wait, I have another call. Wait!
Hello? I told you
it wasn't Congresswoman Jo!
No, who told you that?
It's not true. I'm hanging up.
Hello? Let's talk about this
over dinner sometime. Yes.
Yes, talk to you later.
- Can't you put the phones on vibrate?
- I apologize.
What time is it?
Why hasn't Ji Ah come out yet?
Ki Joon, let's go.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
You're a wanted criminal.
What? Joon Oh is a wanted criminal?
- Hey, you really didn't know that?
- I didn't.
Jae Hyun's case is solved,
but is So Hee's case solved?
It's not solved yet? I'm not sure.
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
Did you say Jang Do Pal
went to find you in China?
He didn't come to find us.
He came to attack us.
He bribed the hospital,
and at first, he tried to kill us.
That was when Ki Joon and I were
being treated at a Chinese hospital.
Choi Tae Ho came
with Chinese gangsters...
They cornered us and attacked us.
And I found out later on...
that he told Ki Joon that he'd let us go
if we said Seo Joon Oh killed So Hee.
- Ji Ah!
- Ji Ah.
How did it go? Was it okay?
Well, he took my statement...
- You don't have to be nervous.
- Really?
- Okay, I'll be back.
- Good luck!
I'll be back too! Don't worry about us!
Don't be nervous.
- See you!
- Yup!
Wow, that's a relief. It sounds like
Prosecutor Yoon pressed them hard enough.
I know.
Joon Oh, something was weird though.
What?
Near the end,
he asked me some weird questions.
It was because of CEO Hwang.
I wanted to save CEO Hwang.
If I didn't do as he told me,
he was going to kill me.
You saw it too!
You saw Seo Joon Oh kill her.
That's why I had no choice.
I tried to tell the truth a few times...
Like when I saw So Hee's dead body.
I was going to tell the truth,
but I was kidnapped by Tae Ho.
Prosecutor Yoon,
I know it's hard to believe
but I did it because I was scared.
Tae Ho is a really scary guy.
He's even scarier when he's angry.
He's already tall, but when he's angry,
his eyes pop out...
When we were on the boat,
he was covered in blood and he laughed.
He was so scary!
He's a total psychopath.
You have no idea what he'll do next!
That's why I'm begging you.
Please lock him up this time.
But Tae Ho Hang.
Didn't you become the deputy CEO
because of that psychopath?
Pardon?
It's true.
If I just focus on your statement,
you're a poor victim.
But it's not like that on paper.
Unless you're doing this because you're
not satisfied with your current salary.
Pardon?
I thought it was over
but that's when the look
in his eyes changed.
Ha Ji Ah, you're exactly how
the media portrayed you to be.
You're very refreshing. You don't
seem like the type to take threats.
Well, does anyone have a choice?
No, I just feel bad for you
because I'm such a big fan.
Geez, but your mother
took a lot of money
from your down payment at the company.
How much did she take?
Why are you asking me that?
I'm just asking to verify,
but you don't have to answer.
For someone who was threatened,
you received quite a large sum of money.
What do you mean by that?
Did you really lose your memory?
The doctor said you regained
all of your memory.
Did you pretend not to remember
to hide Seo Joon Oh?
- Prosecutor Lee--
- I heard you're dating. Is that true?
Did you start on the island,
or did you start during your escape?
Is it Stockholm syndrome?
Prosecutor Lee, what are you saying?
Where is Seo Joon Oh?
Where is he?
It sounds like he understood our
tendencies and made a surprise attack.
Why is it so hard to contact you?
- How is it going?
- Which side are you curious about?
Are you curious about the statements,
or about Choi Tae Ho and Jang Do Pal?
Both.
Jang Do Pal and Choi Tae Ho
are meeting right now.
What? What reason do they have to meet?
Choi Tae Ho asked to see him.
Choi Tae Ho?
CEO Jang.
When you said you'd save me...
is that offer still valid?
What do you mean?
Can you ask that now?
When you cast me for Dreamers,
this is what you told me.
You said if you had to choose one person
to help, you would choose me.
Isn't that why you helped me
with Jae Hyun's incident too?
Yeah. That's what I said.
Please save me one more time.
My lawyer told me I can get out.
If you give me a push, that is.
Let's close our eyes,
and send you off in one shot.
Sa... Save me...
Let's send you off in one shot!
In one shot!
Choi Tae Ho,
you don't talk very much.
Pardon?
Oh, yes.
It sounds like you were threatened too.
You understand.
If that's how it sounds to me,
other people will hear the same thing.
I'll leave first,
so I can try to get you out.
If we both want to live,
one of us needs to get out.
I'll leave first,
and make sure to get you out.
You know I'm the only person
who can help you.
That's how we survived this long.
Am I wrong?
They're trying to pressure
the people around you to catch you
but you can't let their
psychological warfare get to you.
Then they'll end up
getting what they want.
We're doomed.
Did you hear that?
Since the statement,
she hasn't said a word.
I wonder if something happened in there.
Nothing happened.
I gave my statement and got out.
But your expression says otherwise.
Ji Ah and Ho Hang didn't feel good
about it either, but it's nothing big.
You have to tough it out,
Bong Hee and Seo Joon Oh.
What about Tae Ho? He's in prison, right?
They'll probably put him in jail tonight,
since they can't hold him forever.
I'll call you back after I check
if anything has changed with those two.
Bong Hee, I wore a turtleneck today,
but it doesn't sting. Touch it.
It's dangerous. Sit properly.
Look straight ahead.
Choi Tae Ho just got out.
We will change our plans starting now.
Fine. Then there's something
you need to do for me.
What is it?
The lawyer said if I'm charged for
instigating Hwang Jae Gook's murder too
I'll have to do 20 laps in here.
You can take care of that, right?
Prosecutor Yoon has
Lee Jae Joon's evidence
for Hwang Jae Gook's incident.
We don't have time.
Who are you?
Stop! Stop!
You have to get rid of that punk
and put out the last embers.
You can do that, right?
I'll do that as soon as I get out.
And as for your sentence...
I'll do whatever I can to shorten it.
- Seo Joon Oh, it's okay.
- But I'm not okay.
No, I feel stuffy and uncomfortable.
I feel uncomfortable too!
I'm not doing it just for you. It's cold.
Hey, if you refuse, your contract
as my stylist will be terminated, got it?
We don't need a contract.
Because you keep acting like this,
I'm constantly careful with you
and because I'm always watching out,
I end up feeling insignificant.
Do you want your artist to feel that way?
Is that what you want?
Should I feel insignificant and small?
What did I do to make you feel that way?
That's why I want you to lighten up.
Hey, I think of you as someone who's like
my voice when I talk to myself.
But because you're not talking,
I feel alone even when I'm with you.
What does that mean?
I'm your voice when you talk to yourself?
I'm sure you're frustrated too.
I know you're having a hard time.
If it were anyone else,
they wouldn't have survived a single day.
Only you could have gotten through it
and I got through it because of you.
That's why I'm thankful to you.
I don't deserve any of this
but you trusted me,
and stayed by my side...
and looked out for me.
I feel burdened
now that you've told me that.
I'm okay. Really. Don't worry.
Okay. Then to celebrate that you're okay
here's a new lipstick color.
Pardon?
Oh, it's Prosecutor Yoon.
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
Why didn't you come here yourself?
Why do you sound like that?
Is something the matter?
Something went wrong.
Choi Tae Ho got out.
Hide out somewhere
until things settle down.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go.
Should I congratulate you?
You're finally free.
- It was all thanks to you.
- What will you do now?
Are you going to cause trouble again?
No.
I will live quietly.
Can I trust you?
This time, you managed to get out...
but this can always
come back to bite you in the future.
But I'm sure you know better than I do.
Keep yourself under control. Okay?
Jang Do Pal confessed
that he committed the crime alone.
And Choi Tae Ho...
said he did what he was told to do
because he was threatened.
Wait...
What does... What does that mean?
After what Tae Ho did...
Are Jang Do Pal and the prosecution
out of their minds?
Lee Jae Joon helped,
and the prosecutor...
is refusing to change their words
by declaring a war.
I'll send you the documents...
so write a nice article for me.
[The First Survivor, Ra Bong Hee Is Being
Charged For Conspiracy To Commit Murder?]
- Yeah, Mom.
- Yeah, Bong Hee.
Where are you right now?
Are you with that punk, by any chance?
Yeah.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Bong Hee, come back home.
Let's talk once you get here. Okay?
[The First Survivor, Ra Bong Hee Is Being
Charged For Conspiracy To Commit Murder?]
What the hell is this?
Call the journalist and tell him to leave
the special investigation committee out!
Why do they keep targeting us?
But, I was thinking...
Don't you think making Ra Bong Hee
a culprit was too harsh?
- Even if we want to find Seo Joon Oh--
- We have no choice.
- Okay! Let's go!
- Let's give it our all!
- Let's do this!
Let's do this. Geez.
A few days ago, at the press conference
for the Legend Entertainment plane crash
the suspect for Yoon So Hee's death,
and Shin Jae Hyun's incident
was Choi Tae Ho.
However, he was just released,
and there's no evidence--
- Can you turn up the volume?
- Yes.
there is talk of whether or not there is
a need for an investigation.
Choi Tae Ho is receiving
many sympathy votes from the public
and is at his prime since his debut.
[Unknown Number]
- Joon Oh, it's Ki Joon!
- Yeah.
Hey, have you read the paper?
Wait, you don't read the paper.
What is it? What's going on
so early in the morning?
Is Bong Hee with you, by any chance?
Bong Hee's in trouble!
Look it up on the internet!
Okay, I'm hanging up.
I'm going to go home for a little while
because my mom isn't feeling well.
Don't worry too much,
and call me if anything happens.
[Disciplinary Action Notice]
I received the notice.
Then why aren't you packing?
I'll leave if I have to,
but I'm curious about something.
Regarding Yoon So Hee's murder
are you intending to carry out
a fake investigation?
What? This punk...
Prosecutor Yoon! I mean, Mr. Yoon.
- You are the one with plans.
- Me?
It just seems like you're trying to end
Choi Tae Ho, no matter what. Am I wrong?
You are the one who wants to target
Seo Joon Oh, so what are you saying?
And you let Choi Tae Ho go
for that reason.
Hey, Yoon Tae Young! You should
just leave quietly. What is all this?
Fake investigation? Is it fake
and targeted if it doesn't go your way?
Fine, I was ready to resign,
so I'm okay with leaving
but things won't go your way
just because I'm gone.
I will continue to use the skills
I learned here when I get out.
I will make things
very uncomfortable for you.
Wait, you little...
Geez, seriously.
[Real Time Searches - Seo Joon Oh
Concealment, Seo Joon Oh, Ra Bong Hee...]
[Seo Joon Oh's Concealment.
Why is Ra Bong Hee hiding him?]
It's just as you'd think. She looks like
someone who'd possess men.
How could she shamelessly roam around
after blaming our Tae Ho for murder?
If it were me, I'd just stay at home.
Figures, if that were true, she wouldn't
have done this in the first place.
I mean, how could she dare
to mess around with our Tae Ho?
Shouldn't we report her?
Are they offering a reward?
A reward? I wonder.
Who is that little thing?
- Wasn't that girl on the news?
- You mean that murder case?
- Yeah. Yeah. Seo Joon Oh.
- Seo Joon Oh. Seo Joon Oh.
Really?
Geez, isn't it nice
to get some fresh air?
CEO Hwang, should we go back?
CEO Hwang, we're being monitored,
aren't we?
Joon Oh?
We're being watched
because of Joon Oh? Geez.
What will Joon Oh do?
CEO Hwang, let's go to the washroom
and hide out for a little bit.
Let's go.
I feel like someone's following us.
- Should we stop contacting Joon Oh?
- Maybe for the time being.
Yeah, Ki Joon. Yeah, Bong Hee went home.
No, it'll probably be safer
than staying with me.
That's right. You and Bong Hee
are better off being apart right now.
Ki Joon. I'll call you back later.
Isn't that Seo Joon Oh?
He wouldn't roam around
in the middle of the day.
That's right. I heard a small girl
was his accomplice.
- Who?
- If I knew, would I be asking you?
[Get lost!]
[Murderer!]
[You should have died on the island!]
- Hey!
- Stop it!
What? Am I wrong?
Your daughter fell for a murderer
and is running amuck
because she has no fear! Isn't that true?
Hey! You... How dare you?
I should have stitched up your mouth
instead of pouring the soy sauce on you!
Gosh!
Wait! Wait! I didn't do anything! No!
I fell for it once,
so I won't fall for it again!
I said I didn't do anything!
Hey, why did you have
to pop out of nowhere?
Get out of here! You wenches!
How could you do this to my daughter?
Mom.
You've been having a hard time
because of me, haven't you?
Are you mad?
Hey.
It looks like you're really mad.
Forgive me, okay?
Gosh. You frustrating
and foolish teddy bear...
Do you know how scary it is
to be branded by other people?
How did this happen?
No, Mom.
This will pass like a storm.
It will pass.
When it's over,
everyone will find out the truth.
They'll find out
Seo Joon Oh and I... are innocent.
Where did your stubbornness come from?
I'm the daughter
of a strong woman with a kind heart.
I take after you.
Mom. I'm hungry.
I haven't eaten a single meal.
How about we mix your warm rice
with red pepper paste and vegetables?
- Can you eat at a time like this?
- Yeah.
Now that we're here,
let's give it our all until the end.
Tell that punk for me.
If he doesn't settle this properly,
I'll scold him terribly.
Seo Joon Oh is very grateful to you.
Whatever.
- Mom, where are you going?
- How many spoonfuls of red pepper paste?
Three spoonfuls!
I went to visit Jang Do Pal yesterday
but I couldn't see him.
When I asked, they said
he hasn't seen anyone yet.
Why? Is he afraid he'll be swayed?
Maybe. It's probably because
he has a lot to think about
after letting Choi Tae Ho go free.
It'll be hard to visit him
until Choi Tae Ho makes a move.
We have a lot of time now.
Let's try to get both of them.
Do you think you can find a way?
There's nothing we can't do.
The hard part is to endure it until then.
Let's show them that's it's possible
for David to take down Goliath.
Hey, why weren't you picking up all day?
You scared me.
How did you pick up before it even rang?
Hey, I called you so many times.
Don't you check your phone?
You did?
Is everything all right at home?
I guess you read the news.
I'm okay, Seo Joon Oh.
Yeah right.
Tell your mother...
that I'll apologize to her personally
after I settle things in Seoul.
You don't need to worry about that.
Instead of worrying about that...
make sure you stay well hidden.
Hey, I'm hiding. Don't worry about me.
I'm just worried about you.
I'm doing fine too,
so don't worry about me either.
I'll go back to Seoul tomorrow.
Hey, why so soon? Stay there for
a little longer. You'll only suffer here.
But you're so bored without me.
Yeah, that's true.
I'll go back tomorrow.
- Bong Hee.
- Yes?
Come back soon.
Yes.
[You should have died on the island.]
- Bong Hee?
- Yeah, Mom.
Wait, what about food?
It's okay, Mom. I'm not hungry.
You have to eat
if you want to get anything done.
Bong Hee.
Are you confident
you can trust him until the end?
Mom.
If you want to trust and cheer
for someone other than yourself
you have to be stronger yourself.
Can you do that?
Mom.
Why are you so faint of heart?
Thank you, Mom.
Thank you.
Come here.
Me... Me?
- You have your phone, right?
- Yes, I do.
Hand it over.
Yeah, Byung Joo.
It's me, Joon Oh.
Huh? I don't remember
having a friend like you.
Why did you call me?
We used to call each other often.
- Things sure have changed a lot.
- What bullshit.
Hey, I don't want to hear your voice. I'm
hanging up if you don't get to the point.
Joon Oh.
I didn't want to push it this far either.
I'm human too. It hurts me
seeing you become more pathetic.
That's why you should just give up.
You have to give up for the people
around you to live in peace.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
Sir! Sir!
We're in trouble!
I found Ra Bong Hee.
She's on her way to Seoul.
Yes. Bring her here
as soon as she arrives.
They issued an arrest warrant
for Ra Bong Hee.
It seems like Lee Jae Joon
is finally lashing out.
[Prosecutor Yoon]
She's not answering.
I think she's on her way.
But Ra Bong Hee doesn't know anything.
Shouldn't we go and find her?
What are you planning to do?
They're doing this to draw you out.
I know. But how can I sit back
and do nothing?
Don't do this.
- Let's think about this--
- What is there to think about?
Bong Hee did nothing wrong,
but she's going to be arrested, so...
I need to prevent this from happening.
[Prosecutor Yoon]
Is Bong Hee still not answering?
Sir, I'll look for Seo Joon Oh.
Wait, excuse me! Wait a minute.
Here.
Oh.
Yes, thank you.
[Prosecutor Yoon]
Ra Bong Hee!
Why are you doing this?
Where are we going? Let go of me!
- I told you to let go!
- Let's talk when we get there.
Let go of me! Why are you doing this?
- Let's go.
- Who are you?
Let her go for now. Attract attention
and you'll be caught too.
Get out of our way!
Control yourself! If you
butt in now, you'll both be caught.
You won't be able to help her!
If you want to save her,
you have to be patient.
Let's get out of here
before a bigger problem arises.
I'll ask Byung Joo to take your car.
We have to be very careful right now.
It'll be problematic if you get caught.
What happens now?
Now that Bong Hee has been taken...
what happens now?
When she see Lee Jae Joon,
he'll ask her for your location.
He'll try to make a deal with her.
He'll tell her that he'll let her go
if she tells him where you are.
And he'll ask her where you are.
Repeatedly, until she talks.
He has to harass Bong Hee
if he wants to catch you.
He'll drag it out...
until the person looking in
turns himself in.
Where is Seo Joon Oh?
I don't know.
This will only make it
worse for you.
You should talk, Ra Bong Hee.
You can leave if you just tell me
where Seo Joon Oh is.
Are you really going to act like this?
Fine. Let's wait and see who wins.
Are you serious?
Yes.
No matter how much I think about it,
this isn't right.
I don't think I can do this any longer.
You may leave.
What's going on?
Why was I released, Prosecutor Yoon?
It was a choice Seo Joon Oh made.
I can't let this happen, Prosecutor Yoon.
I can't.
Even if you think I'm crazy,
I have no choice.
There's only one way.
I'll turn myself in.
Wow, Seo Joon Oh.
It's so hard to see your face.
Since you came here yourself,
let's make a masterpiece together.
You should have stopped him.
You were the one who didn't want
the prosecution to be involved.
Yet you just let him go?
If he went there without a plan,
it'll be over for him. What do we do?
Seo Joon Oh. Look here.
How many hours has it been?
You have only told us your name.
Why aren't you answering my questions?
Didn't you come here to cooperate?
Geez, seriously.
- Still?
- Yes.
It's been six hours.
What does he think he's doing?
What is that bastard doing? Look at this.
[Water.]
He's a total nutjob.
First, don't say anything.
Don't give them any reaction,
no matter what they do.
They will talk to you.
You had a fun time with your food.
Are you full?
Let's be quick about this.
What was your motive
for killing Yoon So Hee?
I heard Yoon So Hee
called you a murderer. Is that true?
You're going to keep doing this?
When will you stop?
You walked in here
on your own two feet.
So why aren't you talking?
Dragging it out won't make it
better for you!
Do you think this will stop me
from putting you behind bars?
What is it that you want?
Why aren't you talking?
At this point, you will say one thing.
The most tempting proposal
to Lee Jae Joon's ears.
I'll start talking.
If you do me a favor.
A favor?
Jang Do Pal. Let me see him.
Why do you want to see him?
If I let you see him,
what will I get out of it?
There's only one thing you want,
isn't there? Who knows?
If you let me see him, I might...
do you a favor in return.
For Lee Jae Joon, nothing is
more important than your confession
so he'll let you see Jang Do Pal
at least once.
You ordered him to kill
Hwang Jae Gook, didn't you?
Where did you hide him?
The guy who tried to kill him!
Talk!
Jang Do Pal will feel a lot of pressure.
The prosecution is doing everything
they can to find his associate.
Where are we going?
If that guy is caught, Hwang Jae Gook's
case will come into the light as well
which means he'll spend
the rest of his years in jail.
But Jang Do Pal shut his mouth
and is refusing to say anything.
What could that mean?
That means he put his trust in someone.
It can only be Choi Tae Ho,
who left under an agreement.
He agreed to take care of it instead.
Then...
that means I need to split those two up?
It's your job to win Jang Do Pal
over to our side.
We're not certain of anything.
That's why it won't be easy.
Geez, what is that on your head?
- You look good.
- Why did you want to see me?
Do you think it'll be okay
to leave them alone like this?
Turn up the volume.
Have you been doing well?
I feel at ease because
I have nothing to worry about.
It's more like you're generous.
You've even in jail for Tae Ho.
If...
If you're trying to
get something out of me--
What about Tae Ho?
Does he come to visit you?
Do you know what Tae Ho
has been doing out there?
- Do I have to know that?
- Geez, of course you should.
You should be curious if you confessed
to a crime in return for a favor.
But do you think Tae Ho
will do you that favor?
Even if you're willing
to get your hands dirty for Tae Ho
Tae Ho would never do that for you.
It seems like he already
forgot about your favor.
I'm not sure what you're saying.
I never asked for a favor--
But CEO Hwang...
can speak now.
So? What do you want me
to do about it?
I don't know why I'm listening to this.
What is he doing?
- Do you trust Choi Tae Ho that much?
- Let go!
- Get out there! Hurry!
- Yes!
- What is this bastard doing?
- Open the door!
Hurry up and open it!
Subtitles by DramaFever