Subtitles by DramaFever
I'm the co-pilot. The co-pilot.
- Hey, Tae Ho!
- Yeah, I'm over here!
- Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
- Do you want to live?
If you want to live, listen to me.
I don't know about those people,
but I can save you, okay?
I can help you get out of here!
What the hell are you saying?
There's a lifeboat on a beach nearby.
- A lifeboat?
- But...
The boat can only hold four people.
That's why I was watching you guys.
I was looking for people
to escape this island with.
Two people.
You're saying we just need
two more people, right?
Isn't that Tae Ho?
- Hey, seriously!
- What the heck?
- Where were you?
- Wow, seriously.
You should have said something
before leaving!
Let's go together next time, okay?
You're a top star!
Take care of yourself...
Let's go together next time.
It's dangerous, okay?
[Episode 5]
Who do you have in mind?
People who can be of help to us,
of course.
So Hee, here's your snack. Enjoy.
We have to exclude people who think
we all need to survive together.
- Joon Oh! Have some chocolate!
- No weak-hearted people...
And we must exclude people
we can't understand...
- Tae Ho.
- Oh. Thanks.
Sure.
How are you feeling?
Geez, you're still pale.
It's okay.
It's something I have to live with.
I have Ki Joon. I have my boyfriend too.
Eat.
No physically weak people...
Okay.
Here I go... Damn it!
- You stepped on it three times.
- The chocolate?
- The chocolate touched it. So--
- Hey, no!
Joon Oh.
- You stepped on it!
- Hey, Joon Oh!
We can step on that part! If you pass
half of it, the lines don't matter!
You have 10 seconds to go or stay.
- If I take one off...
- No one who is full of themselves...
No, in hopscotch, you have to speak
correctly, and stay off the lines.
- No one who thinks they're all that...
- Did you speak correctly or not?
Someone who is appropriately dirty,
and appropriately selfish.
Someone who cares about their own safety
more than anyone else.
CEO Hwang.
Can we talk for a moment?
Right now?
Don't you think someone like that
will be helpful to us?
Really?
Yes. I'm certain.
So the man that you followed...
was our co-pilot.
And he has a lifeboat,
but it's only for four people?
- Yes.
- Really?
How many times do I have to tell you?
You, me, and the co-pilot...
Who's the fourth person?
Well, for now...
I'm thinking about Secretary Tae...
But if you can decide for us--
I want to go too.
So Hee, what brings you here?
I'm not somewhere I'm not supposed to be.
I want to go too.
So Hee, I know how you feel...
But it's not that easy.
There's no guarantee that we'll live
if we get in the lifeboat...
And if one of us gets tired and
stops rowing, we could all die out there.
- So Hee, that's why--
- You want me to wait here?
And you'll get help if you get out?
- Yeah.
- Do you even know where we are?
You don't know. So how are you
going to get help?
- If we look, it's all possible--
- How can I trust you?
I saw what you did.
What did you see?
Do you want me to say it right now?
So Hee, what is it that you saw?
Okay, let's go, So Hee.
What did So Hee see?
Did you... record some kind of footage?
No.
Don't worry about it, CEO Hwang.
Anyway, we're going to leave
tomorrow, so please get ready.
Tae Ho.
Do you feel guilty?
Of course. We're leaving the kids here.
We'll send a rescue team for them.
You want to look for that person?
Yeah. I was unable
to catch him yesterday.
Why?
Why do you have to talk like that?
If there's another survivor,
we should find them.
That's not like you.
Is something going on?
Do we need a reason to save someone?
Okay, let's do it.
Let's start tomorrow at sunrise.
I stared at the fire for too long...
Rest well. You worked hard.
Everyone's here.
We have nine people,
so let's move in groups of three.
I'll...
go with CEO Hwang and So Hee.
Are you both okay with that?
- Yeah.
- You're okay with it, right?
- Sure, whatever you're comfortable with.
I'll go with Ra Bong Hee...
and Yeol.
Ki Joon, Secretary Tae, and Ji Ah.
Ki Joon, is that okay?
Yeah, I'm okay with it, but...
Will you be okay?
Why would it be a problem if my boyfriend
is going with other people too? Let's go.
We'll be back soon.
See you when we get back. Don't get hurt.
Okay, you too.
Don't forget to be back
before sunset. Let's go.
- Okay.
- This way.
- Hey, aren't you going?
- Yeah, we're going.
- Let's go CEO Hwang.
- Secretary Tae!
Take care of yourself. Stay healthy.
Okay, CEO Hwang.
- You look healthy enough to me.
- Stay healthy!
Let's go.
Is something the matter?
No, it's not that...
Then what's wrong?
I'm bothered by
what So Hee said yesterday.
Why? What did she say?
She told me to rest,
and that I worked hard.
Rest well. You worked hard.
But it felt like...
I wasn't going to see her again.
So Hee.
What did you see?
Do I have to say it?
We both know what I saw.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
If we get out of here, that is.
My younger sister died.
To be more exact, she was murdered.
When it came to my feelings...
I was sad at first,
but I calmed down over time.
I feel calm inside.
Am I weird?
No, not at all. That is understandable.
The same goes for physical wounds.
They heal slowly, over time.
No, I think you misunderstood me.
My wounds are not healed, they're getting
deeper. I think about it more and more.
The reason why I'm calm...
Is because I'm thinking about
what I should do when I meet her killer.
I'm wondering if I should
kill that person...
Or if I should put that person
through more pain...
I wonder if I should use a knife
to get my revenge...
Or if I should use handcuffs
for a public trial.
Let's go that way.
These are my thoughts.
Let me ask you again, Doctor.
Am I weird?
My younger sister's name was Yoon So Hee.
I'm Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young of the
western district prosecutor's office.
I've found the right place
for a consultation, right?
Regarding what's going on between
Chairwoman Jo, you, and Ra Bong Hee
and what you're hiding, I don't know
very much. That's why I came to find out.
Well, um... I don't know how I can help--
It seems like you've misunderstood.
I don't need your help.
All you have to do is go for lunch.
That's all you need to do.
You won't refuse, will you?
It's a prosecutor's request.
Well, um...
I'm trying to help you out right now.
The Republic of Korea
is a constitutional nation.
The attacker should be punished,
and the victim should be protected.
Concealing the truth is a crime.
But going for lunch isn't a crime, is it?
Which way
would you like to go, Doctor Kim?
Would you like to become
the attacker or the victim?
What will you choose?
[Treatment Records]
[Ra Bong Hee]
A necklace.
Do you remember who owns...
that necklace?
- Tae Ho!
- Yes?
I don't want to go.
You guys can go.
I want to stay with my kids.
- CEO Hwang.
- Go before I change my mind.
- CEO Hwang!
- Tae Ho.
If he tells the others, it'll get
complicated. We should go.
Is it okay if we have three people?
Let's hurry up and go
before they show up.
What? What is it?
Oh, I was wondering if this is So Hee's.
- Is it So Hee's necklace?
- Yes.
She said she lost it
in the woods not too long ago.
That's good. When we return later today--
- No, I should give it to her now.
- Right now?
I'm still bothered by what she said
yesterday, and she's having a hard time.
This will give her strength.
She won't think so negatively either.
Let's go.
Geez, seriously.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
- Hurry up!
- One, two, three! Lift!
CEO Hwang!
What are you doing here, CEO Hwang?
I've... sinned. I've done you wrong.
I'm sorry!
Geez, if you go into the ocean now,
you'll die!
- I didn't know, Punk!
- Wow, really...
So... So where did they go?
That way! Over there!
Joon Oh!
- Ki Joon, Tae Ho caused trouble!
- What?
Let's go.
Hey, don't get too pissed when you see
Tae Ho! You're still a patient!
Choi Tae Ho's dead.
- No!
- Hey!
- Tae Ho!
No!
What are you doing? Row! Like that.
No! Hey, you bastard! Choi Tae Ho!
- Tae Ho!, no! Get out! Hurry!
- No!
Get out! If you're
going to be like that, get out!
You can't go right now!
- Keep paddling!
- No! Stop!
Me too... Take me with you!
Secretary Tae!
Row already!
Hey! Hey, don't move!
- Secretary Tae!
- Let go! Let go!
- Hey, stop it!
- Let go! What are you doing?
What are you doing instead of rowing?
- I told you to stay still!
- Hey, seriously!
Geez, damn it!
- The boat!
- Damn it!
- Stay here...
- Choi Tae Ho!
- Joon Oh!
- No!
Take me with you!
- Ho Hang!
- Wait! Take me with you!
Come to your senses, you punk!
Geez, what do we do about our kids?
Hey, Tae Ho! Choi Tae Ho!
Wait! Hey!
Wait, no!
- Help...
- So Hee!
Tae Ho!
What the hell?
Who the hell are you,
and why did you faint?
Damn it!
Seo Joon Oh!
I...
I killed her...
I killed Yoon So Hee.
Seo Joon Oh!
[Prosecutor Yoon Tae Young]
Yes, Prosecutor Yoon.
I'm sorry. I had my reasons...
Did you... kill her?
My younger sister...
Yoon So Hee.
Did you kill her?
If you did...
If you...
If you really killed my sister...
I will put everything on the line
and send you to jail.
Pr... Prosecutor Yoon... I...
You'd better pray to the heavens...
Pray that it wasn't you who killed her.
We're over here! Over here!
We're over here! Over here...
We're over here! Please...
Over here!
Please... Please look over here...
We're over here!
Please...
Over here!
We're over here!
Please... Over here!
Jo... Joon Oh. Joon Oh!
Joon Oh's not there.
Joon Oh's not there. They're both female.
I don't think Joon Oh got out.
Hey, what the heck are you saying?
Let's save So Hee and Bong Hee
and then look for Joon Oh. Ki Joon!
How can we go in right now? We'll all
die if we go out in this weather!
I'm sorry, CEO Hwang.
I must have lost my mind.
Hey. Let's use this boat.
We have to save So Hee and Bong Hee.
Let's use this.
Oh, and also... Let's break up.
I can't date you anymore
because you're such an asshole.
Help me with this! Come on!
Go and help her.
Ki Joon, what are you doing over there?
No! Don't go out there!
You can't go out there right now!
It looks like they're coming to save us.
Over here!
So Hee. So Hee, do you see
Joon Oh over there?
- Do you see Joon Oh?
- Over here!
We're over here! Please! Over here!
Seo Joon Oh! Seo Joon Oh!
- Please... Please...
- Seo Joon Oh!
- Over here...
- Answer me, Seo Joon Oh!
Geez.
I told you not to go!
Why aren't you listening?
Let's abandon them.
This is more important.
So Hee, you saw, didn't you?
What happened to Seo Joon Oh?
Hurry up and answer me!
You already know...
what happened to Joon Oh.
Seo Joon Oh!
Tae Ho, what are you saying?
If we lose this boat...
we're all going to die here.
Let's abandon them.
We're more important.
How can you say such a thing?
Do you have the right to say that?
Let's talk about who has what right
after we survive!
Get out. You can't take this boat.
We can't do anything about
someone who's already dead.
Keep yourself alive.
How can you talk like that?
How did we get tangled up in this mess?
Whose fault is it
that Seo Joon Oh ended up like that?
- Are you crazy, you punk?
- I'm crazy? Am I the crazy one?
You're all crazier than I am.
It was hard to bring this boat back.
How can you take it back out after that?
Let's not do this. Let's save them first!
Then should we just die? Should we stick
our thumbs up our butts and die here?
Come to your senses, I'm begging you!
I'm the one who caught it
and stopped it from floating away.
If we take it out again and lose it,
we'll all die here.
Am I the only one
who wants to get off this island?
Am I the only one who wants to live?
Is it so wrong to do everything it takes
to live? I think you guys are weird!
Why are you so satisfied here?
We need to get out of here!
Don't you want to live?
Is it really living if I survive alone?
If I abandon everyone else...
If I leave them here...
If I run away so I can live,
is that really living?
Anyway, no one can take this boat!
If you want to save them,
swim or make a raft.
- Let go!
- Hey.
You son of a bitch.
There's nothing you won't say.
Were you always such garbage?
How dare you speak like that
to someone who has seniority?
- Seniority, my ass.
- Let go!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, are you crazy?
If you want to live, listen to me!
Stop thinking about yourselves!
I'll hold him down! Go!
Damn it!
- One! Two!
- One!
If something happened to Seo Joon Oh...
You and Choi Tae Ho...
I won't forgive either one of you.
What do you think
you're capable of doing?
Wait and see.
Wait and see what I'll do.
You son of a bitch.
You son of a bitch!
We need to survive too!
Wake up, you son of a bitch!
- One... Count like this!
- The waves are too strong!
- Count like this. One! Two!
- One.
One... I think we're moving forward!
No, we're not... Wait...
- Two! One!
- Hey, aren't we going backward?
No, what are you saying?
We're moving forward...
Tae Ho is pulling us back!
We're going backward!
- Hey!
- Tae Ho!
Hey!
This bastard put a hole in it!
When the waves calm down...
we'll fix the boat and get out of here.
If you want to live...
Listen to me.
- Damn it!
- That little...
Who does he think he is...
Well, what brings a prosecutor
from the western district
to my office?
I know we are both busy
with government affairs
so I'll make this short
and easy to comprehend.
I'm...
Yoon So Hee's older brother.
You know who Yoon So Hee is,
don't you, Chairwoman Jo?
Of course I know.
I really enjoyed her drama.
Yesterday...
I received a report saying
that a body was found in China.
Gosh, it's quite unfortunate.
That's comforting,
even if they're empty words.
We're people who make money
on empty words.
It's a relief that it was comforting.
Even while you know they're empty words.
Now that we've exchanged words
of blessing, let's talk about work.
I heard...
Ra Bong Hee confessed
to killing Yoon So Hee.
Is that true?
I see that you're not here for no reason.
How much do you know, Prosecutor Yoon?
I... killed her.
I killed Yoon So Hee.
This is all I know.
It looks like there isn't much
discrepancy in how much we know.
What source did you get that from?
One person's hand is not big enough
to conceal the sky.
No matter how much you try
to conceal the sky with your hand...
The sun will keep shining,
and the rain will fall.
The truth will be revealed.
How do you know if that's the truth?
They're just a few words said by
a hypnotized girl who lost her memory.
This can't be used as evidence.
You know that.
It looks like you're thinking
about that girl, quite a bit.
She's a survivor.
Isn't it our nation's obligation?
Our nation's obligation...
I don't think that term
was meant to be used like that.
In law, everything can be arbitrarily
interpreted, so interpret it as you wish.
Then...
What about...
the fact that you bribed people
to get your son into school
and illegally laundered money, using a
fake company under your husband's name?
Should I interpret that
arbitrarily as well?
You prepared a lot before coming here.
What is it that you want?
All you have to do
is what you were supposed to do.
Just as you saw it...
Just as you heard it...
Just as it is...
Announce all of it.
"A survivor returned,
but she lost her memory."
"The only thing she remembers
is that she killed someone."
"The victim of that murder
was the top star, Yoon So Hee?"
Are you intending to kill Ra Bong Hee
by making her into a murderer?
I'll say this. I think you are
continuing to misunderstand.
Please listen carefully.
As Chairwoman Jo of the special
investigation committee, you will inquire
and as Prosecutor Yoon of the western
district, I will investigate.
And the judgment of what
should be done with Ra Bong Hee...
will be made by the nation.
All you have to do is announce
what you found out.
I'll be the one to investigate.
Are you...
aware that I have seniority over you?
Of course. I know it very well.
I even listened to your lectures
at the training institute.
I'm just living the way you taught us to.
The way my brilliant instructor
told us to live.
I hope you act the way you taught us
to act back then, Ma'am.
Take care of yourself.
Wow... It must have been hard for you
to come all the way to China.
Wow, seriously.
The plane crashed, of all things
and we ended up on a deserted island.
I thought I was going to die. Seriously.
But it's such a relief that
you made it back alive, CEO Hwang.
But...
What happened on that island?
That girl, Ra Bong Hee, who was
Joon Oh's stylist made it out--
Ra Bong Hee, that girl?
- She's alive?
- Yes.
The special investigation team
is questioning her
but they don't know anything.
There are rumors
that she lost her memory.
She lost her memory? She can't remember
what happened on that island?
Yes, that's what they say.
But I'm not certain.
Wow, we were out in that blood bath,
but she can't remember it?
Wow, that can't be true. No way.
I don't know about anyone else,
but she should remember! She should.
CEO Hwang,
when the public safety guys arrive
you'll officially return to Korea
but we won't have time to talk
because you'll be questioned.
You're probably right.
- What about the company?
- It was crazy.
The crazed fans of our kids
are camping out at our company...
CEO Hwang, when you come back
and see everything...
But, anyway, CEO Hwang.
What really... happened on that island?
Please tell me about it, at least.
It'll be hard to see each other
when we return to Korea.
- Do Pal.
- Yes.
Do you think you can handle it?
I need to handle it.
This is our company we're talking about.
They won't come. Of course they won't.
If they were coming,
they would have come a long time ago.
They should have come for me!
Choi Tae Ho...
It's because of that bastard.
He's stopping all of them from coming!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you thinking of dying here?
What answer can I possibly
give you in this situation?
Should I curse with you?
It looks like we're going to die here.
It looks like we're going
to starve to death here!
We'll freeze to death
before that happens.
Hey.
If you're so scared of dying
why don't you care about
anyone else dying?
I've never met anyone
as selfish as you in my entire life.
You've been getting on my nerves
since we got here.
It's not only your life that's precious
and you're not the only one who's scared.
So stop whining.
I ended up like this
because I was trying to save you
and Seo Joon Oh...
Seo Joon Oh...
They'll be here soon.
They'll come to save us soon...
So don't be too anxious.
They're not coming to save us.
They can't! How can they? How can they
come when that bastard is stopping them?
They'll come. They will.
If we wait a little longer--
He killed a man.
Choi Tae Ho killed someone.
And I saw all of it.
I saw him kill someone else
just so he could live.
Hold on a little longer!
I... want to live...
Do you have anything in your bag?
Do you have any food?
I want to live...
Please...
You're going to die anyway.
You'll die no matter what.
I'm sorry.
Hey. Hey. Punk, be careful, seriously!
- I was just...
- Are you okay?
Yes.
Geez, you call yourself a man,
but you got beaten to a pulp.
You're badly hurt!
There's a first aid kit
in one of the suitcases.
I'll clean you up. You need it.
Give me the boat.
Where will you use a lifeboat
with a hole in it?
Even if you take it, it's of no use.
It's deflated.
Don't worry about that. We'll fix it
and use it, so hand it over.
- No.
- Hey, Choi Tae Ho!
Never mind. I'll just take it then.
Stop it already, seriously!
Hey!
That's enough. Okay? Stop it.
Ji Ah, are you okay? Huh?
- Stop it already! Stop it!
- Hey! What are you doing?
Wait, stop it. Stop it!
What are you people doing?
Stop it already!
- Wow, stop it already!
- That's enough!
Do you want to die? Do you?
- Do you--
- Hey!
What's wrong with you?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why are you making me out to be
the weird one? Let's survive together!
I don't want to die here!
I don't want to die here either, Punk!
None of us want to!
They don't want to die here!
- You're trying to survive on your own!
- Wow.
We should collect ourselves
at a time like this!
Tae Ho's right. Yes. He's right.
It's important that we survive!
Who cares about them?
If you think about it carefully,
Tae Ho is right. Yes.
Let's just forget about them,
and leave them to die!
Ki Joon.
I'm saying, let's leave them to die!
- Why are you winking?
- Ouch! Seriously!
Sand got in my eye!
Anyway, I completely agree with you!
Let's just go back to the hut.
Let's go back to the hut!
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Like Tae Ho said, let's go back,
and when the waves calm down
we'll come back later,
much later, to save them. For now...
Let's go back to the hut, okay?
- Hey, Manager Jung, you son of a--
- Yeah! I'm a dog! A dog! A dog!
I want them to die, so I'm a dog!
I have my reasons but none of you
understand me! I'm so annoyed!
Right, Tae Ho? Are you all right?
Geez, you're badly hurt!
There's a first aid kit back at the hut,
so I'll put some medicine on that, okay?
I'm sorry for hitting you earlier.
I think you're right.
We didn't think it through.
We... didn't... think it through!
It hurt a lot, didn't it?
It's okay. It's okay.
Let's go back to the hut and talk.
- You found something that pumps air?
- Yeah. An air pump.
I found it at the beach.
It seems like it came with the boat.
So what are you saying we should do?
First, Tae Ho can't find out,
so very carefully and slowly...
One person will move at a time.
While we live our daily lives,
we'll look for something to fix the hole.
As naturally as possible.
Where are you going?
I'm going to search for food.
That was good. Yeol, search in
the upper parts of the mountain.
There's no time,
so let's split up to search.
Ji Ah, you go first.
Go that way.
- I'll go get some water.
- Yeah, okay!
- Get lots!
- Okay.
Ji Ah, you were a little awkward.
You have to be more natural
so he doesn't catch on, okay?
Where should I look?
- Tae Ho isn't suspicious of me, so--
- Ki Joon, where are you going?
I'm going with Ji Ah because it could be
dangerous. Do you want to go?
I have stuff to do here.
Go with her, then. Go.
You can go.
Okay. You need more medicine.
I'll put more on for you later.
Bong Hee sacrificed herself...
to keep us alive.
When she was in pain,
she didn't even show it.
This time, let's help Bong Hee.
That's the right thing to do.
If we are human,
we should do that, don't you think?
That's why, even if it's hard, let's
push through it, and keep our strength.
That's the only way
we'll save Bong Hee...
and find Joon Oh.
Do you think Joon Oh is alive?
I once asked Joon Oh if he thought
other people were still alive.
Do you know what he said?
He said, we should hope they're alive.
He told me to hope.
Okay. Let's hope.
Yesterday, Yeol brought
the most materials back.
There were a lot,
but none of them were useful.
Ji Ah didn't bring anything back,
so it was also useless.
I hope we have a better day today
than we did yesterday.
- Airplane parts...
- There isn't much time.
Today will be another hard day,
but let's do our best today.
Why is this here?
I should bring something
so they don't scold me again.
- Did you find anything?
- Nothing.
- What about you?
- I found this.
- Where did you find this?
- I picked it up.
- Hey!
- Be quiet! Seriously...
Hey! Good job. Good job.
This is more than enough
to cover up that hole!
- Huh?
- Because this is rubber.
The boat is rubber too. We just
have to burn it, melt it, and attach it.
- How will it stick?
- Geez, never mind.
- Good job!
- Don't push me!
Hey, anyway,
two days have already passed.
If we wait any longer, it could
get dangerous for Bong Hee and So Hee
so let's hurry up.
Yeol, work on it tonight.
Okay.
When Yeol is finished, we'll depart
as soon as the sun rises.
- Before Tae Ho wakes up.
- Okay.
I'll go first, so get back
without being noticed, okay?
I'm leaving.
As Chairwoman Jo of the special
investigation committee, you will inquire
and as Prosecutor Yoon of
the western district, I will investigate.
And the judgment regarding
what should be done with Ra Bong Hee...
should be made by the nation.
Yeah, it's me.
Call in the reporters.
What for?
Um... Regarding the Legend Entertainment
private plane crash...
It's a special announcement.
That'll be enough, right?
Okay.
When we arrive, you will be transferred
to the public safety team.
Oh. Okay.
I took care of it without a doubt.
Okay. Okay, good work.
- This place is good.
- Thank you.
You should eat too.
Where are you going?
- You weren't sleeping?
- Where are you going?
- I'm getting some water.
- At night?
Yeah.
Okay.
Be careful.
They won't come to save us, will they?
They won't come.
If they were coming,
they would have come already.
We're...
going to die here.
This is so hard for me.
It's so cold...
Oh, that's right.
Where did she go?
So Hee!
I knew it.
You son of a bitch,
why didn't you listen?
You son of a bitch.
I said we need to survive.
We won't get out of here, we're going
to die here without that boat!
Do you want to die here?
Do you, you son of a bitch?
Ji Ah, it'll be okay.
Ji Ah. Ji Ah? Wait...
Oh... Wait...
Ki Joon!
You son of a bitch! You dumb bastard!
So Hee!
Yoon So Hee!
Stop it!
You son of a bitch.
You crazy bastard.
You son of a bitch!
Why do you keep making me
into the crazy one?
Why do you make me into
the crazy one, you son of a bitch?
Get up, you son of a bitch.
Get up, you bastard!
Get up.
Yeol.
No!
You can't, So Hee. No! No, don't do it!
Come back down with me.
They'll be here soon to save us.
Soon! They'll be here soon to save us!
So let's--
- They're no coming.
- No, they will! They will!
They'll be here soon
if we wait a little longer!
I'm sorry about not responding. I was
wrong. It was because I was scared too.
I was afraid too!
I did it because I was afraid Seo Joon Oh
is dead, and we'll both die too!
So... So come back down with me.
Forget it. You don't have
to answer me anymore.
- I'll go first--
- Wait! This!
This.
Your necklace. I found it!
I found the necklace your brother
gave you. You wanted to find this!
Wait, no. Yeol! Yeol!
Wait, no. No...
Yeol, wake up! Yeol!
No. No, wait a minute. Wait, Yeol.
Yeol, wake up. Yeol!
Yeol. Yeol, no! Yeol, wake up!
Geez, what do I do?
Yeol! Yeol!
Yeol! Wait! Wake up, you son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch...
Yeol!
On the 17th of last month,
Actress Yoon So Hee's body...
was found in Huizhou, China.
She was murdered.
Ra Bong Hee, who visited the island
to try to regain her memory...
said--
Um... They found another survivor.
Prosecutor Yoon.
I regained...
all of my memory.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Missing Nine]
- Does she remember if she killed her?
- Yes, she does.
Let's not doubt each other or fight.
What did you do to Yeol? Where is he?
Why are you all acting like this?
- It's not good to leave Tae Ho here.
- Then should I kill you?
Did you live together,
knowing she killed Yoon So Hee?
I said Yoon So Hee committed suicide
to cover up the murder.
They found another survivor. The survivor
is coming back to Korea right now!