Teacher
Let's go have a look
We'll come some other day
You're welcome
Let's go
Please... inside please...
Sir, please come in
Please
This way please
Please sit here. It is more comfortable
Can I get you something?
Bring me some Chinese food
Yes, Hsiao Wang, be quick
Yes
Hurry up there will you
Coming
Hsiao Hu, our restaurant's had
many new customers recently
Do you mean the Japanese?
Right, can't you see that your uncle
keeps smiling all days?
Will it be enough with five dishes
and a soup, sir?
That's okay, just make it more tasty
Alright...
Be quick
Yes...
Have some tea
How old are you?
Don't go, I want to talk with you
Let me go...
Sir, please show some respect
None of your business, I do what I like
You dare to beat me?
Sir, you are a gentleman
How come you bully a girl?
Mind your own business
or I'll kill you
Get out
What are you doing here?
Get out of here
You...
Hsiao Yu, go upstairs
Stop
Don't go too far
I am not an easy guy. Nakamura!
Beat him up
They're fighting outside
Stop it
Stop it, what's going on?
Damn it, get away
Dad
I'll see where you can go
Hsiao Yu, go upstairs
Out of my way
Sir, please stop. Can't we talk about it?
Alright...
She dares to hit me
Please excuse her. She is too young
Damn it
Dad...
Let's kill those Japanese
Damn it
Crawl
What? Crawl?
Crawl like a dog
Crawl
Hurry up
Be quick
I'll kick you until you crawl
Crawl
Right, crawl like a dog
Crawl...
Bark as a dog!
Bark? I don't know how
Shit, then I'll step on you
Hsiao Hu
Don't try to stir this matter up
Uncle, you better go inside
Don't get into this matter
Hey, you want to die?
Hsiao Hu... you...
I can't bear this
What? Damn it
Kill him
Yes
Hsiao Hu
Hsiao Hu, calm down
Listen to me, don't fight anymore
Go inside
Don't go
Hsiao Hu
Don't fight any more, get in
Listen to me, don't fight anymore
Damn it
All of you Japanese get out of here now
Hold it
You, kneel down
Kneel... down?
Yes, kneel
And crawl out of here
Crawl?
All of you kneel down and crawl out
Crawl
Hurry up
You too, crawl out here
Me too?
Crawl out
Hold it
Bark while you're crawling
I don't know How to bark
Bark like a dog
Woof...
Listen, we're not so easily bullied
Your dare to come back with a failure?
You brought shame to all Japanese
You couldn't even defeat a kid
Look at your faces
Musashi club won't be bullied so easily
You're all stupid fools
Who is the one who beat you?
He's a cook
You're all stupid fools
How can you all be defeated by a cook?
Teacher, we'll never make you
ashamed of us again
We must deal with him
Please... Come in
Please... Sit down... please...
Please...
Please
Sir, please sit down
Are you Mr. Lee?
Yes I am, please sir, have a seat
Who's that guy who came out
fighting yesterday?
Tell me
What's his name?
Lang Hsiao Hu
Lang Hsiao Hu?
Hsiao Hu...
Ask him to come out
He... has returned to his village
Don't fool me
He's really gone
For real
Go down there
Search around
Go
Get away
Where did he go, fatty?
I... I don't know
You don't know? Damn it
Sir, he's really not here
Tell me, did he really go back to
his village?
I wouldn't cheat you
Dad
Chief
We can't find him
I warn you...
If you want to run your business here
you better hand over Lang Hsiao Hu to me
or you'll be making a big mistake
Go
Be careful
Hurry up
Is it funny?
Yes...
Let's go and play
Hurry up
I want that one
Which one you want?
Alright
The swing
My father wants to close down
his business
Did you know that?
I've heard of it
I'm really sorry about that
it's my fault, I was causing all trouble
It's not all your fault
Since the Musashi club opened
those Japanese started to screw around here
They're too bad
You should be careful
Don't worry, I'm not afraid of them
Do you know that Chinese people
are not allowed to enter this park?
I know
The guards dare not interfere me
Why?
I've once fought with one of
the Japanese guards
You seem to like fighting very much
I only want to help the weak
What are you doing?
Get up
What do you want?
Get up, don't you hear me?
Hsiao Hu
Sister
What's the matter?
That bastard pulled her down when
she was playing on the swing
What did you call me?
I'm gonna mess you up
Don't hit the child
You dare to stop me?
You're not a man
Okay, watch me bust you up
Tell you what. It would only hurt you
Who would dare to?
Me
Listen, I'm the chief of the Musashi club
You've got the guts?
Dad
Wen Lan, take the children home
Let's go in advance
Dad... Stop it... Dad
Look over there. The chief is
fighting with someone
It's Lang Hsiao Hu. Go...
Dad
Stop it...
You're not Japanese, who let you in here?
This is our land, why can't I come in?
We Chinese aren't easy to bully
Goodbye
Hold it
Chase him
Stop
Dad
Stand still
Chase him
Our club has existed for 73 years
There wasn't ever any trouble
But after the Japanese came here
A lot of trouble aroused
Teacher, the fight in Shanghai restaurant
that happened a few days ago
was also caused by the Japanese
So I've heard
But it's disgraceful to learn Kung Fu
for fighting
I think they will be back
We should be careful
Contemplate rather than take action
You have to calm yourself up
Don't try to stir the trouble up
Yes, teacher
Mr. Lee
Mr. Kuroki
I'm not here to cause trouble
Tell me if Lang has come back here
Mr. Kuroki, it's my fault that
there was a fight
please excuse me
I'm not here for you
I want Lang Hsiao Hu only
He's so young and don't know any better
please forgive him
Never
I'll pay the medical fee for your men
please don't start any trouble again
Shut up
I won't let him get away
Mr. Kuroki...
I warn you, if you are hiding him
you won't have your restaurant here anymore
Damn it
Hsiao Hu
Uncle, why did you ask mercy from them?
If you beg them, they will scare you even more
What would you know? You've caused us big trouble
Hsiao Hu, it seems they won't forgive you
What shall we do now?
I refuse to fear them
I'd rather bust them at once
and drive them back to Japan
Chief, look over there
Hsiao Hu, good bye
Good bye
I'm going to see Brother Liu
Fine, See you later
OK.
Let's go
It's the cook of that restaurant
The one who beat us up
Yes
Isn't teacher here?
He went to the village
How's the business lately?
Not so good
Those Japanese come here often to cause trouble
Uncle wants to close the place down?
Didn't they come to look for you recently?
They've been here twice
You should be careful
Alright
Take care, I have to go now
Don't worry, I'll go by the side door
OK.
I'll come to see you tonight
What are you doing here?
Go
What are you doing?
Brother, the Japanese are here! Go quickly
Stop it
What do you want from me?
Where is Lang Hsiao Hu?
Ask him out at once
No one is called Lang Hsiao Hu here
Don't go too far
Shut up, get him out here now
He doesn't want to see you. Get out of here
Alright, you'll go out the same way he did
I'll sort you out one by one
Charge
Hsiao Hu
Hsiao Hu, something bad is happening
Those Japanese came back
There came to fight?
Where are they at?
The Chung Hua club
Brother, look
Stop it
Are you looking for me?
Why didn't you come to the restaurant then?
You really know how to play tricks
First you're here, and then you're there
What is it that you want from me?
Nonsense, I'll fix you real good
You Japanese are all devils. Come on then
Brother
More of them are coming
Charge
Hold it
Brother Liu, don't fight with them
Let me bust up those Japanese dogs instead
Fine
Kill him
Charge
Go... Quickly...
Can you still shove off the duty
in your club?
It's quite serious
I wasn't there yesterday
Maybe this wouldn't be happened
if I am here
No matter how
you've to hand out the murderer
Where does the murderer Lang hide?
I don't know where he has gone
In fact he just want to
protect himself
Don't try to side with him
You should be responsible for this
as a chairman
Mr. Man, don't you think over
that we Japanese won't forgive
this matter easily
I feel very sorry for this
Let me tell you
An eye for an eye
They are all inside
You better have some food first
I'm not hungry
You better eat some
I really can't take it
Up till now, it is no use of worrying
The most important is to
find a way out now
To escape, or go to surrender
I protected myself only
they can't say that I am a murderer
In fact, you're just protecting yourself
but they wouldn't be so reasonable
What did teacher say?
He was asked to the police station
this morning
He hasn't got back in afternoon
They're too harsh
I can't bear it no longer
Since the set up of Musashi Club
the Chung Hua Club opposite us
always try to defeat us
We're of the same society
We can't let them going on
especially Susumu and Kojirou
were killed
We can't bear it any longer
We, Japanese Empire
can't be insulted
We've to think of some ways to
destroy the Chung Hua
We came to China as we
want to be the King
We should fight for our country
Teacher, shall we challenge to
Chung Hua Club?
They can't compare with us
Right, the best fighter among them
has escaped far away to the mountain
If I find him, I would like to have
a fight with him
You're...?
Ask your chairman to come out
Tell him that I want to challenge him
challenge?
You are not qualified
to fight with him
If you look down on me, I'll kill you
You dare not to do it
Teacher
Are you chairman Man?
Yes, what can I do for you?
I'm Kuroki Tetsuo
I want to learn from you
Teacher, it's not they really want to
They want to stir up troubles here
You kid, let me kill you
Chief
Let me try
Thanks for coming, brother Liu
Recently the police of local and Japanese
keep their eyes on Teacher
Teacher wants to come to see you too
Don't worry
everything is going to be alright
It will be settled someday
I'm uncertain of my future
Then I better go somewhere far away
Hsiao Hu, you must be courageous
or turn yourself in
Don't be so hurry
What can we do now? Let our teacher
think about it
Hsiao Hu, take care, we've to go now
Fine, please ask about teacher
OK.
Goodbye
Where did you go to?
Why shall I tell you
I'm sure that you are going to see
the Murderer?
Brother, let's go
Stand still
You'll be killed for the revenge
Pull up
You kid, where can you go now?
You are all the dirty bastard
If I get kill, my brothers
will take the revenge
Shut up, I'll let you die peacefully
Brother Liu, I must take revenge for you
Hsiao hu, you must be calm down
Your teacher suffered a lot as
he didn't want you to be imprisoned
the Japanese consulate keeps on
pressing us
There're rumors in the newspaper
Maybe they'll arrest him
No, we won't let them do what they like
We've to oppose them
You shouldn't cause any trouble again
You better hide away for sometime
and don't go to stir trouble
Uncle, how long will you hide?
You...
I don't feel easy here
I can't even eat or sleep
In the night
it is only sounds of insects,
or keep on raining
I can bear any longer
You should overcome all hardships
It's not so hard to bear
for a young man
Of course I'm not afraid of
but I've to oppose to
their evil deeds
The ministry has a letter for Mr. Man
Say if he's offended again
the club must be closed
Hsiao Hu
I'll surrender after revenge
Cheers
No... I can't drink anymore
Don't try to run away
Come on...
You can't get me
Let me go
Give me a kiss
No
You're disgusting
Come on... let me help you to take off
your clothes
No...
Don't look at me
OK, I won't see...
Who is there?
Who? Speak up
It's me
Who are you?
Lang Hsiao Hu
You want to be killed?
Are you Mr. Kuroki?
Yes, you want to die?
Why did you kill my brother Liu
Go away
Men, come here
You're coward, Kuroki
You kid, you...
You...
Teacher, you see that
Stop it
Are you the murderer in
Chung Hua Club?
No, I'm the cook in Shanghai restaurant
You dare to intrude here
and kill my chief
He deserved it
Let me wrap you up
Let me see how skillful you are, come on
Charge
Hold it
Let me try
OK.
Mr. Takahashi, come on
Japanese are the puppies, isn't it?
You...
Right? Say it
Remember, Japanese are the puppies
I'll spare your life
Halt it, halt it...
Stop it
Don't fight any more
Teacher...
Sir
Sir...
Sir, we must take revenge for you
Sir
Sir...
Things are getting more serious
you should know it
The police keep their eyes at upon them
They pressed on your teacher to
hand you up
he'd rather get into prison
If we keep on fighting with them
we'll be finished
I've made a decision
What?
I don't want teacher to be implicated
I'll surrender to them tomorrow morning
What?
Surrender?
Hsiao Hu
It was caused by me
I'll take it by myself
Look before you leap and
let teacher to decide it
Please sit down, please
Sit down please
This letter is for you from the ministry
You shouldn't be too lenient to him
the case is getting serious
you've never thought of the consequence
It's impossible to move our club
and I can't restrain how
Lang Hsiao Hu acts
Why you put the responsibility on me?
Lang has been your student for ten years
You have great influence to his behavior
Although he was not at your club
he committed murder there
You can't say you've no responsibility
for that
Don't you know that the incident
was caused by the Japanese
They used to make troubles in
my restaurant
You should try to stop them
As you're backing him up
Maybe you've ordered him to kill
the Japanese
You've to give full evidence
Look clearly into the letter
First
you better hang Lang to the police
Second, you better move the club away
You must give me the answer
in these three days
It's here
Someone's coming
Go away quickly
Be quick
Where are they?
Wen Lan
Hsiao Hu
I thought that you've gone
Wen Lan, what have you brought
for him today?
I've brought a lot but none of your share
I can't take it
Brother
You guys take it
Are you okay?
I am not hungry
You'd better go away now... be quick
I...
Where can I go? I better fight with them
You...
Don't speak anymore, go quickly
Halt it...
Halt it, don't move
Don't try to escape
Don't try to get away, murderer
Go to catch the murderer first
Be quick, Hsiao Hu
You're finished
It should be you hell
Halt it...
Hsiao Hu
Where are you?
Wen Lan
Hsiao Hu
I've found you for several days
I am worrying of you
I am sorry, here is full of Japanese
I've to hide here
When can I stop hiding?
I decide to go north
I go with you
No, you can't bear the hard life
Stay here
Hsiao Hu, I don't want to leave you
I'm sorry
Listen to me
bring me some food tomorrow night
and also a quilted jacket, I wait for you
We lived happily in our childhood
I remembered, one night in the new year
we played the fire-crackers together
I've burnt your clothes
and I'd cried for that
my mother made three new clothes
for you
I still keep them
Really?
the life was so beautiful and happy
in the past
It's all over
What would it be in the future?
Only God knows
Let's go to that way
You see, inspector
There's some smoke
Have a look
Yes
Lang Hsiao Hu, wake up, it's dawn
Wen Lan, wake up
Excuse me, I'm a Japanese vice inspector
Yamaguchi Tstsuji
I come to bring you back
I won't go with you
Don't resort to violence
Come with me
Daydreaming
I've promised the commissioner
I'll hand you out when I've found you
I won't trust you that, let's go
Halt it
You ought to take the punishment
I'll surrender by myself
You better go with me
otherwise you'll be in trouble
Let's go
Wan Lan, go
Chase them
Quick
Hurry up...
Hurry up
I think you better come with me
I won't
Don't you want to be tortured
I won't let you go
Get back
Yes...
Wan Lan, you stay away
Do you think that I'll go with you?
Let's go
As they want to challenge us
we can't escape anymore
I'm afraid they play tricks
We have to win or we'll have to move
Losing our Chinese's face is
the most important thing
Teacher, seek help from Shandong uncle
then we'll be sure win
It's unnecessary
If we cannot win those Japanese
we should better shut down our club
you mean you agree to take challenge?
Self-strengthening?
We've no choice
We should be well-prepared
before the duel
We should be succeeded this time
Mr. Sasaki, I'm confident
to win over them
Mr. Yamamoto, do they accept the duel?
Yes...
What did they request for?
They want to make a stage in front
of the two clubs
and to fight in a openly and fairness way
without weapons
We've to show them
our strength this time
It'll be held five days later
Both invite three persons as the judges
Fine, we should grab the chance
to take revenge
for our chairman and first chief
and to destroy the Chung Hwa Club
Cheer up, Chung Hwa Club
Brother...
Is there any good fighters in China?
Hold it
Chairman, I've heard of you for long
Heard that you're the kungfu expert
in China
My pleasure
I want to learn from you
You're welcome, come on
Come on
Cheer up
How's going on?
Get away
I, on behalf of Japanese Karate Club,
challenge you
Fine, please
Cheer up
No
Don't play tricks
What do you want then?
I am the representative of
Chung Hwa Club
Who are you?
I'm Lang Hsiao Hu
Hsiao Hu
Teacher
You're the murderer
Take him, he's the murderer
Take him
Hold it
I'm not the murderer
You're the murderer, I've seen it
He is only self-defending
I've also seen it
Do you want to challenge me?
Right, I've heard that you're the
chief teacher of Karate
No matter how, let me try
Whatever win or lose
I'll go surrender
You think you'll still alive?
You...
Chairman, please accept my request
Alright
Thank you very much
Hsiao Hu, take care
Cheer up...
Teacher
Hsiao Hu
Tell you that our Chung Hua Club will
never fall down
Although you win, you're still
the murderer
I go to surrender now, okay?
Go
Teacher
Hsiao Hu
Don't worry
Take care, teacher
You too
I gotta go
Don't be sad, Wen Lan
Teacher, I've to go