[Seulgi]
Oh haessal nunbusin hangaron hyuil
It’s a sunny and relaxing holiday
[Seulgi]
Yeppeun saehayan wonpiseureul ipgo Oh Oh
I’m wearing my pretty, white dress
[Irene]
Nan jibeul naseotji kotnorae naoji
I left the house while humming
[Wendy]
Neon nareul barabwa neogseul neohgo tto bwa
You’re looking at me, staring at me
[Wendy]
Ni mameul sarojaba beorin geu sungan Oh
You’re looking at me, staring at me
[Yeri]
Tteollineun moksori ni mameun boksori
My trembling voice is like drums in your heart
[Joy]
Deo banjjagineun jungsoriga ulliji
The twinkling sound of a bell rings
Juseyo dalkomhan geu mat Ice Cream Cake
Please give me that sweet taste, ice cream cake
Teukbyeolhajin oneure oulineun maseuro
With a flavor that fits this special day
Ibgae mudeun Ice Creame
The ice cream that’s on my mouth
Ni gaseum dugeungeoryeo naege daga ogetjyo
Makes your heart pound and you’ll come to me
It’s So Tasty
Come And Chase Me
Mot chamgesseo
I can’t hold it in
I Scream, You Scream
Gimme That, Gimme That Ice Cream
[Wendy]
Oh Vanilla Chocolate Honey With A Cherry On Top
Maeil dayanghage boyeojulge neoegeman
I’ll show you different things every day, only to you
[Joy]
Mujigael geuryeodaeneun jeo bunsudae boda nan
More variety than the rainbow reflected in the fountain
[Joy]
Sarange geuryeonaeneun nege jom deo keullil geoya
I’ll be pulled even more by you, who draws out my love
[Seulgi]
Neon nareul derigo tteona eoseo tteona
Take me and go, hurry and go
[Seulgi]
Jogeuman seukuteoe taewobwa Oh nal
Put me on a small scooter
[Irene]
Uh ne heoril gamssaneun nae sone oneuri
My hands that wrap around your waist
[Yeri]
Da gado mami dugeundugeun georiji
Your heart will pound even after the day has passed
Juseyeo dalkomhan geu mat Ice Cream Cake
Please give me that sweet taste, ice cream cake
Teukbyeolhajin oneure oulineun maseuro
With a flavor that fits this special day
Ibgae mudeun Ice Creame
The ice cream that’s on my mouth
Ni gaseum dugeungeoryeo naege daga ogetjyo
Makes your heart pound and you’ll come to me
It’s So Tasty
Come And Chase Me
Mot chamgesseo
I can’t hold it in
I Scream, You Scream
Gimme That, Gimme That Ice Cream
Gimme That, Gimme That
[Irene]
Pops nae ibane noga naerineun jung
Pops, it’s melting in my mouth, Putting so much in
[Irene]
Jantteuk neoheo nae ibane noga naerineun jul
That it’ll feel like my mouth is melting down
[Irene]
Baby Boy dareun namjadeureun amogeotdo molla
Baby boy, other guys don’t know anything,
[Irene]
You’re So Fine haeseo an twineun otman golla
You’re so fine so only wear clothes That don’t make you stand out
[Joy]
Never Get Me Wrong My Boo
Never get me wrong my boo,
[Joy]
I Have No gwansim In That Bag
I have no interest in that bag
[Joy]
Jiruhan wolhwabuteo sumokkkaji Man I Wanna Pass
From boring Mon-Wed, Thurs Man I wanna pass
[Joy]
Nal boneun ne siseone See Some Good Vibe
Your look toward me, I see some good vibes
[Joy]
Gibeun joheun neukkimiya
when my eyes meet yours
[Joy]
Neowa nuni majuchineun sungan
It’s a good feeling
Gimme That, Gimme That, Gimme That
Ice Cream
Eoseoyo budeureoun geu mat Ice Cream Cake
Hurry and give me that soft taste, ice cream cake
Ojik neol gidarimyeo chotbureul kyeodulgeyo
I’ll light the candles as I only wait for you
Ttaseuhan mame Ice Cream Cake
In my warm heart, ice cream cake
Nogabeorigi jeone naege imachwojwoyo
Kiss me before it melts
It’s So Tasty
Come And Chase Me
Ni ibsuri
I’m closing my eyes
Dalkomhage nogayo naneun nuneul gamayo
Your lips are sweetly melting,
Dalkomhan geu mat Ice Cream Cake
That sweet taste, ice cream cake
Teukbyeolhajin oneure oulineun maseuro
With a flavor that fits this special day
Ibgae mudeun Ice Creame
The ice cream that’s on my mouth
Ni gaseum dugeungeoryeo naege daga ogetjyo
Makes your heart pound and you’ll come to me
It’s So Tasty
Come And Chase Me
Mot chamgesseo
I Scream, You Scream
Gimme That, Gimme That Ice Cream
Gimme that, Gimme That, Your Lips
Shrine