Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
Just before the F3 Debut
Gunma's Visited by the Black Devil's Hand
His style is getting
better every day!
I can barely believe ...
...he only started with the
Formula 3 just 10 days ago!
Yes!
But he drives too fast.
That's not very safe.
Speed isn't everything.
I know that
speed is not everything,
but I find his determination exhilarating.
He'll learn over time.
He reminds me of that time...
...when I tried it once in my life.
It was twenty years ago,
when I saw you drive, Kuroi!
That guy drives with the same
determination that you once drove with.
- Attack!
- Come on!
And now a toast to Gunma
and his debut in Formula 3!
- Cheers!
- Thank you, my friends!
I still can't believe that
you'll be entering Formula 3!
I thought it would
take at least six months ...
...for you to make it.
- It's all about skill and talent!
- You are a genius!
Well, soon enough
you'll all see what I'm made of.
After I win the races in
Formula 3 I'll head to Formula 1.
Monaco, Brazil ... All the
grand prizes will be mine!
You serious?
Sure! But what
about the train tickets?
Yes! Yasu decided to
reserve seats for everyone! First class!
Meanwhile, he and Kuroi will
bring the car to the circuit tonight!
Tomorrow we will all be there!
And as soon as we get there
, I will send the pass to enter!
So will you be rooting for me!
I need your support!
I will be cheering you on
like a young girl at a rock concert!
Really? I didn't know
you were young.
We won't be able to
make it, we've got work.
Yeah! Though I hope you win the race.
- You serious?
- Yes.
We can't stop
work even for a day.
- I really hope your kidding.
- We're not, Gunma!
Come on, guys!
Don't make a fuss!
You can't do this, you must
come and see me tomorrow!
Because I will be fighting
with Tamotsu and Hiziri.
I know...
it's because your jealous of me.
My friends, it will be a
fantastic race! Don't miss it!
- So you'll go?
- I told you, we have work!
Someone else can do your job!
Don't be a spoilsport
What! This is not
a job that ...
- ...I can just leave!
- What?
Hey, brat, don't
make such a fuss.
Your making too much noise.
Am I wrong or
do you want a drink?
You little shit!
Someone please stop them!
I won't show
you any mercy!
Sempai!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
You shouldn't have done that!
Stop that right now!
Hold it!
Cowards, where are
you going? Come back!
- Hold it right there!
- Hey, let me go!
- What are you doing? It was them!
- Shut up! Come with us!
What?!
- Come on, let's get to work.
- Oh, yeah.
If we do it now,
we can take a nap later!
I'll check the stock,
while you get the doors,
- ...and close the windows.
- Right.
What's that?
I wonder?
Come on, stop moving!
Why the hell
did the cops take me?
When I find those two,
I'll make them pay!
Your hurting me!
I hope this time
you've learned your lesson!
Lesson ?!
It wasn't my fault
It's not about
who is right or wrong!
If you got your way,
what do you think would happen?
I though you were a professional!
Yeah, but what
do you mean by that?
Help! This is Yasu!
We need help!
Get here quickly,
they are destroying everything!
Help, they've got me!
- Gunma!
- Sempai!
Smash it all!
Don't!
Why, just why?
They destroyed
everything for no reason!
What did we do wrong?
- Yasu!
- Gunma!
- Kuroi!
- Call an ambulance!
There is a phone booth
on the street corner!
- Quickly, go!
- Sure!
My Formula 3!
I can't believe it!
My Formula 3 is burning!
There's nothing
more we can do, Sempai!
Sempai, stop it!
Everything here is burning!
Let's go!
Sempai!
Stop it, sempai!
S-sempai!
Sempai.
- Everything's been destroyed!
- Gunma...!
- Are you alright, Kishida?
- Yes... I think.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
Did you see who did this?
Do you have any
idea who sent them?
Come on, you saw
their faces didn't you?
They came with bulldozers
and broke through the wall ...
Before we knew it
they were already inside!
We were not able
to look at their faces!
Where do you think your going?
Please don't scream,\M we are in the hospital!
What do we do now?
He didn't say a word!
And won't even eat!
I feel sorry for him!
He lost a unique opportunity!
I have never been in
agreement with Gunma's decisions.
I knew something was wrong.
Exactly! I don't know if
Kuroi was a legend or not,
but I never liked the guy.
Don't talk nonsense!
- Are you crazy?
- No! Gunma can no longer ...
"participate in the race
and you continue to play ...
- ... As if nothing had happened!
- Listen ...
Don't you remember that we
worked with him for a long time!
It's only natural that we forget
about what happened the other day.
Do you think that we...
...don't care. It's just that
Gunma is unlucky, get it!
Why should we cry
when it wasn't even our fault.
And we can't even
give him back his car!
Gunma a stubborn person!
He won't give up so easily!
Soon we will see
him leave. And we'll say, "Yo!"
And then we start over!
Watch where you throw the ball!
- Gunma!
- Sempai!
Hey, don't you want
a nice cup of tea?
- What?! He's not back yet?
- Yes!
We have received your reservation,
and all is in order.
Is that so...
Thank you.
I have dealt with them personally!
But the one who will
suffer most will be Gunma!
And listen up,
don't you dare cry for him.
My father was right when he said ...
...I was a fool to give you money!
And I was even more crazy ...
...when I asked you what you needed!
But you know, now I
understand all too well!
I swear that I'll never
make the same mistake twice.
You see, I discovered
an interesting thing!
The more you trust a person,
the more they will betray you.
That's the truth.
Yuki.
Please, Yuki, forget about
Gunma and live with me!
I need you!
Oh, Yuki, you don't know
how much I need you!
Yuki, I love you!
I love you!
I am willing to do anything for you!
Gunma Akagi
Gunma! I thought that
you would have raced in Formula 3!
Tamotsu! Try to concentrate
on todays race.
I must absolutely
win it and I don't need...
...you being distracted!
I need you.
Y-yes.
You shouldn't throw
away your ticket.
Well, I don't need it.
If things had gone
as they should have,
you'd be in the preliminaries!
I discussed this
affair with Kuroi and ...
And I'm afraid there
is no hope for our team!
- Eh?!
- Really?
What are you saying?
Can't we start over again!
Who are you kidding!
That's crazy!
It would take at least 500 million!
Then that's it! Just find a
sponsor and that's us!
You and your friend Kuroi,
at least owe me this, eh?
But why?
Try to understand, Gunma!
If we don't offer concrete results,
- nobody will sponsor us.
- Who cares about results!
If I drove,
I would have definitely won!
What's wrong with you, Gunma?
Don't you think I know that!
I've decided!
I'll race in Formula 3
...without your help!
Hiziri! You are the best!
Great job,
you're the strongest!
So, Kuroi, how are you?
You know, I continued to
call to get in touch,
...with our sponsors. They
might have been threatened like us.
Yes, it's possible!
Though...
Have you talked with
Gunma about our decision?
Of course I did.
He was furious!
- I thought as much.
- Though, I'm sorry.
- Kishida, are you hungry?
- Yeah,
- Would you like something to drink?
- Why not.
- Why don't we have a game?
- And if I was to drive?
- It's a good idea!
- I have one desire ...!
- Me too!
- Then let's do it!
- Yes!
This won't stop me!
I'll show them.
Sempai, but...
I promise you, Kishida!
I will return to racing at any cost!
Yes, sempai!
- ... We will not give up!
- We will not surrender!
I wasn't born to be beaten.
Eh ?! They withdrew
Gunma's license ?!
It can't be!
What did he do this time?
No, he didn't do anything!
- Damn!
In the next episode:
Gunma's License Is
Taken by Force, He Can't Run!
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you