STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Thank you, and
I'm sorry for troubling you.
Your very kind.
Your always asking
favors from others...
Does he mean that much to you?
I don't care about the guy...
...but his car.
Gunma's in a Pinch!
Rival Hiziri Approaches Tamotsu
Can the next patient enter.
Sit down on the couch.
Stay still.
It's a radiograph.
Your bone hasn't cracked.
Thank God!
Though it would be fun ...
...if I got treatment from that cute doctor.
MORIOKA MOTORS
What?
He injured his left foot?!
So did he participate?
Well since his
left foot was unusable,
he had to use his right!
And that's not all!
Are you saying that he threw ...
...a shoe at Haitani
during the race?
Yeah!
Unfortunately theres more, Morioka!
When he was in the pits,
he started fighting with Haitani!
We had to call the
police to separate them.
So, what was the verdict?
There...
Must have been
some kind of punishment.
In fact, they should
have revoked their license's,
but they were saved by
the intervention of another rider!
It may seem unbelievable,
but it's true!
The pilot was the
great champion Hiziri!
Hiziri? I know him.
He won the championship twice in a row.
His father is a  doctor!
That was kind of him.
Otherwise it would have ended badly.
Now Gunma won't lose his license.
He has the skill to do it.
However, the jury haven't
announced their decisions.
Hiziri is a kid at heart.
- Is Gunma his friend?
- No, not yet,
though I hope they will be.
I wonder why Gunma acted that way.
- I wish I knew!
- Hey, hey , Tamotsu.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Thanks for letting me work with you.
You've even helped out a lot,
even with Gunma.
Instead of being grateful
he just causes trouble!
I just hope he doesn't
create anymore trouble.
I know you two have a lot of talent.
But Gunma can't keep causing trouble.
Don't you agree, Tamotsu?
He must change!
And there's more problems.
To stay in this sport
you will need a lot of money.
More money than what you have.
In any case, Tamotsu,
take my advice ...
...and try to keep Gunma under control.
It's absolutely critical
that a mechanic and pilot ...
...get along well.
- What did she say?
- She said the swelling ...
...will decrease in a
few days if it heals right.
Are you alright?
Do you mind if I lean on you?
I'm still not used to the crutches.
Okay!
- No!
- Serves you right!
Just leave me alone!
Hey, wait!
Stop, Junko!
Come on, Junko!
- You can't leave me like this.
- You can walk on your own!
Oh, don't do this.
Hey, what about a...
...walk on the beach?
Alright.
Don't even think about it!
I've no time to lose!
I only came because
Grandma asked me to,
She had to ask me to come.
Now get back to work!
You can't let Tamotsu do it all.
As usual! You just let
everyone else do all the work,
while you do nothing!
Goodbye!
Wow, what bad luck!
I wonder if she's okay!
Hey, Gunma!
Hey, Kishida!
I was worried about your foot.
I rang and they told me you were here.
Fortunately the bone wasn't broken,
I'll get well soon!
- Yeah!
- But you can't participate ...
...in next weeks race.
A toast to your speedy recovery!
I'm so sorry that you
can't participate in the race!
How was I supposed to know!
Why didn't you tell me?
- Damn!
- Let go of me! I'm suffocating!
Well, after thinking for a while,
I decide to enroll
and take part in the race!
They say that in this competition ...
...the two champions
Hiziri and Haitani will participate!
What?
Alright!
- That's means I have to race too!
- What?!
But to enter I'll need money.
What about lending me some money?
Well ... Actually ...
If you don't
lend me money then...
...I'll race in your place, Kishida!
Right?
But you can't!
If you want the loan,
you gotta be ready,
Though you won't be able to drive with that foot!
Don't worry about it,
I'll be in perfect shape for the race.
- I'm sure I will!
- Well...
Even if I'm not
healed in time I'll...
- ...just use my right foot!
- Right!
Hit the break!
- What are they crazy!
- Are you alright?
- Idiot!
Hey wait...
Isn't that Haitani's car!
Sempai!
It's him.
What the?
The two of us have
a matter to settle.
Sorry, but today I'm in a hurry.
I don't have time for you and I have to...
...get ready for the race!
You will not win,
the same thing applies to your friend Hiziri.
- What?!
- Listen to me, you two have...
...no chance of winning.
I'm the best...
...and no one can beat me!
You got that, Haitani?
But you already know that.
Listen kid, on the track
your words mean nothing.
Real drivers don't brag.
- You idiot!
- By the way ...
If the jury decides
to withdraw your license,
You can say goodbye
to your career as a driver.
Don't complain,
you asked for it!
See you later.
I can't stand him.
Damn you!
Now you've really done it.
- I'm home!
- You're finally here!
This poor guy's
been waiting for hours.
- Hello!
- Hiziri?!
Gunma still hasn't
returned from the hospital!
This gentleman told me
what happened in the race.
right...
Just where is that crazy Gunma?
By the way,
Gunma will have to write a letter!
- What?!
- Yes, that's right!
Hiziri was very kind.
He intervened...
..with the Commission
and achieved the impossible!
In short, he managed to
convince them that Gunma was sorry.
But it is necessary that he
has to write a letter of apology?
Is it that serious?
Even though I intervened.
Gunma will still
have to write a letter,
then the commission will be happy.
I don't know how to thank you!
Guys, I'm home!
It's about time Gunma!
What took you so long?
Hiziri has been waiting all afternoon.
What!? Hiziri?
LETTER OF APOLOGY
What are you waiting for?
You've got write that letter.
Come on, write!
Don't be stubborn.
...I went out of my way to help you,
If I didn't,
you would have lost your license.
...and then you wouldn't
be able to race anymore!
Not only here, but all over the country!
Has Haitani also written a letter?
Because if he hasn't,
then I don't...
..see the point in me writing one!
Do you want to end your career!
It's true, that Haitani is also to blame,
-  but you started it.
- That's not true!
He threw the first punch!
Just ask him!
Don't you remember he
pushed me against the rails!
I wasn't the one looking for a fight!
He's responsible!
He tried to force me off the track!
It's easy to see why he did it,
he couldn't tolerate that I was faster!
Why should I have to write a letter?
Alright.
Haitani will also write a letter!
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
Fine.
Then go and tell him the good news.
You'll find him in bed!
What did you do?
Gunma!
I don't think he's recovered
from the blow I gave him!
He's swollen like a ball!
Me and him had
a slight problem.
- What did you do?
- I had a problem.
Hiziri, why did you help me out?
Why did you poke your
head into other peoples business?
Unless you want something.
Tell me what it is.
Let me guess.
You probably realized that...
...I am such a skilled driver!
A driver like me is only born...
...once in a hundred years!
Yes, I'm sure that's why.
Are you trying to be my
friend so ...
...you can learn my secrets.
You'll be applauding me
when I become the champion.
Your right about that.
I knew it!
I'll write the letter now.
SINCERELY GUNMA AKAGI
There you go!
Perfect!
I'll send it right away.
Listen, Hiziri ...
I'll give you a
preview of the news:
witness my triumph in the race ...
- ...in two weeks.
- What are you saying, Gunma?
Didn't you hear me Tamotsu.
I will be racing.
Are you crazy, Gunma?
Don't you understand,
you're still injured!
And where will you get the money?
You're not getting my savings!
No! Kishida was the one
who gave me money!
How?
Anyway your not ready...
..for the race!
You need to train,
many hours more!
You won't be able...
...to train because of your foot.
Cut me some slack!
Grandma, I'm hungry,
Make me some food.
Now!
Why are you in such a hurry?
What?
I'm not!
Because of your stupid speeches,
I always eat late.
Thanks again for everything.
I'm sorry for Gunma behaving rude,
I don't know how to apologize.
- But nothing serious happened!
- But he ...
- I saw your car!
- Eh?!
The one you prepared for Gunma.
I was very interested in it.
During the race I saw ...
...how his car was as equal as mine.
You must be a genius ...
- ...with cars.
- I'm actually a beginner.
Why don't the two of use become friends?
See you soon, Tamotsu!
I just knew it.
Where is Gunma?
Maybe he went for a checkup at the hospital?
Whether or not he's racing,
you have to talk to him!
You have ten days to do so.
He will only listen to you!
Yes, this is Morioka.
Sure, he's right here.
- It's Hiziri, he wants to talk.
I wanted to tell
you that I sent the letter.
I've done my part.
There should be no problems.
Thank you very much!
I'll tell you one thing that might surprise you:
in a couple of days somethings coming from Europe.
... a brand new car.
I want you personally to set it up.
You really want me.
I hope you agree...
...otherwise you won't get to drive it.
In short, I want you,
...because you have talent.
You should...
because you'll develop even more skills.
You should seize this opportunity.
Call me soon.
I'll be waiting.
- What is it? Bad news?
- No, no, it's nothing.
That's okay then.
- It was a blonde?
- What are you thinking, Rita?
- I got you!
- I was just kidding!
So you spoke with Gunma's mechanic then?
He may be...
just like everybody else.
No, not this time.
This one really knows his engines.
- He really is the bomb!
- Wow, a real champion!
Damn!
I am the fastest!
No one will ever beat me!
You know those giant
tires on the F1 cars?
They only last for around 300 miles.
They are used once per race.
They are disposable!!
In the next episode:
"The Storm of Tsukuba Circuit, Another Genius Appears".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away