STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
I will be able to win without...
...your help.
I don't need it anymore.
Desert-colored heart?
Gunma Makes His Second Start Alone
Kojima, how much money will
it take to enter Formula 3?
Let me think ...
The machines are very expensive.
If you aren't covered by a sponsor,
...it will be near impossible!
However, I think this figure
will be enough for at least a year!
- What?! 30 million ?!
- No! You forgot a zero.
- 300 million!
- Eh?! That's just too much.
Sempai, Formula 3 is
reserved only for professionals!
You need to have a sponsor ...
...or become part of a team!
Sempai, isn't your motto,
"I will win no matter the cost"?
The only way to get into
Formula 3 is to always win!
Now concentrate,
you've got to win the remaining races!
Yes, you're right.
Morioka told me the same thing.
I know you can do it.
You'll see that when your famous
you'll be able to get a sponsor!
I'm sure I will win!
I'll make it to the top
and then I'll be the champion!
That's the spirit.
- Aren't you training today?
- Yes!
Tamotsu...
Is he alright...
- ...without his friends?
- He'll manage.
He knows how to
win the sympathy of everyone.
- Is something wrong?
- I'm alright.
It's already been a week!
I wonder how he's doing?
You know what...
You see how he just
hire a new mechanic?
Even though we can do any job...
- he gives us...!
- I don't know where he's from,
but it will be ten years
before he touches that motor!
Well!
Let's go grab a bite!
Hope you can handle it.
- Wash mine too!
- Why me?
Don't complain!
The newcomers...
...always do the washing!
By the way, don't forget
to wash the other stuff!
I see they're making you work,
They are good mechanics,
but it's also their first time in...
- ...Formula 3!
- Don't worry about me,
I can take care of myself.
Gunma, my friend,
what are you doing right now?
I've never seen Gunma so determined!
Though he's probably just brooding.
Since Tamotsu left after his victory.
I can understand how he feels.
Before he could count
on the support of Tamotsu.
He came down the
track calm and relaxed,
and he knew that he
would always be there for him.
Unfortunately, now,
Tamotsu is gone!
You know?
He's just like a mountain climber,
worrying if his rope will break.
Well, this shows that
even Gunma has a heart ...
- ...and also suffers!
- He's not back yet?
No, he's still out.
Even in this rain.
Running like a madman will
do nothing to calm his anger.
He needs confidence, otherwise
he probably won't make it.
Come on, turn off the engine!
Hurry it up!
I think this motor
needs a full overhaul.
- I was thinking the same thing.
- Who's doing it?
Aren't you the chief mechanic?
Yeah, but I don't know how to.
Eh?! And you?
- Then who's gonna do it.
- You know!
None of us are that
experienced, right?
So who will prepare
the car for the next race?
- What are you doing?
- Hey,
Now that you no
longer have bandages,
your nothing but
a guy wearing glasses.
It's true!
And your really short!
Don't you dare change the subject!
The race is coming up soon.
If Tamotsu were here,
he would have already solved the problem.
Well, he left because
he could no longer...
- ...stand Gunma!
- Hey!
There's water?
Where's it coming from?
- I see.
- You need to fix it.
Yeah, but it might be broken.
Excuse me,
who's the expert here?
Now disassemble the
engine and repair the fault!
You know very well
that we can't fix it!
- We aren't experts you know!
- Yeah!
What?! Then who
will prepare my car?
Maybe he can fix it!
- He can't!
- Why not?
Don't you remember
that you said...
that you could win
without the help of Tamotsu?
Morioka will only
help if he wants to,
so don't worry
about the setup.
But that doesn't meant that
you should depend on him.
You must understand this.
Any other problem
you can do yourself!
Gunma!
It's time to prove your worth!
- Yeah, good luck with that!
- Why don't I show you,
In fact, I bet that you're dying ...
...for me to teach you a lesson!
Come on! Let's get this
done by midnight.
- Eh?!
- If your...
part of the team,
then you'll do it.
I'm not feeling too good today.
I knew it.
I should have known that ...
...you were just a layabout.
Maybe I should send
you to the hospital,
is that what you want?
It would be quite the show.
Why are you saying such things?
We're all trying our best here.
Everyone else is in Formula 3!
I'm the only one left.
They're all laughing at me.
That's why I've gotta win!
Sempai.
Ouch, my head.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You shouldn't walk
around with a wrench!
And who do you think are?!
Look who's talking!
Who do you think you are!
- What ?! Allergic to oil?
- Yes! It's your fault!
You did all this!
Look at the suspension!
It's covered with oil.
And the coolant is leaking!
This is quite the mess.
Change the coupling of the
machine or the engine will melt!
The coupling?
It's cracked.
I'm sorry, are you a mechanic?
I see that your not from around here...
...but I'm the best mechanic in the area!
You could say I'm a magician of sorts.
You probably didn't even know of me.
Stop talking!
Can you fix this problem!
Don't be afraid!
I said I was good!
...and everybody around here trusts me!
In fact, I'm probably the best ever.
Oh, my arm is getting all red!
Wow!
I hope your as
good you said.
You obviously aren't doing this for free!
What's your price.
D-Don't you trust me!
I charging you a good price,
you'll be lucky to
even get half price!
- I'm so stressed!
- You better be good!
I've never seen a mechanical like you.
Your not even manly!
Watch your mouth or I'll
take a hammer to your engine!
Calm down, guys!
If you say so!
I replaced the seals.
Now we have to remove
the oil from the piston!
But my arm is covered in red dots!
- I'm ruined!
- Tamotsu, my friend ...
I have a vague feeling that we'll be...
working in
the fields with your mother!
You better do the job right.
- I want it fixed!
- Hey! That's my bike.
Is this clean enough?
I said to remove all the oil!
Here he is.
- Why is he returning?
- He only did three laps!
On home stretch,
at full speed,
the rear wheels
had abnormal vibration.
And when you brake for the
bend, the car swerves.
Strange. I don't know why that happened.
- Maybe something is loose.
- It's possible...
...that one of the brakes were loose.
We'll get this fixed now!
- Tamotsu, get me a wrench!
- Do you want my opinion?
We don't have the time to waste!
Tamotsu, speak up.
You see, the temperature
of the right bearing ...
...is different from the left.
It's likely that the
bearings are not suitable.
We'll need to replace them.
How can you know this?
Anything could be wrong,
There may be a loose screw
or something else may be broken!
Didn't you hear me, we
obviously know what's wrong with it.
If the car skids when
the brake temperature rises,
- that means temperatures are different.
- I know that!
Okay.
Proceed as planned.
Replace those bearings immediately.
Then I'll do a test drive.
Just as I imagined.
It seems that Tamotsu will work
in Formula 3 for at least ten years!
This is great.
You did a great job!
Congratulations!
I didn't do anything fancy!
- What's the time?
- 01:05:02!
Five more seconds to go!
He needs to improve.
It's like the engine is on fire.
That engine has just been serviced,
its performance should be
improved by at least 10%.
If he cannot improve his time,
he can at least get seventh place.
If he keeps going at this rate,
he won't improve,
because time is running out.
If Tamotsu were here
things would better!
- Enough! Stop complaining!
- Right.
What an idiot!
I heard a rumor
that your mechanic has left you.
I hear that he went
and worked for Hiziri.
Well it is hard to refuse Hiziri!
Mind your own business!
You should concentrate on the race!
By the way, you know
what I find very funny?
It's about this guy
that  repaired the car.
He once worked for
a very popular garage,
but one day he was just fired.
And do you know why?
Because there was something wrong with him.
- Wanna know what?
- Does he have, shortcomings?
- What do you mean?
- He's really a great mechanic,
but just don't do
anything to tick him off,
Because he will ruin your engine.
That's not all,
They say he repairs the
machines but they still break,
...after ten laps at full speed.
W-What?
The results were announced.
You start in ninth position.
Well, do your best during the race.
- So, Gunma?
- What is it?
We need to talk about the machine.
It's okay overall,
but there's some problems ...
- when it turns the curve.
- The machine is the same.
Since Tamotsu has left,
and nothing has changed!
That's where you wrong.
It's different.
In my opinion, it's a purely
psychological one, sempai.
What did you say?
Hey, is that a puddle of water?
Another machine probably left it!
I'm not so sure.
Check it now!
That fault from before
has already been fixed!
The engine is a real gem!
It's real quiet.
I saw you drive
during the qualifications.
Your driving isn't aggressive at all!
You looked like a
total pansy out there!
- What did you say?
- The truth!
So you poured the
coolant under his car ...!
Well, you can't drive if you...
...don't trust your mechanic.
Now that Hiziri has moved to
Formula 3 the real champion is me!
On the track you
gotta give it your all!
Anyway I'm done here!
My payment please.
- Eh?!
- Where is it?
You still have to pay me, remember?
Uhm, sure.
- What are you doing?
- Your not getting it yet!
You'll get your money after I
have finished the race safely.
What's the meaning of this?
Don't you trust me?
You shouldn't worry,
your good with ....
engines, aren't you?
Don't you trust me?
Of course I do.
I'll do anything you like.
Don't do anything to tick him off,
Because he will ruin your engine.
But that's not all!
They say he repairs the machines,
...but they still break after 10 laps.
I have to do this! I'll get to
Formula 3 no matter the cost!
I cannot afford to
lose this championship!
Of course I do.
I'll do anything you like.
I'm willing to bet...
that water came
from my radiator.
I'm sure of it.
Oh, Tamotsu, I'm in trouble!
Now that your with Hiziri,
I'm stuck with Konpon to do the repairs...
...and now my mechanic.
Why did you leave, Tamotsu!
I'll make it without you!
I will become the
champion of Formula 3!
Hey! Where are the others?
Where are they?
Hey, the situation is
getting really desperate!
Is there no way out?
- Leave it to me, I have an idea! !
- Eh?!
In the next episode:
Has Tamotsu Returned?
Gunma's Dramatic Change
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away