STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
We could not ask for
anything better.
His time was astounding!
The sound of the
engine is really something!
Tamotsu Is Shaken!
Hiziri Conceals a Horrible Secret
MORIOKA MOTORS
I stopped racing because
my family was against it.
I'm not upset.
I must say that after the
accident, I leave without regret!
Though something else is bothering me.
I have to find the
answer to that question.
I want to study the behavior
of men and what pushes them ...
...to challenge the universe!
A disturbing question!
Because man wants to conquer space?
What drives him to climb mountains,
go to the sky,
and to probe the depths?
My thirst for knowledge
becomes larger by the day!
Let's stop talking about these things ...
...we have more important matters!
Only the thought
that Gunma will drive my car ...
I feel suffocated by
the pride and emotion!
This is great! This engine is
a gem, I assure you!
- I could not ask for better!
- Really?
A few more tweaks
and it'll be really fast!
We were lucky that Kishida...
...gave his car in Gunma.
Did you say yes
or no to Hiziri's offer?
I haven't had the time
to contact him. I'll do it tonight!
Guys, I want to go now
and try out the new engine.
What ?! Are you crazy?
You can't do that here!
- It's not finished yet!
- Oh, really?
I don't give a damn, understand?
There isn't much time
before the race.
- Why didn't you say?
Gunma...
Listen here...
...no one can stop me!
I want to go to the track and...
...try it out, alright!
Is that it?
Okay, go on ahead.
Don't be angry with me.
We wouldn't have
been able to stop him...
Have you noticed that
the driving style of Gunma ...
- ...has improved?
- Yeah!
He wasn't very good
in the beginning, but he's improved.
Now his driving is much more fluid.
And even his confidence!
I really think he has a good chance.
Him and that car has
what it takes to win the race.
Yeah, Gunma is a natural
when it comes to driving.
You know Tamotsu, I though
natural born drivers didn't exists...
In my life I have
met countless drivers,
and none of them
were natural born drivers.
I think they go fast ...
...because there is something bothering them.
It's anger that drivers them.
More like revenge.
Their desire to emerge
depends on an irrational desire ...
...to make the world
know that they exist.
I'm back!
- Hey, I'm starving!
- About time!
Aren't you two late?
- Good evening!
- Now that's a surprise!
Have you already been
discharged from the hospital?
- Are you okay?
- Hahaha, yeah.
- Hey, Grandma, I'm hungry!
- Coming!
Do you want some food too?
Tamotsu, I almost forgot ...
This afternoon Hiziri phoned.
He said to call him back.
He said around ten o'clock.
Tamotsu, hurry up and
deal with this money matter.
Because I won't drive with his money,
- Got it?
- Understood!
Hey, you two!
You still have to paint the car!
Get busy!
You know my car...
...must look really awesome!
- Right!
Hiziri?
This is me, Tamotsu!
I have to
talk about that thing.
Are you still there, Hiziri?
- Hello!
- I'm here.
Sorry, but I was
getting a cup of coffee.
I'm sorry to tell you,
but I really can't accept your offer.
You see, we found a
man who sold us his car.
Don't take it personally,
but it's better that
I remain by Gunma's side!
Hello?
Hiziri?
If your still there, answer me?
Hello, Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry,
but I have to hang up now.
- You'll have to call back later.
- But...
Won't Hiziri be angry with me...
because I refused his offer?
- Not at all!
- But I'm sure of it!
No, I assure you
that you're wrong!
He's just having a big headache!
Hey! What's going on?
Answer me!
- Hello, what happened?
- Please, get here now!
That sounded serious!
What could have happened?
Hiziri
Oh!
Tell me! What happened?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Uhm, I'm sorry.
You're so beautiful when you cry.
I'm sorry.
Hiziri...!
Hiziri?
S-Sempai.
That car is truly a gem!
With it's class, Gunma will use it to it's fullest.
- Yeah!
- Uhm...!
Yesterday afternoon,
You said just the opposite about the car!
That natural born drivers don't exists!
that they are drive
by revenge and desire ...
...to make the world know them.
But you just mentioned "class"!
About that...
What I meant to say is that
it's never just a matter of talent,
other factors are involved!
Especially for people who
have encountered difficulties in life.
Excuse me, but your
words aren't entirely clear.
Take for example the life of a boxer.
It would be logical to think
that after all those punches,
he would stop fighting.
But he continues to box.
And not only for his passion for boxing,
but also to get rid of
the wrongs he suffered in life.
In short, it is a way to
give meaning to their existence.
But why do you want
to know these things?
Well, that's because ...
Since you started ...
with a reference to
Gunma, I was interested!
I am convinced that he goes fast ...
because of the anger inside of him.
A revenge of sorts.
He wants to prove to
the world that he exists!
MR Tamotsu Ohishi
Terms of the agreement for team Hijiri
Hey, Tamotsu...
Hey, what are you hiding?
Let me have a peek!
Come on! Friends don't
keep secrets from one another!
- Let me see!
- Stop it!
It's personal stuff!
What kind of friend hides secrets?
I already said that it's personal!
Stop right there!
I've got it
Eh?!
What is it?
- What does this mean?
- Well ... Actually ...
You are a dirty traitor!
Don't you remember
anything that I've said!
This contract?
What are you doing with it?
I ... I wanted to return it,
but I didn't have the time!
I knew it, you were
dying to work for Hiziri!
- That's not it!
- You're lying!
I know you've got a crush...
- ...Hiziri's girl!
- Eh?!
What are you thinking?
You're wrong!
I'm not interested in her!
Fine then, If you won't...
- then I will!
- Gunma!
Remember, Tamotsu,
I'm the fastest,
You are my mechanic and
I don't intend to give you away!
- Gunma!
- Bye then,
Hiziri, come on out!
Or are you scared to face me!
Whatever you have in mind,
I will make sure that
Tamotsu will never work for you!
I suggest you leave him alone ..
or I swear you you'll regret it!
He doesn't understand...
..I always get what I want!
And as usual, what
I say always comes true!
I bet on it.
Aren't you in a good mood!
Even when working,
you find the time to whistle!
What's wrong with that!
It helps pass the time!
Right!
Yeah! Your right!
So, what do you think?
It's great!
But where's Gunma?
Wasn't he here a moment ago!
He shouldn't miss
a moment like this
He'll be back soon!
In the meantime, let's eat!
Easy, or you'll
break the bandages!
- I'm not hungry.
- But you haven't eaten!
Are you sure you
don't want anything?
No, it's alright!
I'll be fine.
He's strange,
This isn't right! I can't just leave
him to fend for himself!
Only a few hours until
tomorrow when I'll win!
Ready.
Go!
Here there is a curve to the right.
This is the first bend.
I'll have to pay close attention,
I'll have to slow
down when turning here.
And then full speed...
And when I get to the second bend,
I'll have to slow down.
just for a bit.
Then onto the finish line,
...at full speed!
I am the fastest and no
one will ever beat me!
In the race it is forbidden
to strike or push the other cars.
It is recommend
that you avoid such acts!
In the next episode:
He Really Is a Genius?
Gunma Runs Amok
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away