STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Tamotsu, in the world
there is two men that I hate.
One of them is an asshole! Do you
remember him?The one who beat us.
There are tons of people who are
a lot faster than you in the world of racing!
As for the other one,
it's my old man!
I hate him for abandoning
my mother, I've never forgiven him!
I know I did the right
thing by coming to Tokyo!
I will do anything to
become the fastest in the world!
But to achieve this,
I need you,
your a genius with engines!
I'm glad I came here
from the countryside!
Now I've got
myself a FJ 1600.
and I've even got a license!
We'll make it!
So, follow me, Tamotsu!
Junko's Love! He's the
Guy Who Saw the Limit of Speed
I'm sorry that I got
you involved with this Junko .
Now worries.
It's alright.
You really are too kind.
You've wasted so much
time with those lessons!
Gunma, say something!
Come see the
beautiful crescent moon!
Isn't it romantic!
I've never seen the moon like this.
It reminds me of love.
Even in the country
it's nice and shiny,
but your prettier, Junko .
Hey, Gunma! Morioka
loaned us this tape,
so you could
at least look at it!
Tamotsu, didn't you say that...
...you had
a date with a girl?
Stop trying to trick me!
Couldn't you at
least go make a snack!
But I'm not hungry Gunma!
Com one!
What are you stupid?
Give me a
moment alone with the girl!
You struggled to
get your license,
and now your trying this
right after being arrested!
Why are you reminding me?
- Because it's the truth!
- Come here!
No need to get serious, Gunma!
To drive on the track
you need a special license...
..but all you have is a normal one!
So how are you gonna race?
Even though the
tape is boring to you,
you've gotta watch
it so you can learn!
Try to understand, Gunma!
Stop screaming...
...I was only pretending
to choke you, honest.
I wasn't serious!
- How far are you willing to go?
- I'm sorry.
Your goal!
Do you think you will achieve it?
- Come on Tamotsu, you tell her!
- Of course...
He hasn't had any
serious thoughts on the matter!
If possible,
he'd like to enter Formula 3!
- What was that for?
- Your wrong, Tamotsu!
Formula 1!
So that's your life long dream!
- It's not a dream!
- Then what is it?
You don't understand,
Formula 1 is not a joke!
You have to
be a great driver...
...if you want to
compete on the track!
You're so pretty
but your annoying!
Well, wait and see!
If you have the patience,
one day you'll see the
moon at Monte Carlo,
- If you're nice to me!
- Stop it!
- What did I say?
- Hey,
I'm gonna give
you some advice!
If you want to become a real driver
you have to get to know yourself,
and stop acting
like you know it all!
Is it me or is it warm in here?
That's because life is ...
Too precious to waste!
You done yet?
You worry too much ...
...you need to
have some compassion.
Or maybe I'm wrong this time?
No, no, you're right!
- Good morning, Grandma!
- Is it time to get up?
It's the afternoon!
Did you forget that you have to train?
- I got my license suspended!
- You don't...
... have time for this!
Tamotsu told me ...
...that theres
other ways to train.
That friend of yours
has a heart of gold!
Don't waste valuable time,
watch the tapes Morioka sent!
Heres Junko 's room key.
But I warn you, Gunma,
in that room ...
...don't you touch
anything else but the VCR.
What do you mean, Grandma?
Don't you trust me!
Do you think that I would search around ...
- ...in Junko 's room?
- Yes!
This isn't fun at all,
I'm just a fool...
...acting like this!
Let's see if theres something else on.
What is it!
It must be something special.
I wonder what it is!
Maybe it's a secret of Junko 's.
You could never know what's on it!
- Junko , I love you!
- What?
And for you I'll do
anything to win this race.
I know, Ryuji!
Do you really love me?
- Come on, strike a pose!
- Well?
I assure you that I
have never been so serious.
We'll get married when I win,
What is this?
Who is Ryuji?
For two years now.
Ryuji...
Come on, Junko!
This will all be
settled at the finish line,
Her comes Ryuji!
No!
Ryuji!
- Junko, please ...
- Move back!
- No! Let me see him!
- Stop it! Junko!
I want to see him!
Ryuji! Ryuji!
Answer me!
Ryuji!
Why?
Tell me, Grandma, who is this Ryuji?
Who's Ryuji?
Well, you see ...
It was Junko's first love.
Now you understand why she
doesn't like to talk about Formula 1.
Ryuji was an exceptional driver,
perhaps the best in the world!
It's easy to tell that
your in love with her.
Am I right, young man?
Don't be silly, Grandma!
Listen, their love was
deep and passionate.
Nobody in the world
will make her forget him!
Even you can't change that.
Don't forget that!
Ryuji!
Watch out, Ryuji!
Oh, no, Ryuji! Why?
No, don't leave me!
Don't leave me!
Please!
Please, don't leave me!
Don't leave me!, Ryuji!
Ryuji!
I'm just a fool!
You idiot!
We'll get you...!
Yes, I'll tell him.
Yes, yes, thank you.
Bye.
It was a call from France ...
...it was about a new car.
They said that it is almost ready.
GAKURAZAKA POLICE DEPARTMENT
WE RECOMMEND A GUIDE
BOOK JUST TO BE SAFE
Don't leave me, Ryuji!
That's enough for today.
I'll see you tomorrow morning, Tamotsu.
Okay.
Bye.
- Hello, Gunma!
- Come on, get in!
How was the lesson?
Your showing up in a tractor?
That's right, Morioka.
Did the instructors say anything?
Are you crazy!
What is the police stop you?
Why should they
It's alright,
I have a driver's license.
By the way, Tamotsu, tell me one thing:
How long will it take
to get my B license?
If you start now you
can have it by next Sunday!
- Do you want to take the exam?
- Of course! How long will it take ...
... for a motorcycle license
and a drivers license?
Well, a bit more!
Probably a month.
What? A month?!
- Gunma, if you don't want to ...?
- Yeah, you guessed right.
I will attend the race next month.
And Tamotsu, I'll need your help!
But it is too early to participate in a race!
I don't agree with you!
You don't understand!
I will race!
Very soon!
Yeah! Sooner than you think!
It could happen tomorrow!
Tell me, Gunma,
you're not mad, are you?
- What?
- I was just saying?
- What about the others?.
- Remember one thing:
no one will ever beat me!
But what happened to your belly?
You feeling alright?
Don't worry!
It's just swollen!
Do you know where Gunma is?
- We've got a surprise!
- What?! A surprise?!
Hey there!
We're both starving!
- Eh...?!
- So what!
Is there something wrong Gunma?
Dinner!
Serve me my dinner!
Stop that now!
If your so hungry,
go make it yourself!
Why didn't you tell us about him Junko ?
- What?!
- Maybe it was not true love.
He must've been a bad driver...
...to have an accident like that!
It's funny!
He was only a Formula 3 driver!
- What do you mean, Gunma?
- If you loved him so much,
why aren't you dead with him?
- I don't understand!
- Stop ignoring me!
I'm talking about Ryuji,
your great love!
Now I know all of your history!
I saw the tape!
- What did you do?
- That accident happened...
... right before your eyes!
But you didn't have the courage ...
...to die with him!
That's got nothing to
do with you, Gunma!
He must have left a lasting impression,
since you repeat his name at night.
What a mighty speech!
I knew you were like this!
- You still love him so much?
- Now you've really gone too far!
Please, Gunma!
Come on, calm down!
I decided to give you a gift.
Here it is!
Try it on!
On the left side: "G"!
And on the right side: "T"!
And so it becomes a "Gran Turismo" helmet!
Its good luck for the pilot!
Remember: treat it with love!
Wait a minute!
- Shut up, you idiot!
- Hold it!
Wait, Junko !
Let me! Don't touch me!
Why didn't you die
with him? Tell me?
I wanted to die!
If I had followed the fate,
then I wouldn't have suffered.
But ...
I wasn't successful!
Why is that?
Because the Ryuji that
died that day was not my Ryuji!
You cannot understand ...
...I just couldn't do it!
Every time that Ryuji was driving, I was at his side.
In those moments
we were body and soul!
You see, he raced as if we were one!
My thoughts were his!
I was with him always!
Always at his side!
But that day was different.
I had the feeling that Ryuji
didn't want me there with him.
Though it was just a gut feeling.
Maybe he knew something would happen!
Do you think so too?
I've thought about it too.
Maybe that's exactly what happened!
Then I decided to go ahead
and dedicate myself to the world of racing.
- Now leave me please, Gunma.
- Not yet.
Grandma, this helmet
is out of this world!
I know!
It's one of a kind!
It was designed by
a friend of mine just for you!
For real?!
But there is something missing!
What are you doing?
- Let me go!
At long last!
My dream has come true!
I won't hurt you!
Just a little kiss on the helmet.
You're a scoundrel!
We scoundrels get along well!
From now on,
your my girlfriend!
We'll see about that.
Before an important race,
I recommend everyone ...
...practice at the weekend!
You can be just like Satoru Nakajima!
you too can join the paddock!
In the next episode:
"The Wandering Young Woman Yuki".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away