Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
Gunma? Have you decided
on the next race?
- I won't go!
- Eh?!
I won't.
Gunma vs. Hiziri!
Final Countdown
But why?
You got your license back.
Kishida told me.
Because Junko begged Tamotsu to help me!
And so he asked
Hiziri to do something.
I was in the
dark about everything...
...and I couldn't accept it,
so I went on a rampage.
My pride prevents
me acting properly!
Junko!
I don't agree with you.
It's foolish to give up
over something like that,
Do you realize that you have
overcome many obstacles to get here.
...and you want to
screw it up over your pride.
The Gunma I know
would not surrender ...
because, one day you decided on...
becoming the
world champion of Formula 1!
Damn you.
Snap out of your daze
and repeat your phrase.
"I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!"
I don't want it.
You were brilliant!
I thought you would become an expert!
You have to drive!
You can't give up now!
Please! You have to drive!
- The engine has a nice sound!
- The piston is my passion!
Good job, Tamotsu!
Now Tamotsu, where do they
drive the fastest machines in the world?
- In Formula 1!
- Good job my baby!
And that's where
you father drives.
- Sempai...
- It's not cash,
but it's worth a hundred million!
It's the only memory I have
of my mother. Will you give me the car?
Do you really think
you can beat Hiziri?
Fantastic!
A record time.
Are you sure this will work?
The radio will put
out the fuel pump ...
...and Hiziri will be left dry.
I just want to tell you
that it's not fair to him.
Look, we're doing it
for his own good!
I'll assume all responsibility!
There is no alternative ... unfortunately!
Hey, Hiziri! I'm sorry for not
being able to return the favor on the track.
Are you listening?
Let's see who's the best!
This is it, Hiziri!
This is weird,
why isn't he moving?
Hiziri is slowing down!
Gunma!
That noise...
Is there something wrong, Tamotsu?
Are you feeling okay?
No, I'm alright.
You see, it's just that
Gunma's car has an engine...
...that sounds very familiar to me.
Oddly enough, by the roar of the engine,
a mechanic can recognize his setup!
And that engine has left me stunned.
When I heard the engine it
reminded me of something familiar!
Hey, you.
What are you doing here?
Father!
Why didn't you stay at home
and work in the fields, Tamotsu?
Did your mother let you leave,
or did you run away?
- I don't have to answer to you!
- What did you say ?!
I want to get to Formula 1!
And I will succeed!
Formula 1?! Shouldn't you be
back at home in the fields.
The world of Formula 1 is
uncertain and full of disappointment!
On the other hand, if you work
in the fields, this won't happen.
You only speak like that
because you weren't able to succeed!
D-Damn you!
The engine ...
The piston ...
Father! Stop for a moment!
I have one last thing to say to you!
Mother believed that you
wanted to become a mechanic.
And she believes that you
left her for that career!
Instead your greatest
aspiration was to become ...
... a Formula 1 driver!
Deny it if you dare!
For this reason you
have forsaken me and mom!
Well, what's your answer?
I'm just saying that your machine
will never be able to overcome mine.
That's the only
answer I can give you.
Gunma will start in the second
row and Hiziri in fourth.
If my car were to win,
it would deal my
father a tremendous blow!
- Gunma!
- Don't you know it's useless...
...to read this!
Even if it starts to snow...
...I will gain the pole-position.
With a father like Eijiro ...
... you must have suffered very much!
However blood does not lie!
His car has the same roar
as a car you would setup.
I'm sorry,
but I'll win the race tomorrow!
Sorry to contradict you, Gunma!
But you won't win tomorrow.
- What?!
- Hiziri is in top shape.
And for reasons
that I will explain you,
he is absolutely
determined to win!
What's with all this seriousness?
When he asked me
to go to work for him,
he wanted to improve
his car to get to Formula 1.
And now the car is 100%!
Hiziri also...
...after months of
hard training, in top form!
This will be a
hard undertaking for you...
..and virtually
impossible since I'm with him.
I hope that your prepared...
...because this time Hiziri
is stronger than you.
I don't care!
If Hiziri is in perfect shape,
I will prove to
him that I'm better.
I have to win the
race at any cost!
I could not bear to be
defeated by you and Hiziri!
Just to let you know,
I don't plan on losing.
How long
will it be snowing?
What's wrong, can't you see?
I can't see.
Stop joking, you
were training earlier today.
That's because,
I know the circuit by heart.
I couldn't see at all.
On the track, I could
barely make out the shadows!
In fact, I didn't even
know it was snowing.
Don't worry, Ruiko,
tomorrow it will all be over.
Please, don't say
anything to Tamotsu.
- Do you want to drive...!
- Yeah!
Okay...
It's alright, there's
no need to be afraid.
Would you stop
if I asked you to?
Would you go all the way?
I have to do it, Ruiko!
Try to understand me.
I'm here about my drivers
license, I want to thank you.
This is truly an event to celebrate!
It's rare for you to thank someone.
However, I'm not the
one you should thank,
I did it only as a favor
to your friend Tamotsu!
He's a true friend
and loves you very much.
Another thing ...
I just wanted to let you know ...
...that, thanks to
your generosity my friend,
you were able to
get my license back.
But remember that
I will beat you.
Actually, you better
settle for second place.
What?
You will be the
one finishing second!
I'm stronger than
you and I can prove it.
I ask only one thing!
Listen!
If you have the chance,
try to keep up with me.
Because I'm going to teach
you something interesting.
- Something interesting?
- Exactly!
I'll teach you how a great
champion behaves on the track!
What's wrong with him?
He had a strange light in his eyes!
His expression was totally different!
Come on.
Damn! Where does
he think he's going.
Hiziri, enjoy it while you
can but I'll overtake you!
I see enough to at least distinguish the track!
I have to win at all costs!
Formula 1 is waiting for me!
Hey, Tamotsu...
I've changed my mind.
Let him drive.
- What changed your mind Ruiko...
- He wants to drive!
After all, everyone is free
to choose their own destiny!
I've done everything I could...
...to set-up the car.
But I couldn't stop him...
...from his goals.
Hiziri, it's all up to you.
Look at that, another lap and
he's got  the same time!
- Hooray!
- Yes, I know he can do it.
Damn it!
Ah!
He's catching up to Hiziri!
- Damn it!
- Come on! Keep it up, Gunma!
Hiziri, I'm sorry but I'm tired
of keeping up with you!
- He's overtaking!
- Sempai!
Great, don't stop now!
You can do it and...
...pass him with ease.
Gunma!
Enough, eat my dust!
Damn it!
I see that your
still keeping up with me.
Your a good driver.
- Phenomenal!
- He's the strongest!
This is bad.
If he continues to force the machine,
...the car will break down
before the race ends.
I don't think so! In any
case, Hiziri is ahead of him.
Gunma is chasing him desperately!
In my humble opinion,
he has a chance of winning.
My vision is once
again clearing up, that's good.
I have once again become
more aware of my surroundings.
But where's Gunma?
Gunma, I will teach you...
...how a real driver races!
Hiziri, hold on! Don't die
Tamotsu! The world is waiting for you!
Conquer the world in my place,
- with Gunma Akagi!
- Hiziri!
In the next episode:
Farewell Gunma!
Rise Fastest Man in the World!!
"I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!"
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you