Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
- What's wrong?
- Oh, dear.
Gunma vs. Hiziri!!
I Am the Champ!
Sempai, I've got drinks!
There is orange and bitter orange.
Which one do you prefer?
Sempai, what's wrong?
I don't know why Sempai did that!
An article on Hiziri.
Take a break, Tamotsu,
you've been working for hours.
I saw that the light was
on and thought I'd enter.
I'm sorry but I'm pretty busy.
Tomorrow will be the big debut!
I brought you some coffee.
Come on, help me up.
Uhm...
I know you can do it!
Though I'm pretty heavy, you know.
- I'm not sure about this.
- It's alright.
Uhm...Uhm...
- You okay?
- Ruiko...
- You're heavy!
- I'm sorry.
- I told you, I'm pretty heavy!
- Yeah.
By the way I'm almost finished here...
Look, is there a way you can
make it not drive tomorrow?
- Why would you want that?
- Uhm...
...the car isn't yet fully developed.
But you can't ask that of me!
There is a danger...
...that Hiziri might have
an attack during the race.
What kind of attack?
But he has never felt like
that during any of the tests!
- Your thinking too much!
- I'm not.
Just today he had an attack!
It happened right after training.
He's fully recovered,
but no matter,
these attacks are
becoming more frequent.
Thanks. But didn't Hiziri know
that this would of happened?
You were the one...
that convinced me to take this job.
That night, you revealed
everything about his illness!
Your right.
I was the one that insisted...
...because you saw
the condition he as in...
I was hoping that
you were gonna help.
Hiziri is very sick.
You know?
- He's sick ?!
- Yes, he has a serious illness.
But unfortunately there
is no remedy to cure him.
Little by little...
...the condition of his eyes
and heart will weaken.
Now you know
what is happening to him...
...and why he insisted
on you working with him.
This is why he must pass Formula 3...
...and win the championship.
He only has so long left.
This is his last chance, you know?
Help him, Tamotsu!
Make sure that he wins!
Please!
That evening, Hiziri,
went on a rampage!
But I still think
I made the best ...
...decision, because you finally...
...became part of the team.
However, there was another
reason why I wanted you to join.
- Huh?
- I wanted an ally!
If he withdraw from
the world of racing,
He could live for at least
four or five more years.
At this point I don't
care who wins,
just that he remains
at my side for longer!
I beg you, Tamotsu, try to
make it not drive tomorrow!
But I can't!
I could never do that!
I gave my word to
Hiziri and I won't betray him.
And I didn't accept this
job because I felt sorry for him,
I agreed to become his mechanic ...
because I wanted to improve
my skills and become stronger!
That's why!
And this...
decision has cost me dearly ...
because I lost the
love of my dearest friend!
I beg you!
Only you can stop him!
Listen..
I can't do it.
- What did you say? He was angry?
- Yes.
Knowing Gunma,
I bet that he went to the circuit!
Doesn't Hiziri make ​​his
debut in Formula 3 tomorrow!
- Oh, yeah!
- That article probably...
...probably sent Gunma into a rage!
But how do we know he won't...
- ...do something stupid!
- We don't!
When it comes to Gunma
we don't know what he'll do!
He's quite capable of entering the circuit ...
...and doing something
stupid in front of everyone!
We've gotta find him.
Oh my!
She was like a lightning bolt!
She must really be in love...
...since she went to look for
him in the middle of the night.
- Hiziri!
- Just today, he had an attack.
It happened right after training.
Hiziri, why are you here alone?
Are you felling alright?
Have you finished your work?
Relax!
Have a drink with me!
Don't worry about my health,
I went out just to
get some fresh air!
Hiziri, can I ask you a question?
- Sure!
- You see...
...Martin  said that drivers
always try to surpass themselves ...
...for taking revenge on someone.
I want to know what drives you!
Does each driver want his own destiny?
Do we just drive?
You think it's stupid, right?
- That's not it! You misunderstood me.
- So why do I drive?
By the way, Tamotsu, I will not
take pole position tomorrow!
Why don't you want the
Pole-Position? Are you crazy?
Aren't you going to
be first like always?
Don't you want to
overtake them and win big?
You're right. I should win big.
But I can only do
that with your help.
Tamotsu, Tamotsu.
Hey! Can you see Gunma?
No, he's not here!
Yesterday I called them and
they said they didn't see him.
- Look it's Tamotsu!
- Eh?!
I haven't seen him in a while.
- He looks relaxed and calm!
- Good.
02:08:57!
Something must be wrong!
Hey Chief, are you sure
you did a good job?
- I did everything I could.
- He's coming back to the pits!
What is it, Hiziri? Engine trouble?
You need to do better.
No, the cars perfectly!
It's a true masterpiece!
But don't you want to
achieve pole position?
Right now any
position is fine for me.
Pole-Position is a
bit too much for me.
Great! Let's take a break too.
Sure!
Boss knows what's right.
- Tamotsu!
- Hi!
- Hi, how you doing?
- Junko and Kishida!
I didn't know you were here.
But how did you all get in here!
They just don't let anybody in!
Well, we used this pass, you see!
- That's how we got in!
- Is Gunma also with you?
- Probably!
- Huh.
In fact, we came here
because we thought ...
...you could tell us where Gunma is!
Sorry if we've disturbed!
You must be busy.
- Let's go, Kishida?
- Yes.
- Good luck!
- Goodbye, Tamotsu!
Hey, wait a second!
Let me know if Martin and
Gunma are still angry with me.
If they are, they have their reasons.
I betrayed their trust!
But I have not given up on
the dream I share with Gunma:
Him a formula 1 driver
and me as his mechanic.
Please tell him!
I will come back to work with him ...
- ...when the time is right!
- When the time is right?
- What does that mean?
- I can't tell you anymore for now!
But, please, take care
of Gunma until then!
- I beg of you.
- Tamotsu.
The race has begun and
we haven't even seen Gunma!
I would love to know
if he even came here.
Did you see something, Kishida?
Hiziri...
This is awesome!
In Formula 3 you race completely different!
Just you wait. I'm coming.
02:07:24!
He gets faster and
faster on each lap!
- It would be better if I left!
- Eh?!
I just can't stand this.
I hope you understand.
I can't help but look at
him and think that ...
Ruiko ...
I have to admit that
you ain't half bad, Hiziri!
However, you won't remain the
undisputed champion for much longer!
What?!
There's a man on the bridge?
You idiot!
You talked with the mic on!
Hey, they said that
there is a man on the bridge!
Who is that crazy guy?
- I dunno!
- Let's see!
What the hell are
you people looking at?
Huh
It's Gunma!
I've participated in a few races ...
...and realized that you
need to finish first.
Well he'll need
more luck that that.
Just answer yes
or no to my question.
I hope the answer is yes.
Okay, proposal accepted!
But I do things my way!
So I won't be taking responsibility...
if this project turns
out to be a waste of money.
Fine then.
It'll be there in a few days.
And remember don't
try to discover my identity!
Remember that.
Gunma Akagi...
Come down or they'll be trouble!
I can't let them take me!
Get down here now!
You didn't think I would fly!
Let's hope that didn't hurt!
- Come on, Kishida, let's go!
- Yes.
Remember, if the drivers are to be strong,
it's only because they are
motivated by the spirit of revenge!
Hiziri!
How can I explain to him that,
it's been an entire year
since I've known something was wrong.
The numbness isn't limited to my hands but also...
to my legs and knees ...
Sometimes my vision blurs
and my ears start to ring.
Every time, the
pain gets more intense.
And every time...
Death is slowly getting closer,
but he won't let me die.
He knows that I don't want to drive,
for fame or money!
I don't know what to do!
The reason I'm driving is ...
The reason I'm driving is
only a race against time ...
...because I'm trying
to escape my situation.
I'm helpless!
The very fact of
going a second faster,
gives me the illusion of
being able to stop my fate!
At that precise moment I felt ...
That I was the absolute ruler of time!
This is why I continue to
drive and I'll never stop!
- Great job!
- Congratulations Hiziri!
You did it!
This is truly amazing,
he won Formula 3
on his first try!
He's one of a kind.
From now on, thanks to him,
the league will be more exciting!
Tell us: are you excited?
What are your future plans?
Well, I will be aiming high!
Sorry, but could you
explain it a little more?
I already said it.
So does that mean that
you will go to Formula 1!
Drivers are always unpredictable.
Excuse me, I've gotta go.
You've heard him!
The strongest driver of the last decade,
will go and race in Formula 1!
Well, that race and
interview has left me very tired.
If you don't mind,
I'll be heading home.
Sure, go ahead.
We'll take care of everything.
- It's Gunma!
- Sempai!
Gunma?!
What ?! Formula 3?
They came to propose
to race in Formula 3!
Finally they've realized the
talent of the great Gunma!
In the next episode:
Gunma's Winning Everything!
Finally, an Invitation to F-3...
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you