STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Goodbye, Gunma! Rival Hiziri
Announces His Step-up to Formula 3
You think this is funny?
My mother bought me this,
...to wear on very special occasions!
Don't you believe in
celebrating for Hiziri?
Look, Tamotsu,
you can't be serious?
But a lot of important
people will be there.
Ruiko said that we will have fun.
Who knows,
maybe you will.
You're in love with Ruiko!
And that's the truth.
What are you saying?
That's nonsense!
Is it!
If not why...
...did you dress so fancy?
The fact is that I've
never been to a party so...
...I didn't know how to dress!
Grandma, please,  tell me:
should I also bring a gift?
Maybe, a cake,
or a box of chocolates,
- Or a bunch of flowers!
- Tamotsu!
Your like a school
boy on his first dance!
Well, guys,
I should be going.
You'll join me later,
won't you?
Go on ahead!
Gunma will be ...
...making an appearance later!
Stop joking!
Don't even think...
...that I'd go and
celebrate in my rivals home...
...just so he can gloat!
Have fun!
So, are you
going to Hiziri's party?
Of course I'm going!
And will Gunma be going?
I get it ...
Look Tamotsu, go ahead
and enjoy yourself.
Get to know nice people!
The important thing is
that you don't provoke Gunma!
- Yes, you're right!
- You're a good boy.
If there are any problems,
let me know right away.
I would hate for
you two to fall out.
UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL HARUKA
This is terrible!
- Hell there!
- Sempai!
You alright?
What bad luck!
Once I've done more than fifteen,
I'll then be able
to overcome Hiziri!
I almost beat him!
I am very sorry!
By the way, you know what?
I got my revenge!
- Haitani got what he deserved!
- You serious?!
Once you win the next race,
Hiziri will know that your better!
Heal faster,
then we'll race together...
- ...all over the world!
- Sempai!
Okay ...
See you!
Sempai!
- See you later.
- Bye Tamotsu.
Am I going or not?
I came to
check up on you.
Oh...! Thank you.
Don't worry about the party,
you don't
- have to come!
- Uhh...
Hiziri picked up Tamotsu!
It's none of my business,
but I'd though I'd let you know.
Tamotsu seems worried about something!
Why is he worried?
Why would he be worried?
I'm home.
What are you up to?
"I'll be back late.
In the fridge you will find...
...everything you need for dinner.
Yours, Grandma.
By the way,
Kinoshita and Matsuura aren't here either.
They probably went out for dinner!
And Tamotsu went to that party ...
It's just the two of us.
Why don't we both go out for dinner?
It's my treat!
Since we are alone,
why do not you give me a kiss?
At least one! Please!
It's always the same with you!
Don't you think about anything else?
I'm going to dinner alone!
Wait Junko!
I'm coming too!
- Then your paying the bill!
- Wait!
But it is logical that I pay!
We'll go to a luxurious French
restaurant by the candlelight!
Wait here a minute!
Okay? Don't move!
Tamotsu will pay.
He must have
money hidden somewhere!
Where is it?
Is this it?!
I knew I would
find it sooner or later!
Damn,
he's spent a lot of money...
buying that race car,
but he still has some left over!
There's so little left!
Hurry up!
Hi, who's calling?
No, Tamotsu will be
back later this evening.
Would you like to leave a message?
Wow, he was polite.
That person sounded very nice.
It's great
that Gunma is felling better.
And Tamotsu...
...and Junko.
I must admit that
Gunma is a handful,
however he needs
more money to race.
So it would seem.
Shoma will be arriving home soon,
...and if he found these
magazines he would get angry!
No! Don't worry.
I'll hide them.
I get it.
Well, I'm going.
This is delicious.
Waiter, bring me more, please.
Junko, what was Ryuji's position?
I don't understand what you mean.
I'm talking about money: funding!
I'm guessing he was very rich.
No, he wasn't.
One day, however,
he managed to find a sponsor:
a service station.
I remember that he was very happy!
They instructed Ryuji...
I'm curious to know what
Tamotsu is doing at that party!
- I don't care.
- You mean ...
...you wouldn't like to go?
Are you kidding?
It isn't too late you know.
Why don't you go there?
Stop it!
It's none of your business!
Why do you feel such angry towards Hiziri?
Instead, you should be grateful.
You wouldn't have a
license if it wasn't for him.
Why don't we change the subject?
Hiziri was here!
He picked up Tamotsu.
Fight me, Hiziri!
Next time I'll win.
Hi, Tamotsu!
This is a surprise!
- What happened?
- I have to talk business with Hiziri.
Are you serious?
What kind of business
do you have with him?
Hiziri...
He's a trouble maker!
So, you're having fun tonight?
Yes. But I have
come here for another reason.
So, Tamotsu, go ahead!
Can I ask you for a big favor?
With all the knowledge
and influential friends you have,
it would be easy for you...
...to put in a good word for me.
It would be great if you could...
...help me get a job as a mechanic.
I beg of you.
Why do you want to change your job?
I can't stay there any longer!
Anything would be fine.
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
Really? You will!
Though, remember one thing,
my car is always here waiting for you!
I'm honored,
but I can't!
Wow! He owns a whole
villa filled with young ladies!
Where are you going?
Just where is Tamotsu?
Hello, Mr. Akagi!
Don't even think about stealing anything!
...or there will be trouble!
- What?
- Don't tell me you came...
- ...to join us?
- No way!
Then stop looking at
me like that and go home!
How dare you!
- I'll show you!
- Oh, my God!
Good one.
Hey, why are you
staring at me like that?
- Tamotsu, where are you?
- Excuse me!
Gunma?!
What are you doing here?
I'm obviously here to find you.
You asshole!
How rude!
- Well, Tamotsu, let's go home.
- Why don't you stay, Gunma?
- It's good to see you again.
- Look, it's useless ...
...to try and get me to stay...
...you won the race.
I won't let you gloat!
Gunma, control yourself!
Listen up:
if that accident didn't happen,
I would have won the race.
However I won't lose again.
Next time I'll win.
It's really a shame,
I probably won't see you for a while.
What?
Just this evening I decided
on moving up in the world.
From now on,
I'll be racing in Formula 3.
Although this is still a bit away...
...I intend to go there eventually.
This time, next year
I'll be celebrating once again!
- Congratulations!
- Hiziri!
Enough!
I will get my revenge soon!
I wish you good luck...
...and treat Tamotsu well,
he deserves it!
I'll have the last laugh!
I'll catch up to you,
no matter where you go.
And then we'll see who's the strongest!
Remember that!
Stop that!
Before you can beat me ...
...you need to learn
how to finish a race!
- What was that?
- Stop!
- Let's get out of here!
- But I don't...
Do I have to repeat myself!
I still haven't finished
talking to Tamotsu.
Do what you want!
But remember, Tamotsu:
whatever proposal he makes,
don't accept it!
Me and you are
a team, aren't we?
Gunma.
Goodbye!
- Damn!
- What happened?
What happened in there?
Come on, tell me?
- Formula 3?
- Yes!
But how do I
get into Formula 3?
Listen, don't let him bother you!
Junko, I said how
do I get into Formula 3!
It's simple!
You have to win the championship ...
...and then
make your way there...
...and prove your a good driver!
So all I have to do is win all the upcoming races?
By doing so then you'll
reach Formula 3 next year,
- But you can't do it!
- And why not?
- You'll see that it's too difficult!
- I will succeed!
And don't forget:
it takes a lot of money!
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
This is the new machine.
It just arrived.
Can I look at
it a bit closer?
Sure, why not.
- Really?!
- Sure! Go on ahead.
You can use it,
the walls are soundproof.
- Do whatever you want!
- Eh?!
This is fantastic!
It's the most...
...beautiful car I've ever seen!
It sounds exciting, right?
It's a wonderful feeling!
Isn't it?
Don't worry about Hiziri...
- Come on, stop this.
- Don't you like me?
Of course I do!
I'm a man, aren't I?
The fact is that I have no
experience with women, and...
I'll be gentle.
Get off me!
I'm not that type of guy,
who succumbs
to something immoral,
Now, please,
leave me alone!
I'm sorry for what Ruiko did.
Forget about that,
what about a drink?
I've got something to say.
I've been dealing with an idiot?!
Do you treat me like
this because I'm from the country?
I've lost all respect for you.
Is that so...
Whatever makes you happy.
A drive and a
mechanic....
...should both treat each other well...
...to prove that both of
them care for each other.
I propose a toast
to our future cooperation!
A cars setup is everything.
If a bolt is loosened,
the rider could die.
But if the bolt is in place,
victory is assured!
The world of racing
is a dangerous place...
...time and money
can't solve everything.
Though a man can feed
his passion for engines.
And his skills can be improved,
My door is always open to you.
Think about it.
Your speed is determined
by what category your in.
In F1, you start from
what is called "the grid" ...
this is decided the
day before you race.
In the next episode:
"Tokyo Is Blown Away!
Gunma's Secret Part-time Operation".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away