STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
He Really Is a Genius?
Gunma Runs Amok
VICTORY AT ALL COSTS!
GUNMA
Come on, Gunma! Don't you
dare fail! Do your best!
Madam, we have to at
least wait til he's finished!
The driver who completes the
fastest lap, wins the Pole ...
I don't care about
any of that, okay?
- Come on, you can do it!
- That hurt!
Excuse me, Hiziri, I'm from a magazine...
It's a great honor
to have met you.
Thanks, but I'm here
for personal business.
As I said on the
phone, we decided ...
to dedicate a long
article to you in the next issue.
Call it a homage!
We could not ignore the champion ...
...who in mid-season
switched to Formula 3.
You flatter me.
Tamotsu, what's the time?
- What's the matter?
I can hardly believe it!
DANGER! TO PREVENT
ACCIDENTS STAY AWAY!
SPECTATORS SHOULD MOVE ELSEWHERE
Because man wants to
conquer space at all costs?
Only Gunma will
give me the answer!
He who gives his all \Min every race ...
...risks his life
to enjoy driving fast!
If I don't say it,
no one will!
That's why I will study
Gunma's guidance in detail .
Who knows what prompts
him to drive fast ...!
This is it!
Amazing, Gunma!
Oh! what?
What is this...!
- 01:02:07?!
- It can't be!
Tamotsu, are you
sure that's right?
Yes, of course it's right!
I may have pressed
the button too soon.
But I could be wrong.
but this time is close to Hiziri's time...
...which is 01:01:47!
- I don't believe it!
- I'll write it down anyway.
It's his best time,
although could be a mistake.
Should it be written down.
Are you crazy?
Everyone will laugh at us!
- Sorry, I'll be more careful.
- Look!
- Here he comes!
- Gunma.
Can you give me
your opinion on these tests?
And the way the
drivers tackle the curves!
Which of them has impressed you the most?
Your opinion is valuable to us!
I'm really Flattered, but I think ...
...your over thinking this.
The circuit seems
empty without you.
It seems that the boy,
will take all the attention!
His car is out of control.
The driver and his machine must ...
...both work together
and form a bond.
Usually a driver will try and
get too much out of his car.
- ...and he'll lose!
- Huh?!
01:02:05?
Yet the stopwatch works perfectly.
Tamotsu can't be wrong again!
So we have to agree
that this is his real time.
This is impossible!
I can't believe my eyes.
Even if I did set
up the car myself!
His time is out of this world!
There is something strange about it!
Did Gunma rig it?
You have to expect this from him,
No, no, it can not be!
He could never have
done something like that!
I've drove countless times on this track,
and I can assure you that...
...the sharp bends,
will not stop you at top speed,
it takes skill to deal with the curves...
..the make your best time!
Your words do nothing
but increase my skepticism.
I don't think that Gunma
has ever been so clever.
Gunma, doesn't have
enough experience to do it.
Though I'm not so sure
about him driving on this track.
In a straight line, but
especially when tackling the curves,
you must maintain the correct trajectory.
You can't do it with intuition alone!
But only if he had
the intuition of genius!
Isn't that how you define Gunma...
...isn't it?
It's true... The answer
was right in front of me!
A really great time!
01:02:04!
The pole position is now yours!
No one can beat me!
How dare that brat?
- Gunma!
- Junko, what's my time?
Right!
Are you sure this is right?
I understand your doubts,
but there are no errors.
- Its a great time.
- Still...
But I though I was
a couple of seconds faster.
Instead I have been so slow?
Well, before the official
announcement let's go for a drink.
Gunma, tell me the truth!
How could you
get a time like this?
You must have done something?
Tell me the truth!
Hey, what are you talking about?
Gunma!
What's wrong with you,
Tamotsu?
Look, I am your trusted mechanic,
therefore you must
hide no secrets from me!
Let me go!
You're hurting me!
- Answer me!
- Let go!
Not until you tell the truth!
I don't have any secrets.
The truth is, I'm a genius!
And I'm sure I could
improve that time if I wanted to!
Hey, what's taking so long?
There must be a mistake!
Both of us have similar times.
What! In Pole-Position
is Gunma Akagi!
- You know him?
- No, I don't!
Never heard of him.
01:01:30
He beat the record I set last year.
Hey! There must be
something wrong with the time!
- 01:01:30!
- Seriously!
- A guy called Gunma Akgai
has beaten the record?
- Who is he?
Do you realize?
He beaten Hiziri's record!
Gentlemen, I'm the fastest!
Gunma,
stop showing off!
Gentlemen, I invite you
all to drink to my health!
He's really a nice guy!
I needed a cold drink.
My friends!
I propose a toast:
Gunma Akagi's first great victory!
Stop it, you ingrates!
Is that the thank you
I get for getting you drinks!
- Let's go!
- How ungrateful!
- Gunma, stop it,
that's enough!
- Try to calm down!
- Let me go!
Now that's a surprise!
A practically unknown driver
...managed to beat
your previous record!
- What's your response?
-  You see, an exceptional driver ...
is usually accompanied by
a extraordinary mechanic!
An extraordinary mechanic
prepares awesome cars!
Though sometimes,
the machine is ...
...is better than the driver!
Right.
By the way, do you know
this rising star of motoring?
It doesn't matter
if I know him!
I have a goal to achieve!
Mine is a challenge ...
...that takes all my energy, and my purpose...
... is to set new records!
The others do not
concern me in any way.
Can I take your picture ...
...while you do a handshake...
- ...with the rising star?
- What?!
It's a good idea to take
a picture with...
... the future
champion of Formula 3!
Alright.
Gunma, will you stop
fooling around and listen to me?
You cannot continue
to act like this!
You must get along
with the other mechanics and drivers ...
...if you want to keep driving!
This isn't funny at all!
- Are you even listening?
- Huh?!
- Gunma!
- Stop yelling!
I don't care if
people like me or not!
- Why are those two like that?
- Because their friends!
It's the same thing every day.
Let's just let them
fight it out, let's go.
Listen to me, Gunma!
Try to be calm!...
Your not the only
on the track, you know!
Shut up!
Your always do this.
You never listen
to a word I say.
Your always getting into trouble.
But I'm willing to
put up with your tantrums,
but others will not.
We're only beginners
in the middle of the season!
And only after two races
you've got a Pole-Position!
Do you realize what this means?
No, and I do not care!
- but I know I'm the bets.
- Eh?!
You know, Gunma, other drivers
have run on this track for years,
- don't take this so lightly.
- I won't.
Where would I
be without you, eh?
Gunma, I understand
that you're excited and happy ...
...since you beat the record...
...but you shouldn't have
toasted before you won!
You have not only increased
the envy of those people!
And with your cocky attitude ...
...you've made enemies of the drivers!
Boring as usual!
You never change,
Do you remember that day
in the countryside when we met Hiziri?
And all you did was apologize.
You've always been like that.
Haven't you?
You've got to be
deluded if you think that...
...everybody's a nice guy.
Do you think they will change
if I act differently?
I'm sure that when we race ...
...they would become my enemies anyway.
On this I agree with you.
But you shouldn't hate them
anymore than what's needed!
Maybe guys like you
can also have a ...
...peaceful race in the company of friends,
but not me!
You never know,
you've just got to keep at it!
You've just got to
do your best and you'll win!
That greenhorn!
He's just lucky that ...
...he was able to beat Hiziri's record!
But he doesn't know
who he's dealing with!
Hey there buddy,
your time was very amateurish!
What's wrong?
You got lady problems?
Let's see if I'm right,
you're so used to...
...chasing girls that you can't think of...
...anything else and
you can't driver properly?
Bad habits die hard!
- That guy gets on my nerves!
- Yeah!
- I've got a debt to settle with him!
- You do?
Do me a favor if it doesn't
bother you too much.
Gunma, in order to move forward,
we have stick together!
You see, I'm your mechanic
and I know all about you!
But you always insist on
doing things your own way!
The trouble is that
our goal is the same,
but we use different means.
Isn't that right, Gunma?
Ruiko!
Here, inside you'll
find your work program.
I wonder who drew
these three pictures of Gunma?
Hey!
This is a prohibited area!
- Hurry, get away from there!
- I'm sorry.
A new round of testing
is about to begin, understand?
Hiziri wants a response
as soon as possible.
I'll be waiting.
Bye!
Good luck for the race!
Part tomorrow!
Maybe Gunma really is a genius!
This is a very important race for him!
He can only rely on himself to win.
Go on, let it all out,
- ...because it will be your last!
Sempai! Look what
I found along the way! Look!
- Eh?!
- Along the grass path ...
...there were just scattered everywhere!
Cherish them as if
they were relics!
Stop making absurd speeches!
Your not a saint!
- What's going on?
- Eh?! What did you say?
You placed those in
strategic places, didn't you?
- I don't know!
- Come on, stop lying.
Those drawings
served you as a reference ..
...for the race,
didn't they Gunma?
Ready!
Last night I came here,
and secretly ...
...I placed all those references.
They remind me of
the recommend speed.
I did this so I could
improve my time on the track.
I thought it would be easier ...
... since I highlighted the key points.
I have also placed other signals:
woven grass, flowers on the fence,
- Drawings on the wall.
- Huh.
Now I understand how you
were driving magnificently.
It's really brilliant!
Wouldn't you say?
Why are you surprised?
Other riders are using this system.
Then it is true,
even geniuses work hard!
Oh, Sempai.
Now I feel bad because...
I didn't help you out
with your valuable signals.
Don't worry about that.
I don't need them anymore.
I've memorized everything!
Gunma!
I really hope so.
- Is there something wrong?
It's nothing.
Tell us, Hiziri, who
do you think will come first?
Well, we'll know once
the race has ended.
But it will certainly be
the car with the best setup ...
..and the driver who has
the most experienced mechanic.
Do you know how long it takes
to change tires during a race?
Don't be surprised!
To change all four tires ...
... it takes eight seconds!
Only eight measly seconds!
In the next episode:
Short Lived First Victory!
Tamotsu's Betrayal
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away