STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Don't kid yourself.
You'll never be the fastest,
- not even in you're wildest dreams!
- You're just some asshole!
Gunma!
There are tons of people who are
a lot faster than you in the world of racing!
Hey brother,
Once the plane touched down,
- I was moved to tears!
-Be quiet, Yuma!
- Mr. Gunma!
- That is so moving...
...a picture perfect family!
Can I come in too?
- Why not? Sit next to me!
- Yuki, bring some dinner!
Wait a minute
and dinner will be served!
Don't even think
about serving him here!
As usual, Yuki.
Bring it to his usual place.
- But madam...!
- Today is a special occasion,
I just returned from America!
Let him sit with us.
There is a big difference
between him and you.
Gunma knows this, but he
doesn't want to understand.
- Mom!
- Don't say anymore, please!
Fine then! Where does
it matter where you eat?
- Yuki! Fill it!
- Yes!
So...
Someone advised me to...
...run as a candidate for
the House of Representatives.
- But I'm not sure about it!
- What did you say?
They must have found out
about you're skills as a politician.
And so, before accepting,
I wanted to know you're opinion.
It's really great, Dad!
- More please, Yuki!
- Alright!
Go for it. Of course you will be elected!
I know you can do it!
So you are not opposed to
my candidacy, Shoma?
Of course, if I am elected,
I will no longer be able
to take care of my other duties.
So, since you're
the eldest son,
all the responsibilities
of the company...
... will fall on you're shoulders.
Of course, Dad!
I'm ready!
- More please!
- Alright!
Dad, I'll always be by you're side.
I'll gladly accept this assignment.
You're my golden boy, Shoma,
- You're very responsible.
- Thank you very much.
- Give me some tea!
- Right away!
Don't forget
that when Yuma grows up...
he'll be able to help you too!
Though he'll have to
finish high school first.
Sure thing! I'll work with him!
- I'm done! Yuki, prepare me a bath!
- Yes!
Wait, Gunma!
I've got something to say to you.
I'm not interested in
the company or you!
As I suspected.
In fact, I wanted to talk to
you about you're bad behavior!
I want to go to Parliament,
but to be able to get elected,
the behavior of the
family must be acceptable...
...or I won't be accepted.
I'm warning you:
don't you get into trouble,
you hear me, young man?
- How cruel!
- Hey, father...
but couldn't you have
used a nicer tone with him?
Quiet, Yuma!
It's been five years,
since you're poor
mother passed away,
you haven't changed one bit,
in fact you've only got worse!
I was hoping that you hadn't
inherited any traits from that woman!
Don't you dare insult my
mother, you hear me?
I wouldn't if you
would behave better!
- How dare you!
- Please stop!
- Let go of me!
- Calm down, Gunma!
Now you listen to me!
She was mad at you and
yet she was still in love with you.
Now watch what you say about her,
if not then I
might just go berserk!
Now I can say with confidence ...
...that no one can
make you change!
All my attempts have failed miserably!
I'll give you anything
you want... just leave!
- I have nothing more to add.
- I'll go with pleasure!
- Mr. Gunma!
- Yuki! Stay here!
Take this!
Fill the bowl!
Yes.
Mr. Gunma.
Mr. Gunma. Are you there?
Where could he have gone?
You love him, don't you, Yuki?
I know about love.
Believe me, it's worth it!
But him... He is
nothing but irresponsible.
It's very different for my father.
That's not true, it's nothing but lies!
I don't want to hear it!
It's useless to discuss it now!!
Maybe one day you'll understand!
Okay, sir.
Flashback talk
Way to go!
Now overtake him!
Speed up, move forward!
You've almost got him!
No! Don't slow down!
Then you'll never get by him!
That drivers a real idiot!
A child could do better than him!
So, how is it?
Overall not bad, but
there are still some problems ...
...to fix. For example,
the turning needs fixed,
but otherwise everything is fine.
We'll find a solution.
Make another round!
Hey, you stressed out
drivers, listen up!
Who gave you you're license?
Where did you learn to drive?
Never seen such a
bad driver in my life!
Did you know you're a
disgrace to the track!
That car should have been able
to surpass the other one easily!
- Stop this now!
- What? And you are?
We are grateful for the
advice that you have given us,
but could you go away now.
I hate busybodies!
Then I'm leaving,
I'll do another lap then.
Good luck!
You try you best now!
Hey, wait, let me do it!
I'll show you how!
I'll show you how to
drive a car like that!
Enough is enough, stop this!
We have no time to waste!
There is still much to do!
Let him go!
Let him go, I said!
Don't you realize what you're doing?
Help me, Kinoshita!
- Enough! Let him go!
I'll leave him alone if I can drive.
Are you out of you're mind, kid?
Maybe I overdid it!
- You're right about that.
- What the...?
Hey, did I hurt you?
I'm sorry about that. Honest.
I understand perfectly
you're passion for racing cars.
But you see, it's hard for us too!
We need to shell out a
large amount of money to drive,
so we don't have time
to waste. Understand?
You must still
be in high school.
Do you have a driver's license
or have you yet to take the test?
You must know that to be
able to race on a circuit like this...
...have obtained a special driving license!
Hey! Are you listening?
Hurry!
I think he's fainted after that blow!
This guy's just a pain in the ass,
what a waste of time!
- What! What did you say?
- Huh...
So I'm a pain in the ass?
Wait til I get you!
Get back here!
- Damn-it!
- Hey you, let me in!
- What are you doing?
- Where do you think you're going?
- Out of the way!
Damn-it!
He's chasing me!
Stop!
Stop, I say!
I'll get you!
Sooner or later I will!
Oh, no!
That guy's catching up to me!
The race isn't just a simple test drive!
Damn it!
What an idiot!
He can't even handle the curves!
I knew it!
All bark and no bite!
Perfect!
We're coming up on the corner!
He's right in front of me!
All right!
Move, you piece of junk!
I'm the best!
No one will ever beat me!
- He'll end up going off the track!
- Such power!
I knew it, you're just a beginner!
I'm the real driver here!
That's the guy
from the other day!
I have to
show off my skills!
Hey you! Are you okay?
Where? Where?
Just where did that guy get to?
Calm down! You've interrupted
the trials and smashed a car!
You've done enough, haven't you?
Have you quenched you're thirst for speed?
Not that I care but...
tell me who you are
and then you'll have to leave!
- How dare you speak to me like that?
- Didn't I tell you...
...to leave!
Take him away!
Let me go!
This morning, you're
family sent me this letter.
APPLICATION FOR WITHDRAWAL FROM SCHOOL
I'm sorry you have to leave so suddenly...
- ...and interrupt you're studies.
- Right!
I've already learned a lot here!
"He must quit for
using excessive force."
Father, I know you have
something to do with this!
Of course, I know it's been rough for you!
Don't you feel even a little
sad since you've left the house?
Not at all!
As you know, five years ago
I decided to come back here.
I wanted to talk to him
about what he had done to my mother.
For this reason I have no regrets,
in fact, I'm almost glad
that I got him to kick me out.
Can you even believe that?
Everyone knows you
misbehaved on purpose!
Maybe it's better that way!
Suddenly finding yourself
living alone and without help...
- ...will make you more responsible.
- I hope so.
Even so I'm not going!
That's just the easy way out!
Gunma, try not to think
about such things right now.
You know, today at the circuit...
- I saw that guy again.
- Which one?
- That one who chased us last night.
- Really?
I need to tell you something important.
I've made a decision:
I want to be on the
track for the rest of my life!
Cut it out already!
What did you say?
You know, this is the only
way I can talk to anyone!
Surprised?
Though I will need you're help!
Because you're a genius
when it comes to engines!
I can't keep doing this,
Gunma!
I can't leave my mother
alone to work in the fields!
- But, Tamotsu, you've gotta help me!
- I just can't!
First of all, you'll
need a lot of money,
a really big amount!
But you'll never have enough!
Would you say that
even if I had a mountain of money?
Gunma...
Why don't you use
you're brain for once!
What would you do
with that amount of cash?
And why should I give it to you?
When have you ever
done anything for our family?
Stop acting ridiculous!
But I'm not asking
for all the money, Shoma.
I just want to talk to Dad.
That's not necessary!
From now on...
...I'll be the one in
charge of our company!
Anyway, Dad wouldn't even
give you a penny!
Damn!
What's wrong, Yuki?
Mr. Gunma!
What a lovely surprise!
It about time that you...
...became responsible
for something, Shoma!
- Yes, it's really something!
- Now, Mr. Akagi,
can apply for the
House of Representatives.
- Shoma, please serve them drinks.
- Right.
Thank you!
It's time to say goodbye.
That lady...
A short while ago she told me...
...that I have to prepare you're suitcase!
Please, do not cry Yuki!
Are you leaving for good?
Yes, but I don't want to say goodbye!
Gunma, don't!
Gunma?
What's the meaning of this,
As you can see I'm obeying you're orders,
I'm going away aren't I!
I hope that I will
never see you again, Dad!
Soon you'll just forget about me...
Just like how you
forgot about my mother!
Please,
don't play the victim,
because, deep down, you
know you're not so different from me.
Understand these
words in memory of me.
Take a good look at my face.
You have a son a lot like you,
that bears the same name as you!
Fine then, I'll remember that!
Gunma.
Gunma?
Mr. Gunma!
Mr. Gunma.
Mr. Gunma...
Do you know how many
circuits are there in Japan? Eight!
And the best one of
all is the Suzuka circuit!
That's where this years
Formula One Grand Prix will be held!
In the next episode:
"Dear Mr. Tamotsu!".
"There are a lot of little Girls in Tokyo...".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away