Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
- He's in third place!
- What time did he get?
01:02:08!
Great! He's improved!
He's perfect today!
Gunma's Winning Everything!
Finally, an Invitation to F-3...
My warmest congratulations!
It must have been hard for you,
to win on the day of your debut.
Look, what was thing you
couldn't mention on the phone?
Sempai
I will see if everything is alright...
... during the next meeting.
There are still two races
until the end of the Season ...
...and if you win both,
nobody in the world...
...will be able to challenge you
since you've won three races already.
After all, with a combination
of great drivers I'm sure
the championship
will be quite the spectacle.
The commission will have
nothing to complain about.
Thank you very much.
I can't understand
why your in a hurry.
They are many people who
would be willing to sponsor
You can get great results
if you have the patience.
Thank you for your advice,
but I prefer to do my own thing.
- Your here too?
- I'm sorry, but I don't have,
time to waste!
Formula 3 is waiting for me!
I should be like that!
Though I'm pushing my car to the max!
Damn, this isn't fair.
Hooray! He passed mark and is
second with three laps to go!
So, what did he say?
He said it will be
discussed in the next meeting.
I want to change category.
The President,
has placed a condition:
I must win the next two races.
And so everything is
going as you wanted.
Next year you'll race in Formula 1!
Provided that my
illness does not betray me.
But I need to get to
Formula 1 no matter the cost.
Also to prove to myself ...
...that I am up to
the challenge, I must win.
I'm on the last lap now.
I am the fastest and no
one will ever beat me!
- He did it!
Sempai!
- You did it!
- It's the second win in four races!
If you manage to win the last race,
you will become the
champion in this category!
Yeah, I know!
Now stop fretting!
These are not the
victories that excite me!
I'm sick of this!
These races are for amateurs!
There is no satisfaction,
no one opposes me!
It's too easy to win.
You're right! The fact that
you win easily against amateurs,
means you're a step up!
Who the hell are you?
You know, the automobile
world does not end here!
This category, after all,
is only a stepping stone.
What do you say, Gunma Akagi,
Are you ready for Formula 3?
What kind of question is that?
Of course I will
compete in Formula 3!
Well then, here's my business card.
"Kuroi Racing Team"!
The name "Kuroi" is a guarantee!
I choose you because
your car goes fast!
I have a very close-knit team.
Join me an you'll go places.
You are an exceptional driver,
I know that you
are up to the challenge.
For this reason I've
decided to become your sponsor.
Somethings going on here.
I'll give you a couple
of days to think about it.
I expect you to call soon.
What luck! This is his first
big opportunity to shine!
I can't believe it!
It's like a dream!
Exactly, sounds a little fishy.
We just need to wait and see.
Why do you guys always
see the negative side of things?
Gunma is good, his car too...
...it's about time someone noticed him.
Wait a second, if he accepted this job,
he would be forced to
become part of a team.
Don't think about it too much.
We'll find another way.
I know this Kuroi.
In the past he had the
nickname "Terror of the tracks."
Eh?!
You may not know it,
but it's been several years since then.
I remember very well that
every race was a spectacle!
He was a reckless driver!
But he always managed to keep calm.
I don't want to be a buzz killer,
- but is your opinion true?
- Maybe.
I must admit that he
always was a honest driver.
Don't take him lightly.
He sounds like a legend,
- but he seems suspicious!
- I agree!
We should give him a pass,
since we can always...
...find another sponsor.
No!
It's my decision.
Think this through, Gunma.
You can't stop me?
In the end, it's my decision,
- don't you get that!
- How can you act like this!
He's right!
We care about your future ...
- and you should trust us!
- Don't you understand!
He told me that
I had great talent.
And that I was a great driver.
Looks like I'll take up his offer.
I'd be a fool to refuse!
I need to get to
Formula 3 no matter what.
I can't wait any longer, I should take
up his offer while I still can.
I absolutely want to race
in Formula 3 with Tamotsu!
Hey, are you ready?
Come on, let's go
celebrate my victory!
I want it to
be a memorable evening!
Hey, but Gunma!
Excuse me!
Sempai!
What an idiot!
Who is he kidding.
Tell me, Junko,
what do you think?
- About what?
- About Gunma of course!
He's moving away from us all...
...and we'll see him less.
He'll become like Ryuji!
What do you think, Junko?
I doesn't matter what I think.
It's his life...
...and he must seize the opportunity.
But you're hurting!
I can feel it!
Don't suffer like this.
Junko!
Just a moment!
You're forgetting the bags!
They contain your suits,
clothes and linen.
Less luggage I have, the better!
In the end,
I won't be gone forever.
Yes, but you're
going away for ten days.
Go now or you'll be late for work.
I asked for a day off.
Well ... since the
tests are starting today,
I'll come too, if you allow it.
I don't need dead weight, and I
mean you and the suitcases.
But I would like to be with you.
I promise I won't
give you any trouble.
Please let me come with you!
Oh, Junko...
I love you!
Wake up, it's time!
Damn, you woke
me up at the climax.
Come on,
the fateful day has arrived!
- Goodbye, I'll see you soon!
- Bye!
Oh, what luck!
I arrived just in time!
Why are you here?
Well, take this.
Consider it a liquidation.
Thank you, Morioka. I feel
sorry leaving, you'll be helpless
Don't mention it.
You should concentrate..
...on winning!
I wish you good luck.
- On becoming a professional!
- I'll make it!
Until yesterday you
were just an amateur,
but now everything will change.
You must not ever give up!
You have to keep winning ...
...and show everyone
your talent and skills,
Otherwise throw in the towel.
There's no going back now.
I got it.
Sempai!
Hi, did I make you wait?
Let's start the introductions.
This guy is an excellent driver.
His name is Gunma Akgai.
This is Gordon Turner,
the first pilot of our team
Hi there, my name's Gordon.
It's my pleasure!
What car is that?
A twenty year old Formula 1 car.
An old Formula 1 car?!
But then ...
Is that the car
which I will be racing with?
You got that right.
- What are you doing?
- Sempai!
What is this all about?
I didn't say you would be using it.
In this way you will experience
first hand the acceleration,
and deceleration and
as you go round a curve.
- This is necessary for racing
in Formula 1! - What?!
And just to let you know this car's...
speed varies from 300 kilometers
per hour to about 70 miles.
I assure you that
you will have the feeling ...
...of having your eyes removed.
Then your gut will
come up to you're throat.
Then you'll really want to drive!
Well, let's go!
Damn it!
I can't breathe!
We'll be turning to the right next...
We are on a straight line.
Let's go over 300 km/h!
My back is breaking!
I can feel it cracking!
Here we go! Deceleration!
I can't take it.
Excuse me, are you Gunma's girl?
Ah!
We're just good friends ...
...because we stay in the same building.
I don't see any difference!
Tell me, is he serious about...
-  becoming a great pilot?
- Of course!
Gunma really wants to
go to Formula 1!
Heading to Formula 1...!
He'll need some luck!
It would be wise
to take my advice.
You'll see when he comes off that car...
...that he'll be knocked out...
Well, he will recover,
but it will take time,
because believe me he'll
lost confidence in himself ...
...and never want to race again!
From then on he'll...
...need you to help
and encourage him.
Do you understand
what I'm saying, Miss?
In a nutshell, he'll probably
tell you he's going to quit,
and you should just let him quit.
You see, in Formula 3,
there are plenty of guys ...
...who believe they're good drivers...
...because they're friends
keep thinking they are.
Right, Gordon?
You know very well that every driver,
has their limits.
Changing category is not a joke!
If he leaves now he might
still leave with some pride.
A driver must have
the will to make it.
That is why it is
dangerous to let him believe ...
...that he's an excellent driver.
You understand? In this
sport, any error, is fatal!
Stay awake, boy?
Well! This is the last round!
It may seem despicable,
but I suggested to
Kuroi to use this method.
Twenty years ago, his dream
of going to Formula 1 was stalled.
Though he was a smart driver.
He is the best person to
tell us if your friend has talent!
Tell me, what will you do if
Gunma doesn't want want to quit?
This "method", as you called it,
may be torture but
it will make him better.
I can assure you
he will not give up.
What a temper! It's rare
to meet a girl so strong!
Yasu, you can untie him now.
- Gunma!
- Sempai!
Nothings wrong, calm down.
If I had really gone to
300 he would be dead.
I just tried to scare him,
by driving at a high speed.
This is amazing!
So far he's the only guy...
- ...to not get knocked out!
- What?
What were you
trying to do, kill me!
Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
- S-Sempai!
- Gunma!
Say what?! In Formula 3?!
Where did you find the money?
Tell me...
Well, I found a great sponsor.
Someone finally realized my talent.
I don't need you anymore.
I found a way
without your help!
- I'll soon be in Formula 1!
- Gunma.
- Oh!
- Gunma, what's wrong? Gunma!
Just where is sempai going?
Leave him alone! Some fresh
air may do him good.
He needs some
after a day like this.
Ah, what are you doing?
Is there something wrong sir?
No, the line was just cut.
Though I'm short on cash.
- What's wrong?
- Hiziri!
Gunma just told me
he's going to Formula 3!
But he didn't have time
to go into the details.
Well then, do you regret
joining me now?
Absolutely not!
By the way, do me a favor
and study these carefully.
They are new engine schematics.
- They gave you a new car?
- Yes! And next year ...
...I'll change category.
I'll still need your help.
Hiziri!
I hope...
...you don't let your illness
stop you from winning.
- A challenge ?!
- That's right Gunma...
...and if you win
you'll be in the next race.
It will be your first Formula
3 race, isn't it a bit early?
You shouldn't underestimate me!
In the next episode:
The Vicious Horse Rides an F-3
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you