STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
If you think you're the fastest, then try and take the lead!
You know what?
Your just one
asshole out of a thousand!
- Do you remember me?
- Yes!
- I never forget a face.
- I'm glad you do.
Now remember the face
of the man who will beat you!
Do you know
who you're talking to?
You only won because
I was driving a truck!
I'll beat you on the track!
What were you thinking?
- I do not know, Hiziri.
- I wasn't expecting this!
Can't you see that
he's just a rookie?
Don't go looking for trouble!
I'll get you.
Defend yourself!
I advise you to keep
your energy for the race.
Assuming that you're going.
Do you understand, boy?
I am a Genius!
Gunma vs. Hiziri! The Axles Scream!
Isn't that Gunma!
Gunma, could you
please go a bit faster!
Oh, shut up!
Damn it!
Gunma, do you even
know what you're doing?
- Go faster!
- I said shut up!
Alright, now I'll do it!
Ouch, my foot!
I feel sick...
...damn it all!
Gunma!
You alright?
Why aren't you going faster?
Will you shut up!
Either be...
...quiet or just go away!
It seems to me that
you're really annoyed!
I'm younger so
I have to follow you!
I would never dare to get ahead of you!
Then stay where you are!
There's no way I'll
be able to change gears!
Why is Gunma moving so slow?
Maybe he has gear problems?
There must be something
wrong with his machine!
If his machine keeps going...
so slow the engine could melt.
Right!
Sorry, Gunma, but we are moving ...
... at an average speed of 5 km / h!
Cut it out!
If you don't like it just go on ahead!
But ... But you're crying!
Are you hurt?
I came a long way to get
here and participate in this race,,
- Do you understand?
- Give it a rest!
Now who will pay for the damages?
I would give anything
to have automatic transmission!
Damn it!
My eye is swelling!
And I also have a fever!
Gunma, listen!
I think I've discovered ...
...why your moving so slow.
- Are you using your left foot?
- Mind your own business?
I'll tell you for your own good,
Gunma!
With one foot
hurt its impossible...
...to change gear!
You have my sympathy!
I know this isn't my business,
but you better come into the pits...
...so we can heal you.
Gunma, I'm sorry...!
That was a close one!
Gunma!
You gotta go to the pits.
Your foot could get worse!
Stop being a pain in the neck!
Wait... I could try using my right foot!
What?
Are you crazy!
I am the fastest!
Nobody in the world can beat me!
What is he doing?
I can do it with my right!
Lets see what else I can do!
Alright!
Fear me!
I can't believe my eyes!
He sure is lucky!
Everyone, eat my dust!
Out of my way!
I am the fastest!
I am the best in this race!
I've finally become a champion!
Look! It seems the rookie
has found some courage!
Okay, champion ...
it's me and you!
Damn it!
- Look, Peter! He's coming! N- Gunma!
GUNMA, PIT IN!
- Wow! Did you see that?
- He's amazing!
Am I wrong or was
he driving with one leg?
He seemed to be.
This is crazy!
What is he thinking?
I've never seen driving like that.
He must be pretty good!
Anyway what do I care!
Let's see what he can do,
he's only a little boy.
Is he drunk?
What is he thinking?
He's driving like a mad man!
I want to try too!
Damn it!
How can he...
...go round curves like that?
I'm coming for you, Haitani!
That mad man's coming!
He's behind Haitani!
- You will not succeed!
- We'll see!
- Once more!
- Help!
If you want my advice go back to...
...the nursery and drive your  tricycle!
You shouldn't have done that!
Look,
I have a bad feeling about this!
They'll both end up getting hurt!
- What can we do?
- You know that Gunma ...
...gets angry when he's in trouble!
We must act,
otherwise it will be too late!
When he gets angry
he's capable of anything!
You know, I am a perfect gentleman!
The most polite circuit driver.
Take this!
What do you think?
Was I polite enough?
- What do you mean?
- I hope that ...
I am wrong about
this whole thing though,
I doubt it!
I can't stand this!
How could he insult me like that!
Anyway, I've gotta move.
I won't give up this easily!
You will never overtake me!
You won't get away
with this! You'll see.
Frankly, I don't give a damn!
Go! Go! Go!
It's Hiziri I want!
Now it's just me and you, Hiziri!
I see, he finally
managed to overcome Haitani.
Though he is still behind by three laps.
Though in this round...
- ... he's was faster than Haitani! !
- I think he's in trouble!
Even though Gunma's
ahead he still has laps to do!
And he might not have enough time.
And he might run out of energy.
If this continues,
we may need a replacement.
Hang in there, my friend!
You can do it!
Damn it!
Another stupid curve!
I can't afford
to go off track.
And it's even harder
because I'm only using one leg!
I'll have to slow
down or else I'll crash!
But I can't slow down
because Haitani will overtake me!
This time I'll get you!
There is no alternative!
Hey, Haitani! Here's
another gift! Take it!
Perfect! It hit him!
Bye bye!
Damn!
Eh?! It's Gunma!
Hey, Kishida,
how's it hanging?
What!?
How dare he say that!
Gunma Akagi is phenomenal!
Even though he's in poor condition,
he managed to surpass Haitani!
Oh, finally! Here he is!
Hey, what happened?
Did you have an accident?
Thank goodness you weren't hurt!
I was worried!
- I'll take off your helmet for you!
- I'm fine!
- Gunma had an accident!
- Gunma had an accident?
I didn't notice!
What happened to him?
Apparently he can't
use his left foot!
- For real?!
- He's driving with his right foot!
So that's why he had
trouble about turning corners!
But, despite everything,
he managed to overcome Haitani!
Yes, he really does have
the Haitaniings of a champion!
Yet I still have a bad feeling about this.
Gunma, please don't take any risks!
Here he is!
Where are you, Hiziri?
GUNMA,
REMEMBER THAT YOU ARE A GENTLEMAN!
Cheers!
That car's starting to intrigue me.
If he keeps this up
he'll catch up to me,
he must really have a
great engine and mechanic!
He should work for me.
I'll contact him sooner or later!
Just you wait kid,
the race has only begun.
I've got you! You'll be
heading round the bend soon!
Perfect!
I'll show you!
- This is it!
- He won't stand a chance!
Okay!
Come on!
This is it!
I'm the fastest! Nobody
in the world can beat me!
Wonderful!
That engine is perfect!
What is he doing?
You idiot!
Out of the way!
It's time for my payback,
Gunma!
Take this!
Goodbye, brat!
Damn!
This isn't over yet!
Hey, kid, what are you doing?
No!
What are you doing?
- Isn't it obvious?
- Don't be stupid!
- Gunma!
- Sempai!
You're a lunatic!
I've done nothing
but return the favor!
- Stop it, Gunma!
- Just remember,
- You started it first! !
- What?! You provoked me!
You pushed me
to the edge of the road!
And you were the one
who started throwing shoes!
You don't understand!
That was in self-defense!
- Calm down, Gunma!
- Get off me! Get off me!
I'll have to teach you some manners.
- If I catch you, I ...
- That's enough!
This isn't over yet!
I'll give you a crash
course in manners!
- Please don't be reckless! !
- Don't worry!
I'll obey the rules!
No one can scold
me over my behavior!
I only responded
to his provocations!
Get your hands off of me!
I'd like to know which one
of you guys is his mechanic!
- Gunma!
- Stop being so barbaric!
You can't keep acting like this,
Gunma!
Sempai!
I'll teach you!
I'm dreaming!
This is just a dream!
For heaven's sake! Someone wake
me from this bad nightmare!
The cars used in F1
are not made from metal,
but from carbon fiber,
a special material
that is light and robust.
In the next episode:
"Gunma's in a Pinch!
Rival Hiziri! Approaches Tamotsu".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away