STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
I'm sorry for Gunma behaving rude,
I don't know how to apologize.
- But nothing serious happened!
- But he ...
- I saw your car!
- Eh?!
The one you prepared for Gunma.
I was very interested in it.
During the race I saw ...
...how his car was as equal as mine.
You must be a genius ...
- ...with cars.
- I'm actually a beginner.
Why don't the two of use become friends?
The Storm of Tsukuba Circuit,
Another Genius Appears
Okay, thank you very much.
I have just been informed
that the ship with your new car ...
- ... has arrived in port.
- Good.
Now I'll have a new machine
and a new mechanic.
Now you've put all that behind you.
I hope that you won't change girlfriend.
- In fact I already have!
- Eh?!
My true love came into port.
How can you compare me to a car?
It's absurd!
And that's why I'm such a great driver!
If I didn't love the car and the mechanic,
I wouldn't be a real driver.
Excuse me,
I'm going to take a shower.
Sempai.
How's your foot?
- Damn it!
- What's wrong?
The doctor said it was healed.
That's great! Hurray!
I'd had enough of
these stupid bandages!
Anyway thanks for your help.
Move it!
He's so smart.
SHIPPING SERVICE
I never though you'd heal so fast!
I was willing to bet that I was...
...going to race.
I'm unbeatable.
And it shows! You can
start training tomorrow!
There are only five days til the race.
So you've got to train for eight hours,
- for four days!
-  That's more than enough!
Now don't overdo it!
Eight hours is the bare minimum!
Stop whining!
Listen up!
This isn't a game!
Even a tenth of a second
can make a difference!
It's important that
you remember the path,
- So nothing goes wrong!
- Stop it!
The most important
thing is that you win!
Uhm ...
I have something
interesting to show you.
It might be useful!
I analyzed the track
in a scientific way ...
...and I got this detailed diagram,
in which I reported the
speed and trajectory ...
- ... to turn the corners!
- But how?
If you prepare well and
study your opponents,
no one can beat you.
Second.
You can't race on an empty stomach!
A nice plate of spaghetti!
Tell me, are you still
entrusting your new car ...
...to that young mechanic?
I don't see why I
should change my mind!
You look troubled.
Maybe your doubts are justified!
That guy is so young!
Don't worry,
everything will be fine.
You lost again!
Your not good at this are you?
You should quit!
- Anyway you owe me money!
- We'll see, I'll win the next one!
You never give up, do you?
You just got lucky,
you hear?
- Hello everyone!
- Welcome back!
I'll make dinner soon!
After I beat this cheater!
It's alright,
I've already eaten.
I was at the restaurant with Morioka.
Tamotsu, I decided to leave early tomorrow morning.
I'll go to the circuit to do some training.
- Eh?!
- Look!
My foot healed.
The doctor gave me the green light.
- But you can't!
- I can!
Hurry up and make your move!
- Here it is!
- Victory!
What did I tell you?
I knew that I would win!
Okay! Now I can
cook dinner, guys!
In my opinion you are not
yet ready to participate in that race.
What did you say?
Gunma,
don't you understand!
To be able to run on the track
you must first rehabilitate your foot!
Who do you think your talking to?
Let me go!
- I will race!
- Alright then!
Are you convinced?
If you had listened from the beginning,
this would not have happened!
Okay, but on one condition!
A condition?
I demand that you promise me one thing.
Whatever decision you intend to take,
you must tell me before hand,
By now you should know!
A mechanic and a driver
should understand each other!
We must work as if
we are a single person!
This is important to
the success of the race!
I hope your happy,
Tamotsu, but remember:
I will not race just to race,
I will race to win!,
Just remember, I will win!
It's strange that both Hiziri and
Haitani can't understand this!
- Gunma!
- How come your so slow?
I've done three laps already!
I told you to keep up!
I ain't that good.
Incredible!
Gunma's doing great!
- It's the engine!
- Hiziri!
You know, the straight, sharp bends, ...
Easily done by a driver like me,
But they become impossible to deal when ...
...you've got a bad setup!
Tell me, how old are you, Tamotsu?
Eighteen years old, the same as Gunma!
Eh?!
One wouldn't think so.
Thank you! I...
In fact, my father
was also a great mechanic.
I started very early with engines ...
...and I soon learned the trade.
- I feel sorry for you.
- Eh?!
In my opinion,
that car is wasted on Gunma.
Your more talented,
it should be yours.
He'll never become a good driver.
I'm sorry if my words
offended you.
There's no need.
I was not offended at all!
I think, that Gunma has
several chances of success!
If you say so ...!
Seeing him drive ...
...makes me think that
he won't be a great driver!
Well, we'll see!
I want to put him to the test!
Pay attention to what's happening now!
Gunma which way?
Did it work?
What happened?
See?
He had to guess the direction!
Up, down, right or left.
This test shows this!
Your friend, really is a strange one!
As kids we spent the
afternoon's on the river bank.
Gunma would always
read the trains advertisements.
The train passed at a
distance of about fifty meters!
"Hiking in the mountains.
Weekly departures throughout the summer.
For more information
contact the following number. "
I beg your pardon, friend.
It was not my intention to upset you!
- I'm not angry.
- I'll make you a promise:
I won't speak ill of Gunma,
Agree.
Let bygones be bygones.
But...
- I have to go now. Bye!
- Hiziri.
By the way ...
Do you remember?
My car arrived two days ago...
...straight from Europe!
- What are you saying?
Well, I thought you'd like a look.
You two should drop by
when you have the time.
A new car...
Lucky him!
I knew he wouldn't come!
Though he'll come around eventually.
He's probably just being stubborn!
I will succeed, my dear.
I just need more time.
My visit has only
served to test the water.
I'm sure that I can convince him.
At any cost!
Hey, what was that about?
It was nothing.
He seemed interested in you.
- Am I right?
- Don't be stupid!
Anyway you should concentrate on the race,
You should know that I
don't like being tricked by anyone ...
- ..even by you!
- Gunma!
Now it's serious,
The champion of the
world champion, Hiziri,
is racing!
He's mine!
Don't do anything crazy, Gunma!
Remember that we have to
go home as soon as possible!
Have you forgotten that
Morioka is waiting for us?
- Let him wait.
- Listen to me Gunma!
We still have a lot of work to do!
I am the fastest!
He won't beat me!
You're finally here!
What have you done to this engine?
It's a disaster!
I told you to follow the instructions!
I at least followed most of it!
- Is Gunma still on the track?
- Unfortunately!
- Gunma!
WE HAVE TO GO HOME!
Gunma is trying to beat Hiziri ...
and prove that he's the best!
He's such a great driver!
Damn it!
This won't be easy.
I must win! In fact I was the
one who started the challenge!
This guy's crazy!
I'm first.
You damn frog!
Did you have to do that?
Damn! Don't you know
there wasn't any time to break?
You were lucky!
You didn't die!
It's now leaking oil!
I'm afraid that won't be
able to fix it.
- It's very serious.
- I'm sorry about this.
Gunma, you could at least apologize!
Don't even think about it!
What are you thinking?
This was your fault!
You can't avoid
the blame this time!
Isn't that right, Hiziri?
How dare you speak to Hiziri like that!
- Apologize right now, Gunma!
- I won't!
- Gunma!
- The one who wins the championship ...
...should at least
know how to avoid a car!
Or did you do it on purpose.
because I though you were a pro!
Stop talking nonsense, Gunma!
- How dare you!
- Enough! stop this!
I am a human being just like you!
And as one,
I made a mistake!
If you want I could
help repair the car.
You gotta be kidding...
...a beginner could never repair it!
- But I just wanted to ...
- Let's go, Tamotsu!
Your just wasting your breath!
Let's get moving,
we have work to do at home!
We can't leave, we're the one's responsible!
It's okay, Tamotsu,
It's your choice.
- Thank you, Hiziri!
- Hiziri...
While you're there, do a general
overhaul of the car,
so that I can race with confidence,
You can do anything,
but on one condition:
put it back together again!
You have my word!
Alright, I trust you!
Great!
I'll do my best!
I didn't expect this from Hiziri.
He must have confidence in Tamotsu.
In any case, I don't trust him
Hiziri should have been able to dodge me.
Maybe he did it on purpose!
I'm sure he did it on purpose!
You've know it!
You didn't dodge on purpose!
I know you could have avoided it!
I wanted to test Tamotsu's abilities,
I just had to.
However, the accident on the track was beneficial.
So you did it on purpose!
Though I didn't expect
Tamotsu to help fix the car.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It took me a while but it's fixed.
- Very good!
- I admit that it was not easy!
Unfortunately, the damage to
the engine was considerable!
Thank you, Tamotsu!
You did well.
Though I'll be resting for a while since I'm tired.
Thank you again!
Tamotsu, can we go?
Have you finished
...being a good Samaritan?
- Gunma!
We have work to do at home,
don't you remember?
In have to go.
There shouldn't be any problems.
- if there is let me know!
- Bye, see you soon!
You done yet?
I'm coming!
So is Gunma training today?
Those two are desperate because
there are four days until the race!
And also he needs money to train.
- A lot of money!
- It must be hard for Tamotsu!
He spent all
morning at the circuit,
and then goes to work...
He works very hard!
He's still not back yet!
How much money do
they need for each race?
A lot of money!
That's what you need to race!
Just where is he?
Well he's probably doing something!
One minute, and eighty-two!
That's unheard of!
This engine is just perfect!
This engine does not miss a beat!
It's great!
Nobody will beat me!
Yes! I was right!
That boy is the one.
No one can beat me!
The cars run on two circuits:
Tsubuka and Suzuka.
Throughout the year,
there are 30 games in all!
Would you like to try?
In the next episode:
"The Blade of Elimination Matches!
Aim for the Pole Position".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away