STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Understand these
words in memory of me.
Take a good look at my face.
You have a son a lot like you,
that bears the same name as you!
Fine then, I'll remember that!
Dear Tamotsu! There are
a lot of little girls in Tokyo!
Excuse me!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Why are you sitting there?
You aren't at a restaurant!
You can't eat in the
middle of the road?
Be quiet,
or else you'll have trouble!
THE MEN WHO
DO NOT SURRENDER
"Driving School"?!
TESTS FOR
STATE DRIVING LICENSE
TESTS FOR LICENCE: A+A1,
B, C, B+E, C+E, D+E.
SPECIAL CLASSES HELD
EVERYDAY AND ON SUNDAY
STATE DRIVING SCHOOL
Attention: if you are already enrolled
in driving school
...please take a seat in a driving car.
I repeat.
Attention:
if you are already enrolled
in driving school
...please take a seat
in a driving car. Thank you.
Very well, we can start now.
Mr. Akagi,
Mr. Gunma Akagi is it?
It's true that you never
know who you could meet!
What a surprise!
Who would have thought?
The Queen of the circuit
is but a simple driving instructor.
Well then!
Can we go now?
Wait a minute, I
haven't told you yet!,
You must remember not to
break the most important rule!
Before getting into
a car it's a good idea...
...to always look around
as to avoid any accidents.
Unfortunately, on the streets,
accidents are waiting to happen!
For example, children could
be playing behind a the car.
So you have to always
look before you get in!
Or you'll be knocked out
just like before,
am I clear?
Now we can take the practice test!
Come on, get into the car.
To begin we'll take a
drive around the block!
What are you doing?
We're you listening!
The speed limit is 30 miles per hour.
It's essential to be
careful when driving.
I can't believe this!
You don't even have...
...a driver license!
Drive faster you...
- ...piece of junk!
- Where do you think you are?
Listen to me!
If you want to get a license...
...you have to do what I tell you!
Driving school's boring, you know!
This really is the "paradise of the turtles"!
I realize that I'm a beginner,
but that doesn't mean
I have to act like one!
Hi, Grandma!
How was the lesson?
It's really simple!
Just slow down to stop...
...and accelerate to move!
Come on, try it!
You know you can!
If you can't do that just go home
and look after the grandchildren!
I would like to know one thing:
the last time we saw each
...you said you wanted
to drive on the track.
Now you've got it!
That's why I decided...
to come to school
and get a valid license!
Listen, babe, wish me good luck.
Because I'm gonna be the fastest.
You can't be serious!
You'll never become a driver!
How do you know that?
You don't even know what it's like
to drive around the track!
Racing isn't a joke, boy!
- What? Boy?!
- Driving as a sport ...
...requires more than just brute strength...
...just like a boxer you've gotta train to win!
Don't you know that
the essential thing in this sport...
...is one's driving abilities!
A driver must be
quiet tempered when driving.
A driver must also work with a team!
And as a team you'll
fix a car's mechanical problems.
Driving isn't just a personal challenge!
If you don't have these qualities,
you'll never become a driver!
A driver must also be
smart so he doesn't crash!
I don't think the track
is the right place for you.
You must respect others,
especially when you'll be...
...... going 300 km/h!
Man, what a scolding!
You are too irresponsible!
Come on, now!
Perhaps, some practice,
will help you better understand
how to behave behind the wheel!
Open the door!
That's an order!
I told you to open the door!
I don't think so!
I didn't come to driving school...
...just to listen to someone preach!
Watch this!
You'll change your opinion of me...
...after you see this little stunt!
Get out!
Don't do anything crazy!
Get back here!
Get out of the way!
What an idiot!
I have to stop him!
Lady, don't you understand?
This is the stop line!
You must never cross it!
Hey, Grandma, go home and
look after the grandchildren!
Come back, you scoundrel!
And stop calling me grandma!
Why me!
He must be stopped!
Hey you!
Pull over right away!
I came here to get my driver's license!
Not to see some...
...idiot driving around!
This can't be happening!
In my day,
this wouldn't have happened!
Stop right now!
This is really too much!
I'll make him pay!
Hey, look at that!
Come on, keep going!
Wow, he's real fast!
We're all with you!
You can do it!
Attention!
There's a madman at the wheel!
Quickly, abandon your vehicle!
Abandon your vehicle!
Gunma Akagi, you scoundrel!
I'll get you!
This is amazing!
That boy's got talent!
- A real ace!
- I wish I was like him!
He should become a driver!
I can't believe this is happening!
This is amazing!
I haven't been this happy since 1915!
You're good at this!
I'll give you that at least!
Perfect! He's going towards a dead end!
STOP
Come on! I can't be beaten like this,
I can't let that happen!
I will not be beaten!
I won't alone anyone
to get in front of me!
It seems we're almost at the finish line!
I'll show you how
we deal with...
...people like you!
- I've gotta hurry!
- They might be hurt!
- Move it already!
- Theres been an accident!
Hey, kid, are you okay?
What an accident!
My dear Tamotsu,
how's life been treating you?
It's been fairly quiet here.
This city offers many opportunities.
I enrolled in a driving school
and was immediately promoted...
...thanks to my abilities!
- It's a miracle no one was hurt!
- But even so...
...what made him act this way?
I've learned a lot from using the tractor!
Unfortunately, my dear sir,
as you probably understand,
we have to reject your application.
But why? My driving skills
were awesome, weren't they?
- The same goes for the lady!
- Won't you reconsider?
I kindly ask you to
withdraw from this school.
That's not right!
And Tamotsu, the girls here in
the city are out of this world!
You know what?
I'm glad I came to live here!
I'm even in love
with a very beautiful girl!
Come on!
Gather round, everybody!
I'm not some circus freak!
Forget them, kid! Lets go!
Who cares anyway!
I'll just enroll at another school!
I go crazy for guys
who prove they have guts!
All young people
should show more character!
Don't you agree?
Come on, let's go get a cup of tea!
I'm sorry, but another time,
granny. I'm busy!
I only arrived a few days ago
and still don't know the city well.
I also need to find a place to sleep!
Really?!
Why didn't you tell me before?
KOMORI VILLA
Here we are.
You are really lucky!
Nowadays, it's impossible
to find cheap rooms...
... without giving at least
three months rent in advance.
I still have a room available.
You can have it.
You'll like it!
Come on, this way!
At least theres a bed!
- Of course! Would you have preferred the floor?
- It's also very comfortable!
It's just what you need!
I've also lived here...
...since the day I got married.
I spent the best
days of my life here!
This was our bedroom!
It hasn't been used ...
...since my husband
died two years ago!
Maybe it's better to
sleep in another room!
Don't expect to be sleeping in my room!
Only if you were here, Tamotsu!
I found a house!
A white mansion
surrounded in green!
This place is just too cool!
Not to mention the owner,
is a widow!
Young people are just full of energy!
It's just wonderful!
Young people always
give me such enthusiasm!
I feel like I have been reborn!
- Drink up!
- No thanks!
I turned this house into an
apartment building after being widowed
...then I rented out the
rooms to young people!
I'll introduce the
other tenants to you later!
They're all just like you!
- Come on, drink up!
- We're home!
- Hello, Grandma! Is dinner ready?
- Don't tell me it's dinner time already!
- And who is he?
He just arrived in town!
You're the one who caused
a lot of trouble at the circuit!
This is the worst day ever!
All because some
guy got carried away!
I'm home.
Grandma, what's with all the racket?
Hello!
Tamotsu, I hope
you come and see me soon.
Well, let's eat!
What is this guy doing here?
- What?
- More rice!
Join me, Tamotsu!
You won't regret it...
...you know you want to!
They have a lovely room just for you!
Don't listen to you're mother,
she'll never let you come!
I need you here!
Dear Tamotsu, I look forward to you're arrival!
With you by my side
I'll feel much better!
Who knows, one day...
we could become rich and famous!
Mom! Can you come?
There's a phone call for you!
- Yes, of course. I'm coming.
- What are you doing?
Nothing, I was just
looking for a screwdriver!
Gunma!
Just lying around all day will not...
...help you
get a drivers license!
- Here!
- What's this?
Books to help you get a drivers license.
I bought them myself!
You said you wanted to take
the exam for a driver's license...
...without attending driving school, right?
I thought about doing it myself!
- We'll study together, okay?
- Well... alright...
Who was on the phone?
They asked me if I could go to town!
Gunma's father is making a speech.
- I see that you don't want to waste time.
- Yes, that's right!
Maybe that's why his son is gone.
Tamotsu, tell me:
Are you envious of Gunma?
Why should I be? Gunma is
happy with the choice he made.
Stop pretending you don't understand.
Engines are your life.
Would you like to go to Gunma?
I really don't want to go.
It would be better if you didn't...
...follow in the
footsteps of your father.
M-maybe.
He only made mistakes in his life,
and was never
a man of character!
He truly lived his own life,
totally neglecting everyone else!
Everyone considered
him a great mechanic,
but then he started to
lose his friends, one by one...
and everyone hated him for that,
then he was truly alone!
But you're not like him.
He was a weak person,
and only created disappointment!
You're nothing like him!
What you go thinking, Mom?
Why are you telling me these things?
- You shouldn't have read that!
- I know, my son!
If you believe that
your future is in engines,
don't mind me,
honestly!
I will accept whatever
decision you make.
R-Really?
I am!
You're a man now!
Working on engines
has always been my dream.
I've always been
fascinated with mechanics.
If I become a
qualified technician,
then maybe one day
I'll become somebody!
What I lack is confidence in myself.
- You gain that in time.
My son, this is a difficult
and important decision.
Listening to your conscience,
and choose the right path.
Know that in spite of everything,
I have always loved your father.
I wish you luck, my child!
- Say hello to Gunma for me.
- Okay.
I know I can't help much but...
contact me
if you need me.
You're smart,
I know you can do it!
I'll miss you very much.
Goodbye!
Don't worry, Gunma will be in
good hands.
You'll see that he'll become famous.
Mom ...
Did you know that to drive on
the track you must have licenses A and B?
If you watch "engines
on the track" you'll understand more!
Next episode "Double-dealing his friendship,"
"Still his dream is the best in the world".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away