Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
Oh, Tamotsu, I'm in trouble!
Now that your with Hiziri,
I'm stuck with Konpon to do the repairs...
...and he's now my mechanic.
I need to get into Formula
3 as soon as possible!
Eh ?! What ?!
But where did
the others go?
Has Tamotsu Returned?
Gunma's Dramatic Change
But Gunma is left for last!
He's that last!
What happened to him?
I haven't got a clue.
I don't know.
But one thing is
absolutely certain:
Gunma must have
something tormenting him.
Maybe, though he might have
problems with the transmission.
Come on! We've got to
do something about it!
That's my money!
Don't you forget about it!
What is he doing?
Didn't...
...I fix up his car!
Just as I thought.
He's a misfit.
Damn it!
Why is this happening?
If this continues the
audience will fall asleep!
What's wrong with you?
Let go, you're hurting me!
Strange, your skin is
soft and delicate.
Morioka, what does this mean?
I've never seen anything
like this in my life!
Get away from me!
My allergy might...
...come back after your
paws touched me!
Don't do that again, understand?
He must be a great mechanic.
Even though his hands
are soft they're covered in blisters.
- What ?! Are you sure?
- So he's not a fake!
So then there wasn't anything wrong...
...with the transmission,
it must be something else.
Yeah, Gunma himself.
At the time of departure he
was overwhelmed with fear...
...and therefore couldn't concentrate.
When you lose you concentration,
it's impossible to race properly.
And if by a miracle he managed
to regain his composure,
the body will not respond
until there is tension and fear.
There he is!
Sempai!
I'm the fastest!
And no one will ever beat me!
What's wrong with him?
Has he gone mad?
He's changing gear
but he's driving straight!
Oh, no! Can we do nothing?
I know! I've come
up with a great idea!
After six laps I've
overtook only three cars.
And there's still nine laps to go!
Is that true?
If the drive isn't nice to him,
He'll damage your engine!
No! I won't believe it!
Remember, your victory or
defeat depends on my efforts!
Tamotsu! I need you!
Hey! Judging by your speed
I would say that the likes you!
Well, at least try to
remain on the track!
Oh! He overtook me!
Tamotsu.
Did he come back to me?
No, it' can't be!
He's working with Hiziri!
- Here he comes!
- Start moving.
- Well, did it work?
- I'm sure it worked.
Well, as a child I was told ...
By my teachers that this
was one of my strong suits!
Yeah, you sure are...
...but does he know it's a dummy?
Don't worry!
Our aim,
...is to make him think that
Tamotsu has come back!
- Right?
- That's right,
I can do it,
I'll keep at this until...
...Gunma wins the race.
Tamotsu, you came back after all,
I knew you cared about me.
Oh! He passed
four cars at once!
We did it!
Grandma you were great!
Great! He finally went faster!
Though this isn't his doing!
When I fix cars,
...they always go faster!
It's raining?
Look!
He's going faster!
It's starting to rain!
Hopefully this won't stop him.
Don't worry!
Can't you see...
...that with Tamotsu here
he will surely win!
That's right! I totally agree!
I didn't know that sempai had such....
...a deep
relationship with him.
I wonder what reaction he will...
...have considering it's just a dummy.
I've gotta be strong!
I don't care if the radiator melts...
...or the breaks get damaged.
This is it!
I'm going all out!
Look! He's surpassing Haitani.
Incredible! He increased
his speed despite the rain!
He'll win if he keeps it up!
I can't believe this!
I knew he was a great mechanic!
I've never gone as fast before!
Just like he said, he's a great mechanic!
What's wrong, don't you trust me?
Though one thing is
for certain, he's strange.
Fantastic!
You're the strongest! You're the strongest!
Keep it up, I didn't know
he could drive so fast!
If he keeps going fast,
he'll become the strongest!
Thanks for the help, Tamotsu!
Tamotsu...
- Oh, no! The rain ruined it!
- What!
Now that it's wet we can't repaint it!
What can we do now?
Only if we weren't excitied,
There's nothing we can do.
Damn!
He's got one more lap left!
The rain's stopped!
Sempai...
- But why?
- It doesn't matter...
...he would have found out eventually!
He's just got to hold on.
Gunma is almost in second place...
and they he'll have a chance to win!
We can't give up
on him at this point!
Where they just making fun of me!
I thought that was him...
...I actually thought he came back.
It was only a dummy!
What a joke!
I should have know better...
...how could I allow myself to be tricked!
They tricked me!
Damn it! This can't
be happening to me!
I though Haitani was great!
Better for us!
Now Gunma can win!
This is it!
Only one more car to overcome!
Come on, Gunma!
We know you can do it!
Hooray!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
- Hooray! He did it!
- He's won! Great job!
- Come on! Come on!
- You're the best!
Now you'll understand!
Next time never make a fool of me!
Oh, what the?
What was that for?
What did we ever do to him!
What's wrong with him?
He never changes!
You got that right!
He's so good that
he could win again!
I don't believe it!
Give me my money!
I want it now!
How can you take the
money when I didn't win.
And since I didn't win
you don't deserve the money.
What are you doing?
I deserve that money!
I was your fault, so I'll keep the money.
Take my hands off of me!
It's not my fault if you lost.
Weren't you paying attention on the last lap!
If the water wasn't leaking...
...you probably would
have won the race!
What did you say?
If you had serviced it better...
- I would have won!
- You have some nerve ...
- ...to blame me!
- Hey stop it!
- You mechanical misfit!
- Sempai!
- Gunma!
- Come on!
- Help!
- Get back here!
- Let me go!
- I won't!
- Stop it both of you!
- But my money!
Gunma! Gunma, control yourself!
- Man, what a show!
- Driving ain't so easy.
They say he wants
to go to Formula 3...
...all because Hiziri
got there before he did!
- What a spectacle!
- But to race in Formula 3...
- ...you need money!
- He'll need a sponsor.
Yeah, how sad.
Make sure that machine is well polished!
- I got it!
- And don't get cocky!
Just because you were
right doesn't mean your good!
Hey! Since your Hiziri's favorite we'll...
...make you work even harder!
- I understand!
- Good!
Then get to work immediately!
What do you want?
Hiziri wants you to
go to his studio.
It's rather important.
Cheers!
Come on.
- If you have something
to say then say it!
- You are a fool!
You let victory slip
through your fingers.
Why did you do that?
Even though you had my back...
...you made me think
that Tamotsu came back!
We're didn't mean to make fun of you.
We were hoping you'd stop worrying ...
...and concentrate on the race.
And this is the thanks
we get after all we've done.
Consider yourself lucky
that we are even celebrating!
However, since you saw
that dummy of ours,
you became more
focused on the race!
You were able to see
how important it was,
that Tamotsu needed
to be by your side!
You have quite the fragile,
unstable and emotional character...
...and how you always
need someone to help you!
What's wrong!
Sempai, calm down!
Next time be careful
about what you say!
Remember the old saying:
"The truth offends"!
This shows that, after
so long, I still don't know!
Listen up!
I'll tell you.
I don't need Tamotsu's help!
I don't want to talk about him.
Remember why I asked
you all to come here.
I have decided to appoint ...
...Tamotsu as the chief mechanic!
That's not fair.
He hasn't been here that long.
He's right, but we've
been here for years!
I know.
I know that you
are great mechanics ...
...and I'll remember you as such.
That's the reason why
I have always trusted you!
And, I will continue to do so.
Are you trying to humiliate us
..by making him the chief!
I need to win Formula 3.
Age and career don't matter!
Only your skills do!
I'm sure you agree
with what I said.
- Sure, boss!
Tamotsu is a very young boy,
but he is also very good.
He knows how to
communicate with the machine.
But I don't want to be chief!
I just want to take care of the car!
I'm sure that you'll be
fine with your work.
And we'll do our
best to help you, right?
But I can't!
Congratulations, boss!
It seems that I'm thanking you again.
Okay! From tomorrow everyone
will do their best to help Tamotsu!
They didn't accept that.
Disregard what others think!
B-But, they...
I asked you to come
here to take care of my car.
Now hurry up and
make sure it goes very loud!
Even just for a day!
Despite the rain,
Gunma could have won.
This time I'm really
tired of his tantrums!
I know.
Why are you laughing?
- I feel very relieved.
- Eh?!
Since Tamotsu is gone,
I saw Gunma react!
- He's never done that before.
- You're right.
Will I get by without the help of Tamotsu!
Tamotsu, I'll show you.
I will win one race after the other!
I'll win the next one,
and the one after that!
Everyone will adore me.
And next season I'll race
in Formula 3! That's a promise.
- Listen up, Gunma...
- What?! He's gone?
I'm sure he went to
Suzuka to watch Hiziri race!
In the next episode.
Gunma vs. Hiziri!!
I Am the Champ!
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you