Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
I don't know what to do!
I have no money, no car
and no driver's license!
I've got to find a solution.
I just can't give up the world of racing!
Hiziri's Disease Creeps Closer,
But I Am not Afraid of Death
I am concerned about Gunma!
- He isn't back yet!
- He'll be back soon!
Unfortunately, I have to
go back to the hotel.
If there is any news, let me know!
I am very sorry to have
kept you here all night.
- See you later.
- Wait!
Listen,
can you spare five minutes?
But how do I ask Hiziri?
Please, Tamotsu!
Remember who you once were.
...isn't he a friend of the president!
I beg you! He's the only
person who can intervene...
- ...and get back his license!
- I can't.
The fight wasn't his fault.
I was there.
He was provoked!
They can't do this without...
... giving him a chance to explain!
You must help him!
There is a lot of
work to do right now...
...and Hiziri is very busy!
But racing means the world to him.
- Help him!
- I can't promise anything.
But I will ask about it.
Though...I don't know
if Hiziri will do anything.
Well then, let us
know the answer.
- Alright, I will.
- Thank you.
Get out of there now!
Leave her alone!
This engine is great.
It would be a shame
if it was left in this dump.
You won't convince me,
your not getting it.
I don't need it anymore.
Because the have
withdrawn my license!
I couldn't drive
even if I wanted to.
I only came to see the machine.
Listen, can I ask you a question?
Why do you keep
it hidden like this?
I don't think
you can drive it.
- Well?
- Mind your own business!
In my opinion you have...
...prevented her
from making a career.
Well, what is it?
You wanted to ask me something,
I just wanted to know
if the route plan Hiziri ...
...made had been
studied with for the race.
Hiziri's road map?
- Why do you want to know that?
- Actually...
There are things
that concern me, but ...
What's the problem?
Why do you want to know my plans?
Hiziri!
It's nothing important,
I was just curious.
I wasn't born yesterday.
Tell me the real
reason your here, come on.
I can clearly see
that you need help.
I wanted to ask ...
- Is that true?
- That's right.
We can't do much.
When you told me to come over,
I expected something more.
Come on, what's the rest.
Well then, listen to me.
I know a guy that
could be very useful!
- You serious?
- Of course!
I'll let you know if you
promise not to behave as usual!
But you mustn't run away,
this is your only chance.
Hey, don't get my hopes up.
My hands are tied
without my license.
And yet ... I have to
race no matter the cost.
I have a score to settle with Hiziri.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah?
Until I have beaten him,
no one will take me
seriously as a driver.
Okay, okay, I get it.
Excuse me if
I've been a bit rude.
But I didn't expect this!
You caught me off guard!
Do you think I
should help him, well?
But your the
only one who can speak to the...
...President of the Federation!
I know the race is approaching...
...and that your really busy,
but I'm begging you.
You gotta do something
or Gunma will be ruined.
I don't know,
I wish I could help.
But I must say that Gunma
is lucky to have a friend like you
He's like a
brother to me, Hiziri.
You are invaluable to the team...
...and the constant concern
you have for him ...
...prevents you from
concentrating on my machine!
I don't like it.
Nothing should distract
you from your work.
Though I will talk to the president.
Hiziri!
I'm only doing it because
you make my car go faster.
- Is that alright, Tamotsu?
- Yes! That's great.
I'm sorry to ask...
But can you give
Gunma Akagi his license back.
Gunma Akagi must be special...
...if you are intervening for him.
They don't know him like I do
so they can't pass judgment like this.
Though i can't tell
whether he's worth it or not.
I just wish that you give
his license back and re-evaluate him.
Listen to me Hiziri, in my career
I have met many drivers.
But I have never met
one so uninterested as him.
I don't see what
the problem is here.
That's not the case!
Usually..
...we would get rid of the
driver because he is your rival.
Anyway, I'm interested in
seeing what will happen next.
How was your meeting
with the President?
He assured me he
would do everything possible.
But he couldn't guarantee success
because he's not the only one voting.
I didn't think you would
put in a good word for Gunma.
Why is that? Even the
most proud, over time,
must eventually soften up.
What's wrong?
It's just a plane.
Don't tell me you're scared!
It's nothing, it's over now.
- Don't worry.
- Hiziri, if you feel bad,
Don't be afraid to
tell me what's wrong.
Ruiko!
What's wrong with Hiziri?
Emergency Room
I understand, he's inside.
He's regained
consciousness right now.
We've calmed him down,
but he needs to rest.
Though we can't be too
sure until the tests are done.
Of course we are
doing the best we can.
Though I'm not sure
how much longer he will last...
Take my advice and
keep him in the hospital.
Do you think Gunma
will return this evening?
What happened Tamotsu?
You said you would phone me.
Sempai!
Where are you going?
We're all worried about you.
Want something to eat?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I don't want you to be angry.
- Come on, I'll make it real fast!
- I'm not hungry.
What's wrong with you?
Even if your sad,
that can't change anything.
It's easy to talk when
your not the one in trouble.
Gunma!
Now what are we gonna do?
His condition is serious.
He can't participate in the next race!
It's clear that he
will not go to Europe!
And his dreams of
Formula 1 will just fade away.
Where are you going?
Come back!
The doctor said you
have to rest! You can't leave.
Let's go home.
- How are you feeling?
- Ah...
I feel slightly better.
But I feel weak
when I turn my head.
Is this the end?
While in the hospital I had
the most beautiful dream of my life.
I dreamed of racing in Formula 1!
I would like to know
why this room is so dark!
Turn on the light, please!
Hiziri, what's wrong?
Are you hurt? Can't you see?
- It's alright.!
- But you said ...
It was just a normal attack!
I just have to change the program!
You go to the circuit.
No person in the world
has the right to stop me!
No one can stop me
from driving! Up until the end!
I am not afraid! I am no
longer afraid of death!
My state of mind even
surprises myself sometimes.
I realize that my driving style ...
...since I've started driving in Formula 3.
I never imagined ...
...that the fear of
death would change me.
At first I thought I could get ...
...rid of it thought driving.
But now everything is different.
I'm used to living with his shadow!
And he's now
a good friend of mine.
There I expect a better world!
Where my rivalry does not exist!
The wall inside of me,
has given me comfort ...
...when I'm up against
the outside wall of speed...
Now neither of them exist any more!
There is nothing that limits me!
Now I can only pray to
have no attacks during the race.
Good evening! I found by chance,
You were right to call me.
We needed to talk.
Yes, yes.
What ?!
They've withdrawn the license?
But now he can't compete.
Indeed, this is troublesome.
- His career is over!
- I...
Is that so...
Hello, hello...
Hello, hello.
Gunma!
Hiziri, my friend, you have to
keep on fighting till the end!
Don't give up!
- Eh ?! He quit with the races?
- Don't be silly!
Don't you ever ask Hiziri
for help with my license!
- But, Gunma...
- Shut up!
In the next episode:
Gunma Draws the Line!
The Enemy's Compassion Is Bitter
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you