STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Please, make sure
he passes the test!
Gunma is unstable!
They will throw him out!
He can only get a license if,
you help him.
You have to!
I'm not sure about this.
Please, Junko!
You've gotta help.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
Junko's Private Lesson!
Now I've got my license
Wake up, Tamotsu!
You snooze you lose!
Why are you waking
me up at this time, Gunma?
Must you ask?
We're working out. Come on!
Come on! We've got the power, Gunma!
Sure! We're athletes after all!
We've got to keep in
shape in case we need to run.
I admire you, Gunma,
but you still have a way to go!
- And what's that?
- There are quizzes in driving school.
Now answer yes or
no to a few questions!
Stop with the bullshit!
To get a driving license,
first of all,
-  you need to pass a written exam!
- I know!
First question: "You
have a date with a girl...
...but your late.
On the way, you,
run into a series of red lights.
Do you drive through it?
- Of course!
- Be serious for once!
You know that you
stop at a red light!
You'll never get a
drivers license at this rate!
So sorry, friend, but when there's a girl involved...
...nothing can stop me!
Moving onto the second question:
"You are progressing
at a moderate pace ...
... attempt to overtake a car.
What do you let it pass?
Absolutely not!
No one can surpass me!
Third question:
"On the way ...
...you come near a bump.
The visibility is very poor, what
do you do? Slow down or not? "
I pass over the
bump since it's fun!
Fourth question: "There a
traffic jam in an intersection ...
not regulated by traffic lights.
In this case ...
do you comply with the rules?!"
Of course not!
No car will pass me!
Fifth question: "Do you
fall asleep, or keep driving?"
Fall asleep at the wheel!
Sixth question: "You are near a walkway.
There are pedestrians,
do you stop and let them cross?"
But in this case,
the pedestrian is ...
- ... a girl in a miniskirt!
- Stop!
- You'll stop?
- Am I wrong or do pedestrians...
...always go first?
You said stop! You stopped!
Finally you stopped!
- Was my answer funny?
You two sure are up early!
- Hello!
- Hello! , Junko!
- Hello, Tamotsu!
- Good Morning! Wait, Junko!
- About that matter yesterday evening ...
- Tamotsu, what are you doing? Come on!
Tamotsu!
I am not a magician
with engines, Gunma is!
He's the real genius!
And you have to help him!
What was that about?!
- Was he just saying hello?
- Junko, what was he talking about?
Nothing important.
You know, Tamotsu,
I want to do the exam today!
What?! This is madness!
You don't even
know the traffic rules!
Stop it!
You know that I have no time to lose!
Do not rush!
- I don't think it's worth it.
- What?!
- Please, Junko!
- Look, if you want I can give you ...
...driving lessons in the afternoon
It's my day off.
Junko, thank you!
Can't you at least thank her?
To be honest,
I'm doing it out of pity!
Tamotsu knows this,
so I promised to help.
I'll be in my room.
What was that?
This is wonderful!
It's so different from our room!
You can tell right
away that it's a girls room!
Please, sit down.
- Where are you two going?
- Get your hands off me!
If you hope to have her
all for yourself, you're wrong!
What are you talking about?
Have you already forgotten ...
...that me and you are studying together,?
Well, I've changed my mind!
- I think I know why!
- What?!
I'm sure you will take
advantage of the driving lessons ...
...and try to grope her.
How can you say that?
Did I look like a ...
- ...someone who would do that?
- Of course!
Well, anyway, that's enough,
Your annoying me!
So, Junko ...
Let's work as two good friends.
Okay...
Don't touch me!
Why are you looking
at me like that?
You're so cute!
Listen, before starting
our first lesson,
I would like to
clarify one thing:
I am nothing like you!
Remember it well!
You've got a strong character.
I like that.
Look! Up there?
There's nothing to worry about.
If Gunma had that in mind
he would lose he teeth.
Junko is tough, you know?
I get the impression
that he wants to, but...
Read the second part.
So: "Parking is prohibited in
the vicinity of curves or bumps."
Enough!
I've got a headache!
Let's do something
more fun, please.
Just keep reading!
Look here,
what does this mean?
Come on, do it like me!
- Do as I told you!
- Alright!
- Now don't move!
- What kind of game is this?
You'll see!
- No! No!
- Well, lets resume!
Hey, wait!
This is most unorthodox!
So ... "Parking is prohibited
in the following cases:
- When you are in the vicinity
of curves or bumps... - Well...
Good evening!
Hi, Tamotsu!
Did you finish the repairs?
Yes! And I did a general
overhaul of the engine.
You can test
drive it if you like.
Fantastic!
It's just like new!
You're great, Tamotsu!
By the way, where is Junko?
Junko... Uhm...
I don't know where she is!
What?! Are you saying that
she spent the whole afternoon ...
...studying with that guy!?
I bet she wasted her time!
- Yeah.
Why didn't you stop them?
What are you looking at?
Isn't this enough?
- Gunma...
- Priority must be given ...
to those that come from the right.
Okay! You've learned that!
And now onto the practical test.
Let's move!
This lesson is important so don't fail!
I want to make sure
that the engine is working.
- Please, can I come too!
- Theres no room.
Oh, no!
Now reverse, turn
left and then right.
Now consider you
options very carefully!
Before leaving,
you should always look ...
in the rear view
and side mirror.
Then you can turn safely.
To turn left you
have to get closer ...
...to the middle of the road.
Now, to turn right, keep ...
Who told you to do that?
It's time, guys!
Where are they going?
- Stop right there!
- It's time to have fun!
I'd had enough of
all this useless chatter!
You're a fool!
That is not the way we do it ...
- ...in driving school! !
- Watch out!
I have to turn right, right?
You could have killed him!
Do something, you two!
What's with all the screaming?
I haven't done anything.
Stop! I told you to stop!
Hey, look over there!
It's suicidal ...
... to drive in this traffic!
Watch out! There is a huge truck!
I have to turn left, right?
Left or right?
These three are
knocked out cold!
Don't try that again!
- How you doing, Gunma?
- Not bad!
Grandma, to do these exams you need,
to have lots of luck!
Is that all?
Grandma just copied
Gunma and got it all wrong!
- That's funny!
-Oh, poor me!
I'll never have enough luck!
Gunma's finally ready!
Do you think he'll pass the exam?
He'll have no problem passing it!
- I hope everything goes well!
- Of course it will!
He can't fail again!
Gunma is late today.
Maybe he went home.
I told you he wouldn't show!
I won the bet.
We've got to see if he comes first!
Stop this you guys!
Is this the car that
Gunma spent all that money on?
- Does the engine work?
- Of course it works!
Obviously it's a used engine,
but it's great,
almost good as new.
Have you got news
about Gunma's exam?
- Not yet.
- He's still not here?!
It's already four!
Stay calm,
he'll be here...
...it's not like he
jumped off a bridge!
Were you talking about me?
Gunma!
How come it took you so long?
We were all worried about you!
Sorry, I was tired.
I've never seen him so down.
I don't think he passed.
I wonder how Gunma did?
He looks sad, maybe he failed!
I'm think I lost the bet!
That's my lunch.
So, don't keep us in suspense!
How was the exam?
Tamotsu, you see, I ...
Excuse me.
Ready? Yes, I'm Martin.
Hello, Mr. Jordan!
Yes! I understand perfectly.
That's fine. I understand!
We'll take the car tomorrow!
Gunma!
Here! My dream!
I have a mad desire to
hear the song of your engine.
Tamotsu! Could you
turn it on, please?
Certainly.
But tell me, how as the exam?
Perhaps it is best to humor him.
We all know,
- how it went.
- Yes, but...
If he gets angry
all hell will break loose!
Maybe he's just trying to be brave.
Excuse me.
You've failed, didn't you, Gunma?
And this is the gear shift, right?
Tell me, what's wrong with you?
Its a melancholy roar!
I don't understand this strange behavior.
I lost the bet!
Here we go!
Damn, I didn't expect this!
This is too much!
Your really...
You really something!
- Where did he go?
- Probably to the police station.
Then turn that way!
What's happening?
The body is touching the ground!
Stop! That's an order! Stop!
You won't catch me!
I am the fastest
driver in the world!
What's wrong with you?
Get out of the car! Now!
What?!
You told me to get out!
I hope your expecting resistance!
He's crazy!
Don't waste your time with him.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute!
I am in possession
of a valid driving license!
So what?
Arrest him!
How can you?
You can't do this! Help!
That's what he gets.
For him, it's just
business as usual.
Let me go!
Let me go, I said!
For once I'm right!
Can't you see my license!
All drivers need a license,
though you can't go full speed!
So don't break the rules!
What?!
I already knew the rules?
In the next episode:
"Junko's Love! He's the Guy
Who Saw the Limit of Speed".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away