STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Yes, that's exactly
what's happening!
I'll tell Shoma that he
shouldn't treat you badly!
- Gunma...
- Yuki...
I will not let you face
the same fate of my mother!
Farewell Hometown!
He Learns an Unbelievable Secret
Hey, wait for me, Shoma!
According to me you
were too relentless with Gunma.
In the end he
is always your brother.
I know, but even our father ...
he never considered
him a son like us.
Gunma is different from us.
And why are you siding with him?
Well, it's because ...
I love him very much!
However, I know that you
accompanied him the station.
He has a dangerous
tendency to get into trouble.
And he better stay away!
I'm very sorry.
Send the others away.
We need to talk in private.
This should be
enough to get you home!
And don't come back here!
Go on, pick it up!
I hope it's enough.
Stop it, Shoma!
Don't try to humiliate me!
I don't want your charity!
Or don't take the money.
However, I strongly advise
you to leave here at once.
Yuma, come on!
What are your intentions with Yuki?
You better take care of her!
I thought you wanted money
but your here to blackmail me!
Are you tired, dear?
My job is certainly not the easiest.
Soon it will be over.
Shoma and Yuma are
making great progress.
We have two smart children,
don't you think so?
- Gunma!
- Keep your dirty money!
I want none of it!
Are you looking for a fight!
Don't you touch
me ever again, got it?
I'm waiting for your answer, Shoma!
You'll take responsibility
by marrying her, right?
Please, stop it now!
- Dad, stop!
- Shut up!
Open your ears!
You can no longer afford ...
- ... to make a fool of me!
- What are you saying?
Shoma and I were
discussing a personal matter.
Get out! I don't want
to see you ever again!
You have nothing to
do with us, understand?
Shoma, I have to go
to an important meeting,
but I think you'd
better go in my place.
- I'm already late!
- I'm going now!
One moment, Shoma!
You still owe me answer!
Shut up!
Gunma,
He has nothing to
do with a wimp like you!
You're not part of our family!
I'll remind you that
the elections are close,
I don't think you
can afford to kill me!
But if you want to
risk it, then kill me!
Mr. Gunma, stop it, please!
Apologize instead!
I've never seen your father so angry!
- Father!
- What are you waiting for?
- Will you be quiet?
- Are you going to make me?
I speak because
I'm not afraid of you!
Go, on! We will see how
your career will benefit!
I want to become Member of Parliament!
And I will not let a wimp like you ...
...shame the whole family!
So now, I'll let you go.
Your just an old fart!
Are you afraid of a scandal?
I'll never see you again!
I'll make you pay!
You two!  If you have
something to say, say it!
- He will never understand!
- Gunma!
Yuki!
I wonder where he's gone
to mess around, this time?
I've forgone sleep waiting for him!
Well, maybe he went to his house.
Perhaps. But I think that
he would have told us,
Gunma isn't on good
terms with his family.
Does anyone want coffee?
But ... Tamotsu,
aren't you working today?
It's already
past nine o'clock?
Really?!
I hope Morioka isn't angry!
Today is my first day off.
I'll stay in the house all afternoon.
- As soon as he arrives, I'll call you.
- Thank you, Junko.
Okay! I think I'll get
a good night's sleep!
Gunma probably went to look for someone...
...to give him a loan,
or to see Kishida in the hospital.
I've had enough of this!
Gunma, come back soon.
Your aspirations and dreams
are the same as mine,
Only we have chosen
different paths to achieve them.
But we won't succeed if
we don't work together!
Gunma...Come back!
I need you.
We need to stick together.
Ah, he just walked in.
- Huh?
- Hiziri wants to talk to you.
Hi, I'm sorry about
yesterday, I was out.
So, have you read the contract?
If there is something wrong,
I am willing to change it.
Can't we talk about
that in a few days?
Is it not to your liking?
If something needs changed, tell me?
I can't make a decision
like this right away.
Try to understand,
I need time to think!
Have you talked with Gunma?
Listen, I assure you
that it is a contract ...
...that is open and transparent.
Well, to be precise.
I have already organized
some work for you.
I've also already made a
despot to you bank account.
Five million!
You can start whenever you want.
Yes ... Thank you!
AKAGI FAMILY
Mom ...
Gunma ... If anything bad
should happen,
take this ring, it's yours.
It's the only thing I've
asked your father for in my entire life.
Keep it to remember me by,
and don't sell it.
Unless you are in trouble!
Promise me, Gunma!
Even if you are short on
money, don't sell it!
Never get rid of it...
...it's the only thing you
have to remember me.
I'm so worried about you!
You see, my boy, I want
you to use my gift ...
only if your future is in stake!
Do you understand?
Promise me this.
Don't worry mother,
I kept my promise.
KUMADA JEWELRY - WE BUY
PRECIOUS STONES FOR GREAT PRICES
So what is your assessment?
Fifty million? One hundred million?
Or are you not saying
because it's worth half a billion?
I am very sorry,
but this stone is fake!
What ?! That can't be ?!
The ring is worth at
maximum, fifty thousand yen!
This is impossible!
Sorry, but it's the best I can offer!
- This isn't true!
- Young man! What do you want to do?
Did she know that it was a fake?
Calm down, please!
Please, calm down!
It's the only thing I've
...asked your father
for in my entire life.
Are you sure it's a fake?
- I'm sure..
- I understand ...
How about seventy
thousand yen for it, then!
- No, thank you.
- That's all right,
I'll take it anyway.
I already said that I don't want to sell it!
I will not sell
it even for a billion!
Is the lens defective?
No, it can not be!
A pauper like that ...
cannot own a diamond
that is worth a billion.
It can't be true!
- Honey, dinner is on the table!
- Right.
I'm right.
It can't be true.
- Be strong!
- Don't you see?
He mocked my mother by ..
...buying her this fake!
- What now?
- Well, I don't know.
I have an idea!
Would you like to come to town with me?
Even if you married Shoma,
you wouldn't be happy!
You could start all over again.
But...
Remember you promised
to be honest with me.
You need to stop
being afraid of my brother.
If you have problems,
I can fix them!
What do you say?
- Why not? ?
- Because ...
- ... Junko would suffer.
- What?
Hey, more beer, honey!
- We need to celebrate! Hurry!
Don't you understand
that when Shoma tires of you,
he will leave you?
What will you do then?
- Hey, you're not half bad?
- Get your paws off!
That is enough!
Yuki, come with me.
I just can't.
Gunma.
Thank you so much, but
I'm making my own way now.
Yuki...
Oh, it seems like you're
having a serious talk!
I bet she dumped you, boy!
It's humiliating to
see you beg, just stop!
Understand that she doesn't want you!
But I'm really curious to
hear more of this conversation!
- Go on, keep going!
- Look here!
This is ridiculous! He bought
her a ring! A ring, you know ?!
Boy, did you think to
win her over with a ring...
...which can be found on any stand?
Instead of the ring, get her a car!
It's the better
option, you know?
Remove your smelly foot
immediately from that ring!
Are you deaf?
I told you to remove your foot!
I see you know
how to fight, young man!
Gunma!
It's the only thing I've
asked your father for...
So that's it...! Gunma
is having financial difficulties.
I found a solution!
He could drive with my car!
I know I don't have
what it takes ..
... to become a great
driver, you know?
Anyway, following this dreadful accident,
my family has practically forced ...
...me to get rid of my
race car as soon as possible!
And since that's happening,
I would like Gunma to have it!
Thank you, Kishida!
I know that Gunma will...
be overjoyed by this news.
Thanks again!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Are you sure about this?
Don't worry. I am happy
to give my car to Gunma!
If there's on thing he
needs to do, it's to win!
Yeah, I can't wait to
give the good news to Tamotsu!
Yes?
Gunma, it's you?
Gunma, why can't
you behave properly?
Before you disappear again,
don't get caught...
...for speeding!
You could have told us ...
...that you went to your family.
Remember that, okay?
And Tamotsu was worried!
Hey! Are you listening?
I don't know what happened,
but based on his mood,
he probably doesn't have the money.
Hey, Gunma, don't
be so sad!
I have good news! Look!
Sempai!
He told me that if you
feel like it, you can race with his car!
Do you realize that in this way ...
...you can participate in that race?
- Sempai!
- Come on!
Kishida, are you serious?
Of course!
The car is all yours!
- Sempai!
- Don't you think...
...that it's time to at least react!
Come on Gunma, show
us what your made of!
- Sempai!
- You're an angel!
I don't want you to thank me,
I just want you to be happy!
To be honest...
My opinion on your car is...
that it's not a technical masterpiece.
Though with my abilities,
victory is assured!
Wouldn't you say?
- Wouldn't you say?
- Yes!
Yuki, I swear I'll make it!
I will win for you too!
I promise you, Gunma, I won't,
End up like your mother.
If the car had a problem
on the track, the drive ...
...must solve it without any help!
The other alternative
is to go into the pit!
In the next episode:
Tamotsu is Shaken!
Hiziri Conceals a Horrible Secret!
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away