STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Hiziri, who do you
think will come first?
We'll know when the race ends.
But it will certainly be the
car with the best setup...
...and the driver with the best mechanic.
Short Lived First Victory!
Tamotsu's Betrayal
Move it!
Damn it!
In addition to being an idiot,
you can't drive!
It takes technique, boy! Technique!
You can't hope to win against me!
Go!
What's he doing?
He's getting close...
...to force me to speed up
while going round the corner!
Is he crazy! He's trying to
knock me off the track!
This is it!
Time to slow down.
Now he will be
forced to slow down!
I must hold on!
This is it.
Technique! It takes technique!
You can't hope to win against me, boy!
Hey! But where am I?
What happened?
- Way to go, Gunma!
- Hooray!
Wow! For a beginner
he's really strong!
Gunma...
Well, I can also gain
the crowds admiration.
I will become a star like Hiziri!
Hey, listen up!
Make sure that the rookie
does not cross the finish line!
Sempai's amazing!
He sure is!
What's the time?
01:01:58!
Are you sure?
A new record!
Incredible!
These test's are improving his times.
He couldn't have drove
like this months ago!
Well, he did say that
he would win this race...
- ...so he will!
- You're right! He'll win!
Did you see that Hiziri?
That novice could
win at this rate!
The race is getting interesting!
If he keeps this up he'll...
- win by a large margin
- He won't win ...
- ...that easily!
- What do you mean?
You see,
even a few years ago ...
I too was
a complete novice.
But, when you start to win,
everyone pays attention!
That's the truth!
Fantastic!
He's improving with every lap!
He's way
ahead of the others!
- There are only three laps left!
- Hold on Gunma.
I hope he won't need my...
assistance,
at least for a while!
Eh?!
What did you just say?
I though you said that you
hope that Gunma didn't need you.
Eh?! What?!
Why would I say such a thing?
Sempai!
That's against the rules!
I knew it,
everyone loves me!
They won't give way even
though he's a lap in front of them!
They aren't allowed to do that!
They're doing that because...
...they want him to proceed slowly!
Since they're behind a few laps...
...they can afford to do so!
Come on, Gunma! Go on the
attack!  Victory is yours!
Did you know this would happen?
- Yes!
- Has it ever happened to you?
- No, never!
- And you others?
I consider it a waste of time
and a futile gesture.
Come on,
get out of my way!
Move! Do you hear me?
Victory will be mine!
We'll see!
Are you getting out
of the way or not!
Sempai, you need to do better.
You made an idiot of
yourself before the race...
...this is just the after effects!
This is all happening on purpose!
As long as you drive on the track,
you will be surrounded by enemies!
This is because of your personality.
Gunma, it's up to you
to solve this predicament!
Do not rely on the car,
you have to rely on your skills!
You can do it Gunma,
lets see what your made off!
Damn it!
I have to do this!
Listen you idiots!
Now you'll see what I can do!
Gunma!
- Impossible! I must be dreaming!
- I should have taken a picture!
- How did he do that?
- I don't know.
- I wonder how...!
- He's the best driver in the world!
- I can hardly believe my eyes!
- Hand me the glasses.
It's just me and you!
- Victory!
- Gunma, you're great!
Those are my glasses.
He's almost won!
Come on!
Aren't you the fastest driver in the world?
You can't lose!
Oh...! I'm sorry.
Gunma, you've finally you made it!
You have won!
Wow!
Now that's a surprise!
Then the record that was
made during morning practice ...
...wasn't just a mistake!
We'll go and congratulate him.
Why don't you come...
...and meet him,
didn't you say you would?
You two should meet and
take a few photographs.
Come on, please!
- Sempai!
- You were great!
Congratulations!
Gunma!
You were terrific!
You deserve a great big kiss!
You take her.
Gunma!
Your lip is bleeding!
Are you alright?
Eh ?! It's nothing!
I bit the inside of my cheek ...
...when I passed that group of cars!
Next time, take more care.
- You shouldn't worry!
- Congratulations!
I am from the magazine "Race".
You were awesome.
You broke the record in a trial,
and you also won the race!
From the magazine "Race"?!
Yeah, I guess I earned it!
Can I take a photo while you ...
- ... have a handshake with ...
- Okay, okay!
You can take all the pictures
you want, come on Tamotsu!
Great, all we need to do is take a
photo of you and Hiziri!
What?!
Hiziri.
Well, about that handshake.
Now smile for the camera!
What is he doing?
That's the champion!
I'll never hold the hand...
...of an asshole!
I'm sorry about this Hiziri.
It's alright.
I expected as much.
That's just the way he is.
- Excuse him!
- What?
Gunma!
Have a drink with us..
We've gotta celebrate!
I've got some French champagne!
Champagne you say?
It's like I'm peeing champagne!
Grandma ...
Hiziri!
I'm sorry Hiziri.
Gunma has behaved terribly!
- I came to apologize to you!
- There's no need.
That machine you put
together is really something...
as I expected of you.
Anyone could win
with a car like that.
Thank you, but I don't
deserve all the credit.
Gunma only won because
of his excellent abilities!s
In fact, his driving has improved a lot.
But in the end what
matters most is still the car!
Hiziri.
I won't give up on you.
In your current state of
health you shouldn't drive.
Please, forget it!
- In order to win I need you.
- But I...
Tomorrow morning we
leave for the next circuit.
I hope you've got the message.
I'm counting on you!
Bye, I'll see you there.
Gunma!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Hey you know,
Is this the way
to celebrate my victory?
Drinking a fourth beer in a tavern!
I would rather be in a fancy restaurant,
surrounded by beautiful girls!
- You really are a true champion!
- Your lovely!
Why don't we have some fun?
This is the way I
would like to celebrate!
- Ehi!
- I'm sorry!
Gunma say sorry!
You know what? Thanks to
you, during the race,
- I seemed to be flying!
- I know!
Today you drove like a pro!
Our eyes were literally glued to you!
But this is only a small step.
I want to get
to race in Formula 1.
Just where are Junko and
the others? I'm getting hungry!
Well, Gunma... I asked
them to arrive a little late.
Well, I did ...
...so because I wanted
to have a talk with you.
Hiziri asked me to become ...
...his mechanic and I accepted!
- What? Why did you do that?
- Hiziri...
...will be making his
debut in Formula 3 next week.
And tomorrow
morning I leave with him.
From now on I can
no longer take care of your car.
But now you're an experienced
driver and you'll be fine.
Did you betray me just for money!
That's not true. That's the last
thing I was thinking of.
However I can't blame you.
It's Formula 3, after all.
So you aren't angry with me Gunma!
Just tell me why your doing this?
I'm trying with all my
might to remain calm.
I wouldn't want to
ruin my first victory.
I'm sorry, I just can't tell you!
Believe me, I want to
tell you but I just can't!
Please let me go.
- I beg of you!
- It's not fair for Gunma.
It's obvious that we cannot
stop you from going to work for Hiziri,
- but tell us why!
- He's right, Tamotsu!
That may be true but Gunma
does not swim in gold,
But he managed to
get a car from Kishida ...
...and gained his first victory!
It's true! Gunma did
everything possible...
...and you just can't walk away!
Well, you could at least answer me!
Don't you remember
our dreams of glory?
We started this adventure
together! Why leave?
It's not right to just leave us!
He's right, you know?
My feelings for you all
have not changed...
..since the day we met!
In fact, my dream
is identical to yours!
I want to travel the
world alongside Gunma!
I am sure that together we
will succeed! No, I know we will!
But...but...I...
Just have to do this.
Sometimes it's good to work
elsewhere for a while...
When he finally returns
to us, we'll all understand!
Granny,
You know what?
Get out, get out now.
I never want to see you again.
I will be able to win without...
...your help.
I don't need it anymore.
The checkered flag marks
the end of the race!
The car that sees the first
wave is the one that wins!
Winning is like living in paradise!
In the next episode.
Desert-colored heart?
Gunma Makes His Second Start Alone
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away