Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
Eh?!
You did it!
Sempai!
- I've got big news for you!
- Huh?
He just called about
the President of the Federation!
He said that your driver's
license has been returned!
- Are you serious?
- You've gotta go and get it!
Sempai!
Gunma Draws the Line!
The Enemy's Compassion Is Bitter
So does that mean I
can participate in the next race!
Of course!
I went to the police ...
...and I have examined
the case in detail.
You were innocent.
However, keep in mind that I
made an exception to the rule ...
...and I can't do it again.
The drivers of the Federation
must have behave responsibly.
If you cause another fight,
I can't help you.
I Gunma Akagi act
whatever way I want!
- Gunma.
- I'm so happy!
They returned my license!
Please, sell me your car!
I was given back my license,
and now I can join the race!
Look, I'm asking you nicely!
- Hey, lady, we're dry!
- Coming.
You can't refuse
without a good reason!
Here you go!
The only way I can win
is to race with your car!
Look, I need it if I
want to switch to Formula 1!
Don't be like that!
Come on, tell me your price.
- One hundred million!
- Eh ?!
- One hundred million?
- One hundred million is my price,
then you can have the car.
What are you crazy? Do you
think I have that kind of money?
Even if I had that money,
I wouldn't come here with it.
Then you can just forget about it.
Hey!
Wait a minute!
- Hey, you still have to pay!
- How much is it?
Wait for me! Don't go!
Eijiro!
Sempai!
I'm glad to have met you!
I warn you that
right now I'm furious!
That madman doesn't
want to sell the car!
- I can convince him!
- How?
I sold my old race car ...
...and got a
bit of money for it.
I did it because
we need the money.
They gave me ten million!
- Quick, follow me Kishida!
- Yes,sempai.
As agreed!
We have the one hundred million.
- What ?! One hundred million ?!
- Consider this a down payment!
You will get the rest
in the coming days.
Sempai, what are you crazy?
Come on, take the money!
- I want all the cash now.
- For now I can only give you this.
But I'll have the rest
in a couple of days.
Well.
Ah, grab it.
- Sempai! Just don't stand there.
- Yes, yes.
D-damn...
We can't possibly get
the rest of the money.
We only have ten million.
And the race is
only two days away.
However, with this money...
...we could find
someone and rent a car.
No one will let us hire a car
if we don't have enough money.
Listen, I have to drive with
his car no matter the cost.
I'll never be able to
beat Hiziri without it.
I willing to beat that if I
had that car all my problems...
...would just disappear.
And my former friend
Tamotsu would be filled with envy.
He thinks he's so smart.
I just need to prove
that I can do it without him!
Answer me! I have a score
to settle with those two,
but to do
that I need his car.
What's wrong with you,
you could have hurt me.
Why are you so insistent!
I will not give it to some freak...
It's mine, get lost.
You will never get my car.
Even if you got on
your hands and knees.
Don't you ever give up?
Listen I will...
...take it by force if necessary.
- Kishida came to see you.
- Right..
He asked me if I knew
someone who could hire a car.
I don't think it's possible.
It's too late.
The deadline to
register for the next race...
...will end tomorrow.
I can't help him.
It isn't your fault.
- You did everything you could!
- Maybe you're right!
Hey, Yasu, do you know
the origins of Gunma?
The only thing I know about
Gunma is that he comes from the suburbs.
What do you know about his
friend Tamotsu, Hiziri's chief mechanic.
Wasn't it true that the
Gunma and him were best friends.
Indeed! They were good friends.
They spent their childhood together.
Why are you asking these questions?
Because there is something
about this story that intrigues me.
- What do u mean?
- Listen, Yasu ...
I really need a change of scenery.
Can you spend a few days with me?
The gasoline consumption is
expected to decrease with this setup.
Listen...
I need him to stay alive.
Only you can do it!
Prevent him from driving in the race!
I could never do that to him.
Hiziri trust me and
I cannot betray him.
I didn't agree to
work for him out of pity.
But because I wanted to...
help him obtain his best...
performance that he deserves.
And to get to this job,
I broke my friendship with Gunma.
That can never be undone.
Please, stop it.
Don't make me say it again.
After what happened, I don't
know what the right decision is.
As his mechanic
I want him to drive,
but as his friend
I want him to stop.
- Your thinking very deeply.
- Salve, Ruiko!
You know, I was
thinking about the next race!
You haven't slept in two nights!
I've been real busy as of late.
The tests will begin
in two hours at the most!
Okay! By the way, I have some
news that will make you happy.
The President of the Federation
has given Gunma back his license.
- Are you serious?
- Of course!
A certain Junko
phoned asking for you.
- She said to call back!
- I'll do that.
Bye.
Hiziri!
I'm so hungry
that I can't stand.
I know that the car is important,
but you should at
least find time to eat.
Formula 3 is waiting for me!
I must participate
no matter the cost.
- We'll go out after we're full!
- Right!
Thank you for what you did, Tamotsu!
Gunma was so depressed!
Since the license was returned to him,
he has started smiling again.
And all this is because of you and Hiziri!
Gunma!
"And all this is
because of you and Hiziri!"
Explain what you mean!
Don't tell me I only
got my license back....
...because Hiziri
intervened on my behalf.
I'm waiting for you to answer me!
Well, Gunma ... I ...
Hurry up and answer me!
- Sempai!
- Back off!
- What's happing?
- Why are you doing this?
I want to know why Hiziri and
Tamotsu is involved in this matter.
Gunma!
Let go of Junko immediately!
- Out of my way!
- I'll tell you...
As long as you stay calm!
I'm sorry.
You see, I was the
one that asked Tamotsu ...
...to convince Hiziri to talk
to the President of the Federation.
- What?!
- I chatted with Tamotsu ...
..and I told him that,
since your his friend,
that he should help.
And since Hiziri ...
...knows the President...
What were you thinking?
Who said you could act like that?
You have humiliated me
in front of Tamotsu and Hiziri!
We didn't have much choice.
They were the only
ones who could help.
That's just an excuse!
How the hell am I gonna race on
the track when you've humiliated me!
I understand your feelings,
but that isn't the case ...
- so don't treat her like that!
- Shut up!
Instead of shouting at her
you should be thanking her.
You should be grateful!
She was trying to help you!
As usual, you two
don't understand anything.
Stop it!
Don't blame them,
it wasn't there fault.
Although, it was unfair...
...for you to be punished for
something you didn't do.
I don't care!
You didn't have the right,
- to take action without telling me!
- But still...
Did you want me to do nothing?
Stop being a bully.
Your friends have
always been there for you.
And without Hiziri
you'd be a goner!
As usual you just
react in a violent manner.
And that's why your
father kicked you out!
- What?!
- Even your family couldn't stand you!
How dare you! You know
nothing about me...
...so how dare you
talk about my family.
Let alone my father.
Stop it!
I want to tell you that
you're a selfish, violent human ...
...being, and you need
to learn to respect others.
I am selfish!
I am violent!
And I'm the lowest of the low!
Say whatever you want,
but I will never change.
I act this way
because this is who I am.
You can never
understand why I act like this.
Are you still here?
We've been
waiting a long time!
We haven't met in years, Eijiro.
I don't know why you
want to see me again.
I'm here to help Gunma Akagi.
I'm asking you to
give him your car.
How did the great Kuroi
get put in a wheelchair?
I can't tell you why.
I'm sure you understand.
I'm sorry, but I'm not
selling it even if you ask.
I just knew that
would be your answer.
I'm not 100 percent sure...
...if Gunma Akagi is the
best driver for your car.
But I'm telling you right
now that he's really good.
No one's getting that car.
You know what?
There is no driver in
the world who knows how to...
- ...handle it!
- Look, Eijiro...
We should all get along with each
other since we're from the same country.
How dare you talk about friendship.
- That's not like you at all!
- Listen ...
Maybe you don't remember but Gunma
Akagi is just like you when you were young.
That's the reason I
care about him so much.
He wants to prove that
he can win without Tamotsu.
NEXT YEAR, HIZIRI, WILL
FACE THE EUROPEAN FORMULA 3?
HIZIRI TOGETHER WITH
HIS MECHANIC, TAMOTSU
T-Tamotsu!
Am I doing the right thing?
This isn't fair.
What if he finds out.
You see, as soon as
he does a few laps,
his car will stop and he will
think that you have failed him.
Gunma will also drive in that race ...
...but I am Hiziri's mechanic.
If I used the remote
control to stop his car,
Hiziri might think that I've
come up with some trick...
...to help my friend Gunma.
But why did I put
myself in this mess?
What should I do?
Sempai, try to calm down a bit!
- Sempai!
- Damn!
Junko should
not have done that.
It was my business.
She should have told me first.
Even if...
... Tamotsu
and Hiziri helped me...
- I will not race!
- But you can't do that, sempai.
You've come too
far to quit now,
You can't give up when
you've almost reached your goal.
- I know that...
- Huh!
I'm doing it because...
...my brain tells me
to do it. That's why.
Sempai, I totally understand
how you feel but...
Don't tell me what to do.
- But I just wanted to say that...
- Listen to me!
I will not go
because of my pride...
...since they helped me!
Soichiro Akagi, has another son...
Gunma Akagi, who lives away from home. Soichiro Akagi...
- is a candidate for the elections.
- Sempai.
ELECTION!
SOICHIRO AKAGI
It's you again.
You may control the world,
but you'll never control me.
You can bet on it!
I am strong.
And soon you'll realize
what I'm capable of.
- Shoma!
- That's just like you,
...to disrespect father...
...with your selfish behavior.
What do you care?
What are you doing here?
- Yuki has disappeared!
- What ?!
- Sempai!
- Take this!
I  loved Yuki...
...more than anything else!
But I lost her.
And it's all your fault!
If she loved you so
much why did she run away!
Bastard!
She's gone...
Because of you!
It's all your fault!
If you cared about
her, you should have...
Knew how she felt about father...
And that she hated him
and how you imitated him.
But how do you know?
You only blame others!
I'm blaming you
because it's your fault!
This wouldn't have
happened if you were here.
- It's all your fault!
- Stop it please!
It's your fault! It's
your fault! It's your fault!
What, what did I do wrong?
You see, even when I
explained everything to him...
I'm just glad he's happy.
If I was in your place I
would have done the same.
The rain makes me sad!
Damn! That asshole Shoma ...
Sempai.
- Don't worry about me, I'm alright!
- Sempai!
I told you I'm fine!
Gunma! Hold on a little longer.
Yuki...
Yuki!
Gunma...
- Sempai! Sempai!
- Gunma!
Gunma, in the race, I will show
you something interesting!
- What?!
- I challenge you!
- You can do it, Gunma!
Today we will see
who is the strongest!
In the next episode:
Gunma vs. Hiziri!
Final Countdown
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you