STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
- It 's a pleasure to see you again.
- Look, it's useless ...
...to try and get me to stay...
...you won the race.
I won't let you gloat!
Gunma, control yourself!
Listen up:
if that accident didn't happen,
I would have won the race.
However I won't lose again.
Next time I'll win.
It's really a shame,
I probably won't see you for a while.
What?
Just this evening I decided
on moving up in the world.
From now on,
I'll be racing in Formula 3.
Although this is still a bit away...
...I intend to go there eventually.
This time, next year
I'll be celebrating once again!
Tokyo Is Blown Away!
Gunma's Secret Part-time Operations
I can't use this.
The radiator and suspension
are beyond repair!
And the carburetor must also be replaced!
So it will cost
about two million, right?
F-Five million?!
That's an astronomical figure!
Yes, I know it
needs to be repaired,
but five millions
is a bit too much...
Give it to me!
Who is calling?
Yes, I know your a garage!
Who am I?! Gunma Akagi,
the greatest driver of all time!
I need my car repaired.
Say... why don't
you get me
a discount or better
yet, do it for free?
You could put my name up in...
big letters on your
garage when I win Formula 1!
As it happens I was
looking for a sponsor!
So, what do you say?
How rude, he hung up!
I'm going to make breakfast!
Gunma, why do you
always make matters worse?
Is this the thanks ...
...I get for trying to help you!
Get to work!
Next week we have a...
...race and we've
got no time to lose!
If you want to race next week,
you have to pay for the repairs!
We need five million!
I know what's wrong with you!
- Tamotsu!
- Weren't you listening?
I'm sure there's
something going on.
I know!
Your in love with Hiziri's girl.
I'm right, aren't I?
Stop acting like a fool!
How can you think of such a thing?
I can't forgive you for this.
How could you do something
like that without telling me?
Your an asshole!
You won't get away with this!
Stop it! I told you to stop!
Junko is watching us!
We're only messing around.
How about you join us?
This is terrible!
It's almost impossible to drive around!
Even taxis are stuck!
Yesterday, I had to
go to the city center,
and it took fifty minutes!
It was crazy!
This can't go on!
A solution must be found!
You gotta take the train!
Yeah, though I'm always in a hurry!
If your taking a taxi,
you always
gotta tip the driver!
Well, it seems that I've
found a solution to our problems.
See you later!
Thank you for the company!
I'm leaving for a while.
I wish I knew what he was thinking.
He drove all afternoon in a tractor.
He's got no time to lose!
Come here, Tamotsu ...
- If you want I'll pay for the repair.
- Really?!
I realize this
is a very high figure,
but I can pay it for you.
I'm sorry,
but I cannot accept it.
This time, we must solve
this problem ourselves.
On the other hand
we knew from the start ...
...that we needed more
money to move forward.
Anyway thanks for the offer,
Morioka! That was nice of you!
Okay, Tamotsu, forget about it!
Now what do we do?
We need a solution
as soon as possible!
Five million ...
That's it!
- Hey, look who's back!
- Good Morning!
Can I ask you for a favor.
Would it be possible to
postpone the payment of rent?
I am currently short of money.
Of course! It's alright!
I'll pay you guys
if you win this time!
I wish you luck!
Don't worry.
I'm very sorry, Gunma!
Things aren't really
working out for us.
We need to find a solution.
Remember, my door
is always open for you.
Think about it.
Taxi! Taxi!
Come on!
Give me a break!
- I've only got fifteen miniutes!
- Cheer up will you!
What do you suggest?
Well, you could at least do something!
Do you understand?
This is our honeymoon!
Do something!
I know, but what
can I do...darling.
What?!
Are you stupid?!
Hello, good people,
you need something?
- Like a ride?
- Eh?! Sure!
Can you get us to the
airport in fifteen miniutes?
Sure! We will arrive in a heartbeat!
But I charge ten
times more than a taxi!
That's great!
As long as we arrive on time...
...I'm willing to pay
twenty times the rate, okay?
- But, darling...
- Stop it
- Get your bags and hop on!
- Yes! Yes!
At full speed,
I'm Faster than the wind!
You have no reason
to worry, Tamotsu.
I'll have the money soon.
And then Hiziri,
we'll meet again in Formula 3.
Metropolitan Motorway
TOLL ROAD
What was that?!
TRAFFIC JAM IN THE DIRECTION
OF HANEDA AIRPORT : 5KM LONG
Eh?!
Come!
please stop!
I beg of you!
I can't take it anymore!
Excuse me, sir ...
What are you doing?!
I had to pay!
This is great!
And this is only the first step!
This is Hiziri's answering machine.
I'm not in at the moment,
so leave your name and phone number.
Speak after the beep.
Hey, we gotta move!
Don't you remember the street?
You said you would go
five times faster than a taxi!
- It's coming!
- We're almost there, dear.
Why aren't you moving?
Stay calm, dear!
Damn!
Is there no other way!
There has to be another way there!
There's a ditch that
passes under the railway.
But it's full of water and rocks!
Why didn't you tell me?
We made it just in time!
Thanks to you!
Wonderful!
She's my spitting image!
This is true love!
She's throwing a tantrum!
Maybe it's just her
way of showing that she's alive.
Ah! The money!
Here! For your
trouble. Thanks again
Well...
It was a pleasure
to accompany her here.
Keep the money,
I don't want it.
This baby is thanks enough!
Be with your child.
- That's it! Shake that bolt well.
- Sure.
In one week I
gained one million.
Where do I go
to find more money?
Although Morioka could give us an...
...an advance.
Probably not.
Damn!
- Where are you going, Gunma?
- I'm gonna get some fresh air!
But you haven't
even finished your work!
- He's gone!
- He's been...
...behaving
strange all week.
I hope
it's nothing serious.
I'm sorry, Morioka.
It's not your fault!
Tamotsu!
Hi!
Sorry for not calling back,
but I was in my home country.
I called as soon
as I got the message.
So, what's up?
Sorry, but I'm
working right now...
...and I'm really
busy right now!
Why don't you come
over after you finish work?
But I have to
work overtime today!
It's alright, just come
when your finished!
- Bye!
- Eh?!
Did he
call about the job?
Yeah! I think so!
Good.
I take it that everything is
going according to plan?
Those papers on the desk ...
Are they the new contracts
for our mechanic team?
- Maybe?
- I think so.
You always get
what you want.
Did you prepare new contracts...
because you know you will win.
For months you wanted
Tamotsu to become your mechanic!
He'll probably accept soon.
He can't be easily persuaded.
Though I'm sure you can convince him.
So, once again,
victory is yours!
Your success will be ensured
with Tamotsu! as your mechanic!
Well, he called you...
so that means that he's
thinking about accepting!
Taxi! Taxi! Taxi!
Come on, it's urgent!
Oh, come on!
Damn! I'll never be able
to get to my appointment!
What the hell is wrong with you?
- Hey, you need a ride?
- What?
Are you serious?
Can you get there in twenty minutes!
Boy, you're really a
great guy, you know that?
I've got two hundred thousand here?!
- What? Two hundred thousand
- Look over here.
Money! Lots of money!
I've just won the lottery!
I this this would be my lucky day.
And now I'm gonna
meet some ladies!
- Fantastic!
- Yes! It really is!
- Nice to meet you!
- The pleasure is all mine, son!
Come on!
Go faster!
Keep it going fast!
This thing can move
real fast, you know?
I've gotta go!
Here, this is for you!
I forgot your hamburger!
Come on man, pay
attention or we'll crash!
- Come on!
- What's the matter with you?
I've got this!
This is great!
We'll get there in no time.
Ahh!
Are you sure this is a tractor?
It seems more like a race car!
You guessed right!
Hold on tight!
I wish I knew where
that Gunma goes?
He comes home
late every night!
He may have found a night job.
- It's possible?
- That's probably it!
Otherwise he'll never make
it in time for the race!
- I'm home!
- Your back.
- Where have you been?
- I have been in the garage ...
... to fix an engine.
Tell me Junko, any news...
-...about the money?
- No!
I do know something,
Gunma asked me ...
...about Ryuji and
when he started racing.
He thought he
was full of money.
But where is he?
Here we are.
In twenty miniutes flat.
Where's the money?
- It's all gone.
- What?!
This is just great!
So how are you gonna pay me?
This is just terrible!
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
I've got nothing!
Lend me two hundred thousand?
Huh..!
Gunma doesn't know yet,
but to pay off our debts ...
...I had to accept another job!
I had hoped to
resolve this problem!
No, I'll get it.
Yo, Tamotsu!
I need a favor...
...I need you to pick me up.
The tractor is damaged.
What?!
How did that happen?
- Is it serious?
- No, everything's fine.
Just wait for me.
And I have good
news about the money!
Everything should be alright,
I found another job.
We'll have enough money.
By doing this, you can
finally take part in that race!
Well, Gunma?
You gotta be joking, Tamotsu!
They gave you enough money!
What job is this?
I'm a mechanic for another driver.
It's Hiziri...!
Isn't it!
Gunma...
Gunma, with Hiziri's money,
we will win!
It's the only way.
Why did you do this?
The motors are switched on
a minute from the start!
Care must be taken:
as to not overheat,
or make noise,
you get a penalty for doing so!
In the next episode:
"Gunma Returns Home!
He Learns an Unbelievable Secret".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away