STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Finally a Decisive Match! Gunma vs.
Hiziri, the Ultimate Dead Heat
- Why don't you take a break, Tamotsu?
- We've brought snacks.
Thank you, Hiziri! Thank you, Ruiko!
I appreciate it very much!
- I saw that Gunma has qualified!
- Congratulations!
He had a very
difficult start to the race,
but then in the last
laps he recovered well.
You are really good!
Anyone can qualify,
provided, that their
machines are finalized by you.
No, I'm not that good.
Why don't we talk about
your performance?
You were amazing!
Only a driver like you could...
take pole position in
one minute and two seconds.
Look, Tamotsu, I really
envy your friend Gunma.
This is a good thing?
Yes, because my mechanics
aren't good enough.
If you worked on my car,
you could improve ...
- ... my performance!
- Eh?!
This is it!
Good luck for the race!
Apparently you've gained his trust!
Though I'm not so optimistic.
Kishida has just arrived at the hospital.
He has bruises all over the body,
and he broke an arm and some ribs.
- It's all because of Haitani!
- Now ...
.. he has to stay in the
hospital for at least two months!
Frankly, I can't even
believe this has happened!
It's hard to
resist provocations.
Gunma, you know,
we said that the qualifications ...
...you got were great,
and if you continue...
...you should have a
good chance of winning!
It would be great if you
could beat the other competitors!
Quiet! He finished only
second-last on the track!
That means his chances
of winning are slim!
How can he win with chances like that?
Today our guest is one of
the most powerful industrial ...
companies in our country ...: Mr. Soichiro Akagi!
Mr. Soichiro Akagi!
Mr. Soichiro Akagi is
here with his ​​two children ...
...and has granted us this interview!
His two sons?!
Does that mean you,
Gunma?
Mr. Akagi is the President
of the Akagi Group,
but in addition to his company,
he's responsible for managing ...
... countless other businesses.
Tell us, Mr. Akagi,
are the rumors circulating ...
... about your falling
out with your son true?
Well, I wouldn't call it a falling out,
let's say I'm trying to introduce...
...him into the world of work soon.
On the other hand, young people
should be prepared to work.
Some argue that they
are too young for jobs,
though I don't think so.
People should start working when they're young.
Who knows, perhaps, under
his leadership, the Akagi Group...
...could be known
and loved across the world!
And now, Mr. Akagi,
one last question:
it is true that you intend to run for ...
...in the upcoming elections
for the House of Representatives?
I'd rather not talk about it,
that's a rather delicate topic.
Your useless,
you'll never change, Dad!
Are you crazy? That TV was brand new,
and I haven't payed yet!
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome!
The race will start in a few moments.
That hurt!
- Be careful, Hiziri.
- Don't worry.
I'm safer here than on the road.
- In any case, be careful.
- Don't worry, Ruiko.
Wow!
- Be careful, Gunma.
- Don't worry.
I'm safer here than on the road.
- Either way your fine.
- Yes.
Don't even think about it!
Now try,
to not get hurt and destroy the other cars!
Three minutes to go!
We ask non driers to clear
the runway as soon as possible!
So, promise to behave well?
Sure! I'll do the race
without damaging any cars.
Listen, Gunma, turn on your engine ...
...it's one minute before departure.
And remember that in the first round ...
...you need to warm up the engine,
then you can start driving.
Try to be careful, please!
Sure, sure!
However, I want to win!
I shouldn't be worried too much.
- What did you say?
- Tamotsu, I've got to go.
Please, don't do anything stupid!
After the lap,
try to keep the engine revved up,
otherwise the engine
won't work properly, got it?
- You already told me!
- You never listen!
Come on, Tamotsu!
Something must have happened to Gunma!
I've never seen him
so nervous before a race!
Probably because he
saw his father on TV.
- Come on, Gunma! You are the best!
- Grandma?
Why are you going so slow?
How can you expect to win!
Grandma, stop screaming!
He's going slow because...
- ...of the starting lap!
- Eh?!
Sorry, I didn't know!
Hopefully he won't cause trouble!
I hope so.
I'd like him to win this time.
I always wonder how you
can be so different from me!
You have to go, Gunma!
There is no place for
someone like you in our family!
- Get out of here!
- Goodbye, father!
Please, do not push the engine
too hard, try to calm down!
Gunma!
Come on, Gunma,
we're with you!
It's pointless to
cheer for him that way!
What?!
I'm the fastest!
You're going too fast, Gunma.
You have to slow down.
Out of the way!
To me you're
nothing but a slacker!
You are wrong. Dad!
- What are you doing?
- Get away from me!
- This isn't  over!
Damn it!
Damn!
Your mine, Hiziri!
Gunma is magnificent!
He's driving rather well!
Keep it up, Gunma!
You're the best!
You'll win at this rate!
Your mine!
I've finally caught up!
I'll win this race and then...
I'll become the world champion!
Your life will amount to nothing.
You're nothing but
an imitation of me!
Damn it! Why can't I get
rid of this nightmare?
Where are you trying to go?
To the country s borders?
Or to the end of the world?
If you continue like this,
you won't go anywhere!
Shut up!
You'll never be a real pilot!
That profession is not right for you!
Your place is here, at my side,
don't you understand?
Dad, please, stop it!
Leave me alone!
I'll beat you, Hiziri!
I will win!
Damn it!
What happened?
Where is Gunma?
What's happened?
Gunma!
What happened to you...
...you crashed into the guardrail.
- Yeah! What bad luck!
- Now there's nothing left to do.
- Don't do it!
- Don't make that face!
For your information
I almost beat Hiziri!
Stop doing everything
by yourself, Gunma!
- What?
- You were at fault!
- What?!
- Take it easy!
It's useless to argue!
You should have avoided it!
With your vision you had
plenty of time to avoid it!
Instead you lost your grip on the vehicle.
You should have slowed down,
instead you did the opposite!
Have you learned nothing?
The speed of your car
was what caused the crash!
I know all about your father.
...and that his
appearance on TV upset you!
- My father has nothing to do with this!
- He does!
Stop lying to yourself,
just admit it!
I know that deep down
you two have a connection!
Look, Tamotsu,
stop it now!
I can't forgive what you've done!
It was not my fault!
You should give the
race your full concentration!
- Nothing else matters!
That's enough, Tamotsu!
This is the first time
Gunma has raced seriously!
Anyone can make mistakes!
Yes, that's true!
But when your driving fast,
even the smallest
mistake could end your life!
Cars can be replaced but,
there is only one Gunma Akagi!
Do you agree, Tamotsu?
Yes I do! Gunma, you
can become a champion.
You're the only one
who can fulfill our dreams!
This would be an honor for Morioka.
Junko too!
And Grandma would be happy...
And even our friends Kinoshita and Matsuura!
And me too!
Think about it, Gunma!
No more dreams of glory!
We'll get to that soon enough.
Then, are we gonna get this car?
Damn it!
Who knows how many laps I lost ...!
All right.
I'll wait a while.
I'll surpass Hiziri at the finish line!
Look who's back!
What does he think he's doing?
Out of the way champion!
Careful, Gunma!
Watch out for the corner!
That car has an amazing engine!
Even despite that accident!
Lets go!
I'm the fastest, Hiziri!
You'll never beat me!
No!
Gunma!
I told them that an oil
slick caused the accident,
but we all know the truth!
I'm sorry. If I wasn't such
an idiot we would have won.
I, Gunma Akagi, dedicate
this tomb to a frog.
Don't worry,
there's always next time.
Didn't you see me!
I was like wildfire!
Even so!
You've still got a way to go.
- Where is Tamotsu?
- Tamotsu?
Never mind.
Ruiko sure is cute!
Though why does she
want to talk with Tamotsu?
I won't stand for this!
I'm really sorry,...
Can I do anything for you?
I don't know.
However, you are kind to me.
Could you give me a kiss?
Sure!
You deserve it!
It was Gunma's fault
that he didn't win the race!
Don't you think so?
Actually ... I ... I
You're so cute!
Don't do it, Tamotsu!
What's wrong with you?
Tamotsu,
now I know.
He's been flirting with Hiziri's girl!
What are you saying?
Ruiko only came to invite me to a big party,
...tomorrow evening for Hiziri's victory!
Party?!
A lot of drives will be attending also.
It would help my future
as a mechanic if I attended!
- Your invited too!
- You idiot!
I would never set foot
into the home of my rival!
Just the thought of
seeing him makes me sick!
- Congratulations!
Every things gone as you had expected!
I think you'll be pleased with yourself!
I don't think Tamotsu will attend the party.
Though one day he will work for me!
He'll come when he sees this,
I know he will.
The engine will draw him in.
A first-class pilot changes
gear at least 20 times ...
...in a single lap
in the Tsukuba circuit!
And it only takes one
minute to complete a lap!
In the next episode:
"Goodbye, Gunma! Rival Hiziri
Announces His Step-up to F-3".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away