Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
My...My car ...
Gunma's License Is
Taken by Force, He Can't Run!
Sempai!
Good luck!
You can't stop me
from seeing him!
Get your hands off me!
Let me go!
- You're crazy!
- What do you want?
What's the meaning of this?
The election candidate,
Michael Sander ...
- She's talking pretty loud!
- ...wants to greet his constituents
... and thanks you in
advance for your votes!
Hi, Grandma!
I wish you a long and happy life!
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Hello, Grandma!
Thank you in advance for your vote.
I won't be voting
for your candidate!
If I'm not mistaken
Gunma's father ...
...is also participating
in this election, and he'll win!
Oh!
Tamotsu!
Long time no
see, grandma.
Tell me, who's
in charge here?
- Your coming with us!
- Hands off!
Tell me who you
are and what you want?
My name is Gunma Akagi
and I'm a Formula 3 driver.
Why are you not interested
in becoming my sponsor?
Your sponsor?
You are the head
of a famous company!
You could easily sponsor me!
With your help I would be
able to get to Formula 1 faster.
- What ?! Formula 1?
- Really?
He must be dreaming.
What have you laughing at?
I'm telling the truth!
I assure you that
I'm an excellent driver.
There isn't another driver like me!
We are unsure
about your abilities.
However, I personally know
a lot of great drivers.
If you are so good then why
have you not won a World Cup?
- Doesn't it seem strange?
- Yes, very strange.
I appreciate your passion
and wish you success.
But our society,
cannot sponsor a stranger.
I'm sorry, but find a
contract somewhere else.
I get it! You'll be
returning to Hiziri soon!
Yes!
I have a lot of work to do!
But, you can
always live with us.
No. I've already
booked a room at the hotel.
Why a hotel?
Hiziri said that a hotel
was the best solution for me.
Well, how is Gunma doing?
He's in a desperate
search for a sponsor!
He had managed
to get into Formula 3 and...
- ...did you hear about what happened?
- I did.
I almost forgot,
this came for you yesterday.
- It looks important!
- Thank you very much!
So what is that document for?
- To get a passport.
- A passport ?!
So you'll be following
Hiziri in his travels?
I envy you.
I wish I could travel abroad!
- Isn't it a bit late?
- I think so.
Oh, well...
Damn it!
Why did they all refuse?
They are all a bunch of morons!
But there's only one week left
It's hopeless!
Hey, sempai, let's
forget about a sponsor...
...and try to find a car instead!
Idiot! We have no money and
nobody's gonna give us one for free!
In any case, in order
to compete in a race,
- you need a lot of money!
- Hello, guys!
Tamotsu was here earlier on.
- Eh?!
- Tamotsu?
He has a lot of
nerve to show up here.
That kid who caused some trouble...
he's a Formula 3 driver and belongs...
- ...to your Federation! !
- Is that true?
Yes! By chance I saw
a report on television,
- and I sent some pictures.
- Why are you doing this?
I am a supporter
opposed to violence in sports!
It seems inconceivable that a driver...
...like him was involved with the Police!
You need to punish him,
before he gets out of hand.
All I ask is for you to take action,
to protect our supporters!
Otherwise, I will be forced
to resort to other means!
Other means?
What do you mean?
If you don't do it,
it will get personal.
- What did you say?
- Eh ?!
Yes.
He's got to abroad
to order a new car.
A new car?
Tamotsu said it is necessary.
Because if Hiziri be able
to win this championship,
- then next year he'll go worldwide!
- What?
That means that the next race ...
...will be the last
one he is here for!
This is just bullshit!
He mustn't change
category before I, I can't be...
... left defeated in Formula 3!
Nobody and I mean
nobody will overtake me!
- Sempai!
- Damn it!
Wait!
- A new car?!
- I need to join that race!
I must catch up with Hiziri!
I just can't do nothing!
Only you can help me!
Of course I can help you.
But if they know it's
you, you'll be removed.
Why should they?
Aren't I a good driver?
I won't let it end like this!
All the cars that
drive in Formula 3 ...
...need the help of a sponsor.
And your personality is
making it even harder.
So you'd better forget it!
Besides, it takes a lot of money!
I will manage to get hold of the money!
You must only show me
someone who can get me a car!
Sempai is an excellent driver!
I think he's the best in the world!
We must do something for him!
I'm ready to use all my savings!
Well, what do you say?
You idiot! I don't need
you anyway, we'll get by on our own!
- Come on, we'll show him!
- Yes!
Wait.
I know a man who could help you.
- He's called Eijiro!
- Eijiro?!
The last time I saw him,
he lived just outside of town.
It's too late now,
however, I've heard ...
...he had a car to sell!
But be careful!
He's not the friendly type.
I was able to endure even you,
so I might as
well impress him too!
Hey, get me a drink!
Are you going
to get it or not?
We are closing!
Ah, you're his friends!
Good evening,
you must be Eijiro!
My name is Gunma Akagi.
Kuroi told me about you.
Would you be
willing to sell your car?
Logically, we will
pay you for it!
I have to participate in the
next round of the championship!
Boy, I haven't the faintest
idea what you're talking about!
Come on, don't play dumb.
It's useless to pretend!
We know you own a car!
What do you say?
Are you willing to
sell the car or not?
Whoa!
This man is a real savage!
Shut your mouth!
No, my friend! It's not my
style to give up without a fight!
- Be careful!
-  Look who's talking!
I'm finally home!
Did you think
you could escape me?
- Hello!
- Why are you here?
The machine has already
been set up, hasn't it?
Don't touch it!
Wow, you've got
yourself a real beauty!
Don't do it!
Yes, it is ...
I'm coming too Tamotsu!
This is great!
Truly outstanding!
The engine is a real gem!
With this car,
nobody will beat me!
- Sempai!
- Get out of that car now!
- What was that for?
- Get out of here!
- Not a chance!
Now hat I've seen
the car I want it!
I badly need to drive this car.
I must participate in the next race!
- I'm begging you!
- Please sir!
Didn't you hear me?
Get out of here!
Or I'll make you suffer!
Sempai!
Please, calm down!
Let us talk this out!
Good thing those two are gone!
This is not for children!
I wouldn't give this car up
for all the gold in the world!
This car is my friend,
it'll never betray me.
And it's all mine!
He was the craziest
guy I've ever met!
Yes, but I warned you!
You were right!
Anyway, his car ...
- ...is really something.
- Yes!
But, as soon as I
got in the passenger seat,
it reminded me of the
days I spent with Tamotsu.
But there is one
thing I don't understand!
Why does he keep
it hidden in his house?
It's hard to explain.
He's always been the kind ...
..who's not good with people.
He argues that machines
unlike humans do not betray you.
Someone must have made him suffer!
That's not a good reason
to keep it under lock and key!
I'll take the care by
force and beat Hiziri.
Kuroi, something has happened ...
Ah, you're not alone!
Gunma is here too!
Well, why don't you tell us?
What's so bad?
Well ... Uhm...I
Speak, tell us what happened!
Well, you see...
It just got this letter.
Hey, wait!
Look! It's from the
President of our Federation!
Who knows what he wants...
- Eh, they want to withdraw his license?
- And for what reason?
They didn't specify a reason.
- What about Gunma?
- He's...
How is your new passport?
Was there any problems?
- No! Everything is alright!
- Hi, Hiziri!
It was kind of Mr. Kasai
invite us to this party.
Just imagine!
This is a party with friends ...
...that happens once a month!
It's nothing official!
I see that she does not drink alcohol.
Do you not drink?
You should at least try a cocktail!
- I don't drink when I drive!
- I'm the same as you.
By the way, has reached an
agreement with management?
Sure! Now I need to
win the next two races.
You have a lot of confidence in yourself!
Okay! I wish you good luck!
The President of the Federation
takes notice of my career.
- Are you sure you're all right?
- I'm better now.
Luckily it was a light attack.
Luckily it wasn't a stronger
attack or I'd be done for.
HEADQUARTERS OF THE SUPPORTERS OF Soichiro ROSS
We were able to make
him withdraw the license.
Our man in the
Federation just confirmed this.
- I understand.
- And finally ... this!
They are the result of the negotiation.
Excuse me, sir, there is a certain
Gunma Akagi who wants to enter.
What?! Gunma Akagi?
For heaven's sake! Don't let him in!
- Mr Kasai!
Looks like I've found you.
I demand you give me an explanation!
Tell me why your
pulling my license?
Oh, no! Why is he here?
Dad, accept this apology
for the trouble I've caused.
However, this is your money!
Then the matter is completely settled?
Yes! And I even sorted Gunma out.
- Perfect!
- By the way, how is Yuki?
I've seen how
you've been treating her.
If I were you I
wouldn't think of leaving.
I'll take care of her.
- Who took these?
- I don't know.
But I had to take action.
But this is an injustice!
I didn't cause the brawl!
I don't see why I
should be punished.
This isn't about who
is right or who is wrong.
Your a sportsman
under everyones eyes.
We just can't be involved with...
...any form of violence when
a sportsman is involved!
I was forced to make this decision ...
...as to prevent problems more
serious problems in the future.
The license has been withdrawn
and there is nothing we can do.
I'm sorry!
- Wait a minute!
- Gunma!
- Tamotsu?
- Gunma...
I am happy to see you!
I never imagined to meet you ...
...at a party as important as this!
If forgot how much
you love parties now.
Gunma,
Is it true...
That they withdrew your license ...
- because you were involved in a fight?
- Why do you care.
I though you only cared
about Hizir and his car.
What's wrong with you!
I'm still your friend and I care...
...about you. I also know how
much Formula 3 means to you.
And since you've no
license, you can't drive.
- Traitor!
- Eh ?!
Do you remember
how hard I worked?
But that didn't stop
you from joining Hiziri.
And you dare to
say you're still my friend.
So why don't I...
My matters do not
concern you anymore.
Gunma!
I don't know what to do.
I have no money, don't have a car
and now I don't even have a driver's license!
I've got to find a solution.
RACING CIRCUIT ENTRY FOR PADDOCK
I just can't give up the world of racing!
Eh ?! Hiziri is sick?
Yes, but it's a secret!
But we've got to be careful.
Unfortunately Hiziri is
suffering from an incurable disease!
It's something that
only me, Hizir and Ruiko know!
In the next episode:
Hiziri's Disease Creeps Closer,
But I Am not Afraid of Death
Hiziri, the circuit will
not become your grave!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you