STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Dear Tamotsu, how are you
doing? I hope so.
Every time I think of that snob,
I get ticked off!
I will defeat him eventually.
It's great not being around my father!
For what he did to my mother,
would you forgive him?
Even though I've left my home,
I don't miss it, not one bit!
Anyway, I'm glad I came to Tokyo!
I went to driving soon
as soon as possible...
...and I got my license within a day.
Also the women in
Tokyo are really nice!
I even found an apartment
with a large luxury condo.
Don't worry, there's room for you too!
Tamotsu, you should hurry up and join me!
I have a lot of money available,
all I need is you to
form the best team ever!
Double-dealing his friendship,
Still his dream is the best in the world!
A white building...
A white building?!
Hey, look over there! !
He's been round six times!
Who's house?
I don't know!
Perhaps you mean this house!
It's not what you imagined, then!
- Eh? Your looking for Gunma.
- That lunatic?!
Excuse me.
Gunma!
Gunma, it's you!
I'm your best friend!
Wake up! Wake up, please!
Hi!
I gave you quite a scare, didn't I?
Tamotsu?
Tamotsu, you're finally here!
Hurray! Hurray! I'm
really glad you came!
I've been waiting
for so long, Tamotsu!
This is great!
Here! This rice was grown
in my plantation.
It's all genuine stuff.
I really hope you like it!
Thank you so much, it's really good!
It's so hard to find genuine things!
Eat up or else it'll get cold!
- Actually, ...
- Eat everything and don't say a word!
Don't you know she is
the best cook in the world?
It's about time that
I've eaten great food!
Enjoy your meal!
- Hey, Gunma.
- Enjoy.
You're really rude!
Where are you going, Junko?
Get back to the table!
You haven't finished!
Don't worry,
she'll be back!
Excuse me, ma'am, I need
to make a phone call.
Where can I find a phone?
I have a phone!
You can use it, if you want!
Really ...
I'll start calling then.
- More please!
- Sure!
Don't be so loud...
... when you wake me up.
Oh, stop complaining!
Come see what
I've prepared for you.
MARIOKA MOTORS
This is it.
- Hey, Gunma.
- I'm watching! I'm watching!
- This way!
- Eh?!
This car is a special model!
It has a capacity of
1600 cubic centimeters!
And an aspirated
engine with four valves!
The tires aren't for racing,
they'll need to be changed.
You'll also have to
modify the cooling system!
The shell is made of
aluminum and carbon fiber.
This is our first step towards Formula 1.
- Nobody will beat me!
- Hey, Tamotsu!
- Oh, Morioka!
- So you finally decided to come!
This is the engine
you've been waiting for.
Oh I'm sorry.
This is my dear
friend Gunma Akagi.
Hello, pleased to meet you!
Morioka will help...
... us get into the
world of motor sport.
He knows everything.
- Hi there!
As you can see, I tried
to do my best to satisfy you.
Although it is used,
the engine is not bad.
And just because it's you,
I decided to sell it ...
...at the bargain
price of ten million,
Though it's worth way more.
Tamotsu sure knows
a lot about  engines.
I'm sure that he will turn
this car into a great one!
- Well. Who's driving it?
I wish you luck!
He's really good, you know.
You got that right!
Hey, Gunma, our dream
is becoming a reality.
I still can't believe it.
I was going to let it go,
but then you gave
me the...
...push I needed!
We will be a great team!
I know that the road to success ...
...will be a hard one.
However, we will give it our all!
You will become a great driver!
We should have enough money!
- How?
- How do you think...
- ... isn't your family rich?
Your father too...
..I'm pretty sure
they could spare some!
- What did I said?
- Forget about it!
Hey, you know that...
...that care.
I love it!
Now calm down,
we don't need to hurry!
From now on we'll need money.
I have managed to
put some savings aside.
I think you should go
home and think for a bit.
Theres no time to lose...
- ...we'll sell the car?
- Alright!
Then we will buy
a brand new car!
It would cost a lot more,
but it's better for racing!
Even so money isn't the only ...
...problem we have!
Understand?
HOUSE AKAGI
- So you need ten million?
- Yes!
That's the truth!
So it's only money you want,
your such a let down!
Shoma, will you satisfy his madness?
Of course not!
- I know your there!
- Gunma!
He doesn't have time for you!
He's already busy with the elections!
- Yuki, get his overcoat.
- Sure!
- Yuki!
- Yes!
Since our father is so overworked,
Can you give it to me.
It should be alright!
Are you not the
heir of the great empire?
Of course!
As far as you're concerned,
you have no right to the money!
You've made a fool of dad.
Remember one thing,
you no longer belong to this family!
So stay away from this house.
What a treat!
This magazine contains ...
a lot of valuable advice!
Just what I needed.
As soon as I get home
I'll get right to work!
Isn't this that mysterious driver!
I haven't seen Gunma all day.
I wish I knew where he went.
I'm the fastest!
No one will ever beat me!
- Gunma!
- Hey there, Tamotsu!
- Did you get the money?
- Nope!
So your going now then?
I wanted to sell the tractor and with the proceeds ...
...I could buy that race car.
Only with that much money...
... will will be able to buy it.
- What's that?
- Give it back, Gunma! Give it back!
You bought a car magazine ...
...and you wanted to read it first?
Gunma, give it back now!
- Give it to me!
- No, I want to read it first!
Stop it, Gunma! Stop it!
- You don't understand!
- Is it that precious to you?
We'll have to dismantle the engine.
Hi, guys, is that okay?
What's with the funeral face?
- What's that?
- Don't you recognize a tractor?
Some teacher you are.
We'll, lets see what it can do!
- So ...
- Don't touch her!
Matsuura is right!
If you don't have a driver's license,
- you can't do it!
- What?
You heard me, go away!
Who cares if I don't have a license?
I can still work with engines!
Also know that I'm
not going to deal with it!
What's wrong with you!
I was only trying to help!
Every time I do something
you always shout,
even though I was only helping!
Thanks for the offer.
- In any case, we don't need you.
- Hey! Tamotsu!
Take a look at the motor!
Look, Tamotsu is a true magician.
He's a master with machines!
- Uhm ...
- Come on, show him!
- Gunma!
- You can trust him!
Where will I find all that money?
I need an idea!
But my brother could
also give me a bit of money!
All I need to do is try!
But this magazine
speaks only of engines!
Oh, I'll never understand any of this stuff.
Tamotsu, are you
sure you can fix it?
I know whats wrong.
The trouble is that in the piston
the cylinder does not flow well.
It'll be easy!
The engine overall okay,
it'll be easy,
only that the cylinder
does not work properly!
If we fix that it'll
be good as new.
It seems Gunma
was right about you.
You are a magician.
- Your exaggerating.
- And your being modest!
- He's great
Your young and yet so talented.
Though you might
need a bit more experience,
Stop it,
your making me blush!
Dammit! I don't know
if I can live like this!
I will become a great driver!
You'll see.
From now on we'll need money.
I have managed to
put some savings aside.
"I've put savings aside"?!
I'm sorry, Tamotsu,
but I have to!
Where is it?
Oh! His savings account!
Ten million?!
Where did he get all that from?
Hey, Tamotsu,
we're sorry.
We only did it because
you were his friend.
It doesn't matter,
nobody's a fool!
In this house,
we're all friends.
We all share the same passions!
That's not true!
And you know it!
How dare you!
Young people have a duty...
...to hold each others hands!
And if memory serves me correctly,
I remember
you two were kissing!
Don't mention that again!
You got it, Grandma?
My niece, as you
already know is very pretty,
works as an instructor
at the driving school ...
...and Gunma kissed her!
- What?!
So she's that girlfriend
that Gunma write about...
...that beautiful brunette was her?
What did you say!
Granny, what have you prepared to eat?
I'm as hungry as a wolf!
What's the matter?
- This time I'll get you!
- Oh yeah?!
You are a great liar!
How dare you say ...
... such a thing? What's next marriage?
Who said you could...
...write such a thing?
You withdrew all my
money from my bank account!
Why did you do this,
Gunma?
Why did you withdraw all my money?
Tell me why?
To... buy a car!
I just had to buy it!
How could you do this?
Didn't I tell you not to rush.
Deducting the money for the trip,
the money to enroll in driving school,
rent money and
some other small items,
this is all that is left.
But Gunma ...
You betrayed me!
In your letter you
told me a lot of lies.
You tricked me
into coming here!
You told me you got
your license in one day...
... and that you were in
love with your instructor!
And you lied about
your father giving you money!
You told me only lies!
Bingo!
It's all true!
but you wouldn't have come if I didn't...
...and our dreams would
have never come true.
Your behavior is truly unforgivable!
You deceived us
to only benefit yourself!
- More!
- Who do you think you are?
How can you act as
if nothing happened,
while your friend is
suffering because of you.
Stop it!
I'm leaving. I can't stay
a minute longer in this place!
You will see, I will
become a great driver.
And when I win,
everyone will love me!
I will do anything
as long as I win!
I'm nothing like you!
I'm better than you all!
I won't hide behind
the skirt of my mother!
I'll do whatever I want!
No one can stop me!
Tamotsu, this goes for you too.
I don't believe it!
Goodbye, my friend.
I wish you good luck, Gunma.
Well, I knew he would act that way.
I understood from the
beginning that it was all lies.
Gunma has always
been good at telling lies!
Tamotsu!
Are you alright?
I'm alright, Junko.
And because I trust you,
I'll tell you a secret.
Gunma doesn't know,
that the money he spent
was not mine, but his.
His brother Yuma handed
me the money before I left.
I hid my savings under here. Look!
I had to do this.
Gunma has a bad temper
and it is best to go along...
...or it would have gotten worse.
So this is why all of this has happened.
Wait a minute, Junko!
Listen carefully. Will you would be
willing to do me a big favor?
- What is it?
- Today Gunma said ...
...that I was a magician with engines,
however this is not true!
The truth is...
The truth is that the magician is Gunma!
- And you have to help him!
- Really?!
Please, Junko!
I beg of you...
...to help him
pass the driving test.
Gunma is unstable,
and will be thrown
out of any driving school.
The only way he'll
be able to pass is,
if you stay with him.
You have to, Junko!
You must help.
- But this isn't right.
- Please, Junko!
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
I'm gonna get private lessons!
This is my first step
towards stardom!
I'll show all of you!
In the next episode:
"Junko's Private Lessons".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away