STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Yuki, I hope your watching!
I will become the
fastest man in the world!
In the world!
Collision! Gunma vs
Hiziri!! The Axles Scream!
The streets are my playground ...
...and nothing in this world can stop me!
- The means you are among the best!
- Are you in a good mood today!
Today is a great day!
The suit Morioka
gave me is fantastic!
It makes me important!
Don't you think so?
Right!
There sure are some
crazy people at the track!
His behavior is
typical of a beginner.
Though he'll soon compete
with the best drivers!
I think Gunma will have a good
chance at wining the race!
I don't think so!
It's one thing to train for
a race but it's an entirely
different from competing in one!
Even so, Gunma has the talent necessary.
And his passion will
overcome any obstacle. I know it.
One day Ryuju
said something strange,
Who knows, though
I think Gunma will...
...become a driver sooner or later.
Please, change the subject.
Hey, guys, you want a push?
You monkey,
how dare you overtake me!
Wait until I catch you!
- Brake!
- What the hell are you doing, Tamotsu?
Remove your foot from the pedal!
Listen, Gunma, we need to
talk before we get to the circuit.
- Could you slow down?
- Why didn't you say so?
- Now there far away!
- I have to talk to you ...
... about the rules of the race.
Now listen carefully.
What is it? I thought
I only had to drive!
Open your ears and remember one thing.
This is a dangerous sport
based on mutual respect.
It's common in all sports,
but especially in motor sport,
in particular,
collaboration is essential!
You must respect your colleagues,
and the engineers and mechanics ...
And especially the director of the race!
You must abide by these rules
if you want to become a good driver.
Follow these rules.
Or else you'll be thrown out!
Or worse, you could
injure the other drivers!
This is why must
show respect to others...
and for their safety ...!
So, are we clear?
In other words should I behave exactly ...
... like a lady!
You know, this
time I think your right!
This is a very dangerous sport ...
...and I must follow the rules.
Am I right, Tamotsu?
Gunma, tell me that this is not a dream!
I've never been more serious in my life!
You know, Tamotsu, I promise
that I'll follow the rules and win!
I'm scared...can I wake up now!
I'm going to talk to
the owner of the garage.
So while I'm there,
go pay the rent.
I'll go with you.
I must say hello too.
If I'm not mistaken it is the duty
...of a gentleman!
It's true!
Don't be silly!
Now you need to focus ...
...on the race.
Then you've gotta hit the track.
...for practice!
Understand.
Where can I get a
bite to eat around here?
Hey, man,
is there something wrong with it?
- The motor isn't working.
- Why don't you call a mechanic?
- Look, I'm sorry!
- Yes, what do you want?
I would like to know where ...
Where can I get something
to drink! I'm dehydrated!
Tell me:
are you new around here?
Well, I ...
You see.
If you are looking for a toilet,
it means that you're new here!
- Yeah!
- It's forbidden to pee outdoors!
The Tsubuka circuit is no
longer what it once was!
Hey my friend, are you a driver?
Yes, of course!
Here, this is yours!
Don't get offended,
but you don't look like one.
Your not the first to say that.
In fact, even I'm not convinced.
In fact I am a student
of the faculty of psychology.
I came here to improve
my introspective analysis ...
...of the interactions of human beings ...
...including their
obvious passion for engines.
Simple, is not it?
You know what?
I am convinced that here
is where I will find my answers!
My focus is on the human attitude ...
...against space!
I will speak of this in detail ...
...in my thesis:
"Why conquer space"?
Scientists have scrutinize the skies for years,
and everyone is trying
to go higher! Why is that?
Why is this happening?
They say it is human curiosity,
but that's not the only answer!
There must be a
more complex explanation!
And I must discover it!
I must, I have to!
I must!
And so on, and so forth!
Look, "Einstein", why don't you
calm down? People are looking!
So sorry if I disturbed you,
I got carried away a
bit with my enthusiasm.
A few years ago I
decided to use my time ...
... to solve the problems plaguing mankind.
The drivers
always driver towards danger,
just to win and...
this makes them more daring!
For them, danger doesn't exist!
I think this sport symbolizes
the conquest of space.
It's for this reason that I
became interested in engines!
Hey, are you hungry?
Is there a restaurant near here,
why don't we go and eat?
Yes, it's a great idea!
I hope I did not offend you ...
- ... so I'll buy lunch.
- Don't expect anymore!
Well, take advantage of this opportunity ...
to talk about
the Rules of the circuit.
- Now I'm a veteran!
- Let's start the presentation!
-  My name is Hideo Kishida!
- My names Gunma Akagi.
You'll remember this when I'm famous!
Listen carefully and remember that,
you have to follow what they say!
And we must obey
their orders without question!
That's the most important thing!
When did you first start racing?
When I was a child.
So have you been racing since then?
I've looked at the
list of drivers in the race's ...
...last year and the year before that,
and your name wasn't on the list!
Maybe they forgot to put me on it.
That's the great Haitani!
Where is he?
The guy with the glasses!
I remember him?
So he races too.
Eh?! You mean you know him?
He's one of the best drivers in the world!
- Look! There's Hiziri  too!
- Hiziri ?!
He hasn't lost a race this year,
A true champion!
Aren't I lucky!
I never imagined ...
that I would see
my idols in the flesh!
Sorry, you're Hiziri
and Haitani, aren't you?
And who might you be?
I don't know you.
Behold, my name is Kishida.
I have the honor to take part ...
...and race with you.
It's good to have met you.
Don't worry, I'll go easy on you.
You look like no Champion I've saw!
- You'll get what you deserve.
- What do you mean, Gunma?
If you think you're the fastest,
then think again!
You know what?
Your no real driver,
your just an ordinary man!
- Do you remember me?
- Of course!
- I remember.
- I'm glad you remember.
Now you know who will beat you!
How dare you?
Do you know who your speaking too?
Hey you, you only won
because I was driving a truck!
I'll win against you this time.
Yes, in fact I remember passing a truck ...
...that moved really slow.
So it was you!
Good-bye, gentlemen,
see you on the track!
- Hey, wait a minute!
- Leave him alone, Haitani.
Listen to what I have to say,
I'm listening!
When you race with
great drivers like us,
remember the rules,
though I don't expect you to remember!
- So what?
- I seem to have been ...
...too kind to you!
Is there anything else?
What were you thinking?
- I do not know, Hiziri.
- Just tell me next time!
Didn't you know
that he's just a rookie?
Don't go looking for trouble.
I'll get you.
Defend yourself!
I advise you to keep
your energy for the race.
Assuming that you're going.
Do you understand, boy?
It will not end here,
Hiziri, I assure you.
Perfect! Now I can
listen to music!
What wonderful news!
That's really great!
Yeah it is, though
I'm alright for now
Gunma!
- Gunma!
- Where is he?
It's lunch time!
I knew this would happen!
Gunma!
Thats it's!
I just gotta remember the curves.
I'll show that idiot who's best!
- Look! Look over there!
- What is it?
He's really good.
Be careful, your turning a curve!
Where the hell did Gunma go?
I'd like to know too.
Don't worry,
I'll look for him.
- You go and grab a bite.
- Great idea!
Here he is!
Gunma is written on the suit!
He took the curve
without skidding! Amazing!
He's crazy!
He's not bad.
Excuse me.
Are you friends with Gunma Akagi?
- Why did you call us?
I thought there was no need for you!
But he challenged Haitani,
and said he would
beat him on the track...
...and him and Hiziri,
got into a scuffle!
I never thought that he would do it.
Gunma said he was racing for years!
Though I never imagined such a thing!
Gunma got angry and was beaten.
Haitani hit him, but
Hiziri stopped the fight.
I advise you to keep
your energy for the race.
Assuming that you're going.
Do you understand, boy?
And fortunately they left.
I knew it!
He is an idiot!
However, even if he was wrong,
Gunma showed
everyone that he has guts!
You're finally back!
How did you
get permission to use my bike?
Why are you so angry?
Because I've got no
time to do a test drive!
Is that is.
What's wrong with you!
Gunma, where are you?
I came a long way to get
here and participate in this race,
- Do you understand?
- Give it a rest!
Now who will pay for the damages?
My new bike!
What will I do?
- Gunma!
- Nice day, isn't it?
That's just like you.
Did you happen to see that one?
You mean the one that
got beat by Haitani and Hiziri.
He must not know the rules,
He's probably a beginner.
He just looks like a fool!
Where did he get that from?
For a rookie,
he has a good car!
Today, I'll show you defeat.
The first in a long series!
Are you satisfied now Gunma?
Why don't you ever listen to others?
This is the first time
I've see such behavior.
Didn't I tell you how to behave!
Get it over with, Tamotsu!
when a pilot ...
...like me has natural talent,
the rules become secondary!
I'm a champion
and I'll prove it!
Let's see what you've got!
I hope you win,
Tamotsu!
This is kinda hard to drive.
Don't worry,
you'll adjust during the race!
- Is something wrong?
- No just wondering!
And, we're off.
I hope he learned his lesson...
- ...and won't cause more trouble.
- Give him time,
- he'll come around.
- I'm not so sure!
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you, I though it would be disrespectful..
...if I went onto the track first.
That's touching! !
Come on, get behind me.
When do I accelerate?
You start small in the beginning.
And work your way
to becoming a champion.
It'll probably take a year.
You gotta learn
to use the car first.
Though setbacks could
happen at any time.
We have a way to go,
we need to tune the
engine and perfect it,
and improving handling...
Then we'll become competitive.
Why isn't Gunma here yet?
Yeah, it's weird. He should
have been here by now.
Look, there's a car now!
It could be him.
It's not him, that's Hiziri.
If this continues he'll will the race.
He's currently in first place,
Yes, but Gunma should
be in the top three!
Here comes another one!
It's still not him!
- He's driving like mad!
- I think that's Haitani!
I'm staring to get worried.
Where are you Gunma?
It's not over yet!
Hey, Gunma,
can't you go faster?
Shut up, Kishida!
What's wrong?
Are you running low of fuel?
I hope your not afraid,
In this circuit ...
...there's no place for tricycles!
Bye, Bye!
Damn this piece of junk!
That hurt my foot!
No one can go
faster than Gunma Akagi!
I cannot stand to see
them pass me by!
There must be something
wrong with this thing!
The speed of an F1 car
exceeds 350 km/h,
though for safety reasons
we race at 200 km/h!
Just like a train!
In the next episode:
"I am a Genius!
Gunma's Drive of Certain Death".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away