STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Gunma...
With Hiziri's money,
we will win!
Why did you do this?
Gunma Returns Home!
He Learns and Unbelievable Secret
- Tamotsu!
- What are you doing, Gunma?
Stop this at once.
Wait til I catch you.
You you'll never work for Hiziri!
Wait a minute!
I can explain!
Explain then,
and be quick!
- Why don't you calm down?
- But I,
though you wanted the money!
I've been a
good friend, haven't I?
So are you going to
through away our friendship!
I didn't know you felt like that!
I don't deserve this betrayal!
I know, this is just about Ruiko?
Gunma, you're wrong!
I did it for the both of us!
That's just a lie!
Where is Hiziri having you work?
Don't you remember
that I can't stand him!
Why are you two shouting
at this hour of the morning?
Shut up,
this guy has betrayed me!
He wants to
work for my rival!
You know what, Gunma?
You really are a fool!
Now come down from there!
Before someone gets hurt!
How dare you say that!
Hiziri took away my best friend!
Should I be celebrating?
Anyway, come down from there!
Tamotsu must have his reasons
for making this decision!
Just talk it out like
good friends should!
Why should I do that, Junko?
I'm very calm.
Help! Gunma, calm down, please!
Hiziri said he would
give me anything I wanted,
in exchange for working on his car...
...and because he
respects me as a mechanic.
But, I told him that me
and you were a team,
...and I would only work
for him when I had the time.
I hope you learned your lesson ...
...and learned to talk to one another.
To tell you the truth,
I'm glad this happened!
Because we need the money!
Now do you understand?
- This has to happen?
- Well, I think that...
you were really
lucky to get the job.
Though you shouldn't trust him,
because Hiziri will want you to stay.
He would never do anything like that.
On the other hand we
cannot continue to depend...
to take money from our friend Morioka.
- Not to mention the rent!
- It's no problem.
I understand! You have to
work for him because...
...you need to get more money.
Well, we probably won't be
getting a lot of money but,
we will be able to
participate in the next race!
Don't even mentioned that!
Consider this discussion closed!
How about you think,
just for a moment,
I would have agreed
to drive with his money?
Even so,
it's our only choice!
You absolutely have
to attend all the races!
You must, if you want
to switch to a higher category!
Ideally you should come
at least sixth in every race!
What? Finish sixth?
I can do better
than that, you know!
If I can drive, rest assured
that I will arrive at least first!
Listen to me carefully:
I understand your dreams of glory,
but reality is quite different!
For your car,
sixth place would be a victory.
Your name would become known!
So you may find a sponsor ...
...since they will
be looking for you!
Logically, you'd also have
a more powerful machine ...
...and at that point I
would have no more reason ...
...to work for Hiziri!
I agree with what Tamotsu said!
I also agree!
Tamotsu is absolutely right!
Listen, Tamotsu ...
I'm sorry, Tamotsu, but this
time you've gone too far!
And another thing: I will not
ever settle for sixth place!
Gunma, try to calm
down now, okay?
- Tamotsu!
- What!
This is the result of my hard work!
- Gunma...!
- I've earned a lot more!
I will do everything possible!
But only if,
you don't take
care of Hiziri's car!
How are you going to
get another 4 million by next week?
And then there's other races!
Your father can't give you money!
He needs it for the election!
- Then how?
- If I had to drive ...
...with my fathers money,
I would never forgive myself!
So you mean to ask
your brother Yuma for help?
Maybe!
If that's what I
have to do, then yes.
- What are you saying?
- Don't worry, I was joking!
However, I'm not going
to ask my family for money!
I see no other alternative
but to work for Hiziri!
I've come up
with an amazing idea!
What do you mean?
I'm sure, you will
earn a lot of money!
So you've already
been paid 500.000 Yen?!
Hiziri really is the
generous type, isn't he?
I'll have the money we
need within a week at most!
Don't betray me, Tamotsu!
What do you think of
my car? Do you like it?
Are you in a bad mood?
I gave you a ride, didn't I?
- You could be more polite!
- I'm not in a good mood.
If you have a
problem, just tell me.
I always give good advice!
- No, I'm alright.
- Well,
your not very sociable!
You have quite a temper, my boy!
Mind your own business!
I was only being nice!
You idiot!
Hey, what's her problem!
I only asked for a ride!
You look like a lost dog.
Eh, listen hear you fool,
stop with this nonsense!
Hey....there's no
need to get so angry...
...I didn't mean to offend you!
And.. if I were you
I'd lay off the coffee!
Why, is it poisoned!
AKAGI POLICIES MADE WITH CHARACTER!
POLICIES MADE WITH CHARACTER!
Wha!!
Take this, you poster!
- What are you crazy?
- Shut up!
Hey!
You better pay for that!
Well, I...
Gunma, is that you?
I'm glad to have met you!
Are you hurt?
What kind of question is that?
I was obviously better
before you hit me!
Oh, your here!
What a lovely surprise!
What are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you that
I didn't want to see you!
Oh it's you Mr. Akgai!
- Did he do that?
- Yes.
This should be enough!
Is this okay?
I'm sorry for the
racket that boy caused!
Don't worry, Mr. Akgai.
Thank you very much!
Tell me, Shoma...
How is Yuki?
Is there something wrong?
I asked you a question!
Yuki...
Gunma...
I'm sure Tamotsu,
Junko and the others ...
can help you realize your dream.
Goodbye, Gunma!
Yuki!
Tell me, Shoma,
after you took her away,
you did something
to Yuki, didn't you?
I didn't take her away. Yuki came
with me of her own free will.
And take your feet down,
or I'll throw you out of the car!
That's a good one!
Even an idiot like you ...
- ...can't do that?
- What?!
Try it if you dare?
Stop it, both of you.
Soon we'll be home.
Today, Mom and Dad ...
... went out for a visit,
so we can rest easy!
Gunma, why don't
we take a walk?
I just need to talk to you!
I might as well accept...
because I have
something to say too.
What are your intentions, you two?
Tell me!
- None of your business. Go home!
- Shoma, but...
I told you to go home!
Didn't I?
Yes?
This is Yuki!
I bet you came to ask for money!
Isn't that the reason
you came home?
I'm sorry to
disappoint you, but no!
I'm not here for the money!
Or returning home!
- Then why are you here?
- None of your business!
You haven't said where Yuki is!
She went away.
What?! First you take her by force...
...and then she leaves.
It was her choice.
I had nothing to do with it.
Yuki wanted to go,
Did she at least leave an address?
No parent in this world would...
...just let their child go.
I hope she at least told someone!
This is none of your business!
I take it your
not going to tell me?
I have something else to say,
You are nothing but
the black sheep of the family.
And you have
disgraced the Akgai name...
...without thinking of the consequences!
And now it's time for your punishment.
Eh?! Hey, come on
- Why don't we talk calmly?
-  I'll let you go,
if you never come back...
...my dear brother!
So that's how it is,
Remember this,
I always go where I want.
And there's nothing
you can do about that!
Damn...
I am sorry, but he
has business to attend to.
He said he was sorry
for making you come here,
Don't worry, it's alright!
So, you've decided to work for Hiziri?
- I don't know yet.
- Well now,
it seems you don't
want to because of me.
No, that's not it.
It's just...
I think its obvious
that you don't like me.
Hiziri told me that it's
very important that you read this.
But ...
What's in the envelope?
I don't know.
Hiziri didn't tell me.
Here, read it carefully.
I won't be satisfied
until I've beaten you!
Well, did that hurt?
I've suffered more
than you'll ever know!
Gunma!
- Gunma!
- So Yuma warned you?
- Why did you beat him?
- Yuma, where are you?
- I'm here!
- I told you to go home!
All of this is pointless.
Even though we have different
mothers, your still my brother.
Why did this have to happen?
Yuma, let's hurry.
We need to bring him to my house.
- What's that smell?
- So you can stand up.
That hurt!
Now I've a mouth full of cuts!
- Why don't you eat more slowly?
- It's too good!
By the way, you've settled in quite well!
It's really peaceful,
- Yuki, tea!
- Yes!
Gunma...
Want to take a bath?
Man, this is warm!
Gunma, I'm leaving you
some spare clothes here, okay?
Thanks, and sorry
for the hassle, Yuki!
Since your there...
do you want wash my back?
Now what do you do,
do you work?
- You know what I do!
- I do?
I beg you to stop making fun of me!
I  don't understand.
Let's just change the subject.
I want to forget everything
and go back in time ...
Gunma!
I feel refreshed!
- You smoke?
- A little...
You've changed a
lot from I've last seen you!
Uhm...
Shoma pays for everything.
When I was taken away
from Tokyo, he put me here.
He told me that
I wouldn't be hurt ...
if I stayed with him.
I could live without having to work.
And your okay?
I don't care anymore.
You see, I ...
What?
- Are you going to marry him?
- No marriage!
Are you out of your mind?
Yes, that's exactly
what's happening!
I'll tell Shoma that he
shouldn't treat you badly!
- Gunma...
- Yuki...
I will not let you face
the same fate of my mother!
Your not allowed to
move before the start,
...of the match!
Otherwise, in one fell swoop,
everything will be messed up!
In the next episode:
"Farewell Hometown!
Gunma Runs Straight to Tomorrow!!".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away