STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
No!
Forget about him!
Don't be afraid, I won't hurt you!
Mr. Shoma!
Yuki!
Go! Go! Go!
The Wandering Young Woman Yuki...
- Will everything be fine?
- Yes, I'm sure.
He has trained a lot
and has a good chance of winning.
Do you understand, Junko?
I wasn't talking about Gunma,
- but the car!
- That guy is dangerous.
- He drives like crazy!
- He better not destroy the car!
Keith, aren't
you going with him?
I would have gladly gone,
but the...
keys were taken from my hands!
Good Morning!
Is this where Gunma Akagi lives?
I'm a friend of his.
What do you say,
Tamotsu, I'm fast enough?
Why do you insist on driving?
I've told you a thousand times...
- ...that speed isn't enough!
- Not for me!
My life is all about moving fast!
By the way, before the race\B what should I do more?
Considering the time of day,
you may take the higher license ...
Though if all goes well...
You can take the exam next week!
Really?!
Next week?!
Tamotsu do you think I
can participate in the race!
I'm happy!
Have you noticed that girl?
Junko, do you think that
girl is from a rich family?
- I don't know!
- Maybe she had a fight ...
with her parents
and she left the house!
Junko! Yuki has started
to do the cleaning!
To me they are just friends.
Though maybe something more!
We finally found
out his secret, Philip!
Your right about that!
Just what we needed!
Stop talking rubbish!
Guys ...!
Its a miracle!
- Hooray!
- Hello everyone, I'm back.
What's going on?
That'll teach you!
- What's wrong with you?
- Why didn't you say anything?
Your girls here.
What girl?
I am happy to see you.
- Yuki!
- What are you doing here?
- Did you run away from home?
- Yes!
What happened?
Were you abused?
What did father do?
- No! Nothing!
- So it was Shoma!
- I had a feeling it was him!
- That's not true!
I shouldn't have come here.
What are you saying?
Damn!
You did the right thing!
How could you endure so long?
Don't worry,
your better off here!
Junko!
This is my friend Yuki!
We already know this.
Could you be more polite!
Hey, wait a moment, Junko!
What's wrong with all them today?
Probably because
as usual your an ass!
Now that was being an ass!
From now on Yuki,
you shall live here...
- ...with us.
- Look, Gunma, I ...
Your just like me.
We both have nobody!
- Actually, I ...
- Don't worry the guys,
here may seem like
idiots but they're nice guys!
You see, Yuki is a
good girl,  a hard worker!
Yes, let's all become friends!
She's right,
I think so too!
Come on, stop standing.
Sit down and eat with us!
Yes.
We'll have to find a
place for you to sleep.
No problem!
Gunma can sleep in my room!
Thanks but no thanks.
- Yuki and I will share the room!
- What?!
- Did I say something wrong?
- You think?!
You must be joking!
Whats wrong!
Don't you guys trust me!?
Of course not!
Listen, Yuki, next Sunday
we will have a nice trip:
- To the circuit.
- The circuit?!
I have lessons
for a drivers license.
Yuki, if I pass the exam I will
be able to participate in the next race!
- But I'm afraid!
- No, there is nothing to fear!
You'll see, my little Yuki, one day I
will be the fastest driver in the world!
- My dream will come true!
- Of course!
Look.
What a spectacle!
I'll remember this night forever.
You know, Yuki, I was
thinking that if you wish,
you can stay with me forever!
- She's a really nice girl!
- What girl?
- I mean Junko.
- Are you joking?
She's a snake in a skirt!
She's unbearable!
But Junko is exactly the opposite of me.
- She's very elegant and refined.
- Please, stop being silly!
- It's true!
- I can't stand her!
Judging by the way
your looking at it! I get it ...
Gunma Akagi,
can I speak freely?
- Of course!
- Gunma, I know your crazy about her!
Hey, how dare you say that?
If I catch you ...
Yuki, look at the acrobat!
Help!
Damn it!
I'm just an idiot!
Hey, Gunma,
I have to say one thing.
- I'm sorry for all this trouble.
- Don't worry, Yuki.
Junko,
do you also do track racing?
Oh, yes!
I'd like to drive too.
Driving isn't easy.
I must confess that I
am worried about Gunma.
Do you think he'll get to Formula 1?
If he's as good as Tamotsu says,
then he'll make it!
Of course Gunma will succeed!
Excuse me.
Sometimes I get carried away with myself.
Good night.
- What did you say?
- I too could hardly believe it!
But Yuki wouldn't run
away without a reason.
Especially from the
house she grew up in!
Something serious must have happened!
It's true.
But what did happen?
I don't care if you love Gunma.
Now you'll forget about him!
Is that clear?
Dear Gunma and Tamotsu,
sorry that I left without
telling you. I had to.
Thank you for your hospitality,
but I've decided to go live alone,
I don't want to trouble you anymore.
- Please, do not come looking for me.
- Yuki...
When I woke up her
bed was already empty.
Damn it!
I should have stayed with her!
I'm sorry! I should have
payed better attention to her!
I have to find her!
She can't live alone!
Where are you going in a hurry?
Look who's here!
What are you doing here, Shoma?
I've come for Yuki.
This is an order from Dad!
What did you do to that girl?
- Stop it, Gunma!
- As far as we're concerned,
you don't exist to us anymore!
But Yuki is different,
she has her dues to pay!
This time, Shoma,
it won't end here!
I get it. Please contact us
should you have any news.
And we'll do
the same if we get any.
My mother hasn't
seen her near the house,
but she'll call us if she does.
That mean even
Shoma hasn't found her.
Gunma, do you know why she left?
Perhaps she feared that Shoma
would find her and bring her home.
Yuki is alone out
there and she needs me!
Uhm... Did you flirt with
her or something?
- Are you crazy?
- Well, you see ...
In the end Yuki
is a very pretty girl ...
...and she's been away from you..
-  for so long.
- Idiot!
Stop thinking like that!
Yuki is the last
person I'd flirt with!
Although I admit that ...
- I have though about it!
- I knew you were like that!
This could cause
Junko to be jealous.
- What?! - She must have
thought that you two were together.
Tamotsu, if there's a girl
in this world I hate, it's Junko.
Yes, but Yuki must have misunderstood.
Now stop saying stupid things!
She must have thought
you were in love with Junko ...
...and she ran away
because she was hurting!
Hello, friends! I managed to
get a garage for the circuit.
- That's great!
-  I'm glad you're happy.
We'll bring the car over this week.
- Thank you! We are grateful!
- It's been a pleasure.
Gunma, look forward
to tomorrows lesson...
...and give it your best!
Yes, that's for sure!
So, get the next license you must,
first pass a written
exam and then the practical test.
They say it's difficult but
I'm sure you can do it...
Stop it!
I heard you the first time!
Now I know it by heart!
That's enough!
Hey! Would you mind
going a little bit slower?
What's wrong you scared!
Sorry but didn't you...
want to go to the circuit,
But your the one that's driving the car!
- The traffic light is yellow!
- Stop, now!
It's red!
Can't you see that I've stopped!
- It's Yuki!
Hey! Yuki!
- Be careful, Gunma!
- Oh, Yuki!
Don't run away!
Yuki!
Why did you run away?
I was worried,
I've been looking everywhere!
You know why, I wrote that letter.
I didn't want to stop you
from reaching your goals.
I've got nothing more to say.
Leave me alone!
I would have only
caused you trouble!
- That's why!
- But how can you think of such things?
Remember when I promised
to take you to the circuit?
We we going there.
You can come if you want.
Come on, let's go!
Don't you want to come?
- There you are! I finally found you!
- Go away, Shoma!
Listen to me, Yuki:
come back home with us.
I promise it will not happen again!
- What did you do?
- None of your business, Gunma,
get out of my way!
Or there will be trouble!
Come on Yuki, let's go home
or father will become angry.
Tell me what you did!
Didn't you hear me,
it's none of your business.
- Come on. Let's go home, Yuki.
- Where are you going?
Yuki will stay here with me!
Do you want to cause trouble!
- Now step aside.
- No, I won't!
This time you'll pay dearly Shoma!
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Enough! Stop it, Gunma!
- Let go of me!
- I'm going home!
Okay, I'll go home,
but no more fighting!
It's about time.
Don't worry about
the bag, I got it.
The boys will take care of it.
Yuki, you...
Gunma, go to the circuit!
- Yuki... What are you saying?!
- Please go!
Yuki...
Oh, Gunma...
You've got Tamotsu and
Junko by your side,
so go and make
your dream a reality!
Gunma...
Goodbye!
Come back!
No!
Yuki!
Gunma, we're late,
we have to go to the circuit.
If we don't hurry we
won't make it in time!
Come on!
Cheer up!
Don't disappoint her,
make your dream a reality!
Yes!
Faster!
I finally found you!
The machine is ready,
- it's waiting for you.
- I'm coming.
What's the matter?
- He's already arrived?
- Who?
Yes! Faster!
No one can beat me!
I'm the fastest man in the world!
That guys mad!
He's driving with a tractor!
Yeah, that guy sure is crazy.
Yeah, but he is too reckless.
Your driving style
was not much different.
Beginners are all the same.
The excitement for speed can kill!
Yuki, I promise you!
I will become the
best driver in the world!
The fastest man who ever lived!
The Regulation stipulates
that the minimum weight ...
of a Formula 1 car
must not exceed 540 pounds,
that's less than half the
weight of a normal compact car!
In the next episode:
"Gunma vs. Hiziri".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away