STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when you're DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
You know, Haitani,
I'm glad you're healed.
I'm furious!
He almost made me into a cripple!
- ...and wrecked my car!
- For real?!
That cars very important to me.
- I'll kill him if he does it again!
- It's that guy...
- he's participating in the race!
- What?!
GUNMA AKAGI
The Blaze of Elimination Matches!
Aim for the Pole Position!
As you can see,
in this drawing ...
...I've highlighted the
key points of the track.
I have indicated each
curve for which gear,
and likewise when going straight.
Try to memorize the plan!
By doing so, you'll make a lap
in one minute and three seconds!
For now, the track
record belongs to Hiziri.
He did it in 1:01:47!
Even if you don't beat him,
You can always
get a good result!
Gunma, what's so funny?
Where are you going?
Don't you remember that the race is tomorrow?
Of course I remember!
Let me go!
- Hey, guys!
- Glad to see you!
So ...
Did you do a good job on my car?
Sure! The car is perfect!
Though I wouldn't say
the same about the driver!
Well, what do you think?
It's monstrosity!
I like it very much!
You could not have done any better!
Now I'll rule all of the circuits!
- Do you really like it, Gunma?
- Totally!
With this car my victories
will be remembered by the audience!
Your victories?!
Gunma, listen to me when I talk to you!
I've told you a thousand times.
When you enter a curve ...
...you better use the right
gear or you'll lose time!
Tamotsu, you're unbearable!
You always...
...have something to say!
Now tell me!
Is this the right gear?
You probably found
that in some manual!
Well, actually I've studied a lot...
..even how Hiziri became number one!
Everything will work out
if you follow the plan.
So I'll be like Hiziri...
...if I follow that plan,
and I'll beat
his last years record.
But this mean I
could also beat his time!
It's decided,
I'll make a better record!
- Gunma...
- Wait a second!
Even if I followed
your precious scheme,
I should go even faster
thanks to our perfect setup.
That's impossible!
Hiziri's can is far too powerful!
...our car can't be faster than his!
That's just your opinion!
I will beat him, I will!
Is that clear?
I'll win!
But you're already one of
the highest-rated pilots, Gunma!
But I want to be the best!
- Gunma!
- Racing is not a game!
Shut up!
I'll do as I please!
I'll do what I want to...
...and I'll turn the way I want to!
Gunma!
MORIOKA MOTORS
Come on, guys, eat up!
There's plenty for everyone!
Thanks for the food!
Hurry Tamotsu!
Or there won't be any left!
I'll be right there!
Your always working!
They're under pressure!
I thought being under pressure ...
...was normal for them...
...though all young people are like that!
That's quite normal.
It may seem strange
because you're not used to it,
but that's what it's like for drivers!
Driver's come after
work and have little time...
- ... To fix their engines.
- And they aren't using the facilities...
...at the circuits.
And they've also got to store them.
And they don't even have
enough room for all the drivers.
If they were rich they
would have no problems,
But money isn't everything.
Yes your right,
but what can we do?
- All we can do is cover them in bags!
- Great idea!
I finally finished.
What are you thinking?
Nothing, I was just
staring at the fire.
Actually I lied,
I was thinking about something.
I am very worried about someone.
- I'm afraid something will happen to him.
- Junko!
Junko!
- Come on, Gunma, get up.
If you sleep in the car you'll have
back problems in the morning!
Come on, get up!
Junko!
What did I do?
I was only sleeping!
Yes, but you tried to
kiss her in your sleep!
When you are sleeping you are
not responsible for your actions.
The same goes for you.
- Sempai!
- Hey, hows it going?
Hey guys,
wanna know something?
Well...
Who does he think he is?
Gunma,
just forget about that car!
Not a chance!
We'll see who's the fastest!
You idiot!
Come on, bring it!
- It's Haitani!
- I came looking for you ...
...because we have a score to settle!
I'll get you this time!
It's about time I had some fun!
What?!
Don't you even think about it!
Stop! stop it!
- That's enough!
- Get off me!
What's this?
- Come on, stop it!
- Sempai
Stop this at once!
What are you doing here?
Hiziri!
Hiziri?
I hope you've learned your lesson!
That goes for all of you,
so behave
better from now on!
Hiziri!
I wanted to apologize for last night.
Hiziri.
Your of no use to him.
What do you know?
Don't take it the wrong way!
You could always team up with me,
But remember no
fooling around on the track.
Just remember: mess with
me and you'll regret it!
This isn't the last you'll hear of me!
Just remember to be
careful in the early rounds. Okay?
Just remember that..
it's important to be up front.
Do that and you'll win.
Just don't mess around with Haitani!
Stop lecturing me!
If you keep it up
- ...I'll end up falling asleep.
- Remember ...
Pay attention and
don't be caught off guard.
Remember your
training and you'll win.
Hey, Kishida, are you ready?
Is your seatbelt fastened?
- Yes, of course!
- Hey there...
- ...don't be going too fast!
- Sempai!
Just remember to remain behind me.
Sure!
This waiting is making me nervous!
I wonder if this is the tension that
stimulates the desire for conquest,
or is the desire to create tension ...!
I wish you good luck.
Thanks, I'll need it!
Gunma, we're cheering for you!
Come on, let's go!
Let's do this!
Sempai, wait for me!
Here we go again.
I wonder how many...
... times I've done this circuit!
A thousand times?
Ten thousand times?
Who knows?
Who cares?
Curse that troublemaker!
It's his fault that Hiziri hit me.
And it's his fault that
Hiziri doesn't like me now!
Why should I
drive just like in practice?
I know what I'm doing.
A real driver isn't
scared of a little speed!
I want to win and
become number one!
I hope Gunma doesn't have an accident!
I wonder what if fear ...
...affects ones desire for conquest?
Look!
Come on!
Give it your all!
The rookie is gaining on me!
I'll show him who's boss!
You won't win this time!
In a duel like this,
misconduct is allowed!
Throw all the helmets
and shoes you want,
- you won't win!
- Whatever!
Don't you remember
last nights lesson?
This is between me and you.
It seems that you still don't understand.
Stop acting like an idiot on the track!
He hasn't passed yet!
I wonder what happened?
Look! Here he comes!
- Are you crazy?
-  Get out of the way!
- I am the fastest?
- Sorry about that Gunma!
You started it!
How can you say such a thing?
But it's true,
you started it!
Two minutes, and thirty seconds!
What? Did you say two minutes?!
If they don't speed up they'll lose!
Well, the race isn't over yet!
They should speed up soon!
They've got two minutes to improve!
This is disappointing!
I'd though they would win!
I can't wait for them to finish,
then I can go home!
Gunma's a real driver!
Didn't you see how he handled that other guy!
Dear mother, something
tells me that ...
...I'll soon be back in the fields!
Damn, this guy is just unstoppable!
I'll show you!
Slow down!
It's too dangerous for you!
Sure, Sempai!
Your wish is my command!
Luck be with me!
Watch out!
On your left!
He's crashed!
Kishida!
- Kishida, are you okay?
- Kishida!
Sempai.
You go on and win without me!
Listen, Gunma,
did you see what happened?
You were reckless out there.
And poor Kishida
has bruises all over his body,
and he had to be
taken to the hospital.
He asked me to tell you one thing:
You are the greatest
driver he's ever seen!
- I've got information.
- Are these the results?
Look!
Hiziri is in front!
Hurrah! Gunma still managed
to arrive in the second to last place!
This is great!
Even though he had problems,
Gunma, did you hear?
One minute and five seconds!
You have qualified!
Before each race, the drivers must
undergo a medical examination.
If they were in poor physical condition
or had too much to drink ...
...the night before, the verdict
would be the same: "Rejected!"
In the next episode:
Finally a decisive match! Gunma
vs Hiziri, the Ultimate Dead Heat
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of you're wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away