STRENGTH...
WEAKNESS...
VANITY...
COHERENCE...
FORMULA 1 ENGINES ON THE TRACK
Riding on the Asphalt,
with an unknown speculation
Is it really okay to wonder why
My body always feel frustrated
You always know
when your DOWN
(Going down) I just can't stop (by any chance)
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) Kid there's
only a little more left
(Getting, all right) Just as you
wanted I'll let you try
(Driving, all right) You gotta run
be ahead of the times
Formula 1 Dream! I'm the Fastest in the World!!
Nobody Shall Drive Before Me!!
You listening?!
Move out of the way or we'll move it for you.
- Hurry up!
- Hurry it up will you!
Were going to be late!
Just what we needed
a motorized snail!
Hey, you, buddy!
Didn't they teach you ...
...that tractors are
used in the fields?
Yes, I know! But this
is a side road!
I don't care! I have no time to lose!
Move it right away, you turtle!!
Didn't you understand us!
Get out of the way, now!
Oh really! Since they're being polite!
We'll just have to let them through, Tamotsu!
Oh, Gunma!
What?!
Damn, and I thought I was old!
If I had another car,
I would climb with you!
- Thank you so much!
- Look, you bunch misfits,
listen to my words!
I will say it only once...
...pass by us or don't!
- Do you understand?
- Did you hear that, everyone?
We've gotta decide!
Listen, beautiful,
we are not interested in
wasting time with loudmouths like you!
Bye bye!
Who do they think they are!
- I want to drive too, Tamotsu!
- Gunma! But you...
If there's one thing that I hate,
it's those who are presumptuous!
They'll get what
they deserve!
And they will finally learn
that my name is Gunma!
Onward!
- Hey! Look over there!
- Huh?!
What... What the hell are you waiting for?
Drive faster!
Can you see me Tamotsu?
I'm sowing too!
Where is the lever
to increase speed?
It's under the odometer, Gunma!
- Ah, yes, the red one!
- Be careful!
We are on a tractor,
not a Formula 1 car.
I know that,
do not worry, Tamotsu!
Tremble in fear, for here I come!
- What is that?
- It's a madman with a turbo tractor!
No one can surpass me!
I'm the fastest!
- Get out of the way!
- Help!
- How do you like it?
- Now you can slow down, you know?
EAT FRESH VEGETABLES
WITH YOUR CHILDREN!
I told you! The tractor wheels
do not have enough grip!
- Your exaggerating as usual!
- Stop complaining!
Admit it: you had fun too!
That tractor is a true miracle!
Gunma, with this tractor
you can have lots of fun!
Sure, it's fast, but not that fast!
Oh come on!
Be modest will you...
- ...Your a mechanical genius!
- A genius?!
I only changed the
engine with one from an old Porsche.
Since we're here, why
don't we change the tires?
No way! If we did that it
wouldn't be a tractor anymore!
A tractor is a tractor and
I think it should stay that way!
Well, I've gotta go now.
Your going? Why don't
we have fun in Maebashi, instead?
I can't!
I have to help my mother in the fields.
And then I have school tomorrow!
I knew you'd say that!
Stop that tractor!
- Come on!
They are too fast!
We won't be able to overtake them!
AKAGI HOUSE
Mind the step, sir.
You dare to go in first?
Move aside, idiot!
Welcome home, dear.
I have to tell you that the
police are coming here today.
Has Gunma done it again?
Yes! He caused a
nasty accident, unfortunately.
He ran around on a tractor
in the company of a group of girls.
He then collided
with some police cars.
- So he's been arrested?
- They've detained...
...him for the investigation.
As for his strange behavior,
I was hoping that Shoma and Yuma
would serve as an example for him.
Unfortunately that is not so!
Besides,
since I'm not his mother,
I can't even scold him!
However, his behavior
is likely to be...
...counterproductive for
your political career.
- You agree don't you, dear?
- Yes, you're right.
Bring him here!
Gunma is here, Sir.
I was told of your
latest stunt this morning.
By doing so did you think
you would gain my admiration?
That's the last thing
in the world I would want.
Maybe you would prefer to
spend some time in juvie.
A great idea,
but I do not recommend it.
It would be a serious mistake.
Especially since it wouldn't help...
... your future
political career, Dad!
Your attitude reminds me
very much of your poor mother.
May the poor woman rest in peace!
My mother was your victim,
you made her suffer!
That's not for you to judge!
However, it is my duty...
...to think about your future.
So if you want to stay here,
you will have to completely
change your entire way of life.
Don't you ever think that I'll become
a mere reflection of you!
You know I can't stand you!
I'd rather not see you again!
Don't you dare challenge me!
Gunma!
It's true when they say that
blood is thicker than water!
When I look at you I only see an ugly
reflection that irritates me to death!
Come on, pull yourself together!
Gunma! Gunma!
You dare to block my path, slug?
I can't stand anyone in front of me!
- Tamotsu, how many have I overcome?
- 91, I think!
But where are we going, huh?
East? West? North? South? Where?
I don't know, any place is fine!
You aren't going to
the border, by any chance?
Who knows, Tamotsu? Maybe I'll
reach the borders of the country.
I'll go to ends of the world,
as long as no one is in front of me!
Look, Gunma!
There's a car behind us.
But where did it come from?
How long has it been there?
It's large car,
very powerful!
- Let it pass by, Gunma!
- What for?
What have they done for me?
He just wants to look good...
...in the eyes of his girlfriend?
I'll show him!
Please, slow down, Gunma!
In the name of our friendship!
Soon they'll be a sharp bend
and then there's a river!
Stop your whining!
I like a challenge!
You'll see them
in the river not us!
- I hope you remember that!
- I'll be careful, though!
Gunma!
Damn tires!
You didn't hold up!
Damn tractor!
An absolute master of the road,
driving without sliding,
even when at high speed,
he can move the best!
Now that's a real pilot!
Tamotsu!
Hello, little one!
I'm your friend.
And you wouldn't even give me an egg?
Ah! Hope you enjoyed that, Gunma!
Tamotsu should be
back at any moment.
Did you know? Your father wants
to stand in the upcoming elections.
My dear boy, you need
to get used to the idea...
...of having an
important father!
Well then,
you'll do your best...
...to help him,
won't you?
Hey! Where are you going?
Damn him!
And his damn election too!
- Oh hi, Gunma!
- Hello!
- What are you doing here?
- What's the matter?
This is nothing new, I'm always here!
We need to change the tires,
don't you remember?
Yes! But now I think it's impossible!
Mom, prepare us some tea!
I may be wrong, Tamotsu, but
you're hiding something from me!
- Huh?!
- I hate ambiguous situations, you know!
No! It's not what you think, Gunma?
I'm not hiding anything!
Don't get smart with me,
somethings up.
If you've spent two
days locked in here,
you must've had a good reason!!
I have to know!
- Gunma!
- That's it
Don't you dare!
Don't look!
Sorry, but now I've
seen it, Tamotsu!
So, Tamotsu, have
you done all this for me?
It's not mine! They asked me
if I could fine-tune their engine.
- Then we'll test it.
- What are you saying, Gunma?
- You deserve a kiss!
- No!
This is awesome!
This engine is a real gem.
What a discovery!
This is nothing like a tractor!
However, the tires
aren't quite right!
It's an economy
car, not a Formula 1 car!
Wasn't that the guy
who we met before.
Luckily Gunma is too
engrossed and didn't notice!
I found him!
What's wrong with you, Gunma?
Didn't you see those
who we met a while ago?
The car was going in
the direction of the city ...
...and in it was that guy from the other night.
But now since we are on an equal footing,
we'll see which one of us will win.
- No, Gunma!
- This time I'll be the victor!
What a sight!
In a matter of a second he...
has totally changed!
Huh, that madman is angry with us!
What a scoundrel!
Probably thinks he's funny!
As I understand it,
Gunma has never...
...driven a car before.
He doesn't even have a driver's license!
Also...
he's driving at very high speeds...
...and even has the
time to joke around!
This is crazy! Mom, I'm
afraid you're going to lose...
... your beloved son.
This is just too dangerous!
He sure showed me!
You're really an amazing driver!
Though it's time to give up, Gunma!
Tamotsu, you're my best
friend, aren't you?
- Well aren't you?
- Yes,of course I am!
So hold on tight!
Let's go!
Gunma!
Are you crazy?
Will you stop that already!
Stop acting like a wimp!
Do you understand?
I can't stand anyone in front of me!
He has guts!
But what about yours?
Take a look!
Seems we've annoyed them.
They'll never pass me,
I assure you!
No!
Stop it!
What are we going to do,
Gunma?
Teach him a lesson!
Don't ever run away from a challenge!
- No!
- Don't worry I'll fix it!
Your behavior surprises me,
James.
This isn't your style!
Don't worry he's only a boy.
I just can't stand that idiot!
Why can't this piece
of shit go faster?
Give up, Gunma. They have a much
more powerful engine than ours!
And he must
be a real driver!
That's not true!
It's just bad luck!
Mommie Dearest, forgive me!
I think my life...
...will be cut short
if this continues!
Hello, gentlemen!
Listen to me!
I've been trying to...
...persuade my friend, but
he's not listening to reason!
I would be very grateful
if you could just drop out of this challenge!
I know that your car
is more powerful!
Tamotsu, what the hell
are you telling him?
- Stop flattering him and come here!
- Please excuse what he said!
Ideally it would be better
if we could talk this out,
but it's unlikely
that my friend will do so!
- Tamotsu!
- Please, You seem like...
- ...very reasonable people!
- So what about it?
Please forgive him!
Come here, Tamotsu!
What are you trying to do?
How would you like
it cooked, ma'am?
Sliced ​​very thin
and not very spicy,
- otherwise Shoma will not like it.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Where are you going, Yuki ?
- I'm going to see Mr. Gunma.
- Leave him where he is!
- But Mr. Shoma and Mr. Yuma
...finally got back after
a long time out and...
I thought that Mr. Gunma
would like to have dinner with them.
Tonight Gunma will dine alone!
Damn-it! What the hell is he thinking?
Hey, Tamotsu, what are you waiting for?
Strip! Take off all your clothes!
- What!?
- We'll make it,
even if we have to drive
nonstop for a week!
I can't give in to him!
No one will ever beat me!
He only has the advantage
because he's in a faster car!
But now, who knows?
Luck is with me today!
Come on, hurry up!
Idiot, you were meant to
throw them on his windshield!
- But I have nothing left to take off!
- What!
- So, how was it in America?
- Not bad!
However, I prefer my home country.
- So your mother was right.
- Yes!
- What about Gunma?
- Gunma is...
Gunma...
Ha! He's quite a lively fellow!
Cars are not toys
for little kids!
What!
A man like you has no right
to get behind the wheel of a car!
Hey, stop messing around!
All your doing is preaching!
Didn't you see how
incredible my driving was?
If I had a car as powerful
as yours, I would have won!
In all of Japan there is
no one who can beat me!
Don't kid yourself.
You'll never be the fastest,
- not even in your wildest dreams!
- Your just some asshole!
Gunma!
There are tons of people who are
a lot faster than you in the world of racing!
Do you know the letter "F" mean?
It's the cars in "Formula 1"!
The cars used in
"Formula 1" are...
...built solely and
exclusively for racing!
In the next episode of
"Engines on the track"
"The Idiot's Resolution: I'm Goin' to Tokyo!".
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
Freak-Out Tonight,
It's Forbidden
Dangerous Motion
I want to forget that
lonely and loud me
Like Clockwork, don't be a
loner in the crowd
Don't you let
anyone ever stop you
These feelings
just flare up
Let's FREAK-OUT Together,
Beyond the night
The fantasy penetrates through you
Keep FREAK-OUT Forever,
don't be afraid of your wounds
You must unravel
the past, Far Away