Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
10 days have passed since
Kuroi brought the boy here.
And they've done nothing but drive the car!
However, I must admit
this guy is a tough nut!
The first day he complained
and tried to attack Kuroi,
but then asked him
to climb aboard again.
I personally think
that this guy is an idiot!
He's all brawn and no brains!
You don't say?
The Vicious Horse Rides an F-3
Kuroi, how long must I wait
before racing in Formula 3?
You have very little experience!
But you'll let me drive in
the next Formula 3 race, right?
Don't kid yourself,
you've still a way to go!
You'll have to wait at least two years!
What?! I can't wait that long!
I want to be in the next race.
I'm tired of waiting, you know?
Hey, even if you made
a good result in your category,
you still need patience, friend!
To race in Formula 3 takes brains!
You don't win with
just a great desire!
That's what a professional is!
Believe me.
What?! Who do you think
you are giving me advice,
You've never come
first in your entire career?
- Shut up!
- You slowpoke!
- Stop it!
- Now listen up,
we don't we race?
Let's see who is the strongest.
I told you to shut up.
Sempai!
I came to get you! Oh!
Hey you!
You better listen to me,
there are two
races left this year.
I will race in Formula 3 and
no one can stop me, understand?
Well, he sure is
the determined one?
I agree!
What do you say, Gordon?
There's no turning back now.
Well, our sponsor has left me ...
...to choose who
participates in the races.
- What do you say, are you up to it?
I'll think about it.
Will he seize the
opportunity or just stand still.
It depends if he's
ready to face him.
Well, I wonder if he'll
face him or just give up.
I my entire life I've never
made a decision like that.
Maybe I'm just a wimp!
Hello, this is Kuroi Racing.
Ah, it's you!
Yes, he's been here for ten days.
I don't know,
the chances are 50%!
- That's all I can tell you.
- Understood.
- I'll contact you when I have more news!
- Okay! Goodbye.
I'm really happy!
Was that news
about your sweetheart?
- Eh?! Why?
- Didn't you notice,
- you get prettier everyday!
- You flatter me!
Look, today I just want
to give you a dress!
What are you saying.
We should be buying it for you.
No! It's alright!
I have a closet full of them.
And then again
you've been so nice to me.
- You're embarrassing me!
- What do you prefer?
An elegant dress
or a sporty outfit?
I would love a red
dress and a sleeveless one!
This is peaceful.
Since Gunma left,
things are back to normal...
...and the house is
quiet for once.
Oh, yeah!
Tell me ...
Are you sure your alright?
Don't you miss him?
What are you talking about?
You like Gunma, don't you?
- Grandma ...
- Take my advice,
You should marry Gunma!
You'll be happy...
with him, don't you understand?
Hey, what's got into you?
Listen, I'm being serious.
I know that your suffering...
...like the rest of us,
thinking about Gunma!
Grandma ...
Hey, girls!
- Eh?!
- Hi there.
- Hi,
- Gunma!
Why are you here?
Don't tell me...
Don't worry, Junko,
I didn't run away!
Tomorrow, the track will
be very busy...
Well, you could have at
least called beforehand?
Have you eaten yet?
Where are the others?
They are out,
they have to work all night!
Anyway could you leave for a bit,
we need to have a talk!
- What's this all about?
- Wow, your really dense!
Those two need to be alone,
so why don't you stay with me!
So, how was it?
Well, it was fun!
I was stuck in
the old Formula 1 ...
and was
squeezed like a lemon!
What is it?
Don't laugh...
because I almost
died of fatigue!
No, that's not it.
I just suddenly remembered...
...the first time I met you.
With a straight face you
told me: "Let me drive!"
And with no driver's license!
I though: "Who is this crazy guy?"
Even after six months
you're aiming for Formula 3!
Yeah! You can
bet that I'll get...
- ...get there real soon!
- I'm sure of it.
Provided I don't exceed
the weight limits allowed!
- Oh, Kuroi...
- Oh, Gordon!
Why are you here so late?
I thought it might
be worth the risk.
The risk?
What are you talking about?
Stop pretending you don't understand.
- You know what I mean!
- Okay, Gordon.
Tell me what you have in mind.
If you got into
Formula 3 for one year,
you would become an important person,
and probably wouldn't talk to us!
That's what happened with Robert.
Suddenly, he had
created a kind of void!
A void.
He created an unbridgeable gap ...
...between those who succeeded
and those who didn't.
A void even love could not fill.
It was impossible to fill that void...
...and then you suddenly appeared.
As impossible as it
may seem, we won't give up.
That's the truth.
You're shaking ...
Hello. Is this Gunma,
this is Kuroi.
Gunma, be here at six
o'clock tomorrow morning.
You'll drive in Formula
3 just like you wanted!
Eh?! What? Are you serious?
What changed your
mind all of a sudden?
Since you challenged Gordon,
he wants to race with you!
Well, I never imagined
that he had the guts...
...to do a race with me.
I'll see you at six then!
-  But on one condition!
- What condition?
If I win, let me participate
in the next Formula 3 race.
Well, what's your answer?
If you don't agree...
Hey, what's wrong?
I was waiting for your response!
So what is it?
- Fine, I'll agree to it!
- Great! See you soon!
See you tomorrow morning at six o'clock!
Understand, after the first ten laps...
whoever is in the lead wins.
Now remember, you need...
to wait until
the tires are warmed up!
Hey, Gordon, I don't know
why you accepted this challenge,
but I'm ready to
drive with you forever.
Or until you can't take it.
Try not to be so cocky, boy!
I'll show you who's a pro!
Don't be so sure of yourself!
Until now, professionals,
I race always bite the dust.
Oh, my!
Look how he's driving!
Whats happening?
What's wrong with this clutch?
I can't control it!
What's the matter, Gunma?
Have you forgotten how to drive?
TRUTH AND LOYALTY
- I am very sorry!
- Fortunately, your father has noticed.
It would have been a
mess if someone else told him.
Yes!
I am truly embarrassed!
How could you be so stupid?
You've let yourself get
fooled by that girl ...
...and you gave her
large amounts of money...
...that was for my election!
Please give me a little time!
I'll fix everything.
Try to be careful.
The elections are approaching.
You must immediately return the money!
And I also want to see that girl!
Yes! I have already
taken all the necessary steps!
Gordon is going too fast!
His tires are very hot!
He's doing his best.
It's not all his fault!
No driver can better
control a Formula 3 ...
- ...when it's first time!
- Wow, it's that much different?
Of course, ma'am! Each category is
completely different from one another.
You see how he is sliding,
that's proof of it.
What's wrong with it?
Why is it moving on it's own?
The machine slides when
the driver is unable to control it.
There is too much
power being sent to...
...the ground and the steering
wheel is feeling the feedback.
He needs better control.
Make up your
mind you hunk of junk.
He hears that the
engine emits strange noises?
He can't stay in control.
This means that he is
driving with the wrong gear!
The engine of the Formula 3 car should ...
...be between the 4000 and the 7000 rpm!
It should not go
either fast or slow!
He looks like an
idiot driving like that.
Though, I still don't understand
what is wrong with Gordon.
Even if he wanted
to do this race ...
- Nice shot!
- ...it won't improve his driving!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Apparently, Gunma
Akagi is learning fast!
I did it!
I did it! I did it!
Finally!
So this is a Formula 3 car!
The driving style!
The most suitable position!
And with the right gear!
The engine screams!
This is so beautiful!
Hey, this is amazing!
And he's only done
three laps on the track!
- Look! He has already
found the right set!
- Extraordinary!
- Sempai!!
- Gunma!
You know, Yasu,
I think this guy ...
...might have potential after all.
Even though Gordon
has had time to improve ...
...he still hasn't
improved his driving style.
But instead Gunma Akagi, after a few laps ...
...has perfect
control over his machine.
It seems that, in his life,
he hasn't ...
...drove like that before.
Now that my
tires have warmed up...
...my speed will increase!
What do you say, Mr. Gordon?
He's accelerating
and wants to overtake Gordon.
He's amazing!
He beat me! !
I've been beaten!
For three years
I've drove these cars ...
...and I've been
beaten by an amateur ...
...who's driving a
formula 3 car for the first time.
I've won!
Now I will make my debut in Formula 3!
It's my time!
No one will ever beat me!
Sempai!
Did you see?
Gunma is a champion now!
You could lose him.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Even if this were to
complicate things between us,
Gunma showed me
that with the will ...
...you can do anything!
I won't give up.
You've become a strong girl!
I'm proud of you!
Yes! I've decided to make
him drive in the next Grand Prix.
- I know, but do you think he will do it?
- Of course!
He's good, I wanted to
let you know that. Goodbye.
Yes ... We have completed
the investigation right now.
Okay! Did you find out
what happened to that money?
The money was handed
over to the Kuroi Racing Team, sir.
A Racing Team ?!
Who's the driver?
There are two: Gordon
Turner and Gunma Akagi!
What ?! Gunma Akagi?!
Yuki...
Gunma,
I hope that you win.
Damn you Gunma!
I won't let you
get away with this!
Gunma...
Gunma, everything
will be all right ...
..even if we are separated.
But please,
be careful...
I hope your
dream becomes true!
It's terrible!
The team was attacked!
Kuroi is seriously injured!
- The cars were set on fire ?!
- Who was it? Who the hell was it?
In the next episode:
Just before the F3 Debut Gunma's
Visited by the Black Devil's Hand
I will not let anybody,
to overtake me!
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you