Formula 1 - Engines on The Track
My heart's continuous signal of love
It's that way because
I want to embrace you
And as I waited I
decided to dance slowly
Both of us could
read each other's lips
We secretly bathed
in the moonlight
After the goodbye
You left without leaving a clue
Don't betray me Darlin'
She passed through the city
Nobody knows Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
I felt you when I
touched your hand
Your a woman
Love Affair
Together until the morning
Making Love and no more
Those words of love
that you want to hear
Your a woman
Now I will teach you how
to overcome someone, Gunma!
Damn!
Farewell Gunma!
Rise Fastest Man in the World!!
Hiziri, now the fight is just
between you and me.
I've finally found you!
It's useless to run away,
because I'll find you again!
Remember that!
Come on engine, don't
give out on me.
If you have the chance,
try to keep up with me.
Because I'm going to teach
you something interesting.
I wonder what
he meant by that.
He must have
meant something important.
But he's probably bluffing!
I'll show him something important instead!
Incredible!
I can hear the engine singing.
It's music beats in unison
with the beating of my heart!
Now me and the
machine are one.
Come on, sing!
Sing louder!
He's pulling me.
- What?
- Fantastic!
That car has an engine much
more powerful than a Formula 3!
H-Hiziri...!
How did he do that?
I'm pushing my car to the limit!
Is it possible
for me to go faster?
It will be an
impossible task for his car.
His potential is
higher than yours!
I warn you that
Hiziri is in great shape!
And he is absolutely
determined to win!
And he must do it!
Otherwise next year,
he won't be able
to race in Formula 1!
He won't be able to race in Formula 1!
So...
Hiziri isn't bluffing after all,
He asked me to follow him so he could...
... laugh at my inferiority!
Finally the world is in my hands!
I don't think
Hiziri saw the signal.
I-I've never seen anything like it!
After many laps of high speed his
engine shows no signs of slowing down!
This is all because of Tamotsu's abilities.
Isn't that right, Eijiro?
Here comes sempai.
My car can't
go faster than that!
Gunma is really
giving it his all.
But he can't overcome Hiziri!
- Unless a miracle happens ...
- A miracle ?!
Hiziri is going strong,
However, his engine could stop working.
This is it! I've had enough
of being behind Hiziri ...
...and eating his dust!
At the cost of ...
...breaking the engine,
I will surpass him!
Hiziri is above his own limits!
And he's definitely not afraid.
And that means only one thing:
Hiziri is by far the
greatest driver of all time!
It's a miracle!
I've never felt so warm inside!
And this means that
the fatal moment is near!
The degradation of the
suspension, tires and brakes,
the roar of the engine, the valves,
the movement of the pistons ...
I can feel it in my hands.
Every square inch of asphalt
and every little wildfire,
has the lust of a diamond!
The grass, the trees, the flowers ...
Right now their colors seem
more beautiful than ever.
I've never noticed,
how beautiful nature is.
Unfortunately, I've
realized it too late.
This world is full of light!
I've never seen
so much in my life!
Are you following me , Gunma?
It's wonderful! I feel like
I'm in control of his life!
I wonder why he
didn't see the signal.
Tamotsu...
He's hurt!
Thanks for everything, Tamostu!
This machine was the
best gift I've ever received!
Glory awaits!
But instead of me,
share it with your friend Gunma.
I'm so sorry!
But ... I can't!
I promised not
to stop your race.
You decide your own fate.
Now it's just you and me, Hiziri!
Ever since this race began
I've done nothing but hang back.
But I am the
fastest on the track!
And I'll prove it.
I have to hurry,
we're on the final lap!
The track is perfect and
I'm not even forcing the engine!
But if I put myself in his wake,
I should be able to overcome him!
Yes!
This is it!
Yes! Just when
he least expects it!
I ask only one thing, Gunma!
I'll teach you how a great
champion behaves on the track!
H-Hiziri.
Is that so, Hiziri!
Now I know what you
were going to teach me!
Hey! Slow down!
If you continue like this,
the engine is likely to melt.
Let's try that again.
Speed up and drag
me like you did before.
And when you do,
I won't hesitate to overtake you!
Gunma! Slow down!
You can't continue at that speed!
Come on, Hiziri! Why the wait?
Do that trick you did again!
This time I'll show you that
I have learned this lesson well!
Gunma Akagi?
So he's still with me, that's good.
Great! He's accelerating!
If I can take full advantage
of his trail, I'll pass him easily!
I only hope that the
motor keeps working.
Ah!
Huh...
Hiziri?
What's going on?
Why isn't Hiziri following me?
He can't have gave up so easily!
Hiziri better be alright!
- Hiziri! Answer me!
- Hiziri!
- Send an ambulance! Now!
- How did this happen?
I don't know!
Maybe it was the brakes!
Hiziri!
Hiziri, what's wrong with you?
Answer me, please!
Hiziri answer me!
In ... In all the world ...
...there is no one ...
...better than you!
Good luck!
Hiziri!
Wait!
I will take off his helmet.
And his mask!
Your free now,
you can breath.
Look at you...
We have to do something...
or your skills will suffer.
Where are you taking him?
I'll teach you how a great
champion behaves on the track!
All you gotta do is
keep up with me, Gunma.
Thank you Hiziri, for this lesson.
You are a great driver and I
will try to follow your example.
Hiziri asked me to
become his mechanic!
I can't explain the reason why,
but I can't betray the
promise that I made to Hiziri.
- Please forgive me!
- Forgive you!
Only now I
understand why you did it!
Gunma!
Hiziri!
Tamostu!
The champagne!
You are the winner!
Forgive me for being presumptuous.
Goodbye, Hiziri
... my friend!
What a bunch of idiots!
Risking their lives on the track
...and now look at what's happened.
Come on, let's go!
Y-Yuki.
Gunma AKAGI (JAPAN)
DATE OF BIRTH: 26/03/1970
CAREER: CHAMPIONSHIP FJ1600
5 RACES, 2 WINS,
1 SECOND PLACE, 2 WITHDRAWALS
ALL-JAPAN FORMULA 3 CHAMPIONSHIP
DEBUT IN THE LAST RACE (WIN)
HAS SCHEDULED TO PARTICIPATE
IN F1 GRAND PRIX 1990 ...
I saw you crying after
you were abandoned
Let's climb that hill
and look back down
In the big world it's undeniable
Yesterday's pain is
not visible anymore
OK Let's start it
In order to grieve
Ah It's as if we weren't born
You are my energy, You are my energy
Courage come out
By just being with you