A girl involved in love
may easily make a slips!
As social ethics are sinking
I must warn you
against this
I hope you understand
what I mean
Mum, I'm going to see
a classmate with my sister
It's been an hour
I'd better go & find her
Oh, no, her mum won't care to see you!
I must go out
Don't go out!
Cut, VTR play back
Auntie Lan, what a powerful slap!
Is it?
What is it?
Be on your guard
No! No one has been following us!
I've been wasting my time
on filming
Mr Chen has openly claimed
he'd date you!
Don't gutter nonsense
Jenny, excuse me!
Auntie Lan, where are you going?
Tung Hsing
Give me a lift
Okay
Don't write about it!
I must leave. Bye-bye
A car will pick you
up in Thailand
The Hotel has been booked
Board the plane and take a rest!
Go straight to the
hotel room on arrival
After you finish, don't go out
Come back by an early
flight tomorrow
Take it, Auntie Lan
Thank you
She is come in
and the further expansion
of our group
I propose we should offer...
Okay! No problem
You guys go ahead
I'll be back in a minute
First of all, we should offer
We guarantee on our reputation
everyone's good
HK$400 for a local
How much did you
make last night?
Nothing
My husband was on leave
So I had to serve him free
I fared even worse
I did my best to
serve my client
and thought he would
give me some tips
But he gave me nothing
How outrageous
Ling-ling, Pi-shan
you go to Uncle 7
You've guests waiting
Tsui-tsui, you can speak English
Go to Johnny
You've nothing to loss
It's $100 more
Here it is!
Beautiful bosom, beautiful ass
Very good! Not bad, very nice
One hundred US dollar, okay?
You want to take a bath first?
Hello Jenny
Oh, looks even better off-screen
Come...
Take your pick
Stallone, John Travolta,
Chau Jun Fat
Anyone will do
I'll go & take a bath
Okay!
Jenny, Stallone's here
Stallone's excited
Stallone's lousy
I should've picked
Chou Jun-fat
How's it Fei-fei? Depressed?
Want to make
a confession in a church?
Innocent?
Innocent or erotic?
I did it when I was 13
I did that more than you ate
Great! She looks like Big Sis!
Hey, you know who did
that to you last night?
Do you remember that?
Not me, not me, not me!
You did it
A few pills
couldn't turn me on
You're sober, you're smart
Since we got on okay
& we fit each other
Why not follow me?
What have I to gain?
Everybody here knows me
If you follow me
You have no worries
I don't mind being your darling
But I'm possessive
If I ever catch you
being unfaithful
you may not return
in one piece
Well, feel sorry?
Bear with it!
Life counts for much, you said it!
I'll pay first, Miss
Hello
Our cleaning charge
has to be raised soon!
When?
The 1 st of next month
Well, they want me
not to come again?
To come more often each week!
Mum, you're lying
What's it now?
You promised to take
me to Disneyland
if I got full marks
Now you're bought me
this toy only
I'm too busy
I can't spare any time for that
When I'm off,
I'll take you there
Reading again?
Don't gripe about headaches!
Oh, no, I've never felt any better
Mummy, mummy!
Don't sit up so late!
Mummy, I've squeezed out
the toothpaste for you
Thank you
Hey, you're using
my toothbrush again!
Come on, use your own
Oh, no. I want to use yours!
Don't get any bleeding like I do
I want to have sex with you, okay?
How much do you want?
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Let go!
Miss Lin
Ever been teased in acting?
What did he say?
He wanted to know your
charge for going to bed!
What did you tell me?
I said you're my fiancee!
Maniac!
Jenny
Jenny, give me
an autograph please
I'm sorry, you must
have made a mistake
That's not being fair
That's no way to treat me!
Sorry!
I'll buy them back for you
How can I contact you?
Do you live in HK?
Yes, but my folks live in Thailand
You'll find me there
in the day for sure
Are you a student?
Yes, I'm a senior this year
Which seat is yours?
Mine? 25B
I'm next to you
What a coincidence
Look
You're kidding
I could get a swap in a minute
Don't take you seat now
If you do, no man would
swap with me!
Crazy
Godfather, Ling Yu's here!
Godfather
Mr Wen
Where's that shrew?
Which one?
My daughters are all nice!
Shan-shan!
Shan-shan
It's loan shark Chan again
Say that I'm not here!
Come on!
It's a friend of
Ling Yu's godfather
Do you miss me?
No, I'm getting angry
There's none better
than godfather
Boss Wen, you must
make a self-review!
When have you bought a new watch?
Show me
Be careful, it's expensive!
It suits me well!
Give it to me!
What? It costs me thousands!
Ling-yu, let's not talk about money!
Remember how much
you took from me?
It suits me well, I'll keep it!
Stop joking
Give it back to me
Or I'll get mad
Give it back to me!
Never!
It's already on my wrist!
What a bitch!
Give it back to me!
Godfather, get it back for me!
Well, well...
Well, forget it, Ling-yu!
I'll buy you a new one!
Why do that?
She's so naughty
Quiet!
He's promised to
buy you a new one!
I'll pay for it!
Take it for my gift to Shan-shan!
Why worry about this?
I still owe you a favor
on that last deal
Ling-yu's out
No need to wait for her!
Is she?
I'm here
You're late,
have another drink to make up
Leave it to me!
You're kind!
When did you buy this?
Be careful, it's expensive!
It's nice! Give it to me!
Never! I bought it for thousands!
Let's not talk about money
Remember how much money
you took from me!
It suits me best
I'll keep it!
Give it back to me
or I'll get mad!
No...
Am I to deposit a check
into your bank?
No
Fucking bitch!
You peep, you're so cheap!
That's no way to talk to me
I'm your dad
My dad?
You fooled my mum
and you're making passes at me
Don't say you've
no flames outside!
So what? I do what I like
Is that any of your business?
What're you talking about?
He! He's a creep!
Me, a creep?
She always returned late
So I warned her against
getting trapped
Shit!
How dare you?
Sister
He's a peeping Tom!
When you were
hospitalized last time
he caressed me when
I was asleep
I feigned ignorance
to avoid provoking him!
She's getting out of her mind
I've been treating her
like my own daughter
Why are you bearing me a grudge?
Why didn't you shout
when he caressed you that night?
What are you up to?
Trying to huff me?
You want to know why?
I was still a kid
I didn't want to give
you a breakdown!
Chuan-chuan, where are you going?
Never mind me
I won't see that creep anymore
What? You...
Chuan Chuan
I want to move to your side
I always wanted you to join me!
Discos, shows!
And you name it!
But we must get together
to make some dough
I'll work at McDonald's
Are you going nuts?
Would you've spare time
to go out?
And how much can you earn
What else can I do?
My darling wants a high pay
Short working hours
freedom and lots of dough
Isn't that right?
Let me give you
a few private sessions
You may resent me
I've slept with many men
Never
It's easy money
Far better than working
at McDonald
Why work so hard bitch?
With dough, we can
have fever anytime
I'm getting a sore heart too
Terrific!
What kind of a guy is that!
He's quite presentable
Well, I'll take your advice
They're coming
Go and get the keys!
Mama san,
why are you late again?
Sorry,
they spent too much
time on make up!
Well, you go
& get the keys yourselves!
Shan-shan,
what's your room number?
Mine's 204
Can't open it. Is this the right key?
Don't weigh on me
This is not my room
Okay, okay
I won't be late!
Wait for me!
She's okay!
A fatty again
Two together? It's killing
What a shapely figure
I can't, it's coming
So much the better I'm a vampire
The sight of blood turns me on!
Yuan, it's the best divination
I'm so excited!
Well, go now!
Take good care of my nephew
It's his first time!
Remember to come to me
if it keeps coming
Well, you can't make it today, can you?
I'm alright now
Miss, may I know your name?
Romona is my name,
romance is my personality
I'm a sentimentalist
& a tender lover
I've good aspiration & ideals
Look at my eyes
They are full of lust
What's wrong?
Have I no appeal?
Yes, but I can't be turned on!
They say when touching
a female leg
a man has a slight reaction
When touching further down,
it rises to a medium degree
Still further down,
it jumps even higher
And still further down...
You're sweating!
It means you've been turned on!
I'm sweating with fear
How come?
Don't laugh if I tell you
What's wrong?
Just tell me! Come on!
You're a man! Don't be sissy!
Come on!
I was in bed with a foreign bird
when I was a student in UK
But after I took off everything
She jeered: Little Man!
From that time on...
So what's the big deal?
I'm not a foreign bird!
Why worry?
But you look like one!
Come on, let's try again...
Keep away! Please go away!
I thought you were a he-man
Calm down!
I'll pay you all the same!
3 grand for doing nothing?
I'm lucky
How much would you pay
if you could make it?
I won't try the second time
It depends on affinity
Don't ever tell
my uncle about this
Who's your uncle?
That fatty you saw just now
Yuan, how do you feel?
Hey, lend a hand!
You're hitting me!
Why are you standing
behind me?
Don't worry
Next time I'll stand in front of you
Take it back!
Well, do I look like a film star?
Go on with your studies
I won't bother you
When shall we meet again?
I'll be free
when the paper is fixed
My schedules are rather uncertain
I managed to come only because
the schedule has been changed
Excuse me
Go on! Don't see me out
Why is she here?
Who is it?
Jenny Lin!
She's quite beautiful!
She has a good personality
I must study hard
Mr Fang, be patient
I can't commit myself now
Doctor, I've already
waited for 6 months
I want to have a kidney
transplant early
You know how many patients
are waiting for this?
Some of them don't
even have family support
We're waiting for
kidney donors too
Fei-fei...
I'll quit! I'll quit! Go now!
Otherwise, we must
pay the loan shark!
I'm scared!
With me here, you've no fear!
Come on!
Don't be scared
Go up, hurry up!
Want to go around the world, sir?
It's alright, perfectly alright!
Please go in & sit for a while
Bobbie, you get me
involved on her first day
Pay us back if she's
in no mood for work
Sorry, Ming
I promised to serve him well
Hurry up!
Sorry
Yours
Bye-bye!
Look, she really is enjoying it
Why not?
She has no family burden
Without me, her family
would have been finished
Jimmy, I want to talk to you
What do you want now?
I want to borrow $60,000 from you
$60,000
I want to buy my husband
a hemodialysis machine
I promise to serve
more guests in a day
Stop dreaming
How much interest on $60,000
40% interest each month
For that alone
you've to do 12 sessions a day
I don't mind
You wouldn't get
so many guests
and you've to allow for periods
or sickness
What if you get sick?
Oh, no!
Ling-yu, a guest for you!
Who's it?
Ling-yu, isn't that the little man
you teased?
So it really is you!
Where's your uncle?
He's not here
So, you've come by yourself!
You know what happened
at the meeting
I opened the file
& your bra dropped down!
Good, let everybody
know you're hefty
Well, why are you doing that?
Only for fun
This is not mine
It's not my size
So, it's yours!
Such a big size must be yours
Good, what a compliment
Thank you
I... I want to leave!
I'll call the waiter for you!
It's beautiful!
So small
Hi, isn't Ling-yu coming in?
What's taking so long?
Well, I'll go out to see
You change & we'll fix the bill
Okay!
I'll do it
$900, please, sir
I'm not used to this place!
I'll give you my home number
Let's go for
some healthy activities then
Sleep! Close your eyes
Mei-feng
Still not in bed?
I'm waiting for you
Go in first!
Are you not tired?
Darling, not tonight,
I've no more condoms
I know how to take care!
No, it's not safe
Come on
Oh, no, next time!
Next time?
I may not live to do it
If you're so depressed
why should I work so hard?
Mine's a chronic disease
which is costly
Who knows how long
you're going to suffer?
For the sake of you & Ming
I don't mind
Ming is our hope
He'd take care of you if
& when I leave you
Don't say that!
I'm going out now!
Where?
I'll go & buy it a 7-Eleven
She has been filming
the whole day
Let her take a rest!
Come and get it
Her mammy's above
Don't alarm her
Climb up quietly
to bring Jenny down
After you come down
go and embrace her
Easy
Try
Jenny, take your position
Jenny... your turn!
Jenny, come... quick!
Come here quick!
You read this
And Hua reads this
You meet
then hug and kiss
Okay, Director
Then you say, let's go up!
Countdown 10 seconds,
5, 4, 3, 2
"Your heart"
"meets my heart, makes a love"
"Your hot kiss is like the rage
of the sea"
What now, Director?
She's so stiff
I just can't play this part
What's going on below?
"Laugh can't be stopped"
"Warmth can't be stopped"
"Everything in you"
"glitters with love in my life"
The whole Hong Kong's asleep
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, my surname is yuen
Oh, it's you!
Sorry for waking you up
I thought you'd risen
You gamble & you take pills
Can't you cut off
the bad habits?
Ling-yu, what are you
talking about?
Never mind,
I'm not talking to you
Have you got any money
Well, fifty-fifty
I've no change
Just say it if you need money
Don't be shy
Let's go eat in a minute
I've no time
I've an appointment
Where?
Play ball
Where's the ball?
Ask her
Now, the ball is mine
What a shame!
Shame on you!
I bet you to play with me
What would I get if I win?
The winner can make
fun of the loser
Are you sure?
Hey, me first
Start!
Oh, good!
Hopeless! Let me!
So you've lost too
Where did you learn it?
Didn't you play in childhood?
Where are you going now?
Anywhere you say
To buy a dress for you!
For me?
That boutique offers
lots of patterns
Chic, isn't it?
Try yours
Don't mess them up!
What? Get away
Sister, does it look awkward?
You're top old fashioned
You're no longer young
Did that bastard do anything to you
He's alright!
Mammy has been matching him
Sister, when are you
moving back?
When I work for 1
more year or 2
Well, you may tell
mum you're off
And move
to join me
I've to work
The bookies may call me any minute!
Shut up! My sister!
2 sisters combining
to make a living
Bobbie, you can all be relatives!
Sis, I'll go & change for
a school uniform
Take it when the fruit's ripe!
Stop dreaming!
My sister's a good student
Jimmy, I must go home!
What? It's busy now
Don't go so soon!
My son's back from
school early today!
Stop acting!
I'll talk to you after
I get a packet of cigarettes
Jimmy!
Ming, why stand there?
Mummy's over there!
Where?
Tsui-tsui
It's not mummy!
Go back home!
Tsui-tsui, wait for me!
Thank you
Jenny, happy birthday
Happy birthday!
Thank you
Jenny, come and slice the cake!
Can we wait a second?
She's waiting for her boyfriend!
Her boyfriend's here
Let's all sit down!
Go there!
Be quick
Jenny, come here!
Come on, hurry up,
here comes the actress
Come on
Beautiful!
Hey... sing the birthday song
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you, Jenny
You're late!
I was busy
What gift are you
giving to Jenny?
I forgot to bring any!
You really are clumsy!
What?
It's now the vogue
to give one's heart!
How much have you got from me?
Help me!
Slice the cake!
Miss Lin, a gift needs
your signature
Wonder what it is
Well, over here!
Great
Happy birthday! Open it!
What does that mean?
My parents are coming
to HK soon
I'll go with you to see them
maybe they want you
to be their escort
and take them around
for sight-seeing
Jenny, got in & have a trial run!
Jenny, congratulations!
Thank you
Comfortable?
Well, do you like it?
Since when did he get the fever?
Already one week ago
but it goes off & on
His fever seems
getting worse today
Go out & check in for him
What's it so serious?
A tonsillitis,
but there maybe complications
Let me check carefully
Wonder how Ming is
Don't worry!
The doctor's report
will be out soon
Sorry
Mammy, I'm a bit late today
Well, Ling-yu wanted me
to see a video movie with her
The hero was your
favorite Chou Jun-fa
We watched till 5 am
I felt hungry and
told her to go to the kitchen
to get something to eat
She came back with nothing
and said:
"There's nothing, what about this?"
What was it?
Two chickens
Mum, I should've
listened to you
Now a hostess is no
better than a whore
But I promise to
earn more money
to get you cured
Mum, don't ever leave me
My wife & children
are returning from
USA next week
I must enjoy myself today!
You've brought all the girls!
How can we cope with them all!
Shan-shan, why don't you change?
I don't like swimming
You must play along
You're paid for
Well, what does money count? I don't
wanna change! So what? Damn it!
We're all here for fun!
Just calm down!
Well, come on, get up!
You creeps, don't cut corner
Shan-shan, shut up!
Don't provoke Godfather!
Why's she so depressed?
Did you force her?
She was not in this mood
when she took the money
She must be out
of her mind now!
Yes, I'm out of my mind!
If you prefer,
I'd repay you the money
Don't be nasty!
Are you a nut!
Shit! Mind your own business,
mainland girl!
Go in to wash &
change for a swimsuit!
Come on!
You're a freedom swimmer,
you must be a good swimmer!
If you like swimming
you go ahead
What are you talking about?
So what, mainland girl?
Say that again!
Fuck a duck!
Say that again
How dare you?
Police check!
Police check! Open up!
What are you doing?
Is your girl working up there?
No, I was passing by
Who's inside?
Why is it locked?
Open up...
What's taking you so long?
I was getting dressed!
Does it hurt?
How old?
Sixteen?
I'm 56, I've worked for 40 years
Every whore has a story!
What's yours?
For love?
Once a whore, forever a whore
Look
I wanted to win a man's heart
Now all I get is a denture,
an ugly face
and V.D. Such a long ordeal
You got in from here,
go out from here too!
Coming, coming
Master
Please come in
You're welcome
Oh, she's ever prettier
off-screen!
Please sit down
Miss Lin, my mummy
is your drama fan!
Last time I saw your
serial drama
I wept on seeing the end
and his dad said I'm a nut
Well, let me introduce
my mummy
Auntie
Auntie, sister
Auntie, take this!
Thank you!
Come and see the others
So you're here!
I was busy at the kitchen
and didn't know you were here!
Never mind
My auntie 9!
She lives here!
Welcome
Nice to see you
Brother, come & play with us!
To see you!
Auntie
Quiet, they're my sister's children
Come & play TV games with us!
Jenny has to see others
Brother's interested
in these pieces of land
Okay, I'll have the data ready
Steven
My uncle!
Nice to meet you
My brother-in-law, Jenny
Where's dad?
He's upstairs calling Thailand
on business
He's busy even on holiday
He's planning to acquire several
listed companies in Thailand
Has he many
interests in Thailand
He must be very busy!
Take Miss Lin
upstairs to see dad!
Coming!
Jenny, my dad
Nice to see you, Uncle
Nice to see you
Auntie, come &
take photos for us!
Miss Lin, come &
take photos for us
Come & take photos
Come... sit down!
Put on something first!
Hurry up!
Wait for me, wait for me!
Don't be so long
Good boy
You were excellent
at games in childhood
Now, you're excellent
at making love
Dad, I'm serious
We're true to each other
How can you be true
to this kind of girl?
Dad, don't tell me that
You look down on artists!
So she's playing you
on her palm!
You know what she does?
She's a whore!
Who says?
I do!
Uncle, did you read it
in the gossip magazine?
Sometimes we take
a moral holiday
but won't tell you about it
Your dad doesn't want
you to be fooled
He wants me
to remind you that
some of these Thai merchants
have slept with her
I want a soft drink
Me too
Don't drink too much!
I want one too
What proof have you got?
Before you left
she flew to Thailand to serve me
Jenny said she had to
rush for recording
Jenny
Steven, don't let your
relationship with a whore
get me into a family scandal
I don't care,
I must marry her
Will you take Chou Chih-hsiung
as your husband
for better or worse,
for rich or poor
And cherish him all your life?
I do
Now exchange rings
Oh, no!
Don't get out before we say 'cut'
Jenny...
Jenny, what's going on?
Jenny
Never mind her!
Jenny, the Director wants
you back for filming
Tell the Director to wait
Wipe off your tears first
Thank you
Your friend has been waiting
Why are you weeping?
Act... ing only
Tell the Director to skip
your close-up first
Okay
Get going
Why didn't you answer my call?
I switched off my beeper
while working
Hi, Jenny, have a pose
They say you've
been in high spirit
Jenny, what a beautiful gown!
When are you going
to get married?
Not sure myself
It all depends on her!
She'd given you the chance to decide
What's your answer?
Excuse me
We've something to talk about
Do you want to talk to me?
Have you been
overseas these days?
What do you mean?
Nothing
I'm going to USA
on family business
Join me
if you're free
What do you say?
Sorry, I can't,
filming's not yet over
Have a good time yourself
Call me when you get there
Excuse me
Is Mrs Fang in?
It's from the office
She's out at the moment
Who's speaking?
Tell Tsui-tsui
to return to office
Didn't you boil
the congee for me?
It's almost time to see Ming
I told you that before
Tsui-tsui
Mrs Fang? This is the Hospital!
Your son's getting serious
The doctor wants you &
your husband to come at once
Thank you
It's from the Hospital
They want us to go at once
They say Ming's getting serious!
I know you never do it
in Hong Kong
Make an exception now
He came from overseas too
Don't worry,
I introduce respectable men only
I've never let you down
You can keep your
family girl image
after these years!
I'm going to Canada next month
You don't have to worry
about me anymore
Jenny, just do me a favor
Don't worry
They won't stick to you forever
Okay, I'll do it
I won't do it!
Have you any say on this?
Come back
What's wrong?
I won't do it without condoms
What's wrong with your girls?
She wants me to wear condoms!
Is the service free?
Bobbie
Well, I'll fix it!
Go through it now!
No!
Who'll suffer if anything happens?
I may lose all my teeth & hair!
So you're getting nasty!
Listen, just do as I tell you
Nuts! Do it yourself if you like
Am I not born of a mother too?
Bitch
How dare you talk back?
Speak up! OK
Please have a blood test,
for it's serious
What's going on?
Has the result been known?
Your son's got AIDS
He won't live for a long time
How could a boy have got this?
The only chance is contamination
with a relative's blood
So we wanted you to
take a blood test
Now the result shows
Mr Fang's reaction is negative
without any AIDS virus
Mrs Fang's blood is positive
She may have
contaminated your son
An AIDS patient looks normal
before the virus
becomes active
It may remain
dormant for 7 years
Mrs Fang
We'll recheck
you in a minute!
The Medical Health Dept
wants your data again
with those men who had
sex relation with you
Can... can I've a word with
my wife alone?
I knew that once I did it
I'd have a lot to lose
I did try to find
other decent work
but then the money
earned would be
far from meeting our needs
I lived in fear everyday
Formerly you could shore my fear
and comfort me
but this time
I've to keep it to myself
I've to face it by myself
I've been accompanied
by fear everyday
I even made myself up
like another person
because I'm ashamed to see you
Sending Ming to school
& cooking for you
was my only pleasure
for I could feel like mammy
& have hope
Now I've dashed it
with my own hands
Why? Why should I make
such a serious mistake?
My mistake!
Not your mistake, it's Tsui-tsui's!
Mum...
Mum... I'm sorry! Don't die!
Ming, is your forehead still hot?
Want to go to Disneyland?
Yes
Shall I take you there?
Okay
Yuan
Get me some shoes from the
drawer in the sitting room
Which box is it?
They all belong to Shan-shan
Look at you, all sweaty
Change now!
Change now! I'll get you a cold drink
Oh, you're burly!
Sit down and have a drink
Are you still hot?
Where are you going?
To take a bath
What do you mean?
You wanted to see
if I'm a whore!
Listen, I quitted
since I know you
What about now?
I know you were the guest
and come to see for myself
I wanted to see
if you were as cheap as they said
I wanted to see your true face
I can show you now
I'll show you
how I act as a whore too
Are you going to bed?
I'll quit if you don't
Ling-yu, is that you?
Yes
Come out!
I want to talk to you!
Wait a minute
Can you come out now?
Ling-yu, don't move out!
Mammy may never
care for me anymore
I'm not worthy of any care?
Are you asking for punishment?
Come on... kill me
I know you don't love me
That's no way to talk to me!
I love you so much...
If you do,
you won't have made me a whore
I don't want to be a whore all my life
Quit then!
Pay off all your debts
& you may go
Come on, have a few pills!
Take them!
No!
Hi, what are you doing?
Sleeping!
Sheeping?
You bitch, don't sleep!
Tramp, you're fighting back
I was nice to you,
but you're so damn cheap!
Is my sister with you?
Your sister's here to see you
Sister
What happened?
Uncle molested me
Where's mammy?
She's out for a party
Sleep with me tonight
I'll talk to him tomorrow
The blanket
I'll go in to sleep with my sister
Go in? We sleep in this room
unless you prefer to
share the same bed
Sister, did you get bullied?
No, but I don't feel too well
Sleep!
The doctor said you
maybe discharged
Sterilize everything
at home with detergent
All utensils should be separated
Don't share the same bed
with your husband
Avoid any more sex
behaviour with anybody
Understand?
Warden, someone in
Rm 216 needs your advice!
Where's my son?
Let me take this down first
I'll tell Shan-shan first
I'll call an ambulance
No, it's too late!
Lend me a hand now!
Come on...
We've searched
and found nothing
There's no answer at home
No answer?
Did you see his dad
enter the room?
Yes
What did he say?
Did he say anything?
He just said: Any headache?
Want to go to Disneyland?
Disneyland
Go now
We've won! It's fun!
Police
Faster! Faster, Shan-shan!
A white Benz DP278
Don't die!
A road block in front!
You've exceeded the limit!
Show me your licence!
Someone's dying!
Sure, I will if I let you go
Switch it off
Open the trunk
Damn it!
You nearly ran us down!
Stop! Stop!
Get out! Get out!
Come out!
Don't you know you nearly
knocked us down?
I... I was rushing someone
to hospital!
I could accuse you
of dangerous driving
& wounding with intent
Have you got wounded?
Are you dying?
The one in the car
is really dying
Isn't life more important
than prosecution?
Are you good policemen?
It's a policeman's duty
to help the citizen!
At least you shouldn't let
someone die without help
A policeman must
execute his duties
Show me your licence!
Miss, show me your ID card
for registration
I seem to have forgot
to bring it
We can't admit her
without registration
It's our rule
Oh, I've found it!
Get a doctor to treat her first!
Go now!
Hurry up!
Miss, please show
me her ID card
Shan-shan
You can't go in! Let me go in!
No!
Ling-yu, let's wait outside
We can't stay here
Don't worry, we'll just wait here!
Miss, don't go!
This is not yours!
We suspect you're
using a lost ID card
Did you have a good time?
Yes
Dad, it's nice here
Well, let me kiss you
Sister...
What are you doing? Stop it
Let me go
What? Sister
I want you to let her go, please
Let me go, no
Stop it
Go away I beg you to stop it
Bobbie, stop!
Stop staring!
Sooner or later she'll have to do it
Why not benefit her own relative?
A grown up girl needs
this sort of experience
Hey, get me back the panties!
Listen,
have your sis attend
some sessions
She can relieve some
of your duties
They're up above
Shao Feng, Hsiao Ming
He's died for sometime!
Let me go! Let me see!
You take her there
Keep cool
Your husband left
this letter for you!
Excuse me!
I even took Ming away!
You've suffered for too long
You need a rest
Love is the most valuable,
not life
and each of us has it
I can now die without regret
I know you are very sad
But I hope you can get it together
And get on with your life
Take my advice & don't
waste the rest of your life
Give me back my gun
Excuse me. A visitor for you
Sorry!
Forget it, it's fate
It was all my fault
Had I watched you closely,
you wouldn't have done that!
I shouldn't have got you involved
Don't cry!
I'm going, not you
Don't be so sad!
If you're still my sister, smile
Okay, Ling-yu
I promise
I'll live a new life
Good
And you, little big man?
Send me your address
upon your return
I'll visit you whenever I can
Why take the trouble?
I'll see you when I return
Keep an eye on him for me
Don't let other girls
get closed to him!
You alone are an exception!
Come on quick!
Keep up!
Get in, get in
Ling-yu
Get in! Go quick!
Come on. Get in...
I'll wait for you
I'll be back soon!
When?
1997!
Get in...
See you in 1997!
"I want to tell you"
"Our story is colourful"
"I remember your eyes"
"I remember the romantic song"
"This is a love that is torn apart"
"The ending is so disappointing"
"That I can't hide away from that"