Everyone is alone
and no one cares about anyone
And our pains
are a deserted island...
To Jacques Brel.
who will give a circus
show for me
nostalgic love in the dust
who will make me go "I'm scared"
the knife in the heart,
in the limelight
who will treat me like a tigress
the whip like
a caress to the music
who will make me
balance between
balloons full of pathos
sometimes I panic
who will tell me
words of love
that can hurt
who will hold me
ITINERARY OF A SPOILED CHILD
when you'll release
all the stars
who will want me
with my red nose and
my heart full of tears
who will love me
when there won't be much
of me left anymore
who will still make me dream
the clown or the rider
who emerges from the shadow
who will still bring me the
artist's performance
the trapeze artist's show
see him fall
who will still bring me
the child that plays
for the performing dogs
or the vampires
Don't you have a ticket?
Where's your mother?
Where? In the bar?
Wait, I'll check. This boy
says his mother's in the bar.
Could you have a look?
Ask for the mother of the boy.
Wait a moment.
What's your name?
Sam?
What have you got there?
Can I have a look?
Is that your mother's?
Sam's three years old. I can't
keep him. I'm desperate.
Look after him. I beg you.
three years later
Sam, 13 years old
Sam, 16 years old
it has a silver shine
the itinerary of a spoiled child
is littered with broken toys
The last time I saw him,
was just before he left.
He wanted to get to know
himself.
This solitary voyage was a challenge
he added to all the storms in his
life.
He always said: when I spend some
hours with you, I want to believe.
When I spend an evening with my
children, I want to believe in family.
When I'm with a woman,
I want to believe in love.
That's Sam Lion for you.
You know why he was called that,
don't you?
He was found near a circus and
when he was registered...
the circus master called him Sam Lion
because he was always near the lions.
This is the best day of my life.
-Because it's beautiful here.
Where does all this water go?
-To Lake Kariba.
It's beautiful. Rainbows
come straight out of the water.
The most beautiful spot
in the world.
Will we see all of that?
You and I?
Look a rainbow. Quick.
Make a wish.
When he falls from the trapeze,
he becomes a street sweeper...
so he can stay with the carnival.
He wins a prize for best sweeper
and gets the award from Yvette...
who becomes his wife.
They have a son, Jean-Philippe.
Then the big drama happens
in Singapore.
He has to raise Jean-Philippe
on his own.
It takes him ten years to
recover and meet Corine.
Ten years to turn his little
business into an international
company.
Ten years before he can smile again
upon seeing a child's face.
Magnificent.
You look more and more like your
mother.
-Then you must be starting to hate me.
Whose idea was it to go here?
-Mine.
I wanted to go to Venice,
but Corine had already been there.
Then I realised they have even more
water here.
Who decided to call me Victoria?
-Your mother.
She's sure you were conceived here.
In this area.
I'm glad it wasn't near the
Niagara Falls.
You were almost called Isabelle.
Because I loved Jacques Brels song.
It's about his daughter.
But because of this spectacle,
you became Victoria.
How did you get the business?
After my accident, I was responsible
for keeping the circus clean.
I looked for machines to do the work.
What shall we do tonight?
American dinner, tamtam, birthday
cake,
champagne. The good life.
Doesn't that give you ideas?
-Why not?
I watched them this morning.
It's great what they do.
Look, he's the best one.
Unbelievable what he does.
Imagine, autumn on the Champs-Elysées.
'Ballet with Brooms'.
When will the machines be introduced?
-In a month.
How did you get the idea?
My daughter and I saw them on our
travels and we improved on them.
They say a minister is interested
in buying them.
That makes sense.
It's of interest to the public.
Are you really going to buy
a circus that has gone bankrupt?
I love the circus,
but that's nonsense.
I only hired people who were about to
be
fired. This is my secretary, by the
way.
The only secretary to land safely
after
a death-defying leap. Most of the
time.
How did you become the biggest
in your trade, in 10 years?
Step in the shit often
and always clean it up.
So this machine will
replace street sweepers?
This machine can clean 10
kilometres per day.
A person can do 1 kilometre.
The operator can also use the
machine as a mode of transport.
But most of all, the operator doesn't
make contact with the garbage anymore.
The work will get a better reputation
and will also be performed by
students.
So, sweepers will be unemployed.
The machine can't reach everywhere and
traditional sweepers are still
required.
But they should learn to
use roller-skates.
Do you find this funny?
-Not at all.
I need to talk to you.
-I understand.
What do you mean?
-I'm just saying I understand.
I don't want to go to the hotel.
It's not a hotel,
it's where I live.
It's also about the rest.
What? I don't have anything.
This machine's my first moped.
What do you want?
What do I have to do to keep you?
Drive a pink Cadillac?
Wait a moment. Wait.
Here, this is for you.
What is it?
-Have a look.
I'd like to take you there.
Near Victoria Falls.
Are you going? Alright.
Can I keep this?
-It's a present.
Will you be roller-skating for long?
-I don't know.
Aren't you taking that thing?
-Leave it. I'll take it tomorrow.
When will you get married?
-Ask him.
Miss, bring me the file of
Albert Duvivier.
It's a machine to pick up shit with,
not girls.
And how often have I told you
to wear your helmet?
Can I speak to the boss?
-I'm your direct superior.
I want to speak to whoever makes the
rules, not to who enforces them.
Can you swim?
-Breast stroke.
Swim into the Atlantic
Ocean and you might see him.
Damn.
That's not clear. Repeat, please.
-Your position, Victoria?
I repeat 42 North, 26 West.
Still the same.
Speak clearly, dear.
I ask him to call you.
-In an hour. I have things to do.
End of call.
-Fine.
So that's 42 North...
That's not my position at all.
Hello, Saint-Lys.
Is there anybody at the pump?
-Céline. I'm here.
What do I have to do?
-Help them with the crossing.
How long will that take?
-Two weeks.
Will I be washing dishes
for two weeks?
Victoria Lion
Starting Point
I'll summarize.
Take it easy with the pills.
What's more important...
Are you listening?
Take your boat out mornings,
afternoons and evenings...
and get far away from us,
for at least a month.
You can't quit smoking like
that either.
Want to bet?
Is it that serious?
-It's in your head.
That's good.
I'll see you at dinner.
Are you still with Martine?
-I'll tell you later.
Jean-Philippe,
your father's not doing well.
I fear a nervous breakdown.
He shouldn't continue to live
close to his work.
It's not good to live in a caravan,
especially for him.
I'll give him a prescription, but talk
to him. We have to get through to him.
Is he doing that bad?
What is happiness then?
-You'd like to know, wouldn't you?
Well, happiness is... it's...
When there is no trouble.
And you have to keep it that way.
You must be very tired
to talk like that.
What tired you out the most in life?
Your mother.
Didn't you love her a bit?
-Yes.
Or you wouldn't have
been born.
And did you love Jean-Philippe's
mother?
Can't we talk about something else?
-You don't want to talk about anyone.
Are you angry with me?
I'm glad you still look human.
You should see the car.
Can you explain to me why
we don't get along, dad?
I've sent you to schools that were
too good.
While we both run Victoria,
I can't be myself.
Hold on a bit longer.
I won't stay for long.
That's not what I mean. You sleep at
Victoria, you eat it, you drink it.
You sail Victoria.
It's all you think about.
We never have time to talk.
To spend an evening together.
Do you really want to cross the ocean?
-I've been sailing for 30 years.
The bay of St. Tropez isn't
the same thing.
Anything urgent?
I'm not available for anyone.
You can't do this.
Can't I go out on the ocean?
-You're abandoning 12,000 employees.
No, I'm not.
I'm selling a company. Quite a
company.
You can't. You are the company.
Who can buy a company like that?
-What about these walls?
What will you do with the money?
-I haven't had a break for 50 years.
Two days of holiday and you'll go mad.
-I want to try.
The doctor said he won't start again.
-What should I do?
Look.
Ride a bicycle.
Look at him. He goes from
one to the next. Look.
I want to write a book. Think I can?
-A book? Why not?
And I want to go to the US.
-Is he American?
Unbelievable.
You always take me to the circus.
-Of course.
My two big passions in life.
When I was young,
I always wanted to marry you.
And now?
-I'd be too scared you'd leave me.
But I do want someone like you.
Shall I tell you something?
I'm not a good catch.
I don't believe that.
-It's true.
What's a good catch?
-Someone who doesn't think too much.
That only leaves the idiots.
-Don't believe that.
Better late than never.
You're even late on the day
of your divorce.
Especially then.
Don't they know what the party's for?
-I was waiting for you.
Is this a joke?
-Don't pull that face. It's a party.
You should celebrate the day of
escape,
not the day of imprisonment.
Isn't she beautiful,
my divorced wife?
You look good.
-So do you.
Will she be in time?
-I think so.
When did she decide to come back?
-The day before yesterday.
I knew she wouldn't like New-York.
She's too French.
What's wrong?
-Nothing. Everything's fine.
Look, there she is.
What has she got in her arms?
-She'll explain later.
You explain it to me.
-He's six months old and his name's
Sam.
His name's Sam, he's six months old
and I'm the grandfather. Is that
right?
Where's the father?
Not here. Of course.
Does the father know, at least?
It's better like this.
Do you want to know what
I really think?
I'm the happiest man in the world.
Look, he's got my eyes.
Not because she's my daughter,
but it's great.
I would love it if you could
publish it.
If there's a problem,
you know where to find me.
Don't tell my daughter, please.
What are you doing here?
-Your pills.
Those pills.
They're alright, it's the rest.
Everything goes wrong. Wait. I told
you to be here before the personnel.
What's this?
Do you call this advertising?
Everything you do,
I have to do again.
Did they pay?
Good, I'll call you back right away.
We'll see each other tonight.
Did you read your sister's book?
-What's it about then?
A 25 year old girl falls in love
with a 50 year old man.
He's a bit like you.
-And then?
He gives everything up to go with her.
That's why it's called 'Starting
Point'.
How are you?
-Excellent.
I can't hear you well.
-Excellent!
Are you coming back soon?
-Not really.
We're all coming to the harbour.
And my son?
-We haven't seen him much.
When will you be back?
-In a couple of days.
Why? Are there problems?
Not really, but we
have to make some decisions.
Well, take them.
Hello? I can't hear you anymore.
Hello? I can't hear anything anymore.
Finished.
Is this really it?
-Yes.
How can I reach you?
-I'll write when I get there.
It's far away, isn't it?
-Yes, it's Africa.
Where is it exactly?
-I don't know yet. I'll find out.
What can I say?
If it fails, I'll be here.
I know. You're always here.
Alright, dad. Take care. Goodbye.
It's in a hurry.
who will give a circus
show for me
nostalgic love in the dust
who will make me go "I'm scared"
the knife in the heart,
in the limelight
who will treat me like a tigress
the whip like a caress to music
who will make me
balance between
balloons full of pathos
sometimes I panic
who will tell me
words of love that can hurt
-Good morning.
who will hold me
when you'll release
all the stars
who will want me
with my red nose and
my heart full of tears
who will love me
when there won't be much
of me left anymore
who will still make me cry
the clown or the rider
who emerges from the shadow
who will still bring me the
artist's performance
the trapeze artist's show
see him fall
who will still bring me
the child that plays
for the performing dogs
or the vampires
who will do the final act for me
to seduce me to smile
who will tell me
words of love that can hurt
who will hold me
when you'll release
all the stars
who will want me
with my red nose and
my heart full of tears
who will love me
when there won't be much
of me left anymore
Remember what you told me last week?
-Last week I was tired.
As far as eating, drinking and
fucking are
concerned, animals do better than we.
You're talking like a spoiled child.
Animals die of heart attacks too.
What about priests and heart attacks?
What reunites us here
is his love of others.
Many of us know that he didn't need
much reason to come to our help.
I've often heard him complain about
the company and talk about selling...
but then he'd think of all of you
and nothing changed.
Victoria and Jean-Philippe,
you now have to survive this storm.
He once told me...
if you love sun, rain and wind,
you have to believe in God.
Let's pray for the days
that he did believe.
Do you really speak French?
-If you want to talk to us, yes.
A taxi driver told me this was the
place to go in Hamburg.
It's 300 marks
for an hour, 1000 marks for a night...
and free if you marry me.
I need false papers.
You'd have to go to granny.
She has the most contacts.
Careful, there's a lot of police here.
-I didn't do anything.
What's your speciality?
-Anything, if you pay.
Did granny explain?
I don't make papers, I find them.
-That's better.
With the Cologne Carnival approaching,
it won't take very long.
Is Cologne far?
-400 kilometres.
Is it nice?
-It's special.
Want to know why I do this work?
You don't want to talk?
When you ask someone how they are,
you take a big risk.
Don't you like me?
My daughter's your age.
I don't know anyone who loves the
carnival this much.
Me neither.
Will you really use those 20 tickets?
-I have nothing else to do.
Well done.
Have you got work?
-Not really.
Come.
Mr Van den Berghe, architect.
50,000 dollars for one hour.
What do I have to do?
Deliver three bags at
Düsseldorf Station.
Three bags?
It's only the two of them.
I'm sorry.
I always work alone.
Your passport, please.
I see you also fly to New-York.
Cancel Tokyo.
Tokyo?
-Cancel it.
Do you also fly to Papeete?
-Cancel New-York. Give me Papeete.
Papeete. If you tell me what you're
looking for, I might be able to help.
Good question.
First, I'll go for some sun.
It's the wet season there.
Where do they go when it rains?
Papeete after all then?
I only have smoking.
I'll start smoking again then.
Are you doing that bad?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're descending towards Papeete.
It's 39 degrees.
Tighten your seatbelts.
an island
an island off the shore of hope
where men would not be afraid
and soft and calm like your mirror
an island
clear as Easter morning
offering the ocean's languor
with a mermaid on each wave
come, come, my love
there, there won't be any of
those madmen
who tell us to be wise
or that twenty is
the beautiful age
here comes the time to live
here comes the time to love
an island, an island off
the shore of love
placed on the altar of the sea
satin lying down on velvet
an island, warm as tenderness
hoping like a desert
for a rain cloud's caress
come, come, my love
there, there won't be any
of those madmen
who hide the long beaches from us
come, my love
let's flee the storm
here comes the time to live
here comes the time to love
an island, which we still have
to build
but that could hold on
to the dreams we dream as two
an island, that's about to
depart
that has been sleeping
in our eyes
since the doors of childhood
come, come, my love
because it's there that it all begins
I believe in the last chance
and you are the one I want
here comes the time to live
here comes the time to love
an island
disillusioned flower salesman
the itinerary of a spoiled child
God believes in those who
looked for him
the itinerary of a spoiled child
Isn't that jacket warm?
-A bit.
Why do you wear it?
-To protect myself.
Do you believe that yourself?
It's because Yvette gave it to
you in Singapore.
Where did you put the jacket, sir?
On my bag,
when I bought my ticket to Papeete.
The car will come later.
This is a honeymoon.
When there won't be much
of me left anymore
Stop, Yvette.
You were very sweet at
the cemetery, yesterday.
I wanted to bring you flowers.
It was the first time I saw you cry.
Can I touch you?
How do you like Jean-Philippe?
-You're rather hard on him.
You didn't raise him.
Yvette.
Come back, damnit!
Where were you?
Sorry, ladies and gentlemen.
That happens with ghosts.
Careful, or I'll leave again.
A little kiss.
Smile.
Perfect.
you're successful in business
and lucky in love
you often change secretaries
your office is in a high tower
from which you look down upon the city
from where you control your universe
the largest part of your life you're
in
the air between New York and Singapore
you always travel first class
you have a second home
in every Hilton on earth
you can't handle misery
you're not happy
although you seem to be
you didn't lose your
sense of humour
when you got your sense
of business
you're successful and proud of it
you only regret one thing
you're not doing what you wanted to do
you wanted to be an artist
to do your act
when the plane lands on the runway
in Rotterdam or Rio
you wanted to be a singer
in order to say who you are
you wanted to be an author
in order to make up your life
you wanted to be an actor
in order to become someone
else every day
and to admire yourself
in colour, on the big screen
you wanted to be an artist
so you could say
why you exist
Van den Berghe, Belgium. Architect?
Are there many French here?
-The whole kitchen crew's French.
Where are you from?
-Belgium.
A Belgian beer.
With foam?
-Without.
Yes, that's better.
On holiday. Victoria Falls?
It's beautiful.
I'll put something under the
table-leg.
It's the humidity.
Where's my bungalow?
Which number?
Number 12.
I'll take you there.
You don't seem to need a guide?
-I've got a good map.
Nice to have a Frenchman here.
-A Belgian.
But you don't have a Belgian accent.
-I can produce one.
Tomorrow morning, the elephants
might have breakfast with you.
Do you like animals?
-They're interesting.
This is Snow White's house.
There are lots of mosquito's here.
Will you stay for long?
Are you a cop or a barman?
I may have come across confused.
You look like an uncle of mine,
but without a beard.
Here, thanks.
Dinner's at 7:30.
I'll go for a walk.
Alright. Breakfast is at 6:30.
They're going for it.
I have nothing to eat.
Are you going with us?
Don't you have a guide?
Excuse me.
Hello.
-Hello, sir.
Early bird?
I've got the day off.
Did you take good pictures?
-Yes, you with the lions.
Any more?
-No.
What's that?
From when is this?
-It's been in the hotel for months.
Did you show it to anyone?
-No, no one.
Behind you. Don't turn around.
It's your fault that I ended up here.
All this talk about Victoria.
I was one of the 12,000 employees.
You were looking for roller skaters
and since I was good at it...
And then I got fired.
You fired me.
What's your name?
Albert Duvivier.
They call me Al.
You're not afraid of lions.
Or of you.
Journalists always exaggerate
a bit.
It's a small world.
Nobody would believe me.
Who will you tell?
I'm just saying...
Good.
Don't you feel at ease?
Stop moving around
I'm getting seasick.
Why did you do it?
Because I felt like it.
Wasn't business going well?
You know enough by now.
I can keep a secret.
It's more than a secret.
If you'd explain,
at least I'd understand.
I left behind what I loved the most.
Do you understand that?
No.
What's your price?
No, I won't sell them, because...
Anyway, I don't have the photos
anymore.
Be honest.
You wanted to blackmail me.
No, I wanted to sell them.
-And what do you call that?
Blackmail.
I changed my mind.
Why did you do that with the lion?
Do you ever toss a coin?
Do you ever play Russian roulette?
-No, I don't.
What shall I do?
Kill you or bribe you?
I'd prefer the first solution.
No, the second.
I really don't know what to
do with you.
I don't know what to do
with me either.
What's your price?
I have no price.
Like with the tip.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll work with you, if you like.
Sell everything and come here
to study the lions.
You've never had 12,000 employees.
Is it true what the newspapers write?
There's something wrong.
People often go missing at sea
to reappear years later.
Do you know of an island
without telephone?
Just say you got a mast against
your head...
and have been suffering
from amnesia.
Are you an author or a barman?
-I said it to help you.
Have you got any family?
My father and sister.
-What do they do?
They have a hotel.
Well...
There's hotels and hotels.
I can understand you wanted to abandon
12,000 employees.
I can also understand you wanted to
abandon your wife or wives.
I can understand all that.
But I can't understand how you could
abandon your children.
You're driving too fast, sir.
Where are we going?
Where?
-To my children.
'It would be a pleasure to work with
you
if you come back to France.
I'm asking you because of your youth,
your talent and your success in
Canada.
And also because I can see many
similarities between you and me.
Our company needs a man like you.
I hope to welcome you soon.
Sam Lion. '
So you're the last person to see
my father?
At least, I'm the last person
to have dined with him.
How did you get to know him?
He contacted me because I had
a similar company as he.
In Canada. Montreal.
And why did you leave Canada?
I was homesick.
France will always be France.
Of course.
The letter, the handwriting...
It affects me.
And?
Once I brought up the circus,
all doors opened up.
And Jean-Philippe?
-He asked when you wrote the letter.
Just before you sailed off,
I said.
We had had dinner,
just like you told me.
We talked business and just before you
left, you gave me the letter.
Did you tell him the way
you're telling me now?
Yes, but I was...
-More at ease.
Yes, completely at ease.
Did you understand why the company's
doing so bad?
I tried to find out more.
He explained things to me,
but it was very technical.
I don't think I completely
understood him.
He talked about debts the company
had when you died.
Debts?
Go away. I'll explain.
We have to play it very safe.
Are you ready?
What do you mean, safe?
From now on, don't do or say
anything without talking to me first.
Within half a year,
you'll be a captain of industry.
You'll have to wear another suit.
Pinstripe suits are out.
Tomorrow, you'll get a room
in the city.
In a fancy hotel.
Four stars.
But you have to learn to say hello.
-Excuse me?
Saying hello properly is one
of the most important things in life.
It's half the job.
Say hello to me.
No, with conviction.
Say hello as if I'm ill.
Again.
Now, I feel you're more interested in
me than in yourself.
People prefer that you talk about
them,
rather than about yourself.
Say hello again.
That wasn't good. I noticed it.
You can feel it yourself now, right?
Can I smile?
-As long as it's with compassion.
Don't smile too hard.
You'll often be confronted with
things you don't know.
Pretend you know them.
The best way to suggest you know
everything...
is to never show surprise.
Understood?
You often show surprise.
That's your weakness.
We'll do a test.
I'll say a few things and
you can't look surprised.
Understood?
Concentrate.
Did you know your father used to get
it
on with the petrol station attendant?
I don't want to see surprise.
-Yes, but that...
You just can't show surprise.
Imagine your father
with the petrol station attendant.
There you go again.
-Another example.
It's a gripping example.
-It is.
Concentrate.
You look like Jesus.
You're doing it again.
Can't I do anything?
-No, nothing.
Look into the distance.
-Absent-minded?
Not too much. Nothing.
Yes?
-Go on then because I...
Now I see surprise because
I'm not saying anything.
I'd be surprised.
I did exactly as you said.
I like you.
I don't know if...
-That's surprising.
Is this still part of the test or...
-Of course.
But you said...
-Don't let it surprise you.
Alright. Are you religious?
I don't know.
To my son, you're deeply religious.
To my daughter, you're an atheist.
And to you?
-I only believe in mathematics.
We get what we deserve.
Do I deserve to be here with you?
I'm starting to think so.
There he is.
Say hello.
Coffee?
Did you sleep well?
You get used to it.
Look, nice and fresh.
Do you still want to give us a hand?
-Of course.
She'll show you around.
I'm going to the pump.
What did you do in Belgium?
-I was with the circus.
I love the circus.
-I was only a bookkeeper.
Will you stay for long?
-Until I get a work permit.
Has Alex left yet?
I hope he'll be successful for once.
You have to go and buy stuff.
We're out of things.
Did it use to look like that?
-Yes, we were almost in the woods.
I'm here for Mr Jean-Philippe Lion.
Mr Duvivier for you.
My sister, Victoria.
Mr Verne, our notary.
An old friend, who'll do the talking.
In which part of Canada were you?
The factories were up north.
The office was in Montreal.
Beautiful country. Our company's
about to be taken over.
You understand we can't
hire you.
I'm prepared to accept a trial
period.
At no expense.
That's very friendly.
But we have more problems,
that we can't talk about.
Can I say something?
When you saw dad,
was he alright?
Yes, he's fine. Was fine.
-My sister asks because...
when he left,
he was very tired and depressed.
We even thought of suicide.
-Not at all.
Your father's... was
in good shape...
both physically and mentally.
So don't worry.
You don't agree to a trial period?
We do...
-No, Victoria.
I consider that letter to be
dad's last instructions.
Of course.
I'll let you talk amongst yourselves.
I'll say hello. I mean goodbye.
I'm jetlagged.
See you soon.
I'll show you out.
How's your mother?
-Fine.
And little Sam?
-All fine.
Sorry, but it failed.
I did what I could,
but they didn't want it.
Your son and daughter
agreed, but...
the notary was completely against it.
He said they're firing people at the
moment and can't hire anyone.
Sit down.
The notary seemed to be in charge.
I did exactly what you said.
I never showed any surprise.
That notary's starting to
surprise me.
Really? I was also surprised...
but I didn't show it.
What are you doing there?
I haven't been able to
explain everything.
When I dined with Sam Lion in
New-York,
just before his departure...
he gave me the letter
of recommendation...
and also a suitcase with important
documents.
He made a last minute decision not to
take it with him.
Check his face to see
how he takes that information.
If he seems worried, you're
on the right track. Keep going.
One of those documents is a copy of
his last will.
Some manipulation seems to have
occurred between...
what the document says
and the beneficiaries.
When he starts thinking and becomes
curious...
he'll no doubt continue the
conversation himself.
I'm listening.
This is my proposition...
You do everything I say...
or I'll show the documents to
the parties involved.
He won't speak for a long time.
Then he'll say those documents are
false and you're blackmailing him...
that you're a fraud.
-You want to blackmail me.
Those papers must be false.
-Perfect...
Then you stay silent even longer.
Keep looking him in the eye...
without blinking and without
showing any surprise.
That way you'll scare him. It's all
in the eyes, And then you'll say:
Then the children will have to choose
between a blackmailer and a crook.
You'll see him regain some hope.
And he'll try something else.
A blackmailer and a crook...
may go well together.
If he wants to collaborate, that's it.
Don't say anything but look...
the way Elliott Ness looked when
Al Capone wanted to bribe him...
and wait until he bows his head.
Maybe he'll raise his head for a
moment
like a floored boxer.
Look him in the eye.
And then knock him out.
He seems like a fine man.
A great man.
Your father really wanted him.
A rara avis.
If he sings as well as
he looks...
it would be stupid not to use him.
What do you think?
When I saw the letter,
I agreed right away.
And since I wanted to slow down a bit,
this is the moment.
Never hint at the notary's
embezzling.
This is an impressive office.
Can I look around?
Treat Jean-Philippe very
carefully.
Dad must have told you about
his love of the circus.
He wanted to turn his office into
a circus museum. Not very functional.
Never go against Jean-Philippe.
He has a passion for architecture.
He told me a lot about his
passion for lions.
Yes, lions were his big passion.
What I hate about this type
of architecture...
is that there is no separation between
the workers and the board.
That's the circus, the team spirit.
My father always said: a boss has to
be
able to see what the personnel are
doing.
and the personnel always have to know
where the boss is.
He's got a point.
-But it's impractical.
Yes, you're right.
Then you'll be assigned an office.
When you're alone, call me.
If he asks where you live...
Where do you live?
-Since I came back from Canada...
I've been staying with my dad, outside
of Paris. It's quiet.
Telephone.
-I'll take it there.
Here, you do it.
Ask for the balance sheets
of the past three years...
with all the corresponding documents.
Or else you won't make any decision.
Bring them tonight.
It went fine with your son.
Better than with your daughter.
A list of urgent things.
Give it to my secretary.
When I call and you can't speak,
cough.
Always ask for time to think.
Bring your portable phone.
You have to explain this.
-We've got all night.
Did you ask my secretary to find
you a room? -Yes.
Did you discuss your salary?
-Yes, I told them what you told me.
I keep saying to Jean-Philippe
that we'll discuss it later.
About my son...
It's normal that he's
nice to you.
He's always nice to young people.
By the way, tell your father not
to eavesdrop.
Or ask him to help us.
Can we get some too?
Telephone.
Are you available for dinner tonight?
Such a smart computer
can't be wrong.
Ask for a printed copy.
We have to be on top of this.
Take your time. I'm busy.
That gives me an excuse not to go
tonight.
I'm coming over.
Am I interrupting?
-Not at all. Come in.
My mother wants to meet you.
She's inviting you to dinner.
I'd love to, thanks.
Is tonight alright?
Tonight's difficult, because
there's a problem in South America.
I have to see him...
I have to read all the files.
I'll see if I can cancel my dinner.
Have a seat.
I'll be right back.
Anything wrong?
-No, I'm going with Jean-Philippe.
Dad's hat?
-I'm always wearing it.
How's mum?
-She's nostalgic.
That's her.
-I know.
I couldn't cancel the dinner.
So I can't tonight.
But some time next week's fine.
-We'll do that then.
I also wanted to thank you
for everything you're doing for us.
It's nothing special.
Dad would be very jealous
if he saw you.
I understand he liked you.
-You're impressive too.
You still dress the same way.
How do you know?
-I know all about you.
He tells me things every day. Told me.
He told me about you each night.
You're a bit like him.
-Do you think?
Not physically...
but your attitude,
your boldness.
The way you greet people, how calm
you are, things like that.
Have a seat. I'll try one more time
to cancel my dinner.
I'll be right back.
Do I have to continue to pretend?
-When I say no, it's no.
They keep talking about you.
You're still important in their lives.
That's why I left.
Do you still not understand?
I noticed that your daughter...
is a bit like you.
You should really consider
going back to them.
If I wanted that,
I wouldn't go through all this
trouble.
They're not biting today.
-We're not forced to fish either.
Alright, I'll go.
You spend lots of money on
unnecessary things.
And you don't keep check of
your expenses, That's not good.
And the way you chase the personnel.
I'm embarrassed.
Is that all?
-No.
Al's fed up with the hotel and
wants to live in dad's caravan.
Can I come in?
-Make yourself at home.
This is your house now. Not very
nice, this close to work.
Didn't your dad like it?
-Yes, but he loved the circus.
Don't you?
-No, I hate it.
I'm surprised. Your sister
loves it, I believe.
Yes, she does.
Is it on tonight?
Tonight? Oh, tonight.
I wanted to say I'm happy about
how we work together.
We're a very good team.
It seems best to me to
keep it strictly business.
I'm here, Jean-Philippe.
Oh, is it you?
-I wanted to know if you're alright.
This is a very luxurious
caravan. I'm very grateful.
I'll be off then.
What do you think of him?
-Strapping.
I like blacks who are
really black.
He is.
We're in a very difficult
situation.
Goal. Yes, goal.
You're kidding me.
There are some bad things
happening here.
You're having fun, but I'm not
having fun with your computers.
This is a misunderstanding.
It's not my birthday today.
This is because you've been
with us for a year.
That's nice of you.
Shall I blow the candle?
There's something else.
-Where are we going?
With a birthday comes a present.
Dad loves old-timers.
We want to give you one.
-You can't.
Choose one.
No, you can't.
-Yes.
You love those cars.
I can't accept it.
I couldn't choose anyway.
They're all beautiful.
I wouldn't know. I'll just
pick the closest one.
I'm speechless.
-Dad once put it very well:
Never give someone a present that
you don't love yourself.
I'm driving a car that used to belong
to Sugar Ray Robinson. Unbelievable.
I'd like to have lunch together.
I'd rather have dinner with you.
-That's alright too.
I'll introduce you to someone
who might become important to me.
Since you've taken over dad's role,
I want to hear your opinion.
Are you planning on getting married?
-Yes, if he agrees.
If he agrees?
Why not?
I don't know who it is.
She'll introduce me to him.
It's simple: if he's ok, you approve.
And if not, I reject him?
-Of course.
Talking about marriage.
Céline's getting married today.
A beautiful car, isn't it?
Beautiful family.
-Yes, they're nice.
Is something wrong?
Family makes you think of family.
-That's true.
But why do you say that?
I'd like to see them again.
Just once.
Once.
How did you end up here?
I was here for work and I was
almost out of petrol.
I saw this petrol station attendant
who
looks just like your dad.
Everyone has a double.
-Exactly.
He's not a real copy of your
father, of course.
That's a nice ride.
Perfect.
Where's the hole?
It's well hidden.
They don't make them like this
anymore.
-It's from'57-'58.
It used to belong to Sugar Ray
Robinson, the boxer.
You had La Motta and Dauthuille.
I remember Dauthuille well.
Graziano was the world champion.
He never gave up. Always attacked.
Bang, and down.
I've seen Robinson box against Big
Man.
Ray was good...
and he had a good left hook...
but he didn't cut it.
Not enough stamina.
Striking, isn't it?
-Yes, unbelievable.
He doesn't really look like him,
but it's how he acts.
And Max Schmeling...
he was very fast. The way
he'd come back with a left hook.
He was younger. But he'd look a bit
like this now.
Did anyone ever tell you, you look
a lot like Sam Lion?
How's that?
-Sam Lion.
What weight category?
-No, a business man.
A business man? Me? No, kid.
That's full again.
That's 400 francs.
Yes, it's a guzzler.
500, I have to change that.
-No, never mind.
Well, thanks. You're as generous
as Robinson.
Could you do the windscreen?
-Of course, that's part of the job.
For that money, I'd polish
your shoes.
That lady has beautiful eyes.
One moment. If you're in
a hurry, do it yourself.
It's true...
strong as a bear.
I don't mean it in a bad way...
but I get the impression your fiancé's
not very polite.
He's always very punctual.
There are always exceptions
to the rule.
He's also very special.
Wait, this is wrong.
You're influencing the jury.
I'll admit it.
I tricked you.
He's been here for a while.
He was exactly on time.
Is he in the restaurant?
At this table even.
What's that?
-He's at this table.
Do you mean that...
-Yes.
Am I dreaming or do you really
want to marry me?
Only if you agree.
Careful, I might say yes.
Say yes then.
I can't.
I'd want to but...
I have to make a phone call...
right away.
I have to tell my dad.
I'm very happy. I don't show it,
because I'm surprised.
But I'm very happy.
Mr Duvivier.
-That's me.
Will you accept my daughter
as your daughter-in-law?
Why do you say that?
You're son's having dinner with my
daughter and she's proposing to him.
Your daughter?
-Yes.
And your son's about to call me and
ask my permission.
And you want my permission?
Is your daughter a serious girl?
Your daughter was going to introduce
me to her fiancé tonight.
The problem is that I'm the fiancé.
You're both adults,
so do what you want.
Aren't you surprised?
-Of course, I'm surprised.
Very surprised even.
And I only have one daughter.
Alright. Talk to you later.
Do you know where she went?
-Maybe to the ladies.
I'll close.
What are you doing here?
-And you?
That's my hat.
Are you alone?
Where's Victoria?
-I thought she'd be here.
Isn't she here?
-No. Weren't you having dinner
together?
Yes, we had started.
Didn't she ask you to marry her?
-Yes, You knew about it?
Everyone did.
-I only heard about it tonight.
It's crazy.
I've always been a bit crazy.
And you live here?
-Yes, it's a bit like a circus.
And you let me marry a clown?
Don't you like him?
-Yes.
I liked him for what you made him do.
-What he did was the hardest thing.
And you didn't make a mistake.
Did you have fun the past two years?
That's hard with so many memories.
-Why then?
I wanted to take a shortcut,
but I got lost.
What do we do now?
-Find him quickly. And call me.
Where is she?
-She left again.
Can I talk to you?
-Go ahead.
No, not here.
Not here anymore.
Was this it?
-Yes.
Are you sure?
Now she knows.
-Listen.
I'm not listening.
I'll get worked up when I want.
It's over. Finished.
Now I want to say something.
You listen to me for a change.
Do you know what you are?
A spoiled child that breaks its toys.
Your wives...
your children, your company.
And now you're destroying me,
but you won't succeed.
You taught me to be strong.
What are you thinking?
That you're the only one who dares
stand in front of a lion?
Come on.
Do you think you're the only one who
dares stand in front of a lion?
He's learning fast.
-He's getting there.
He's doing well.
Dad, it's me.
He's not in the caravan, not in
the office. He's nowhere.
He'll be back. In a bad mood,
but he'll be back.
Call me when he arrives.
Talk to you later.
Some days, I don't understand...
Shall we have a drink?
He's still not here.
I was in the caravan all this time.
He'll be there.
-It's almost five.
Did you call him in his car?
Do that and call me back.
Don't talk to anyone.
-I promise.
Bye. I love you, dad.
Where's that asshole?
Al, what are you doing?
Where are you?
I'm in Thoiry.
The African part.
I want to ask you
a very important question.
He called. He arrived.
Do you think we can make him
come back one day?
He gave me this, just before he left.
He always carried this with him.
LOOK AFTER HIM. I BEG YOU.
-He's at his final destination now.
Did your father say that?
-Yes.
Sam we're going home.
Get up, mummy.
We won't get separated anymore.
Do I have to run you over?
See you tomorrow.
when Isabel sleeps
nothing moves
when Isabelle sleeps
in her cradle of joy
do you know that she pilfers,
the little scoundrel
the oases of the Sahara
the golden fish of China
and the gardens of the Alhambra?
when Isabelle sleeps
nothing moves
in her cradle of joy
she robs the dreams
and the games
of a rose and a butter cup
to put them in her eyes
beautiful Isabelle,
when she sleeps
when Isabelle laughs
nothing moves
in her cradle of joy
do you know that she robs,
the little mean one
the laughter of the wild cascades
which serve as a purse to kings
without a retinue?
when Isabelle laughs
nothing moves
in her cradle of joy
she robs the windows
of their gold opening onto paradise
to put it into her heart
beautiful Isabelle, when she laughs
when Isabelle sings
nothing moves
in her cradle of joy
do you know that she robs the lace
spun in the heart of nightingales
and the kisses which umbrellas
keep from taking flight?
when Isabelle laughs
nothing moves
in her cradle of joy
She robs the velvet and the silk
which the guitar yields to the Infanta
to put them into her voice
beautiful Isabelle, when she sings