Soyuzmultfilm - Moscow -  1952
Subs by Eus,
reconstructed after the American rewrite
The Scarlet Flower
After a tale by S. Aksakov
written by George Grebner
Director: Lev atamanov
art directors Leonid Shvartsman,
Alexander Vinokurov
music Nikolai Budashkin
cameraman Michael Druyan
sound George Martynuk cutter Lidia Kyaksht
words (poems) Ya. Shvedov
Assistent-director Roman Kachanov
artists
Irina Svetlitsa, Nikolai Fedorov, K. Malyshev,
G. Nevzorova, V. Rodgero, I. Troyanova
animators Gennady Filippov, Tatiana Fedorova,
Roman Kachanov, Roman Davydov, V. Dolgikh, Boris Chani,
Fedor Khitruk,B. Meyerovich, V. Kotenochkin, Boris Dezhkin
Good morning Sirs.
What goods have you?
The finest in the world!
Sables and fine mink...
Over there!
On yonder ship!
They're loading now!
A fine ship she is!
Is her captain as fine?
Fine?
That ships captain isthe finest
Captain Stephen Dimjimjalitch
Step lightly men.
Step lightly now!
Fine adventure tomorrow!
Storing away is
only one days hard work.
"figs" "raisins" "Sweet buns"
"Figs" "raisins" "Sweet buns"
Noon hour!
Time to eat, men!
Go away!
Father is here!
Tomorrow I leave on a long journey
When I will return I cannot say...
While I am away,
I want only one thing
from my daughters...
Listen to me , girls...
You must find a way to live
together... in peace...
...and harmony too, with
no bickering and no fighting.
Only love! If you do this one
thing for me...
I will bring you back anything you wish!
Whatever your heart desires!
So, tell me, what will you have
me bring you, dearest oldest.
Oh, Let me think. I want...a crown.
Like no one else has ever had.
Covered in jewels
Rubies and diamonds...Solid gold.
So people will say of me:
"Is she not beautiful".
You shall have your beautifull crown!
And what shall I bring back
for you, my pretty Liodushka?
I don't know. Not much...
Only a triffle i've heard about...
It's a magic mirror.
When you look into it, you are
forever young!
With it I will never look old,
and I will always be...
young and pretty...Ha ha
You will always look pretty to me.
Mirror, or not!
And...what of you...Nastinka?
What shall I bring for you? Tell me.
Once in a dream I saw it. A flower
Crimson red and peculiar, with
a sadness about it.
Ha, ha, ha. A sad flower
- Ridiculious.
Goodbye Nastinka. I will find you
your crimson flower. I promess.
I'll take it! My daughter will
be pleased!
What an unusual country this is!
Perhaps it's the place to find
Nastinka's flower.
Look there! Look at that!
Look over there. Stephen! look!
A crown of gold,covered with jewels
It's what she wanted!
All our goods are sold! We've
done well!
And our gifts are gathered!
It's time for us to go home!
Not quit.
I have no gift for Anastasia!
The crimson flower! It is what
I promised
Look stephen! look out there!
Fish that fly without wings!
Strange creatures that glow...
Perhaps we've reached the end
of the world!
It's time to turn back!
I cannot turn back...
I must find the crimson flower!
The sky is too clear!
A strong wind is with us!
Secure the mast!!!
Comrades, Pull,Pull!!!
Pull!
Stephen!!!
Stephen!! Dear Stephen, Were are you!!
Where am I? Where have I landed?
Where is my ship? My Crew?
This land is like none I've ever
seen! Let's go inland!
If there's a palace here, I'm
not alone here!
Ohh. A boat appears...Would it
be real?!
Is anyone here? ..yone here...ere?
Hello!!
Hello!
Is anyone here? Answer!
If you are there!
Perhaps I am alone after all!
Alone ....and hungry...
Well,...thank you!
Delicious soup!
And This? Ha,ha!
A toast to the master of the house!
Music! You think of everything!
Thank you!
I thank you for the meal.
What is this!?
The flower for my little one!
Ah! What have you done?!
How dare you take my greatest treasure
How dare you take my flower!
I welcomed you!
Gave you every comfort in the
whole of the world.
Yet, you repay me by taking my
greatest joy!
I didn't know.
Why did you take my precious flower?
For my youngest daughter.
Nastinka, if you please.
Your dearest? Nastinka?
What a kind and loving daughter
she must be...
For her...I will let you leave...
with the crimson flower.
but you must give your solemn promiss...
That one of your daughters will
return in your place!
Im my place? No, I cannot do that!
I will not harm her! She will
be well cared for!
Never!
You do not know a father's heart!
So be it!
Someone must pay for your transgression!
Or you must die!
I will give you a magic ring...
who ever places it on their finger
will instantly return to me.
You, or one of your daughters!!
Look there men! On that island!
There he is!
At last we have found our good captain!
look at me!!
Oh, come here! oh.
Get away now...
Let me have a chance to admire my
wonderful gift!
Wonderfull gift?
The flower of my dream!
The sweet crimson flower.
You must swear to me
with a solemn vow...
At sunrise i must put om the ring..
and return... to the terrible beast.
What?
- No stephen, don't go! You musn't!
I gave my word, my promis.
The ship is yours!
and I entrust you the care of my
beloved daughters.
Stephen! Dear Stephen!!
I made a promis.
I must pay the price
- Stephen!
Please, do as I ask!
Thake care of my home!
Be father to my children!
Especially...Nastinka!
What did you cause?You ugly
dream-flower!
It is not your fault, but mine!
And it's not you who should answer for it...but me!
My foolish request made you take the crimson flower!
Not you should pay the price!
Mastinka!
I beg you...
Forgive your foolish daughter!
Nastinka!!
I...brought you flower back.
Thank you, Nastinka.
Forgive me. I am sorry my father
took it!
Forgive you?
It was only for me that my father
took it.
My dreamflower!
I know. I  knew you'd come.
What? You knew I would? Do what you want
with me.
No. I don't want you to feel hurt.
I want only for you
to stay here and feel well with me.
For me?
Can't be for me!
Can't be.
Thank you for your kindness.
But I prefer my own cloths.
They're simple... as I am
Very well
Nastinka
As you wish.
Come and view what's yours now
It is...
It is to be shared.
It's all yours.
Yours....and mine
Thank you for everything, invisible one.
It's all wonderful!...
but not for me...
what shall I do with the ring?
The ring? -It's yours!
It is not for me to keep you here!
You can go with it everywhere you want.
But remember....
your father promissed...
My heart would die without you.
So Nastinka didn't leave the island,
and settled in...
Sing for me my friend.
I have everything that I could wish for
Satin dresses, golden treasures
Who could wish for more.
And I have one who says he'll
love forever
And we'll always be together,
still my heart's unsure
for I have memories that haunt me
But laughter so sweet and true
but all my health means nothing...
so far away from you
I have frightened you Nashtinka!
Now you will leave me forever!
I did not mean to hurt you
You are my dearest friend.
Appear to me again.
and I swear by my heart...
I will not be frightened.
No, Nashtinka.
You are repulsed by the sight of me!
You have the power of the ring...
Use it ...and flee away from me!
And alone I will die of grief.
I'll promis, I will not leave
not if it would hurt you.
I'm contempt here.
and...I care for you...
Thank you, Nashtinka.
If only I could believe.
the platen apple...I did this as a child.
Roll, roll apple, spin round and round...
Roll along the silver plate
Show us snowy places far away.
Snow! So fluffy and light!
Show her something else.
Roll! Roll! Roll apple! Take
Nastya to the underwater kingdom!
Show her the priceless pearls
of the deep! Oh! Oh!
Oh look, the shelves open!
Showing their dearest treasures!
And here Nastya,
you will recognize
... your home shores.
No...
Don't please!
My dear father, my sisters!
I can't bear it...
Don't fret, Nastya!
You're not a prisoner here.
go to them.
Visit them!
Father!
My dearest father!
- Nastinka!
Daughters, come!
Nastya has returned!
Nastinka!
daughter of mine!
Sisters!
Dear sisters
Nastinka! Dearest!
Oh, my, you little pearl, just look at you!
just look at you!
Have you brought gifts for us? have you?
Gifts? Yes gifts!
And for me?
I was longing so much for home.
And he let me come,...
...right away!
Nastinka, My precious!
It's just I feel bad for him.
He is so very kind.
I promissed I would return...at sunset!
Oh, your word, sister!
You've tricked him once-
-you can just stay now!
Tricked him? No,
I haven't done anything of the sort!
If I am not back at precisely 8 PM,
I am sure he will die of grief!
I must return to him.
Hahaha, let him go!
Don't be silly!
Quiet you two chatterboxes!
Oh, what amazing gifts she's brought!
Gifts! I know, I know!
Yes, but think of
what she must have of her own!
Unheard of riches!
It's not fair.
--I am the eldest!.
...And I am the middle daughter!
You know what? (whispers)
She promised!
She promised to return
by sundown...
I'm sorry, sisters! I feel I really must go.
I have this sense that I am being called.
what's the rush?
You've been gone so long!
Why rush to leave?
Look at the clock!
Calm down, my dear.
Go look at the sun and see that it's not set yet
sisters, why have you done this?!
Sun, please stop!
Wait!
Where are you my gentle friend!
Listen to me, I've come back to you!
Please wake up, my dear friend!
I love you my lonely beast!!
Nastinka!
Who are you?!? Oi.
Nastinka.
You looked into my heart, and
loved me when I appeared to be
a beast.
Now see me and love me
for the human I really am.
An evil witch turned me
into a horrible monster.
She cast a spell so...
that I'd live that way...
Until a beautiful maiden
loved me for who I was
for my pure soul and tender heart.
The witch is no more!
And now, I shall love you, Nastya,
We've broken the evil spell,
now and forever! We can go home!
Subs by Eus
www.dailymotion.com/eus347
The end