Two years before
slavery was abolished...
and three years prior to the
Proclamation ofthe Republic...
the cafés and bookshops were
the main meeting places...
of the town's intelligentsia
and bohemians such as:
Olavo Bilac,
the prince of poets.
Marquês de Salles...
bohemian and enfant
gâté of the court.
Chiquinha Gonzaga...
maestro, skilled pianist
and composer.
José do Patrocínio...
novelist and
intrepid journalist.
Salomão Calif...
the tailor who dressed
the elegant half of town.
Miguel Solera de Lara...
owner of the main bookshop,
Aphrodite's Retreat.
They fought for
the end of slavery...
and discussed
republican ideas.
Nanine, I'm going out,
get me my things.
Every day,
we spoke of you...
no one else dared
mention your name.
It was she consoled me...
told me we would see
each other again.
She was not lying.
Did you visit
beautiful lands?
Will you take me there?
It was nothing.
You see, happiness can't
just invade a heart...
which has been desolate
for so long...
not without
being oppressive.
Nanine, give me a scarf, a hat.
Armand returned,
I want to live.
I must live.
I... can't...
You will speak of me,
sometimes, won't you Armand?
Give me your hand.
It's strange.
What is?
I no longer suffer.
I sense a well-being
I never felt before.
But I want to live.
I feel well.
She is dead.
Bravo! Bravo!
Long live the Emperor!
Long live the queen of talent!
What wit!
What riposte!
I do hope Your Excellency
enjoyed the play.
I merely regret
that our stages...
are not yet up
to European standards.
A stage is just a stage.
The world is a stage.
What matters is
what is put on them.
In that case, today we had
the world's greatest,
illuminated stage.
I noticed you arrived late.
A friend and one
of your greatest admirers...
the baroness of Avaré.
-Who? -Her name is...
Dalia Maria Luíza
Catarina de Albuquerque.
Our baroness owned
an extremely rare violin...
a Stradivarius.
Well, it has been stolen...
and Maria Luiza is
simply outraged.
I see. And the police,
what do they say?
Well, the violin was
a gift of mine...
and although our friendship
is purely platonic...
the Empress would hate to see
the matter in the newspapers.
I see your problem,
Your Excellency.
Perhaps I can help.
Sit down.
You and your marquise,
I mean baroness.
It so happens that I am good
friends with Sherlock Holmes...
the world's greatest detective.
Naturally, Your Excellency
has heard of him.
I must confess
my ignorance, Madame.
Holmes is
the first detective...
to use a rational
deductive method.
Once, Holmes found the missing
jewels of a Russian singer...
just by examining the clothes
she had worn at a banquet...
offered for the emperor.
For me?
No, Majesty.
Napoleon Ill.
Well?
By the advanced state
of rigor mortis...
death must have occurred in
the early hours of yesterday.
The victim appears to be between
fifteen and twenty years of age.
Saraiva, anyone
can see that.
Inspector Mello Pimenta, there is
a strict procedure to be followed.
Liver damage,
probably owing...
to excessive ingestion
of alcoholic beverages.
If she had not died
from the murderous attack...
she would certainly have been
a candidate for early cirrhosis.
She was a prostitute.
The cause of death is
the dilacerations...
of the larynx
and the pharynx...
in a horizontal cut
initiated from left to right.
The aggressor possessed
great physical strength.
The ears were also extirpated
with great skill...
Saraiva, is there no detail
which may have gone unnoticed...
in the first examination?
Might it have been revenge?
The final touch.
Literally.
What's this?
It appears to be the
string from a mandolin.
Well, at least it's a clue.
A mandolin string.
Or a ukulele,
some musical instrument.
Could the killer
be a musician?
He might be
and he might not.
From the violence
of the crime...
and the place where
I found the string...
what I do know is
that he is quite mad.
In this bookshop we sell
books, Mr. Bilac...
this is not a library.
Oh, so? Would you prefer
me to dog-ear the page...
spoiling the volume?
What the devil kind
of bookseller are you?
Miguel, has Émile Zola's latest
book arrived, ''Germinal''?
And very interesting
it is, too.
It is about the rebellion
of the miners.
Not a rebellion,
Miguel, a strike.
Isn't that the same thing?
It is to some. Which is why
the imperial police...
continue to fabricate cases
against us, abolitionists.
That is one of the reasons
I am going to live in London...
and open a bookshop
in the East End.
This town cannot live without
its Aphrodite's Retreat.
Only my mother's illness
ties me to Brazilian soil.
I don't know how you come by
that Anglophilia of yours.
Don't you know that everything
you're thinking of is in Paris?
It is pointless
to speak of Shakespeare...
to the ears of Molière.
Don't upset yourself, Miguel.
If you really must go, then go.
You've plenty of money.
Did you by any chance
read Múcio Prado today?
''Two days ago, I had
the pleasure to dine...
with the extraordinary
Sarah Bernhardt...
a woman of radiant
beauty and talent.
The divine actress
secretly revealed...
to this humble scribe,
that our beloved monarch...
has been troubled lately...''
Following a suggestion by
Sarah Bernhardt herself,
our esteemed emperor will
invite an English detective...
to come and unravel
the mystery of the theft...
of the famous
Stradivarius violin...
belonging to Dalia Maria Luiza
Catarina de Albuquerque.
Who can have offered
such a magnificent gift...
to the lovely
baroness of Avaré?''
So, Your Majesty has
the nerve to give this woman...
a violin treasured
throughout the world?
A jewel in the shape
of a fiddle!
That's absurd!
Where can the fellow
have got that from?
The same source
you confided in...
from the lips of an actress!
As if that were not enough,
you have the audacity...
to invite an English detective
to conduct the investigations.
What's got into you?!
Are you trying to demoralize
our police force?
I know, I know.
You won't listen to reason.
There is nothing
I can do...
but take my leave
and withdraw.
Another piece
of cornmeal cake?
No, just the beverage,
thank you.
Odd reading
for a baroness.
My dear Miguel, one should
know what happens...
when the aristocracy
forgets its people.
And as you know,
I am noble by marriage.
My father was a butcher,
as many people are
kind enough to remind me.
I prefer to say he was the wealthy
proprietor of a meat store.
Ah, finally my Balzac
has arrived.
''Splendeurs et misères
des courtisanes''.
Such a suggestive title,
don't you think, Miguel?
The emperor.
I must leave now,
I'm expected at the bookshop.
Quite so, quite so.
Enough now, this is
no time for jokes.
Have you seen
the newspapers?
I found your caricature
most amusing.
The beard was perhaps
a bit too long.
That's not what...
Oh, I've already fretted
enough because of that theft.
After all, let them
take the rings...
as long as they leave
the fingers.
Anyway, it will be
fun to receive...
an English detective
at the court.
A pity you look upon
it all so lightly.
The empress is like
a woman possessed.
Not to mention that
now everyone knows...
the violin was
a gift from me.
How do they know?
Who other than I
would have the courage...
to do something so crazy?
My friend, I think
you are barking up...
the wrong tree,
as they say.
I could perfectly well
have bought a Stradivarius.
My husband left me quite a bit
of money, as you know.
The baroness, young
Talented and pretty
A rich widow,
The most coveted
ln the city
What would they say ifthey
knew we were in the same room?
They would probably
refuse to believe it...
avert their eyes like
they do when they stumble...
on the blacks and
filthy beggars in town.
Ifthe landscape is awful,
then close the window...
isn't that it?
Won't you dine with us,
Haroldo?
I cannot. I already
have an engagement.
What is your name?
Glória.
Glória, what a lovely name!
To Glória, a beautiful
young Brazilian...
who saw me in
Le Passant, in Rio.
There you are,
my dear, good luck.
Saraiva!
Look... no ears,
and another musical string.
Another prostitute?
No, she's from a decent family,
chamber maid at the lmperial Palace.
Her name is
Glória Meireles.
The niece of
that painter, Vitor...
-Vitor Meireles.
-That's him.
My god, a friend
of the emperor's.
That's all I needed.
What is she holding?
Saraiva.
Allow me.
Sarah Bernhardt.
At your service.
Police commissioner,
your servant.
Please be seated.
Careful not to cut yours!
-My what?
-Your ears.
You knew perfectly well
I dislike those jests of yours.
Come on, drink your coffee
while it's hot.
This case
is becoming tiresome.
I don't even know
where to begin.
Why don't you ask for help
from the English detective...
the emperor hired
to unravel the case...
of baroness of Avaré's
valuable violin?
Violin?
Might it be a violin string?
This black dress!
No, get one of my evening
gowns, a white one.
The skirt is covered
with little roses.
That is the one I want.
No! Anyway, that is
the one I want.
And you shall see
how pretty I am!
Once again, you shall
be with Frou-Frou.
Poor Frou-Frou.
A great big rat!
That's all you ever see
in this theater!
It's a disgrace!
And these lights!
My morning scenes look like
they were taking place at midnight!
One can't work under
such conditions!
And the awful climate!
I'll probably catch
yellow fever.
Why on earth did
I come to this country?
It's more like a jungle!
And you, what are
you doing here? Who are you?
Chief lnspector Mello Pimenta,
at your service.
Please be seated, Madame.
Oh, what a surprise!
You speak French?
I don't speak French.
He doesn't speak
French, Madame.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
we were rehearsing.
She apologizes for the delay.
Madame, do you
recognize this?
Yes. A lovely girl who
was outside the theater.
She gave her an autograph
outside the theater...
but doesn't know the girl.
She was murdered!
Murdered!
Could Madame tell me
whether she was with anyone?
He wishes to know whether
you recall anyone with her?
I don't remember.
That is, she seemed
to be alone.
There may have been
someone with her...
but I don't recall,
I'm sorry.
She cannot remember.
Madame is rather late,
will there be anything else?
I hope you catch the beast
who killed that poor girl.
Good luck with
your investigations...
or, as we say in France,
in the theater, merde!
She wished you good luck.
Merde! to you too, Madame.
''Horses shall not gallop
through the streets...
save the Cavalry
in cases of urgency.
Public urinals shall
be constructed...
to prevent citizens carrying out
their necessary functions...
on the sidewalk.
And, finally, all cuspidors shall
be removed from the streets.''
Do you think
this law will catch on?
Tomorrow I shall fetch the English
detective from the docks.
It appears he's coming
in the company of a doctor.
Is the man sick
or a hypochondriac?
An inseparable friend.
Maybe he's a poof.
That's all we need,
an English bugger.
Ours are quite enough!
The other day, one of them
wanted me to make him pants...
with the fly at the rear
to facilitate the vice.
''l'll pay whatever it costs...
there's money, there's money.''
But seriously, I can't believe
an English detective...
has been brought here
just to look for a fiddle.
Not a fiddle.
A Stradivarius worth a fortune.
Not as much as the lives
of those two young women.
Especially with our police,
who are more concerned...
with persecuting those
who fight against slavery...
than saving lives!
Relax, Mr. Bilac,
there is nothing against you.
It is all newspaper
exaggeration.
After all, if our young
men could no longer...
write manifestos what
would become of Brazil?
I just came for a beer.
Bring me a Dois Machados.
A curious coincidence.
Do you know we were just now
speaking of the murdered girls?
Quite a worriment,
isn't it, inspector?
Two lovely girls, victims of
the same barbarous murderer.
How do you know that
it is the same person?
We've already had
fifteen murders....
in the town this year.
I presume so.
They were killed with
the same type of weapon.
What weapon?
A sharp, cutting object.
Look, inspector, any
number of sharp objects...
could produce similar results.
Any chef could tell you that.
Chiquinha!
Our detective in skirts!
Perhaps Dona Chiquinha would
care to assist with her pow...
This is highly secret.
Found beside them...
entwined around each
of the girl's bodies...
I want to know to which musical
instrument they belonged.
Elementary, my dear friend.
They are violin strings.
The first and
the last, G and E.
And I'll tell you more:
they can only be found...
in the Viola d'Ouro.
So Mr. Holmes
speaks Portuguese?
I suppose so.
And do you still correspond?
No, unfortunately he died...
from a concentration of venom
from African scorpions.
Thank you.
Amazing! What is it?
Feijoada, black beans cooked
with several kinds of meat:
pigs' ears and feet,
salted dried meat...
pork sausage and other
varieties. Very good.
I am greatly enjoying
your country.
I am already regretting
my departure for Argentina.
I know I shall miss
enormously this warm public.
Mr. Holmes, try another
rib with red pepper...
an infallible recipe
for a light digestion.
Oh, thank you,
but I think I'll have...
another slice of fish
with dendê oil.
I shouldn't exaggerate
on the dendê.
And the emperor, don't you
like feijoada and vatapá?
Doctor's orders, Mr. Holmes.
I cannot believe these delicacies
could possible do any harm.
You're only
having salad, Madame?
I am like the emperor.
My doctor forbade me
to eat many things:
red meat, eggs, caviar,
goose liver, cassoulet...
All good things are
bad for one.
I quite agree!
I do hope your friend
won't mind.
I feel more comfortable
speaking with you alone.
It is a delicate matter,
you understand.
Don't worry about Watson,
Your Excellency.
I know you are tired
from your journey.
I shan't take up any more of
your time than is necessary.
I don't even know
where to begin.
Try to begin
at the beginning.
It was nothing.
I'm so sorry.
Well then, the last violin
made by Antonio Stradivarius
was an instrument, called, with
good reason, ''The Swan Song''.
The instrument's sonority
is almost unbelievable.
The sole detail,
and it is a poignant one...
that betrays the tremor
of his aged hands...
is the slightly
unsure intaglio...
of the two openings which form
the acoustical system of the top.
I hope I'm not
being tiresome.
No, no, certainly not.
First of all...
I'd like to say how much
I admire His Majesty...
for his role as
patron of the arts.
I was already familiar with the
musical talent of the Brazilians...
for I had occasion
to attend the premiere...
of Il Guarani at
La Scala in Milan.
I was only sixteen,
but I recall it...
as if it were yesterday.
It was my first opera.
Fantastic!
For some time my friend,
the baroness of Avaré...
had expressed the desire
to have a Stradivarius.
You know how
a woman's whims are.
That is why I am
still a bachelor.
All's well that ends well.
Expect for the fact that the
Stradivarius has been stolen.
Yes, well it seems
to me that it is time...
we had a talk
with the baroness.
I want to know exactly
how the violin disappeared.
My coachman shall take you
to the baroness's residence.
I hope my investigations
prove successful.
For now, all that remains
is for me to thank...
Your Majesty for
the magnificent luncheon.
The delicacies conferred
on us were magic.
Good afternoon.
Would you care for coffee?
It's freshly ground.
The sweet potato candies
are from Castellões...
one of our best confectioners.
I don't know what
I can say to help you.
The baroness would
be astonished...
how important small details...
are to those who carry out...
the exercise of deduction.
For example, I can state that
the baroness is a widow...
that your husband was the owner
of an appreciable fortune...
that he died as the result
of a hunting accident...
that he was hunting
beside a river...
that he was quite
a bit older than you...
and that when he died
he left you all his goods.
That's amazing! How did
you deduce all that?
I read it in the
Complete Brazilian Peerage...
that I found in the hotel.
I'd like to know
from exactly where...
the instrument disappeared.
It wasn't here at the house.
I noticed that one of
the instrument's tuning...
pegs was loose,
making it's tuning difficult.
I asked one of my servants to
take it to the Viola d'Ouro shop.
What magnificent coffee!
Baroness, the world
will one day bow down...
to the quality of Brazilian coffee.
May I speak with the servant
Who took the instrument?
Ah yes.
This is Mukumbe.
He's my guardian angel.
He was my father's slave
but today is a free man...
manumitted by me.
It is he looks
after everything here.
I don't know why, but I
feel safe in his company.
I want to know if by
any chance you noticed...
someone following you when
you went to the repair shop?
No, sir.
There's not a man living
or a ghost who comes after me...
when I walk through
the streets.
And are you sure the violin
was in the case?
Yes, sir.
I saw when Madame stored it
before giving it to me.
It was right after we played
a waltz here in the parlor.
Ah, I forgot to say, Mukumbe
is also an exquisite pianist.
He plays the harpsichord
and the organ...
when there is a Mass
here in the chapel.
And what type of music
do you play?
It depends.
In church, sacred music.
When I play with Madame,
polkas, waltzes...
but what I like most are
maxixe and samba.
Hmmmm, excellent!
Good evening, Mr. Isidoro.
Good evening.
What can I do for you?
A bottle of milk, please.
For you, anything.
Here you are.
Thank you.
-Good night.
Help!
Help! Help!
There! A man
tried to kill me.
Stay here,
I'll be right back.
This is Sherlock Holmes!
Halt or I'll fire!
A mulatto with
generous breasts?
That's right, do you know
where I can find her?
I know she's an actress,
but I doubt whether you'll
get anywhere with her.
As I already said,
it's about an investigation.
We all know how good a real
mulatto can be, right, guv'nor?
Good afternoon.
There is not the slightest doubt.
They are very fine
strings, made of gut.
Of excellent origin.
May I ask where
you found them?
Yes, you can.
But I can't answer.
They are part of a
confidential investigation.
Then they must be connected
to the case of the dead girls.
Has anyone been here
of late to buy strings?
Only a violinist
called Haroldo...
who is playing in Madame
Sarah Bernhardt's shows.
-Haroldo...
-Yes.
How many strings
did he buy?
A full set. Four strings.
A full set.
Four strings...
Inspector Mello
Pimenta, I presume.
That's right.
How do you know who I am?
Simple. I was
at the station house
and they told me
I'd find you here.
Sherlock Holmes, and this
is my friend Dr. Watson.
I didn't know you both
spoke our language.
Only l.
Dr. Watson doesn't
understand a word.
As you see...
It was good to find you.
It was I found you,
my dear Pimenta.
Please wait a minute, first
I should have a small chat
with Mr. Peruggio.
Excuse me...
It was my own
carelessness, Mr. Holmes,
my own carelessness,
I put the instrument here.
The shop was broken
into and the violin stolen.
What am I to do?
I cannot fathom why you left
such a precious violin
within the reach
of the malefactor.
I know they steal
everything here...
food, clothes,
boots, everything...
but I never imagined
that those illiterates...
would steal a violin.
Sincerely, I feel your neglect
has caused great displeasure...
to the baroness and,
of course, to the emperor.
The baroness
and the emperor...
Have you any idea of who
might have stolen the violin?
None, sir.
Good-bye, Sr. Giacomo.
I have much to tell you.
I shouldn't think
that will be necessary.
I already know that as well
as cutting off the ears...
with a dagger, the murderer
places a violin string...
among the pubic hair
of the poor girls...
and then goes playing
through the streets.
Amazing!
Several people told the police
they heard the sound of someone...
playing a violin
in the streets.
But the newspaper says nothing
of the murderer playing.
I know this because I was
with your murderer last night.
He had his instrument with him.
Presumably he was going to
play it, but I prevented him.
A lovely girl, a mulatto.
Wide hips,
generous breasts.
I must find her,
at all costs.
We must find her.
For, if she saw
the murderer's face...
she also saw the face
of the violin thief.
But why do you think
he leaves the strings?
-May I examine them?
-Certainly.
-No sign of the ears?
-No.
Serial killer?
Serial killer.
This expression is just
right for our murderer.
He has already killed two.
Don't you see,
the violin has four
strings: G, D, A, E.
If he's already used two strings,
there are still two left.
Are you trying to tell me he
plans to kill two more girls?
Our job is to prevent
these crimes, inspector.
Do you see how delicate
my situation is?
Before long people will think...
the emperor no longer
trusts his chief of police
even to solve the mere
robbery of a fiddle.
Stradivarius.
-Stradi-what?
-Stradivarius.
Various or just one,
it's still just a fiddle.
Pimenta, have you told
the English detective...
about our main
suspect, Haroldo?
No, since we haven't
gathered all the evidence.
You're authority! The police
don't need evidence.
But we're talking
about a ''serial killer''.
Serial what?
It was the name
Sherlock Holmes gave...
to this criminal
who kills in series.
I tell you, Mr. Coelho Bastos,
it's not going to be easy...
to discover the man, because
he kills without motive.
And the first thing
we learn in the police...
is to find out
the motive of the crime.
Let's avoid
embarrassment, Pimenta.
Let's arrest this man straight
away, to show the emperor...
that our police force doesn't
need an English detective.
I'll explain in a moment
And tell you my version
That in body and soul
I'm an unsexual person
It seems you are
already growing...
accustomed to our Brazil.
It is a fascinating place...
I am enchanted
by the customs.
And the people are
extremely cordial.
However one thing
puzzles me.
The dress.
Why do the men all
wear black, as in Europe...
in a tropical country?
Mr. Holmes,
you must understand...
that civilization
does have its price.
Forrobodó é folguedo de reis
Forrobodó de preto forro
Tem um forrobodó na praia
Tem um forrobodó no morro
Forrobodó de D. Pedro é que nem
Forrobodó do seu lacaio
Faz rebolar até um poste
Não há quem não goste
De um forrobodó
Inspector, I found the violin.
Without strings.
Put that away.
It was Gouveia, wasn't it?
My dear fellow, you're in
big trouble. Take him away.
But I don't understand,
Coelho Bastos.
Has the Stradivarius been
found or hasn't it?
Majesty, in order
to answer that...
I shall have to use
a technical term.
No, the violin has
not yet been found.
But Your Majesty
can rest assured...
that we will find
this Stradivarius.
The main thing is,
the murderer has been caught...
and everything points to
the fact that the violin thief...
is also the killer serial,
I mean, the kerial siller...
the murderer,
Your Majesty!
I think the railway project
is an excellent idea.
I will make arrangements
for a study to be made.
What proj...
But, oh, the project!
Of course, Majesty!
Good afternoon.
A very important project.
Brazil needs railways.
Yes, yes, yes!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
This is my wife's doing.
She's bigger than me,
over 220lbs.
And the ears?
Did you eat the ears?
Ears? What are you
talking about?
You've been in trouble
with the police four times now...
I'm in no hurry,
you'll confess.
I'm not lying.
It was my wife,
I told you...
she is cheating on me
with Sergeant Gouveia,
who lives in my street.
Each time I complain,
Marieta beats me
and the Sergeant goes
to the police
and makes the charge
that it was I beat her.
How did you learn
to speak French?
A study grant from His Majesty.
I studied music in Paris!
And why don't you
leave your wife?
It certainly isn't
because of her beauty.
Marieta gets very jealous.
If I left her,
she'd kill me.
...''beard and hair''
I told Mr. Holmes that you were
the best tailor in the city.
Don't disappoint me, Calif.
Something for a
special occasion?
I have here the most lovely
flannels...
and cashmeres
from your country.
What do you prefer?
Neither one nor the other.
I'd like you to make me
four suits of white linen.
Linen?
But here no one
of quality wears that.
It's something
for the hoi-polloi.
Then I shall set the fashion.
So linen it shall be.
And white, don't forget.
More appropriate for
the heat of the tropics.
What style, Mr. Holmes?
Have you something in mind?
Nothing very special.
Make the frock coats loose,
with space for the revolver.
I want the pockets deep,
as I always carry...
a pipe and
magnifying glass.
I see that sir is
extremely fortunate.
Don't talk nonsense,
Mr. Salomão, that's my pipe.
Beard and hair!
Yes, I understand, sir.
I want to know whether you
want me to trim your hair...
or a complete cut?
Beard and hair!
But is it just to trim?
Beard and hair.
A cut.
But sir...
Hello! How good
to see you again.
I feel I owe
you an apology.
Apology? And why should
the young lady apologize?
After all,
you saved my life...
and I didn't even
wait to thank you.
Under the circumstances,
it's perfectly understandable.
How did you discover
that I work here?
Do you forget
I'm a detective?
Sherlock Holmes
at your service.
The English detective? I read
about you in the newspapers.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Ana Candelária.
The young lady would afford
me immense pleasure...
if she were to accept
an invitation to dine with me...
and lnspector
Mello Pimenta.
We are investigating
those horrible crimes...
and your presence is
indispensable...
in solving the case.
Of course. I so much want
you to find the murderer.
Please call me Ana.
Of course, if you will
call me simply Sherlock.
I don't understand why you
didn't go to the station-house...
to relate your encounter
with the killer.
I was afraid. I didn't know
how I would be received.
You know our profession...
is still confused with
that of prostitutes.
Our police treat everyone
with respect and courtesy.
Even prostitutes.
Could you give me
a description of the assailant?
Impossible, inspector.
He was wearing a cape,
a mask covered his face
and hat pulled down
over his head.
It was all so fast.
If it hadn't been for Sherlock,
I wouldn't be here.
It seems it could
have been anyone.
Even someone right here,
observing us.
What?
You think he might come
to this restaurant?
I don't think anything.
For all we know,
it could be you.
Now let's not exaggerate,
Mr. Holmes.
And now,
if you'll excuse me...
I have to accompany
the young lady home.
Methods of deduction, my dear
Ana, have their limitations.
How could I have deduced
that such a hot day
would turn into such
an agreeable evening?
-Where shall we go?
-I'd like to see your hotel.
They say the apartments
are stunning!
To the hotel.
Good heavens,
how soft it is!
And the room is much
prettier than I thought.
May I offer you something?
Tea, sherry, cocaine?
-Cocaine?
-Yes, an excellent stimulant.
I learnt its use with a friend,
Sigmund Freud, a doctor in Vienna.
I'd have thought
I was stimulant enough.
Ana...
There's something terrible
that I must confess.
What is it?
I'm...
I'm... a virgin.
Did you take some
vow of chastity?
By no means. It's just
that, until I met you...
I never had any interest in sex.
My mind was always
focused on criminology.
You mean I'm the first
woman in your life?
Do you understand now why I
was going to resort to cocaine?
My love, those drugs
just dispel desire.
You need to relax.
-What's that?
-They're lndian cigarettes,
made from cannabis,
an Asiatic plant.
What are they good for?
The instruction-paper says
they're excellent for snoring,
asthma, sleeplessness,
impotence.
It's a miraculous medicine.
Besides that, it's wonderfully
soothing on the nerves.
Except for the smell,
I don't notice anything.
Wait, it always takes
a little time.
That's odd...
I'd never noticed how
colorful this room is.
Did you notice, Ana,
what lovely birds?
It's as if the animals
were circling around.
Such a whirl!
All the birds flying.
-Funny, isn't it?!
-It certainly is.
What?
Listen, can't you hear?
The insects.
What?
The crickets, Holmes.
-The crickets?
-The crickets!
What is it?
Do you know what
I feel like doing?
What? I want you to do
everything you want with me.
-Eating something sweet.
-Sweet?
I don't know why, but I have
an irresistible urge for sweets.
Look, sister.
How lovely!
Tea and toast.
Would Mr. Holmes
like anything else?
Coconut candy.
Bring me a plateful.
I love you, Watson.
Excuse me, Mr. Holmes.
Good morning, Mr. Holmes.
Dr Watson, this is our coroner,
Professor Saraiva.
Is the girl's
identity known?
Yes. Her name is Albertina
de Lourdes Calixto.
She was from the Wheel.
I understand.
Another prostitute.
No, no, Mr. Holmes.
The Wheel is a
charitable institution
that takes in abandoned
new-born babies.
The girl was the daughter of a
funeral agent named Josué Calixto...
and worked there
as a volunteer.
Who found the body?
One of the Sisters of Charity
of the Holy House of Mercy.
The Wheel is nearby.
I was already there asking
a few questions.
Did you find out
if she had enemies?
If anyone followed her?
No one knows.
She was much loved.
There's a feeling of anger
and sadness on everyone's part.
The clues are the same.
What worries me is that there
is still one string on the violin.
Do you mind if I make
a brief investigation?
By all means.
You would be doing us a favor.
Dizzy.
I think yesterday I overdid
some herbs a friend gave me.
Indian cigarettes.
I see you tried our pango.
Pango?
That's what the Negroes
call cannabis.
There was even a lovely
bed of it behind the kitchen...
at His Majesty's palace
in São Cristóvão.
It would be better for you
to return to the hotel...
while I go to the morgue
with Saraiva...
to watch the autopsy.
Out of the question, we insist
on watching the necropsy.
If you'll permit me,
the best medicine...
for this morning-after sensation
is some good cachaça.
I don't think it advisable
to give Mr. Holmes cachaça...
at this hour, Saraiva.
Nonsense.
I'm going to the morgue.
Look, my friend here
is suggesting...
I put a bit of orange juice
or lime in the drink.
-Have you either of these fruits?
-We have limes.
And ice and sugar, please.
What's that concoction
they're mixin' up?
No idea.
Something invented by
that hick there.
-Which, the big one?
-No, the big hick is drinking.
The one who made
it is the little hick.
Professor, one thing
I find strange.
I don't know, I have the impression
that the internal organs have been
repositioned in the cavity.
As if the murderer had
first pulled them out...
and then put them
back in place.
Man alive! You're right!
Say it, Mr. Holmes, please!
I know it's horrifying,
but I'm certain...
the monster rubbed the liver
on his own face.
At night, the beard
has already started to grow...
and these tiny striations
must have been caused...
by friction with the facial hairs.
Anathema!
My daughter...
my daughter...
my little daughter.
Oh Lord, why didn't you
take me instead...
Mr. Calixto...
I'm lnspector Mello Pimenta.
I know this is a very difficult
moment, but even so.
I have to ask you
a few questions.
Do you know if your daughter
had made any new friendships?
No, she was totally
dedicated to the orphans.
Did you observe anyone, recently,
lurking near your house?
No. She was dearly loved.
I'd like to have a few moments
alone with my daughter.
Who is the pathologist
in charge?
It is l, Saraiva.
If you have finished
your examination...
I would like to use my every
talent as funeral agent...
to restore to the unfortunate girl
the appearance she had in life.
I don't want her to be
seen like this...
nor would I like a wake
with a sealed casket.
Of course,
it's the least we can do.
My sympathies.
''Dear chief, by the time
you read these scribbled lines...
I shall be preparing
to execute...
better drawn lines on
the body of another wench.
What do you need
to find me out?
To find the crown jewels?
That I sign my full name
on the whores' corpses?''
''l thought the Englishman
would be cleverer than you...
at reading my clues,
but it seems he's such an ass...
that he might as well
have ears larger than
all those I've cut off,
together.
I hope you're having
as much fun as I am.
Do something soon,
because I'm hungry...
and there's still one chord
waiting for the Final Concert.
And speaking of chords...
cordial greetings''.
''Oluparun''.
Doesn't seem very enlightening.
The man does nothing but jest.
I think you're wrong, my dear.
I think he's insinuating
he attends the court.
And where, Mrs. Know-All, did
you get that idea, might I know?
Well, to start with,
it's an educated person.
True. I also noticed that he took
the trouble to write in a scrawl...
so as not to be identified
by his handwriting.
Then, when he mentions the crown
jewels and a Final Concerto,
he might be indirectly referring
to the charity recital the violinist...
José White will organize this
week, to honor Princess lsabel.
Therefore the murderer must
have access to the court...
and therefore belong to it.
How do you know all that?
By reading Múcio Prado's
society column.
Dear lady,
I must compliment you
on your intelligence...
and capacity for deduction.
Many thanks.
And what does
''Oluparun'' mean?
I don't know.
Well, what interests me is merely...
that my culinary talents
please you.
And what have
you prepared today?
Stewed liver à la nature.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I know that tonight we have
with us el señor Sherlock Holmes...
who as everyone knows is
a phenomenal English detective.
But what few know is his
ability as a violinist.
I would like to ask
el señor Holmes to give us
the honor and pleasure
of playing with us.
Bravo! Bravo!
Congratulations, my friend!
I didn't know you played the violin,
marquis, in such a brilliant fashion.
Memorable!
I want to kiss the heroes.
Impossible to say which
one was better. Bravo!
Mr. Holmes, when you wish to
participate in one of our revues...
don't be shy.
The number is worthy
of any theater.
Thank you very much!
Seeing a presentation
like tonight...
I lament a bit less the
theft of my Stradivarius.
I would never be able
to play like that.
Thank you.
Extraordinary! A fusion
of Paganini and D'Artagnan!
Thank you.
Many think these asymmetrical
gardens are an English invention.
And?
But they're not, my love.
They were first used in China,
during the reign of Long-Teching...
and were later transported
to Europe by the English.
-You see?
-I see.
I'm dying to give
you a kiss!
Ana, let's go to your house?
I can't. The housekeeper
is very strict.
Can we go to my hotel?
It's too far.
Don't stop! Don't stop!
Police!
-You're under arrest!
-Calm yourself, constable,
I assure you we were doing
nothing worthy of reproof.
We were merely conversing.
You Portuguese are very cheeky.
What were you thinking?
You have to respect the law.
This isn't a colony any more!
You are quite mistaken,
my dear sir.
I am English and my name is
Sherlock Holmes.
I don't care who you are.
I caught you red-handed in
an act against public morality...
and proper behavior.
This is the Public Promenade,
not a brothel!
Off to the clink with you!
The girl has nothing to do
with what happened.
All right, but if necessary
she'll have to testify later?
Shall we go?
What you have done is
very serious, see.
I have already told you that
I have no explanations to offer.
Please be so good as to call
lnspector Mello Pimenta.
I don't know how it is
in your country.
But here, the law is
the same for everyone. All!
I assure you that you will
regret this imprudent act!
It seems to me the imprudent
act was yours, wasn't it?
Guard, please take
the celebrity to jail.
I demand at least
a separate cell!
Release that man!
Are you all right,
Mr. Holmes?
I came as soon as Miss Candelária
informed me of this nonsense.
I was looking for you.
We have an appointment
with Dr. Nina Milet...
a famous criminologist
and pathologist from Bahia...
who can help us.
Well, what does
Oluparun mean?
It's Nagô Yoruba.
It means ''the Destroyer'',
''the Exterminator''.
Then the murderer
is a Negro?
Apparently, besides
struggling for abolition...
we're also going to have
to fight for our innocence.
You well know how hasty
our marquis is.
He's probably a mulatto.
How can you make such
a baseless statement?
Mr. Holmes, here in Brazil only
blacks and the poor get arrested.
-And abolitionists, of course.
-And detectives, don't forget.
It's purely scientific.
Read the ''Essai sur I'inégalité
des races humaines'', by Gobineau,
an intimate friend
of our emperor.
As Negroes belong
to an inferior race...
the mixture of races leads to
the creation of degenerate beings...
many of whom are born
with propensity...
toward mental aberrations
and criminal strains.
Those are the kind of
absurdities which hold back...
the abolition movement.
You should be ashamed of
what you just said!
My dear man,
I know whereof I speak.
Studies of phrenology
and craniology do not lie...
I know these theories,
Dr. Nina...
but it seems to me a bit hasty
to attribute to Negroes...
the existence of crime.
If this were so, London and
Paris would be peaceful cities.
Gentlemen, this is
getting us nowhere.
One point at a time.
Why the baroness's
Stradivarius?
To draw attention
to his power.
The man leaves clues
on purpose, as a challenge.
It is likely that he has a subconscious
desire to be caught.
Congratulations, Miss Gonzaga.
My thought entirely.
Why does he only kill women?
Because they're weaker.
Not all of them.
Because he hates them.
Perhaps to him woman is the
symbol of the perverted customs...
that dominate our times.
Maybe he's afraid of them.
It's possible.
He fears something
they arouse in him.
Or that they don't
succeed in arousing.
They call what I do cruel.
Why?
It is no different from
what I read in the manual
about carving up animals.
They only don't call
that ritual cruel...
because the sacrificed
animals serve as food.
That's the difference.
Eat, perhaps I should eat...
Finally partake ofthe flesh.
The slaves were right.
When I was a child,
on the nights of Black Magic...
at the farm, terrified,
they called me ''Oluparun.''
Sarah Bernhardt's departure
reminds me that sooner or later...
you too will leave us.
Why don't you come
with me to London?
We have gone far enough.
Stay, dear Enone...
strength fails me,
and I must rest awhile.
My eyes are dazzled with
this glaring light.
So long unseen, my trembling
knees refuse support.
Ah me!
What?
Officious hand
has tied these knots...
and gather'd o'er my brow,
these clustering coils?
How all conspires
to add to my distress!
What is it? I regret that you cannot
return to the theater tonight.
Be brief, I have
a young lady waiting.
My babalorixá, King Obá Shite Ill...
ordered me to take you
to his ilê.
Who?
My great father, the high priest
of candomblé.
He has important information
about the murder of the girls.
A poison, brought
to Athens by Medea...
runs thro' my veins.
Already in my heart
the venom works...
infusing there a strange
and fatal chill.
Already as thro' thickening
mists I see the spouse to whom...
my presence
is an outrage.
Death, from mine eyes veiling
the light of heav'n...
restores its purity
that they defiled.
You are son of Xangô.
Your orixá, the saint
who protects you.
Always use this necklace, my son.
Never forget:
Xangô is your father.
Xangô is your protector.
I do not understand.
The orixás summoned
you here...
but they refuse to manifest
themselves further.
I am very sorry, my son.
There seems to be some
current blocking the flow.
Nothing serious,
Dr. Watson has become Exu.
That's trouble.
I know that you have
the best intentions...
but I can assure you we.
have no time to pratice...
any kind of initiation ceremony.
A ''pomba-gira''?
It's a female-exu.
It is a devil-orixá
in female form.
It usually only comes
into women...
is that fellow adé?
-What's that?
-Effeminate...
No, he's English.
Then the pomba-gira must
have got confused.
What?
I want oti! I want itaba!
And you can light th' inãs!
It's unbelievable!
Dr. Watson never spoke
any of these languages!
No, it's the pomba-gira
asking for a cigar and rum.
So yuh wan' know
whooza zirikila?
Exactly. We need to know
who the serial killer is.
But yuh already know
th' zirikila.
Yuh been with 'im.
He wuz right nex' to yuh.
Yuh ain't found 'im 'cause...
yuh've smoked too much
itabojira in yur pipe.
Yuh hear?
Yuh not e'en listenin',
English-Portuguese man.
Yuh better 'an
the color'd girls.
Th' zirikila is a okorin
with owô odara...
and he's gonna kufá another
obirin with th' obéte'.
She says the serial killer
is a man with much money
and that he is going to kill
another woman with the dagger.
And why does he do this?
Why?
'Cause th' zirikila is kolori.
Well? I want menga!
I want ejé!
If I don't get it,
I won't leave!
Oluparun! Oluparun!
Couldn't I ask the name
of the murderer?
It would be no good.
When she asks to leave the body,
it means she'll say nothing further.
After long years
fantasizing infirmities...
my mother died
ofsmallpox.
I feel no pain, norpity.
A sensation ofliberty
invades my soul.
In spite ofthe ears
and the strings...
I was not found out.
And now, nothing
will stop me.
The time has come to
slaughter the prostitute who...
with her licentiousness, perverted
the witless emperor of the tropics.
I think ofangels...
Not the guardians ofsouls
and bringers of good news...
but those the Lord sends
to earth to carry out
His most terrible plans.
The messengers ofplagues
God's hangmen.
Mukumbé?
You?
I nearly died of fright!
How dare you come
in like this, at this hour...
without announcing yourself?
I heard your mother died.
I was saddened.
I know how you loved her.
So don't you know that visiting
young widows late at night...
might cause the
wrong impression?
Mercy!
No, not the face!
No!
There can be no more
doubt, my dear Pimenta.
The murderer had his eye
on the baroness...
right from the beginning.
The missing D string...
was for Dalia Maria Luiza
Catarina de Albuquerque.
I believe the
cycle of crimes...
of that damned fiddle
are over, at last.
Excuse me, Mr. Holmes.
Something terrible has happened.
Your room has been
broken into.
I am very sorry.
I regret that your visit
to Brazil has been under...
such tragic circumstances.
I would dearly like to invite you
to amuse yourself in Petrópolis...
but my state duties oblige me
to remain at the Palace.
I have already had two passages
reserved on the ship which sails...
-for England tomorrow.
-Most generous of Your Majesty.
We have come to thank you
for your hospitality
and return the ''Swan Song''...
finally recovered under
such fatal circumstances.
Forgive me, Mr. Holmes.
The Swan Song would bring back...
painful memories
of my gentle friend.
Merely looking at it
rends my heart.
I understand, Majesty.
But what should I do?
After all, it is a Stradivarius.
You know that, officially,
this violin never existed.
I would like you to keep it.
I don't know if I can accept
such a valuable gift.
Of course you can:
it shall be our secret...
a remembrance of your time
in the tropics.
In Rome, when Caesar returned
victorious from battle...
and the multitude acclaimed him
in the parades of Triumph,
according him the honors
of a divinity...
he would have a slave beside him
whispering into his ear:
''Thou art bald,
old and hast a big belly...''
He wished to be reminded
that he was merely human.
Humility is the mother
of all virtues.
Keep the Swan Song as a trophy
of the arduous case...
that you were unable to solve.
The only comfort left
to us is that we know...
all the strings are gone and
the violin has been returned.
I deduce that this is
the end of the crimes...
of the mad violinist.
Another brilliant deduction,
Mr. Holmes!
I don't know how you do it.
Elementary,
my dear Pedro.
I don't understand why you wanted
to see me in this empty theater.
Forgive me, my love...
but when I wish to reflect
on something important...
this is where I come.
My ideas become clearer...
Iike a church for some.
And what were you thinking?
About your invitation
to go to London with you.
And?
Try to understand, darling.
In London I would be like
a fish out of water.
How long would our love
endure in a strange land?
Ana, in London
you'd be my wife...
you'd be Ana Candelária
Scott Holmes.
You could work.
The English theater is
among the best there is.
I'm just starting.
My career is nothing great.
I want to find
my own way, Holmes...
and you have your
crimes to see to.
I leave tomorrow.
Will you go to my sailing?
No.
I won't have the strength
to see you at the quay.
Then this is...
good-bye?
I don't want you to go away without feeling
you inside me at least once.
Don't forget,
when you come to London...
there will always be room
at 221 b Baker Street.
And when you return to Brazil,
I insist you stay at my house.
Many thanks.
But although I love this land,
I think the memories I carry...
with me are too painful
for that to be likely.
Miguel!
-Good morning, gentlemen.
-Good morning.
Mr. Holmes, does this mean
we'll be traveling together?
What a happy coincidence.
Going on a trip?
No, moving.
I plan to live in London.
So, you take French leave
even when going to England.
You know very well
this old aspiration of mine...
to have a little bookshop in London
and lead a peaceful life.
If you need anything,
I am at your disposal.
I should like to repay
the generous hospitality...
that I received
in your country.
They'll never know.
The simple-minded
detective couldn't read...
the obvious signs
I left behind.
I recognize that I was playing
with marked cards...
In England the notes
ofthe musical scale...
are always designated
by letters:
G, D, A, E.
The stupid Englishman
didn't even for a minute...
think about the classification
used by Latin countries...
Mi for Miguel,
Sol for Solera,
La for Lara.
Miguel Solera de Lara.
And the Re for Aphrodite's
Retreat, my bookshop.
Aphrodite, a goddess
venerated by whores...
and protectress
of trollops.
And the ears?
So obvious. Flaps.
Flaps of skin, flaps ofa book.
Bookseller.
The half-witted Englishman
knew the language well...
but he spoke like a Portuguese for
whom such flaps have a different name.