This year's best actress is...
Anna Battista!
What are your future projects?
20 films at the age of 20...
Don't the awards go to your head?
Next stop, Hollywood?
Anna, what do you think of love?
Are you in love right now?
You want to direct?
Is your decision final?
Do you want children?
Did the Dalai Lama impress you?
How important is the family?
And religion?
How many hours
do you spend in the gym?
Do you think Italian cinema is dying?
Anna!
"Giovanna of the clouds"
Just a second!
Tyrone!
- They need you on set.
- Just a second.
The pause is over. Come on!
What are they doing?
Fuck it, I didn't come!
It hurts!
Dirty stuff again.
Enough. Enough already!
Remember what this ring means?
- I was sleeping, mom.
- No.
I don't believe you!
I'll send you away to school.
To that place in Switzerland
where Chaplin's kids went!
I've got so much shit on,
so many scripts to read.
She's too much of a pest,
I can't take any more!
- Read that chapter of "Moby Dick"?
- Yes.
Well done, sis, I'm going to make
a writer of you one day.
I could act, like mom.
Then you'll end up like her.
I keep my panties on.
What?
When I do dirty things,
I keep them on.
Shut up!
Enough, Alioscia, I'll wet myself.
Dirty things...
A tattooed eye.
It's Anna Battista.
- Show me up!
- Are you Anna Battista?
Have you really got a tattoo
on your fanny?
No, I put it on every morning.
It's a fake, it's trendy.
How far does it go?
Hands off!
Only my husband knows that.
What husband? Where's your ring?
- Her husband...
- Sorry, got to go.
- Come here!
- A photo!
- She wants to run off...
- Smile!
Give me an autograph.
Grab a pen, man!
- What's your name?
- Maurizio.
Do one for me too. I'm Dado.
Guys...
Got to go.
Come back!
Anna, come back!
Don't go!
Stay with us!
Where's she going?
Leave a message for Veronica
after the tone.
Veronica, hi, it's Anna.
I'm in Locarno for a TV interview.
I'll be in Paris tomorrow.
Be there.
People say...
you're a man-eater.
How would you define yourself?
A relentless romantic.
A fundamentally lonely girl.
It's very hard for me to love someone.
I've been single for two years now.
- How about you?
- Me?
Tell me about your sex life.
I haven't had sex in five years.
I understand.
Can I sit next to you?
Please do.
Can I give you a hug?
Veronica, I'm in Paris.
Where the fuck are you?
Oh my God!
What the fuck's happened?
Anyone home?
Veronica?
Gross...
Oh my God!
Help!
What the fuck...
- Anna, untie me!
- How the fuck do I?
Untie the knots. Use the pincers.
Do something!
Calm down...
Where's she keep the pincers?
Hurry, I can't go on!
Give me a fucking second.
I'm doing my best!
I can't go on! Untie me!
Untie me, Anna!
I'm hurting all over!
Here I am.
Calm down. Stop moving.
Fuck!
Who the fuck did this?
Who was it?
Come here.
Who the fuck was it?
It was Hamid. We fought,
he tied me up like this
and then he left.
How long ago?
Two days, I think.
It's not my fault, Anna.
I'm mad about him.
Why does he have to be like this?
Hamid...
We went to Les Halles.
Where the fuck else?
Yeah, Barbes... Where's the hash?
Hi, how's it going?
- I'm looking for some shit.
- See the Yank.
- The Yank?
- Take her.
- Go with her.
- With me?
My friend waits?
- I'll wait.
- Won't be long.
- What's that guy's name?
- Who? Hamid?
Yeah, Hamid...
Give me some of your apple?
I've finished it.
It's tough today.
In fact, I'm here in Paris
because I'm an actress and...
You know?
- What's "to fuck" in French?
- "Baiser".
Let's go.
A real piece of shit...
We used to be a threesome,
then she went solo.
Veronica, forget Hamid.
This thing has to stop.
Enough already.
I know, but subconsciously
I'm asking him to do it.
What the fuck do you mean?
You're like those American housewives
who get beaten up
and don't rat on their men.
Get dressed,
we're going to the fucking police
and that piece
of shit's going to jail.
Not dead yet, you dirty whore?
Bastard!
Let me do the talking. Calm down.
A man who beats a woman
has got no balls.
What do you do?
Beat up girls? You're a shithead.
I'm going to the police
about you, get it?
Don't!
You're evil!
You can't treat me like a whore!
Leave me alone. Don't touch me!
This time, I'll kill you,
I swear I will!
I'm not a whore!
I love you.
Guys, I'm outta here...
See you after the gig, okay.
Shall I go?
I'll wait for you.
Bye, see you later.
Hold on, I'll show you something.
It's really important.
You like it? It's a gun.
You're my love.
I'll wait for you forever.
Who the fuck
d'you think you are, bitch?
I'll get you, you whore!
It's Veronica.
Hamid's left me.
I caught him screwing another woman.
I want to die.
If you don't call, I'm killing myself.
The wasteland...
Anna, it's grandma.
Where are you?
Recently you've seemed
so detached and sceptical...
You seem unattainable.
I love you all the same.
Who is it?
Quelou.
Who are you?
- What a great apartment.
- You like it?
I didn't get a good look last time.
Last time?
Quelou...
Quelou?
I'm sorry, I remember you but...
I feel kind of...
Tell me, where was it we met?
At a party?
On a plane?
What do you do?
You really don't remember?
Listen...
I've got a cab waiting downstairs
and I have to leave in half an hour.
D'you want
to get off?
You're scaring me.
What do you mean, scaring you?
Remember
how you licked me last time?
When?
You're like a child...
I have to be going now.
- You have to go?
- Yes.
I don't want to miss my flight.
Give me your number and I'll call you.
You know, I'm really catching a plane.
Thanks.
- In case I lose it...
- You mustn't.
Are you crazy?
All this fuss over measles!
Did you bring my Roip?
I'm cold.
- So cold.
- Anna, dear...
aren't you pleased
to stay at home for a few days?
Don't say that in front of her.
What does she know
about pharmaceuticals?
Alioscia?
If I die,
you can have all my stickers.
Mom! Wake up,
we've made your breakfast.
Overdose.
Who the hell do we call?
You forgot to feed them again.
You're like your mother.
I don't know why I married you.
Married me?
What d'you mean?
I'm the father of your son.
I don't know who you are.
My baby!
My baby! Help!
In the head!
- Who is it?
- Mrs... or Miss Battista?
What time is it?
Just a second.
Half past ten.
I'm Vessi, your gynaecologist.
It's about the test...
Yes.
The pregnancy test.
And?
Pregnant.
Hello?
What shall we do now?
Another abortion?
No, doctor.
Not an abortion.
Okay, no abortion.
See you soon.
Paaradei's buying...
the US distribution rights.
It's a great opportunity.
Barry Paar came here in person
to sign the deal.
I mean, it's incredible.
Totally incredible!
What the fuck?
Congratulations on the award!
Good to see you!
Cleopatra... What's up?
I've lost my shoes,
my fur, the award, everything!
What happened?
Who the fuck
did you leave me with?
What d'you mean?
The guy's a top producer.
Barry Paar wanted to screw me.
He said, "I want to eat your fur pie."
Calm down, okay.
Look at the mess I'm in!
Okay, forget that now.
You fly to London tomorrow.
London... God, she's forgotten!
The Vogue shoot with Luke Ford.
That's actress shit. I want to direct.
For God's sake...
Why do they all want
to be directors here?
You're my agent.
You have to help me direct.
I sent you to Barry Paar.
You sent me to a shithead
who wanted to rape me!
What is this place?
"Shining"?
I don't believe it...
Calm down!
Anna, get up.
The crapper...
This isn't me.
This isn't me...
They're laughing at me.
They can see me.
Let's wash our face.
Like this...
My baby...
My belly...
Get away from me!
Let her die.
Anna, its Margherita.
I've got the Cleopatra pages
for Saturday's screen test in LA.
As for the flight, there's one at...
We shall be landing in LA
in 20 minutes.
Would all passengers
please remain seated...
You don't give a shit
about Aaron Ulrich now?
He's always been your idol.
I'm not saying I don't give a shit
about working with him.
Why else would I spend
20 hours on a train to Amsterdam?
He's the world's greatest living
writer-director.
But I don't want to work for him,
I'd like him to work for me.
You can call by here, right?
Come to Paris.
Come on, come to Paris.
Please...
Shit!
Snow started falling softly...
as light as candyfloss...
THE END
Read that chapter of "Moby Dick"?
Well done, sis, you'll be a writer.
Seen that, Alioscia?
Fuck it!
You're irresponsible.
Your first check-up
in five months of pregnancy.
Just tell me
if it's alive or dead.
It's alive and it's a girl.
My baby...
She's clenching her fists...
And you're both in prefect health.
Look at her.
Doctor, thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
Seven months.
You mean you're still going
on that Australian guy?
His name's Kirk.
I don't know.
He's never been in touch...
He's never called, I know it's over.
He's dumped me, okay.
I know his group's
playing the Cigale tonight.
The very place where I met him.
I'm going to surprise him.
God, Anna, surprises suck.
I'm sure it'll all go well.
I'm sure
he'll knock me out tonight.
You always make me late.
Fuck, it's already started.
It'll all be okay.
Love isn't always poison
as Bob Dylan said.
Or my mom. I forget now.
God, he's so good-looking!
It's just like last year.
- Go on.
- Really?
Come with me?
Go on your own, everything's okay.
Let go!
Subtitles by:
LASER S. FILM s.r.I. - ROME