1
00:01:57,726 --> 00:01:59,517
Andrew!

2
00:02:04,441 --> 00:02:06,896
I missed you so much!

3
00:02:06,985 --> 00:02:08,776
Hey, everyone's looking.

4
00:02:08,862 --> 00:02:10,901
Let them look.

5
00:02:10,989 --> 00:02:12,531
OK, let's go.

6
00:02:18,413 --> 00:02:21,367
- Welcome back, Andy.
- Thanks.

7
00:02:21,458 --> 00:02:23,830
To your good health, Professor.

8
00:02:30,217 --> 00:02:34,962
I had you transferred from Hong Kong,
because I need your help on a case.

9
00:02:35,055 --> 00:02:39,218
It might involve a high ranking
officer in the police department.

10
00:02:40,352 --> 00:02:44,764
I need someone with a new face
to go undercover.

11
00:02:44,856 --> 00:02:47,430
- You'll be reporting to Jerry.
- OK.

12
00:02:47,526 --> 00:02:50,811
Papa, stop talking business
and start eating,

13
00:02:50,904 --> 00:02:53,858
or all the food will go to waste.

14
00:02:55,075 --> 00:02:59,025
All right, we'll discuss this
tomorrow. Come on now, dig in.

15
00:02:59,120 --> 00:03:00,531
Yes, sir.

16
00:03:02,457 --> 00:03:03,868
- Cheers.
- Cheers.

17
00:03:03,959 --> 00:03:06,284
He's only been home a few hours

18
00:03:06,378 --> 00:03:08,999
and already you're trying
to get him drunk.

19
00:03:09,881 --> 00:03:12,040
Sally cares about you.

20
00:03:13,385 --> 00:03:16,006
I should be the one
proposing the toast.

21
00:03:16,096 --> 00:03:21,470
I used to just hang around here
until Jerry sent me to reform school.

22
00:03:22,853 --> 00:03:28,523
Then the Professor helped me and sent
me to study at the police academy.

23
00:03:28,608 --> 00:03:33,354
If it wasn't for you two,
I wouldn't be here today.

24
00:03:33,446 --> 00:03:37,491
To both of you. Thank you, sir.

25
00:03:46,710 --> 00:03:51,122
- Shall I walk you to your car?
- No, thanks. It's just there.

26
00:03:51,214 --> 00:03:53,207
- Good night, Professor.
- Good night, Jerry.

27
00:03:53,300 --> 00:03:56,419
I'll take Andy back to his hotel.
You get to bed.

28
00:03:56,511 --> 00:04:01,387
Good night, Professor. I'll see you
tomorrow. I'd better get going.

29
00:04:48,438 --> 00:04:53,729
You'd better get back
and get some rest. Come on.

30
00:04:54,736 --> 00:04:56,527
All right.

31
00:05:01,826 --> 00:05:04,234
Who's visiting the Professor
so late?

32
00:05:11,670 --> 00:05:13,378
Hold it!

33
00:05:55,463 --> 00:05:57,123
"Fingerprint of Suspect"

34
00:05:59,217 --> 00:06:01,459
"Fingerprint Number:"

35
00:06:11,521 --> 00:06:14,522
"Match Number:"

36
00:06:27,829 --> 00:06:31,530
"Carl Chan,
executed January 10th, 1987."

37
00:06:35,462 --> 00:06:39,542
Strange, how could our murderer
have been executed three months ago?

38
00:06:39,883 --> 00:06:42,753
How could this be, Jerry?

39
00:06:42,844 --> 00:06:45,133
It was a well-planned hit.

40
00:06:46,389 --> 00:06:49,841
Using a supposed dead man
to commit a murder.

41
00:06:49,935 --> 00:06:52,686
Either someone's been messing
with the computer,

42
00:06:52,771 --> 00:06:55,309
or there's something up at the jail.

43
00:07:08,203 --> 00:07:10,326
Don't dwell on it, Andy.

44
00:07:10,705 --> 00:07:13,706
I'm OK. You go home if you want.

45
00:07:14,668 --> 00:07:17,372
I want to be alone for a while.

46
00:07:18,004 --> 00:07:19,796
OK, then.

47
00:07:22,259 --> 00:07:25,343
I'll head off, then. Bye. See you.

48
00:07:28,223 --> 00:07:30,465
Give me some stuff, Ronnie.

49
00:07:30,559 --> 00:07:32,966
- Got the money?
- It's all gone.

50
00:07:33,061 --> 00:07:36,015
That's bullshit!
Sell your body, then.

51
00:07:36,106 --> 00:07:39,190
- I can't stand it!
- Get lost!

52
00:07:39,985 --> 00:07:41,811
Boss, someone's looking at you.

53
00:07:41,903 --> 00:07:43,730
What are you looking at?

54
00:08:49,888 --> 00:08:52,094
Do you think it's worth it?

55
00:08:54,434 --> 00:08:58,052
We've checked it out.
The computer is secure.

56
00:08:58,980 --> 00:09:04,057
The prison is our only clue.
I've got to do it.

57
00:09:04,152 --> 00:09:07,153
You might get killed.

58
00:09:09,074 --> 00:09:11,316
I'll take the risk.

59
00:09:12,410 --> 00:09:14,699
And what about Sally?

60
00:09:16,164 --> 00:09:19,414
Don't tell her anything
until I've finished this case.

61
00:09:22,712 --> 00:09:26,580
I won't. But assault
and battery is serious.

62
00:09:26,675 --> 00:09:29,545
You'll be in for two years.

63
00:09:29,636 --> 00:09:32,008
For your safety in prison,

64
00:09:32,097 --> 00:09:36,723
no one can know who you are,
apart from you and me.

65
00:09:38,019 --> 00:09:40,178
Operation - Hunter.

66
00:09:54,786 --> 00:09:57,657
Take these.
I'll inform you of the rules here.

67
00:09:57,747 --> 00:10:02,456
On your clothing is a number - forget
it and it's ten days in the hole.

68
00:10:02,544 --> 00:10:04,453
Fighting is on Saturday afternoons.

69
00:10:04,546 --> 00:10:07,666
Any unsupervised fighting -
ten days in the hole.

70
00:10:07,757 --> 00:10:11,376
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.

71
00:10:11,469 --> 00:10:14,720
Never go against the officers.
Never try to escape.

72
00:10:14,806 --> 00:10:17,973
No raping other inmates.
No breaking of fixtures.

73
00:10:18,059 --> 00:10:20,550
Six months hard labor
for these offences.

74
00:10:20,645 --> 00:10:24,097
If you smoke in bed,
it's ten days in the hole.

75
00:10:24,191 --> 00:10:26,942
Every Saturday,
you'll receive one clean sheet.

76
00:10:27,027 --> 00:10:28,437
Change the bottom one.

77
00:10:28,653 --> 00:10:31,820
If you get it wrong -
ten days in the hole.

78
00:10:31,907 --> 00:10:37,411
You'll memorize these rules. If you
forget any - ten days in the hole.

79
00:10:37,495 --> 00:10:40,413
All right, this is your cell.

80
00:10:40,498 --> 00:10:44,710
All right, guys. That's enough.
Now back off, all of you.

81
00:10:44,836 --> 00:10:48,122
Sorry, that's my bed.
Yours is the lower one.

82
00:10:51,510 --> 00:10:54,843
The last guy in that bunk
was in here for forgery.

83
00:10:54,930 --> 00:10:57,681
He couldn't take it,
so he killed himself.

84
00:11:04,689 --> 00:11:07,524
Hey, is this your first time in?

85
00:11:12,697 --> 00:11:16,861
Don't be like that.
A guy needs a friend in this place.

86
00:11:37,764 --> 00:11:39,342
Charlie.

87
00:11:39,975 --> 00:11:41,848
I'm Andy.

88
00:11:42,352 --> 00:11:45,602
Bed check! Hand over that cigarette!

89
00:11:50,068 --> 00:11:54,611
- A whole cigarette - rich man!
- You scared me!

90
00:11:54,698 --> 00:11:56,108
Who's gonna win?

91
00:11:56,199 --> 00:12:00,363
- What are the odds?
- 20-1 he won't last 30 seconds.

92
00:12:01,538 --> 00:12:03,945
What's going on, Charlie?

93
00:12:04,040 --> 00:12:08,370
The new guy is fighting the prison
champ and the new guy is you!

94
00:12:08,461 --> 00:12:10,288
And if I don't?

95
00:12:10,380 --> 00:12:14,081
Everyone will be out for your blood.
Am I right, Charlie?

96
00:12:14,176 --> 00:12:15,753
Yeah, that's right.

97
00:12:29,316 --> 00:12:32,067
This way. Excuse me, thank you.

98
00:12:33,028 --> 00:12:36,231
Hey, kid. We're all betting on you.

99
00:12:36,323 --> 00:12:40,403
If you stay in for 30 seconds
we'll be rich.

100
00:13:02,891 --> 00:13:04,682
Get back in there!

101
00:13:25,121 --> 00:13:26,201
Get him!

102
00:13:59,781 --> 00:14:02,070
There's five seconds to go!

103
00:14:07,622 --> 00:14:09,247
He's still in!

104
00:14:32,606 --> 00:14:35,179
Get him! Get him!

105
00:14:52,125 --> 00:14:53,869
I'll get him!

106
00:14:56,713 --> 00:14:58,172
It's over.

107
00:14:58,256 --> 00:15:00,545
Come on.

108
00:15:16,525 --> 00:15:18,434
- 20453?
- Here!

109
00:15:18,527 --> 00:15:21,231
- 15783?
- Yo!

110
00:15:21,321 --> 00:15:23,230
- 11795?
- Yeah!

111
00:15:25,700 --> 00:15:29,235
- A letter from your son?
- His mother remarried.

112
00:15:29,329 --> 00:15:35,083
She sent Joey to a boarding school.
His birthday's in two days.

113
00:15:35,168 --> 00:15:38,454
But she's on her honeymoon
with her new husband.

114
00:15:38,547 --> 00:15:42,758
Boarding school's not so bad -
it makes a kid more independent.

115
00:15:54,354 --> 00:15:58,897
I've some fresh meat in the kitchen.
Shall I cook it for you?

116
00:15:58,984 --> 00:16:03,195
It would go well with your wine.
Would you like some?

117
00:16:03,280 --> 00:16:05,319
- Hurry up.
- Yes, sir.

118
00:16:05,407 --> 00:16:08,112
Bill, open the gate.

119
00:16:09,452 --> 00:16:10,911
Thanks.

120
00:16:13,206 --> 00:16:17,074
Hey, cap,
are you going to be a cop forever?

121
00:16:17,169 --> 00:16:18,627
Why do you ask?

122
00:16:20,881 --> 00:16:25,258
Well, if you ever open a restaurant,
I'll be your cook.

123
00:16:25,343 --> 00:16:27,669
What a laugh!

124
00:16:27,762 --> 00:16:33,053
Who's laughing? Don't blame me
when all you have to eat is dog meat.

125
00:16:34,477 --> 00:16:37,229
Hey! What's there to know?

126
00:16:37,314 --> 00:16:39,223
Plenty! I'll show you.

127
00:16:46,406 --> 00:16:47,948
Fry the onion.

128
00:16:49,534 --> 00:16:51,859
Add the meat.

129
00:17:15,018 --> 00:17:16,429
Hold this.

130
00:18:13,869 --> 00:18:15,327
Hey!

131
00:18:16,162 --> 00:18:17,573
You got a light?

132
00:18:26,756 --> 00:18:28,796
Thanks a lot.

133
00:18:29,551 --> 00:18:34,296
It's almost New Year again.
I hope I'm not working this holiday.

134
00:18:34,389 --> 00:18:37,639
My wife will run off
with another man.

135
00:18:42,522 --> 00:18:44,396
What's up with you?

136
00:18:44,482 --> 00:18:48,017
On my salary,
I can't even afford new shoes.

137
00:19:32,239 --> 00:19:36,071
Get out, come on.
I've got to check the car.

138
00:19:38,078 --> 00:19:39,951
What is it, officer?

139
00:19:40,038 --> 00:19:41,865
Doesn't your mother feed you?

140
00:19:41,957 --> 00:19:43,996
She's thinner than I am.

141
00:19:44,084 --> 00:19:46,919
What's going on?

142
00:19:58,306 --> 00:20:00,844
This is all your fault.

143
00:20:00,976 --> 00:20:01,758
It's mine! It's mine!
Get the ball, Joey!

144
00:20:09,526 --> 00:20:12,361
- Joey.
- Papa!

145
00:20:40,807 --> 00:20:44,141
Headquarters,
we've located the stolen car.

146
00:20:44,227 --> 00:20:47,928
We're outside the Lawrence
boarding school. Requesting back-up.

147
00:20:48,023 --> 00:20:49,433
Headquarters -

148
00:20:49,524 --> 00:20:53,356
we've located the prisoner,
requesting immediate back-up.

149
00:20:59,409 --> 00:21:02,529
Listen to your teachers.
I'll visit again soon.

150
00:21:02,621 --> 00:21:04,281
Do you promise?

151
00:21:04,372 --> 00:21:06,448
OK.

152
00:21:09,544 --> 00:21:11,537
Papa loves you always.

153
00:21:12,088 --> 00:21:16,133
Now go back to school.
Your teachers will miss you.

154
00:21:16,218 --> 00:21:18,459
But I don't want to.

155
00:21:18,553 --> 00:21:21,673
Listen to Papa.
Run inside and don't look back.

156
00:21:21,765 --> 00:21:23,556
Why not?

157
00:21:23,642 --> 00:21:29,597
If you do I'll turn into stone. Now
on you go or you won't see me again.

158
00:21:29,689 --> 00:21:32,062
Promise you'll come visit
on New Years'?

159
00:21:33,443 --> 00:21:39,197
I'll count to three and you go in.
One, two, three!

160
00:21:59,344 --> 00:22:01,716
Don't move! Hands up!

161
00:22:56,359 --> 00:23:02,480
Heaven's up there. I'm here.
Then come the dogs.

162
00:23:03,158 --> 00:23:05,696
You're worse than a dog.

163
00:23:05,785 --> 00:23:08,703
Don't go against me again.

164
00:23:12,417 --> 00:23:14,955
Apologize! Go on!

165
00:23:16,796 --> 00:23:20,082
I was wrong. I'm sorry.

166
00:23:49,329 --> 00:23:53,279
My boss's business card.
I believe you've heard of him.

167
00:23:54,334 --> 00:23:58,711
He'll give you half a million
to lose the championship tomorrow.

168
00:23:58,797 --> 00:24:00,873
Be a good boy.

169
00:24:05,303 --> 00:24:08,637
He could beat me...
if he's good enough.

170
00:24:11,017 --> 00:24:15,311
Be a good kid and I'll guarantee you
plenty of dough.

171
00:24:34,624 --> 00:24:37,329
- How was it?
- A great success.

172
00:24:39,296 --> 00:24:40,790
Your shoes.

173
00:24:46,178 --> 00:24:49,297
You know better
than to wear these with me.

174
00:24:59,983 --> 00:25:02,556
Not bad. I've got the touch today.

175
00:26:19,604 --> 00:26:21,264
Think about it.

176
00:26:41,209 --> 00:26:42,620
Kiki!

177
00:26:42,711 --> 00:26:47,788
I'm sorry. I ran all the way.
Don't be mad at me.

178
00:26:47,883 --> 00:26:50,552
I'm so sorry, really.

179
00:26:56,016 --> 00:26:58,139
- I'm sorry.
- I forgive you.

180
00:27:02,772 --> 00:27:05,310
Let's grab a bite to eat.

181
00:27:12,532 --> 00:27:15,403
So you think you're a big shot?

182
00:27:17,454 --> 00:27:20,075
- What do you want?
- No, Kiki.

183
00:27:40,310 --> 00:27:41,769
Let go of her!

184
00:28:00,580 --> 00:28:02,656
Let's go.

185
00:28:03,583 --> 00:28:05,042
Kiki!

186
00:28:07,587 --> 00:28:09,129
Kiki!

187
00:28:09,923 --> 00:28:11,832
Someone help!

188
00:28:13,218 --> 00:28:15,009
Her kidney is badly damaged.

189
00:28:15,095 --> 00:28:18,261
You'll need $200,000
to cover her bills.

190
00:28:18,348 --> 00:28:23,093
If we don't operate now,
we may not be able to save her.

191
00:28:23,186 --> 00:28:25,973
Where can I get it at this hour?

192
00:28:26,064 --> 00:28:28,520
Doctor, can you do
the operation first?

193
00:28:28,608 --> 00:28:32,143
I'm sorry. Hospital policy.
I can't help you.

194
00:28:32,237 --> 00:28:34,146
Do what you can to raise the money.

195
00:28:39,953 --> 00:28:41,744
I'm out!

196
00:28:47,085 --> 00:28:48,793
What's your bet?

197
00:28:49,754 --> 00:28:51,664
It's all I've got.

198
00:28:53,633 --> 00:28:55,044
I call.

199
00:28:56,219 --> 00:28:59,220
I see you. Full house. I win.

200
00:29:07,522 --> 00:29:11,140
- See you.
- Hold it! Play a couple more.

201
00:29:11,651 --> 00:29:13,359
I've got to go.

202
00:29:13,445 --> 00:29:16,565
Bastard! You're a cheat!
You're a cheat!

203
00:29:16,656 --> 00:29:18,982
Hey, my brother says you're a cheat.

204
00:29:39,721 --> 00:29:41,548
Don't let him get away!

205
00:30:26,059 --> 00:30:28,894
I need this money.
Don't make me do it.

206
00:30:28,979 --> 00:30:30,556
You win.

207
00:30:54,754 --> 00:30:56,332
Boss, telephone.

208
00:31:08,351 --> 00:31:11,720
- Get back!
- Please cooperate. Stay back!

209
00:31:12,606 --> 00:31:14,946
- Back!
- He's my brother.

210
00:31:14,983 --> 00:31:18,434
- It's a police matter.
- Let me through!

211
00:31:25,911 --> 00:31:28,865
- Who did it?
- He's in the car.

212
00:31:30,832 --> 00:31:32,872
Boss! Boss!

213
00:31:32,959 --> 00:31:38,250
- What are you doing?
- You! Get out here! I said out!

214
00:31:38,381 --> 00:31:41,133
I'm going to kill you! Get out here!

215
00:31:42,344 --> 00:31:46,092
Come back here! Come back here! OK.

216
00:31:47,182 --> 00:31:50,017
- He killed Teddy.
- Quiet!

217
00:31:53,688 --> 00:31:57,140
No matter where he goes, he's dead.
Come on!

218
00:31:57,275 --> 00:32:02,151
On your clothing is a number. If you
forget it, it's ten days in the hole.

219
00:32:02,239 --> 00:32:03,816
Fighting is on Saturday afternoons.

220
00:32:03,907 --> 00:32:07,027
Any unsupervised fighting,
ten days in the hole.

221
00:32:07,118 --> 00:32:10,534
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.

222
00:32:10,622 --> 00:32:13,623
Never go against the officers!
Never try to escape!

223
00:32:13,708 --> 00:32:15,535
No raping of other inmates...

224
00:32:36,398 --> 00:32:39,731
Charlie, what are the odds
for tonight?

225
00:32:41,862 --> 00:32:44,981
No bet. Not tonight.

226
00:32:45,073 --> 00:32:46,484
Why not?

227
00:32:49,870 --> 00:32:54,828
That guy killed Boss Li's brother
Those other guys are in Li's gang.

228
00:32:55,709 --> 00:32:57,867
They're in the Ghost Shadow Gang.

229
00:32:57,961 --> 00:33:01,626
Word is they're going to kill
that guy Steve tonight.

230
00:34:58,707 --> 00:35:00,367
Those two!

231
00:35:02,752 --> 00:35:06,086
Let go of me! Let me at him!

232
00:35:06,464 --> 00:35:07,709
Calm down, Steve!

233
00:35:07,799 --> 00:35:10,836
- Let go!
- It's all right.

234
00:35:12,721 --> 00:35:14,132
Let me go.

235
00:35:15,891 --> 00:35:17,682
Let me go!

236
00:35:20,353 --> 00:35:23,722
- Take him to the sickroom.
- Yes, sir.

237
00:35:27,027 --> 00:35:30,859
Superintendent,
those guys were trying to kill Steve.

238
00:35:33,575 --> 00:35:38,071
No way, sir. Those guys were
fighting, we tried to separate them.

239
00:35:38,163 --> 00:35:40,736
Better tell the truth.

240
00:35:41,249 --> 00:35:45,164
It is the truth.
He's got the knife on him.

241
00:35:53,094 --> 00:35:56,677
- You're lying.
- No, he's not, Superintendent.

242
00:35:56,765 --> 00:35:59,303
I can prove he's telling the truth.

243
00:35:59,392 --> 00:36:01,468
Here's the knife they used.

244
00:36:06,608 --> 00:36:09,562
Listen up, no screwing up
in my place.

245
00:36:12,572 --> 00:36:15,277
- Take them in.
- Get going!

246
00:36:28,380 --> 00:36:30,253
Write me a report.

247
00:37:37,949 --> 00:37:39,858
You can come out now.

248
00:37:54,257 --> 00:37:55,668
Lucas.

249
00:37:59,137 --> 00:38:06,018
Don't screw up again. Going against
me is like going against God.

250
00:38:08,438 --> 00:38:10,929
We respect our God.

251
00:38:12,150 --> 00:38:15,649
We don't respect you.
There's no comparison.

252
00:38:32,420 --> 00:38:34,413
You're back!

253
00:38:44,766 --> 00:38:46,842
My brothers, never surrender!

254
00:39:09,416 --> 00:39:11,076
Come in.

255
00:39:16,756 --> 00:39:19,627
You asked for me, boss?

256
00:39:19,718 --> 00:39:21,295
Sit down.

257
00:39:31,104 --> 00:39:34,271
I hear you've been asking
about Carl Chan.

258
00:39:35,025 --> 00:39:36,852
- Are you an informer?
- No.

259
00:39:37,986 --> 00:39:40,109
I was looking at your hands.

260
00:39:40,197 --> 00:39:43,281
You've got a well developed
trigger finger.

261
00:39:43,366 --> 00:39:48,408
No one's heard of you.
So the way I see it, you're a snitch.

262
00:39:48,496 --> 00:39:49,825
I'm not!

263
00:39:51,833 --> 00:39:54,620
Talk! What is it with you?

264
00:39:56,505 --> 00:40:00,965
In the service, I was selected
for the Olympic shooting competition.

265
00:40:01,051 --> 00:40:04,471
- That's why I have strong hands.
- And Carl Chan?

266
00:40:04,507 --> 00:40:07,140
We served together in the army.

267
00:40:07,224 --> 00:40:09,893
He owes me some money.

268
00:40:09,976 --> 00:40:11,803
You're lying.

269
00:40:17,984 --> 00:40:24,948
Lucas! I won't yell out.
I won't get the guards after you.

270
00:40:25,951 --> 00:40:29,117
Please, believe me.

271
00:40:30,205 --> 00:40:31,616
Enough!

272
00:40:33,041 --> 00:40:38,664
If you're really here to settle a
debt, Carl Chan's dead so forget it.

273
00:40:38,755 --> 00:40:43,049
His slate is clean.
You watch what you're doing.

274
00:40:43,176 --> 00:40:46,213
Your life is in my hands.

275
00:40:50,350 --> 00:40:52,426
- Andy! Over here.
- Right.

276
00:40:52,519 --> 00:40:54,013
Oh, sorry.

277
00:40:56,815 --> 00:40:59,140
- Use your spoon.
- Yeah.

278
00:41:00,151 --> 00:41:02,025
What's wrong with your hand?

279
00:41:06,908 --> 00:41:09,150
I cut it in the shop.

280
00:41:09,244 --> 00:41:12,743
Oh, yeah?
No more food till I get the truth.

281
00:41:12,831 --> 00:41:15,867
Come get it
when you're ready to talk.

282
00:41:40,942 --> 00:41:43,729
Thanks, Lucas, but I'm being watched.

283
00:41:49,201 --> 00:41:51,952
- So you're great friends?
- No appetite.

284
00:41:53,205 --> 00:41:55,660
- Bring the rice pot.
- Yes, sir.

285
00:41:58,793 --> 00:42:00,751
Move!

286
00:42:04,090 --> 00:42:06,795
Now let's have some fun.

287
00:42:07,886 --> 00:42:12,714
You'd better eat it all,
or it's another ten days in the hole.

288
00:43:11,741 --> 00:43:14,114
Lucas, save some for me.

289
00:44:21,811 --> 00:44:24,896
You've all come here to work,
not to sunbathe!

290
00:44:26,441 --> 00:44:28,766
I won't tolerate any goofing around.

291
00:44:28,902 --> 00:44:33,113
If you're not able to complete the
road, there'll be no dinner tonight.

292
00:44:33,198 --> 00:44:37,776
Officer Chang, what if we finish
early? Can we break then?

293
00:44:38,245 --> 00:44:40,036
Finish early! And I'm a pig!

294
00:44:40,121 --> 00:44:44,534
There's no way you'll finish early.
Now get to work!

295
00:45:09,734 --> 00:45:13,981
Hey, friend, take it easy.
It's a long road.

296
00:45:14,072 --> 00:45:19,279
You heard what he said. If we finish
early, he'll turn into a pig.

297
00:45:22,163 --> 00:45:24,737
Hey, listen up.

298
00:45:24,875 --> 00:45:29,418
If we finish early, somebody
will turn into a pig! Come on!

299
00:45:40,098 --> 00:45:41,972
Come on! Come on!

300
00:45:59,117 --> 00:46:01,359
Come on, guys. Let's move it!

301
00:46:05,415 --> 00:46:06,957
Hurry it up!

302
00:46:08,126 --> 00:46:10,534
Some water, sir?

303
00:46:13,590 --> 00:46:15,915
- Are they crazy?
- I don't know.

304
00:46:16,051 --> 00:46:18,043
OK, let's go!

305
00:46:50,919 --> 00:46:53,836
Come on, brothers! We're almost done.

306
00:47:11,940 --> 00:47:15,558
Are they on drugs?
They're two hours ahead of schedule.

307
00:47:23,326 --> 00:47:25,817
Anyone here see an angry pig?

308
00:47:56,484 --> 00:47:58,477
Get in there, hurry up.

309
00:48:08,747 --> 00:48:11,831
Hey, did you see your son?

310
00:48:11,917 --> 00:48:13,708
Yeah.

311
00:48:19,090 --> 00:48:22,424
He's growing up so fast,
I hardly recognized him.

312
00:48:22,511 --> 00:48:25,796
I promised I'd visit him
at New Years'.

313
00:48:25,931 --> 00:48:28,303
Next time don't get caught.

314
00:48:28,391 --> 00:48:32,519
Every time they bring you back
and they give you another year.

315
00:48:32,604 --> 00:48:34,643
At this rate, you'll never get out.

316
00:48:34,731 --> 00:48:40,022
One day I'll escape for good. My son
and I will sail away on a boat.

317
00:48:40,111 --> 00:48:41,819
Where will you go?

318
00:48:41,905 --> 00:48:43,648
The Philippines.

319
00:48:43,740 --> 00:48:48,402
Living costs are low there.
A few dollars will get you a virgin.

320
00:48:48,495 --> 00:48:53,572
Keep her for a month and you get a
discount, and she does the housework.

321
00:48:53,667 --> 00:48:55,493
What do you want her for?

322
00:48:55,585 --> 00:49:00,164
The usual stuff, you know, cooking
and cleaning... that kind of thing.

323
00:49:00,257 --> 00:49:05,678
No wonder you want to escape. Let me
know if you get another chance.

324
00:49:05,762 --> 00:49:09,926
A live-in maid!
Now that's good for your health.

325
00:49:43,592 --> 00:49:46,758
Boss, sir. Glasses on.

326
00:49:51,141 --> 00:49:52,635
She's not wearing any bra.

327
00:49:52,726 --> 00:49:55,431
Boss, sir! Cleaning glasses.

328
00:50:01,568 --> 00:50:06,479
Dear Lord, whatever I've done wrong,
please don't strike me blind now.

329
00:50:07,157 --> 00:50:10,074
Oh, shit! I can't see anything
with these glasses.

330
00:50:10,160 --> 00:50:12,781
Boss, sir! Taking off glasses.

331
00:50:22,797 --> 00:50:24,956
Why don't any of you help me?

332
00:50:25,091 --> 00:50:27,250
Hey, John! Go help her.

333
00:50:27,344 --> 00:50:29,253
Yes, sir!

334
00:50:31,806 --> 00:50:33,846
- Hi, miss.
- Thank you.

335
00:50:33,934 --> 00:50:36,769
Don't mention it. It's no bother!

336
00:50:41,942 --> 00:50:44,100
- Are you all right?
- I'm OK.

337
00:50:44,194 --> 00:50:47,278
You can break my bones,
but don't strike me blind.

338
00:50:49,824 --> 00:50:54,202
Don't stand there. I need you
to push the car from over there.

339
00:50:54,287 --> 00:50:56,743
Lean against the window and rock it.

340
00:51:17,519 --> 00:51:19,013
All right, place your bets, gentlemen
on one, two or three.

341
00:51:22,357 --> 00:51:24,682
Hurry up, the race is about to start.

342
00:51:24,776 --> 00:51:27,979
Come on, place your bets,
then stand back.

343
00:51:28,071 --> 00:51:31,440
Come on, everyone,
place your bets here.

344
00:51:31,533 --> 00:51:32,612
Come on...

345
00:51:32,701 --> 00:51:36,117
Hey, John, how'd that girl look
up close? Was she fine?

346
00:51:36,204 --> 00:51:38,612
She was better than fine,
she was inspiring.

347
00:51:38,707 --> 00:51:41,910
I didn't need a jack
to change her tire.

348
00:51:42,002 --> 00:51:43,377
Really?

349
00:51:43,461 --> 00:51:45,086
Of course not.

350
00:51:45,505 --> 00:51:48,127
All right, all bets in. Ready...

351
00:51:49,259 --> 00:51:50,670
Go!

352
00:52:05,358 --> 00:52:08,941
You bet on number two
and you lost it all.

353
00:52:09,029 --> 00:52:10,938
Johnny, can I have just two?

354
00:52:11,031 --> 00:52:13,866
Two? Here!

355
00:52:15,619 --> 00:52:19,035
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...

356
00:52:19,122 --> 00:52:20,616
Li's man is out!

357
00:52:47,108 --> 00:52:51,355
In here I'm the boss.
I know all about you and Boss Li.

358
00:52:51,446 --> 00:52:55,396
But what happens on the outside
stays on the outside. Understand?

359
00:52:56,785 --> 00:53:00,284
When you're in here,
it doesn't matter who you are.

360
00:53:00,956 --> 00:53:02,995
We're all together in this.

361
00:53:04,000 --> 00:53:06,954
I don't want any feuds in here.

362
00:53:07,045 --> 00:53:11,043
Lucas, Boss Li's brother's dead.
It's blood for blood.

363
00:53:22,519 --> 00:53:25,354
I'll bleed for him.

364
00:53:42,539 --> 00:53:44,366
Andy, have you seen my mouse?

365
00:53:44,457 --> 00:53:46,830
Maybe he's asleep
in the mattress again.

366
00:53:46,918 --> 00:53:48,958
I'll help you look after we eat.

367
00:53:51,047 --> 00:53:54,333
- Thanks.
- Hey, that's not enough.

368
00:54:22,954 --> 00:54:24,698
Why?

369
00:54:24,956 --> 00:54:30,543
Why? Why? Why did you do it?
Why did you do it to him?

370
00:54:39,387 --> 00:54:40,882
He cooked my mouse!

371
00:54:49,231 --> 00:54:50,974
In the hole with him.

372
00:55:27,602 --> 00:55:29,511
Here, I got it!

373
00:55:31,773 --> 00:55:33,730
Better keep away from him.

374
00:56:03,805 --> 00:56:06,759
Here, take this. I'm not hungry.

375
00:56:17,235 --> 00:56:19,524
Boss? I got to do the business.

376
00:56:19,613 --> 00:56:22,863
Great timing!
Make sure you go downwind.

377
00:56:22,949 --> 00:56:26,069
- Let me know where you are.
- Yes, sir.

378
00:56:44,221 --> 00:56:46,628
Shoot.

379
00:56:51,561 --> 00:56:53,803
I'm here! I'm here!

380
00:57:00,195 --> 00:57:02,816
I'm still here! I'm still shitting!

381
00:57:03,949 --> 00:57:07,365
Don't tell me that, just shake
the grass. We're eating here!

382
00:57:07,452 --> 00:57:11,450
OK, I'm moving the grass now, boss.

383
00:57:49,327 --> 00:57:52,114
Don't let him get away! After him!

384
00:58:02,966 --> 00:58:06,300
Maybe we can find ourselves
a boat at dawn.

385
00:58:07,679 --> 00:58:12,140
I heard your son broke his leg
playing football. Is he all right?

386
00:58:12,225 --> 00:58:15,428
He's a kid.
He'll be fine in a few days.

387
00:58:16,104 --> 00:58:19,769
It's almost New Year. Time flies.

388
00:58:19,858 --> 00:58:22,693
Yeah, time flies.

389
00:58:38,585 --> 00:58:39,783
Why?

390
00:58:39,878 --> 00:58:46,082
I'm sorry. I had to see my son.
I promised I'd see him at New Years'.

391
00:58:46,176 --> 00:58:50,968
They said I could if we turned
ourselves in. Nothing will happen.

392
00:59:17,707 --> 00:59:20,377
Lucas! Lucas!

393
00:59:21,628 --> 00:59:26,586
Why? Why? You said we'd just get
a few days in the hole!

394
00:59:26,675 --> 00:59:29,960
I don't negotiate with convicts.

395
00:59:30,053 --> 00:59:32,129
- Take him away.
- Yes, sir.

396
00:59:33,640 --> 00:59:35,514
I'll report you!

397
00:59:36,893 --> 00:59:39,598
I don't think
you'll be seeing your son.

398
00:59:39,688 --> 00:59:44,563
And if anyone hears you sold Lucas
out, you'll die a terrible death.

399
00:59:44,651 --> 00:59:47,522
- Get him out of here!
- Come on!

400
01:00:05,505 --> 01:00:08,542
Wake up! Everybody up! Wake up!

401
01:00:08,675 --> 01:00:10,383
Come on!

402
01:00:42,375 --> 01:00:45,460
This is what happens
when you break the rules.

403
01:00:45,545 --> 01:00:48,914
Even though John went along
with Lucas' escape plan,

404
01:00:49,007 --> 01:00:53,052
when we caught up with him,
he surrendered and said he was sorry.

405
01:00:53,345 --> 01:00:57,129
He went for the sake
of his son's broken leg.

406
01:00:57,224 --> 01:01:01,056
We forgive him. We are not
as unreasonable as you think.

407
01:01:01,144 --> 01:01:05,806
We'll be watching him closely and if
he behaves, we'll forget about this.

408
01:01:33,677 --> 01:01:36,678
A potato a day won't make you fat,

409
01:01:36,763 --> 01:01:39,847
but will keep you healthy to fight
another day - Charlie.

410
01:02:08,670 --> 01:02:11,873
Boss, Eddie's out of jail.
He's in the back room.

411
01:02:13,216 --> 01:02:15,125
I'll go talk to him.

412
01:02:27,772 --> 01:02:31,391
Sit down. How's everything?

413
01:02:31,484 --> 01:02:36,146
Steve's not dead, he's injured so
they're keeping him in the sickroom.

414
01:02:36,239 --> 01:02:37,650
We couldn't get him.

415
01:02:38,533 --> 01:02:40,193
What are my men doing?

416
01:02:40,285 --> 01:02:43,072
It seems as if Lucas got involved.

417
01:02:44,539 --> 01:02:48,584
Brother, Eddie just got out of jail.
Make him comfortable.

418
01:02:48,668 --> 01:02:51,373
Alfred, get Eddie set up
in the casino.

419
01:02:51,463 --> 01:02:53,254
- Enjoy yourself.
- Thanks.

420
01:02:55,717 --> 01:02:57,128
Well?

421
01:03:00,222 --> 01:03:03,756
- What is it?
- That bastard Steve.

422
01:03:03,850 --> 01:03:06,341
He's still alive and walking around.

423
01:03:07,687 --> 01:03:09,597
God dammit!

424
01:03:10,398 --> 01:03:12,557
Teddy died for nothing.

425
01:03:12,651 --> 01:03:14,939
That bastard!

426
01:03:21,159 --> 01:03:23,199
Boss, let me do it!

427
01:03:39,928 --> 01:03:41,671
Some water, sir?

428
01:03:45,559 --> 01:03:48,050
Here, boss, have some more noodles.

429
01:03:53,567 --> 01:03:56,402
You eat. I'll do this.

430
01:03:56,486 --> 01:03:58,278
Snake! Snake!

431
01:04:02,325 --> 01:04:03,903
Go!

432
01:04:33,523 --> 01:04:35,516
Freddy's dead.

433
01:04:36,902 --> 01:04:39,440
- Get him out, hurry!
- Yes, sir.

434
01:05:14,397 --> 01:05:18,810
Prisoner John Liu escaped three times
during his incarceration.

435
01:05:18,902 --> 01:05:21,440
Additional punishment
proved no deterrent.

436
01:05:21,530 --> 01:05:26,904
Furthermore, he caused the death
of corrections officer, Freddy Tang.

437
01:05:26,993 --> 01:05:30,825
The judgment of this court
is that he be executed forthwith.

438
01:06:10,829 --> 01:06:13,450
ID cards everyone. Come on.

439
01:06:14,624 --> 01:06:16,118
Get in line.

440
01:06:16,209 --> 01:06:18,368
Lieutenant, what's up?

441
01:06:24,718 --> 01:06:26,924
Inspector, what's all this about?

442
01:06:27,012 --> 01:06:28,921
Routine check.

443
01:06:29,014 --> 01:06:30,757
Oh, yeah? Why now?

444
01:06:32,142 --> 01:06:36,887
You only gave my daughter $5,000
as a wedding gift.

445
01:06:40,317 --> 01:06:42,808
If I check here often,
you lose business.

446
01:06:42,903 --> 01:06:45,228
You lose business, you lose money.

447
01:06:48,158 --> 01:06:53,401
This is a nice place. It'd be a real
shame to have to close it down.

448
01:06:53,496 --> 01:06:55,323
Really sad.

449
01:06:56,499 --> 01:06:59,500
OK, how much do you want?

450
01:07:00,962 --> 01:07:04,082
Five hundred dollars and two zeros.

451
01:07:08,595 --> 01:07:12,806
All right, I'll pay you.
Come with me.

452
01:07:22,192 --> 01:07:24,398
Hey, brother, what's up?

453
01:07:25,403 --> 01:07:28,357
- Make him out a cheque for $50,000.
- Right.

454
01:07:55,851 --> 01:08:00,014
We're all good friends here.
You can't come between us.

455
01:08:02,899 --> 01:08:07,976
Now, listen. Choose a day
and I'll take you out to dinner.

456
01:08:08,864 --> 01:08:10,274
I, ah...

457
01:08:12,450 --> 01:08:14,776
I think I'll come back tomorrow.

458
01:08:22,544 --> 01:08:26,755
What did you do that for?
I thought we were friends.

459
01:08:26,840 --> 01:08:31,217
No need to fight. A zero here
or there, what does it matter?

460
01:08:36,808 --> 01:08:40,391
I'm sorry we made you suffer.

461
01:08:41,730 --> 01:08:45,810
I just need to get into the jail.
Thank you.

462
01:08:47,944 --> 01:08:49,818
The cheque.

463
01:08:52,741 --> 01:08:58,945
$50,000- less a zero or two. You're
going to do this favor for me.

464
01:08:59,039 --> 01:09:01,364
- All right?
- All right.

465
01:09:10,592 --> 01:09:12,051
Lock him up.

466
01:09:14,763 --> 01:09:17,468
- Let's go.
- Move out.

467
01:09:18,225 --> 01:09:19,849
Wait a second.

468
01:09:21,311 --> 01:09:24,680
- Brother, look after the place.
- Be careful.

469
01:09:25,690 --> 01:09:27,101
It's over.

470
01:09:27,567 --> 01:09:29,192
Open up.

471
01:09:30,737 --> 01:09:32,730
These are the rules.

472
01:09:32,822 --> 01:09:37,484
On your clothing is a number, forget
it and it's ten days in the hole.

473
01:09:37,577 --> 01:09:39,543
Fighting is on Saturday afternoon.

474
01:09:39,579 --> 01:09:43,103
Any unsupervised fighting -
ten days in the hole.

475
01:09:43,139 --> 01:09:46,627
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.

476
01:09:46,711 --> 01:09:50,045
Never go against the officers.
never try to escape.

477
01:09:50,131 --> 01:09:52,883
No raping of other inmates.
No breaking of fixtures.

478
01:09:52,968 --> 01:09:55,174
Six months hard labor
for these offences.

479
01:09:55,262 --> 01:09:58,678
Ten days in the hole
for smoking in bed.

480
01:09:58,765 --> 01:10:01,434
Every Saturday,
you'll receive one clean sheet.

481
01:10:01,518 --> 01:10:04,009
Send your bottom sheet
to the laundry.

482
01:10:04,104 --> 01:10:06,677
Make a mistake -
ten days in the hole.

483
01:10:06,773 --> 01:10:11,482
Memorize these rules. If you forget
them, ten days in the hole.

484
01:10:11,570 --> 01:10:14,736
This is your cell.
Any questions, ask me.

485
01:10:40,307 --> 01:10:43,261
He's still alive
because of your cowardice.

486
01:10:43,351 --> 01:10:45,925
- You don't understand.
- Yes, I do.

487
01:11:04,748 --> 01:11:08,247
My bet's on you.
Eat and get strong for the fight.

488
01:11:26,228 --> 01:11:30,177
Mr. Li, your brother's death was
an accident. I want to apologize.

489
01:11:32,484 --> 01:11:37,609
My little brother is dead.
Nothing you say can change that.

490
01:11:39,533 --> 01:11:44,159
I had intended killing
your girlfriend to get in here.

491
01:11:45,872 --> 01:11:49,490
But she couldn't wait around.
She's already dead.

492
01:11:52,212 --> 01:11:53,706
You're lying.

493
01:11:55,715 --> 01:11:59,630
They wouldn't tell you
cos it's not good for morale.

494
01:12:00,929 --> 01:12:03,800
It was up to me to let you know.

495
01:12:04,516 --> 01:12:10,186
I want you to feel the agony.
I'll kill you when I'm ready.

496
01:12:36,173 --> 01:12:37,999
Who are you betting on?

497
01:14:54,769 --> 01:14:56,513
Kill him!

498
01:15:00,859 --> 01:15:02,851
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!

499
01:15:08,158 --> 01:15:11,990
Go on, you can do it. Kill again.

500
01:15:13,038 --> 01:15:15,196
Don't do it, Steve!

501
01:15:18,376 --> 01:15:20,001
Don't do it!

502
01:15:22,714 --> 01:15:24,872
Kill him!

503
01:15:49,157 --> 01:15:51,446
Stand back.

504
01:15:57,332 --> 01:16:01,709
Don't! If you do, I'll report you.

505
01:16:04,130 --> 01:16:06,538
- Take him away!
- Yes, sir.

506
01:16:31,408 --> 01:16:33,400
"Happy New Year"

507
01:16:58,852 --> 01:17:00,263
Sit down.

508
01:17:54,699 --> 01:17:56,657
Try your luck.

509
01:17:56,743 --> 01:17:58,736
I'll get some money.

510
01:17:58,828 --> 01:18:00,204
Take mine.

511
01:18:00,288 --> 01:18:03,491
- Thanks. I'll get my own.
- OK, but hurry.

512
01:18:28,859 --> 01:18:32,144
Charlie! Let me go!

513
01:18:32,279 --> 01:18:34,948
Let me go! Let me go!

514
01:18:52,757 --> 01:18:54,300
You bastard!

515
01:19:00,515 --> 01:19:03,635
Why? Why? Why?

516
01:19:04,561 --> 01:19:09,270
Why? Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?

517
01:19:09,441 --> 01:19:12,442
It was him...

518
01:19:22,120 --> 01:19:25,703
- Get this murderer out of here.
- Yes, sir.

519
01:19:25,790 --> 01:19:32,789
No! No! You're just trying to shut
me up! You told me to kill Andy.

520
01:19:32,881 --> 01:19:37,543
Charlie was a mistake.
You're trying to frame me!

521
01:20:57,716 --> 01:21:01,583
Inmate Andy Wong was cited for bad
conduct during his prison term.

522
01:21:01,678 --> 01:21:05,592
He has been found guilty of murder
in the first degree.

523
01:21:05,849 --> 01:21:08,174
It is the high court's decision

524
01:21:08,268 --> 01:21:12,135
that Andy Wong shall be executed
by firing squad.

525
01:22:18,088 --> 01:22:20,460
This is your funeral.

526
01:22:20,549 --> 01:22:22,422
That's where you're buried.

527
01:22:23,301 --> 01:22:24,843
Here's your death certificate.

528
01:22:27,931 --> 01:22:30,504
We've kept you alive to work for us.

529
01:22:30,642 --> 01:22:33,762
You're now a member
of the Executive Committee.

530
01:22:33,895 --> 01:22:36,565
We've been watching you
for a long time.

531
01:22:36,648 --> 01:22:40,231
You're a survivor with a strong sense
of justice, though misguided.

532
01:22:40,318 --> 01:22:46,404
Society is becoming complex. There
are too many criminals on the street.

533
01:22:46,491 --> 01:22:48,863
And too many loopholes.

534
01:22:48,952 --> 01:22:52,819
They always seem to find a way
to escape punishment.

535
01:22:52,914 --> 01:22:55,322
The Executive Committee
is in existence

536
01:22:55,417 --> 01:22:57,990
solely to deal with these criminals.

537
01:22:58,086 --> 01:23:02,131
Blood begets blood,
filth begets filth.

538
01:23:03,258 --> 01:23:07,303
Your Government has given you
the honor of joining this team.

539
01:23:07,804 --> 01:23:09,713
When your assignment is through,

540
01:23:09,806 --> 01:23:13,222
we'll give you a passport
and a new identity.

541
01:23:13,935 --> 01:23:18,272
You can go anywhere you want -
start all over again.

542
01:23:18,308 --> 01:23:22,609
In fact, you don't have a choice.
You're already dead.

543
01:23:22,694 --> 01:23:26,145
This is your only chance.
This mission is your life.

544
01:23:54,351 --> 01:23:58,479
This assignment is an assassination.
The target is Colonel Sama.

545
01:23:58,563 --> 01:24:01,185
The biggest drug dealer
in Southeast Asia.

546
01:24:01,274 --> 01:24:03,563
He's being brought in to stand trial.

547
01:24:03,652 --> 01:24:06,771
But we know he's paid off
all the judges.

548
01:24:06,863 --> 01:24:11,406
Before he boards his plane,
we must execute him.

549
01:24:11,493 --> 01:24:15,407
Each of you has been issued two guns.

550
01:24:15,497 --> 01:24:17,573
When you have accomplished
your mission,

551
01:24:17,666 --> 01:24:24,202
you'll find a jeep waiting for you
directly behind you, 800 meters away.

552
01:24:24,297 --> 01:24:26,788
Leave immediately.

553
01:24:27,300 --> 01:24:29,589
Someone will meet you at the gate

554
01:24:29,678 --> 01:24:32,513
and give you your passports
and airline tickets.

555
01:25:44,211 --> 01:25:45,669
Let's go!

556
01:25:53,970 --> 01:25:56,010
Come on, get in!

557
01:25:58,016 --> 01:26:01,350
There's a bomb in the car. Jump!

558
01:29:31,980 --> 01:29:38,777
Hey! Hold it! If I...
I promised my son I'd see him again.

559
01:29:39,362 --> 01:29:41,521
Move it! You piece of shit!

560
01:30:28,036 --> 01:30:29,827
Come on!

561
01:30:43,009 --> 01:30:45,927
Hurry! Get in!

562
01:30:52,519 --> 01:30:54,393
Tell him to slow down.

563
01:30:54,479 --> 01:30:57,931
- Tell them to hurry up!
- Hurry! Quickly!

564
01:30:58,483 --> 01:31:00,310
Faster!

565
01:32:05,467 --> 01:32:08,172
Hey, Chief, looking for your gun?

566
01:32:10,889 --> 01:32:14,009
Executive Committee member
number 24 reporting.

567
01:32:14,100 --> 01:32:16,888
Well done, good job.

568
01:32:16,978 --> 01:32:19,137
I'll get you your new passport.

569
01:32:19,231 --> 01:32:21,603
You're free.

570
01:32:24,402 --> 01:32:27,522
Using dead convicts to work for you.

571
01:32:27,614 --> 01:32:30,235
Then killing them
when they're through.

572
01:32:31,117 --> 01:32:33,276
A very clever plan.

573
01:32:33,370 --> 01:32:36,489
You didn't realize
I'd come back alive.

574
01:32:36,581 --> 01:32:42,370
I knew you would. I'll give you some
money, you can go wherever you want.

575
01:32:42,462 --> 01:32:45,878
No one will be the wiser.
What do you say?

576
01:32:48,051 --> 01:32:50,340
That's a real good plan.

577
01:32:53,348 --> 01:32:55,388
There's just one thing...

578
01:32:55,725 --> 01:32:57,683
Why did you do it?

579
01:32:59,729 --> 01:33:04,023
That drug dealer was my partner.
I'd be dead if he testified.

580
01:33:04,776 --> 01:33:08,110
What about Professor Leung?
Why did you kill him?

581
01:33:11,074 --> 01:33:15,487
He was investigating me
and he was getting too close.

582
01:33:22,335 --> 01:33:24,494
Here they are.

583
01:33:35,682 --> 01:33:40,807
It's a lot of money. And tomorrow
I can send you a lot more.

584
01:33:40,896 --> 01:33:42,390
It's all yours, Andy.

585
01:33:42,480 --> 01:33:44,354
You make me sick.

586
01:33:44,441 --> 01:33:46,350
So many good men killed.

587
01:33:46,443 --> 01:33:49,527
Aw, Andy, don't be stupid.

588
01:33:49,613 --> 01:33:52,483
You couldn't earn this much money
in a lifetime.

589
01:33:52,574 --> 01:33:55,741
Thousands die every day, what
difference does a few more make?

590
01:33:55,827 --> 01:33:59,991
What difference?
Can you pay for all of them?

591
01:34:00,081 --> 01:34:02,074
The price is too high!

592
01:34:03,877 --> 01:34:08,622
Bastard! I serve God, not you.
I'm going to kill you!

593
01:34:08,715 --> 01:34:11,882
Andy! Don't.

