1
00:01:14,405 --> 00:01:16,428
Mr. Tang Shu-be, the Deputy Secretary
for Mainland Affairs Association

2
00:01:16,472 --> 00:01:20,766
becomes the first communist
to visit Taiwan

3
00:01:20,804 --> 00:01:24,498
He'll be arriving at Chung Ching
International Airport this 15:52

4
00:01:24,538 --> 00:01:26,731
People supporting the Independence
for Taiwan movement

5
00:01:26,771 --> 00:01:30,396
and those who support unity of
the two shores are staging a riot

6
00:01:30,438 --> 00:01:33,370
Which resulted in a massive fight

7
00:01:34,937 --> 00:01:44,893
Against corrupted China
Taiwanese cheer up...

8
00:01:46,104 --> 00:01:48,592
I am thankful to the Taiwan Police Force

9
00:01:48,637 --> 00:01:52,330
What I see at the airport

10
00:01:52,370 --> 00:01:55,529
is not a courteous way
to receive a guest

11
00:02:41,834 --> 00:02:43,299
Get ready

12
00:02:45,167 --> 00:02:46,030
Quick

13
00:02:50,167 --> 00:02:51,962
Cheer up! Cheer up

14
00:02:52,599 --> 00:02:54,689
Cheer up...

15
00:03:15,165 --> 00:03:16,460
Chung-shu

16
00:03:16,497 --> 00:03:17,258
Tell me...

17
00:03:17,297 --> 00:03:19,991
why the party should nominate you

18
00:03:20,798 --> 00:03:22,355
Because I love Taiwan

19
00:03:22,398 --> 00:03:23,454
I am loyal to the party

20
00:03:23,497 --> 00:03:24,156
I love the party

21
00:03:24,197 --> 00:03:25,390
I am loyal to the chairman

22
00:03:25,431 --> 00:03:26,125
I am loyal to you

23
00:03:26,164 --> 00:03:27,130
I love you

24
00:03:30,030 --> 00:03:31,155
Thank you so much!

25
00:03:32,297 --> 00:03:34,025
Chiu-sen, why should we nominate you?

26
00:03:34,298 --> 00:03:36,285
One reason, if you nominate me, I'll win

27
00:03:36,329 --> 00:03:38,625
If you nominate him, he will lose

28
00:03:38,663 --> 00:03:42,289
So, the seat will be taken
by the other party

29
00:03:43,230 --> 00:03:44,253
You're right

30
00:03:45,262 --> 00:03:46,956
The boss shares the same
point of view with you

31
00:03:48,163 --> 00:03:51,186
In fact, we are inclined to nominate you

32
00:03:53,762 --> 00:03:56,956
Chung-shu, how much have you spent
on the election so far?

33
00:03:57,395 --> 00:03:58,622
About 15 million

34
00:04:00,228 --> 00:04:03,320
Chiu-sen, send him 20 million
within three days

35
00:04:03,929 --> 00:04:05,985
And then send a sum of money to the boss

36
00:04:06,628 --> 00:04:09,220
I'll tell you the exact amount

37
00:04:10,861 --> 00:04:12,157
Thank you, Chairman

38
00:04:14,895 --> 00:04:17,122
Go back and settle your gang

39
00:04:17,161 --> 00:04:19,252
Don't lose your cool
and get into trouble

40
00:04:20,127 --> 00:04:22,752
Chung-shu, it's settled
wait for the next election

41
00:04:23,094 --> 00:04:24,651
Don't you have any hard feeling

42
00:04:37,893 --> 00:04:39,484
I won't yield

43
00:05:46,056 --> 00:05:48,614
A nationwide raid against triad code named
1st Liquidation was conducted in 1989

44
00:05:48,922 --> 00:05:51,252
Chau Chiu-sen was put behind
bars for five years

45
00:05:51,955 --> 00:05:55,853
Now, he is an entrepreneur with
a net worth of over NT$3 billion

46
00:05:57,422 --> 00:06:01,252
Let's focus on
his electronic games business

47
00:06:01,288 --> 00:06:06,311
He has 38 electronic game shops
which are actually underground casinos

48
00:06:06,688 --> 00:06:09,176
With a daily turnover of
fifty million NT dollars

49
00:06:09,221 --> 00:06:10,879
He is bigger than Mcdonald's

50
00:06:11,387 --> 00:06:16,944
Approximately half of his revenue goes
into bribery for government officials

51
00:06:17,754 --> 00:06:18,685
This big boss

52
00:06:19,087 --> 00:06:20,950
Being the head of the Sung-lin Gang

53
00:06:21,653 --> 00:06:23,881
Now wants to enter politics

54
00:06:23,920 --> 00:06:25,408
He has enrolled as a candidate for
the coming Legislative Council election

55
00:06:27,987 --> 00:06:29,976
There is a government practice

56
00:06:30,020 --> 00:06:32,610
Once a person becomes a legislative
councilor, he is above the law

57
00:06:33,585 --> 00:06:35,142
Even his seedy past will be buried

58
00:06:35,987 --> 00:06:36,884
It doesn't make sense

59
00:06:37,353 --> 00:06:39,285
So? Let's do something about it

60
00:06:39,719 --> 00:06:41,049
Let's stop him

61
00:06:42,952 --> 00:06:45,349
As for the corrupted departments...

62
00:06:46,285 --> 00:06:49,377
Let's wait for the right time to act

63
00:06:49,420 --> 00:06:51,181
Because it involves too many officials

64
00:06:52,518 --> 00:06:54,711
Be patient

65
00:06:57,252 --> 00:06:58,842
Yes sir, I know the importance of timing

66
00:06:59,285 --> 00:07:02,443
I am proud to have you as my student

67
00:07:24,050 --> 00:07:26,073
So many expensive cars are parked here!

68
00:07:31,116 --> 00:07:32,139
Thank you

69
00:07:50,515 --> 00:07:51,379
Welcome...

70
00:07:51,748 --> 00:07:54,441
Dear customers

71
00:07:54,481 --> 00:07:57,878
Grab a seat quickly...

72
00:07:57,914 --> 00:08:00,210
The sooner you put a bet on
the sooner you can win

73
00:08:08,747 --> 00:08:11,508
Damn you bastard!
All you care about is gambling

74
00:08:34,179 --> 00:08:35,008
Congratulations...

75
00:08:35,046 --> 00:08:38,535
You've won the jackpot!

76
00:08:38,579 --> 00:08:40,441
You've won an electric rice cooker

77
00:08:40,478 --> 00:08:43,672
This is filled with
gambling electronic games

78
00:08:44,178 --> 00:08:46,201
Call the police

79
00:08:51,911 --> 00:08:52,673
Sorry

80
00:08:56,444 --> 00:08:59,877
The cars parked outside are too expensive
ride for this crowd

81
00:08:59,911 --> 00:09:02,241
Fong, the police said they've just
finished their routine inspection

82
00:09:02,277 --> 00:09:04,334
They said that this shop is legally run

83
00:09:04,377 --> 00:09:06,036
They rejected our case

84
00:09:07,777 --> 00:09:10,300
Call again, tell them someone is
trafficking drugs here

85
00:09:17,276 --> 00:09:18,605
"Staff only"

86
00:09:19,343 --> 00:09:21,206
Only members are allowed to enter

87
00:09:27,808 --> 00:09:31,207
Welcome

88
00:09:44,975 --> 00:09:49,497
The couple who have just entered
are using membership card number JKO843

89
00:09:49,540 --> 00:09:50,598
But this card was reported lost
a few days ago

90
00:09:59,807 --> 00:10:03,671
This game is specially designed for you

91
00:10:03,707 --> 00:10:06,003
It brings extraordinary excitement...

92
00:10:06,041 --> 00:10:08,200
There will be six participants
appearing on screen

93
00:10:08,241 --> 00:10:11,467
Their horoscope signs, blood type
and physical condition will be shown

94
00:10:11,506 --> 00:10:16,633
Push the right button to place a bet

95
00:10:16,673 --> 00:10:19,434
The maximum bet is 50 points
minimum bet is 1 point

96
00:10:19,472 --> 00:10:22,199
The dividend paid is shown on the screen

97
00:10:22,239 --> 00:10:23,830
Good luck

98
00:10:27,739 --> 00:10:28,228
Police raid

99
00:10:29,106 --> 00:10:31,230
Change the boards at once

100
00:10:31,271 --> 00:10:32,532
Change the board

101
00:10:38,039 --> 00:10:41,368
It's alright, go on...

102
00:10:41,405 --> 00:10:42,837
Routine inspection only

103
00:10:43,338 --> 00:10:44,167
Miss

104
00:10:45,405 --> 00:10:46,598
May I buy you a drink?

105
00:10:49,505 --> 00:10:50,436
They're in trouble

106
00:10:53,070 --> 00:10:54,297
Ask him to hang on for ten more minutes

107
00:10:54,970 --> 00:10:56,699
Fong said to give him 10 more minutes

108
00:10:56,737 --> 00:10:57,760
Good luck

109
00:10:58,604 --> 00:10:59,400
Nice to meet you

110
00:11:01,070 --> 00:11:02,467
Some coca cola?

111
00:11:06,936 --> 00:11:07,902
You're so kind

112
00:11:07,936 --> 00:11:08,765
My pleasure

113
00:11:19,037 --> 00:11:22,297
We received a report that
you are selling amphetamine

114
00:11:23,635 --> 00:11:27,863
Must be sore losers

115
00:11:28,336 --> 00:11:31,426
Tso, we are making
so much money here already

116
00:11:31,468 --> 00:11:33,491
Why do we want to sell drugs?

117
00:11:33,769 --> 00:11:36,928
We can provide them for free

118
00:11:36,968 --> 00:11:38,195
We never sold any drugs

119
00:11:38,235 --> 00:11:40,701
Captain
two small sized electric cookers

120
00:11:44,000 --> 00:11:45,023
It's too small!

121
00:11:45,933 --> 00:11:47,161
Bring two big ones

122
00:11:55,833 --> 00:11:57,265
Go exchange them for money

123
00:12:01,534 --> 00:12:02,864
Ah Koon, you go do it

124
00:12:02,901 --> 00:12:04,160
I'm in uniform
maybe it's not a good idea

125
00:12:18,499 --> 00:12:20,829
Two big electric cookers
are worth $200,000

126
00:12:20,866 --> 00:12:22,229
Wait, I'll get the right sum

127
00:12:23,166 --> 00:12:24,131
Two hundred thousand

128
00:12:25,365 --> 00:12:26,194
You count it

129
00:12:30,599 --> 00:12:31,963
He stole my cooker

130
00:12:35,897 --> 00:12:37,921
Alright, stop it, just tell them

131
00:13:09,130 --> 00:13:09,686
Run!

132
00:13:27,861 --> 00:13:28,987
May Li, move

133
00:13:31,395 --> 00:13:33,486
Go down this stairs and then turn left

134
00:13:33,961 --> 00:13:36,053
Turn right and walk for 30 meters

135
00:13:40,961 --> 00:13:42,586
Turn left, walk 23 meters

136
00:13:54,093 --> 00:13:54,786
Where are we?

137
00:13:54,826 --> 00:13:55,485
I can't open it

138
00:13:55,527 --> 00:13:56,515
You can't open it?

139
00:13:57,726 --> 00:13:58,385
Are we at the right place?

140
00:13:58,426 --> 00:13:59,722
Open the door, if you see water
then it's the right exit

141
00:14:11,358 --> 00:14:12,416
Over there! Move over there

142
00:14:13,226 --> 00:14:14,021
Go!

143
00:14:30,891 --> 00:14:32,015
It hurts!

144
00:14:32,057 --> 00:14:33,853
Be gentle!

145
00:14:34,991 --> 00:14:35,888
Don't be naughty

146
00:14:38,191 --> 00:14:39,815
Let go of me!

147
00:14:39,857 --> 00:14:40,686
Please be gentle...

148
00:14:40,857 --> 00:14:42,414
It hurts!

149
00:15:04,756 --> 00:15:07,847
Sir, you should get a massage
more regularly

150
00:15:07,889 --> 00:15:09,377
Your health is poor

151
00:15:10,123 --> 00:15:11,679
Really?

152
00:15:11,822 --> 00:15:13,014
When I press the pressure points
and he feels great pain

153
00:15:13,055 --> 00:15:14,385
That means those parts of his body
are in bad shape

154
00:15:15,788 --> 00:15:17,812
So how come he is
not screaming like I am?

155
00:15:17,856 --> 00:15:19,481
His health must be much better than mine

156
00:15:19,956 --> 00:15:21,511
No, it's only because
he has a strong mind

157
00:15:21,554 --> 00:15:22,679
He can tolerate great pain

158
00:15:23,588 --> 00:15:24,611
Tell us about
the strong parts of his body

159
00:15:25,255 --> 00:15:27,686
Tell us

160
00:15:28,122 --> 00:15:29,951
Why talk about
the strong parts of his body?

161
00:15:30,321 --> 00:15:32,651
His weakest organ is his kidney

162
00:15:33,588 --> 00:15:35,610
When I pressed the point
which reflects your kidneys

163
00:15:35,653 --> 00:15:38,245
It must hurt so much
you want to piss in your pants

164
00:15:41,854 --> 00:15:43,876
I can hear the ladies laughing

165
00:15:43,919 --> 00:15:45,646
That reconfirms that you've a weak kidney
which is already affecting your sex life

166
00:15:45,686 --> 00:15:47,653
I am sure I have the right diagnosis

167
00:15:54,353 --> 00:15:56,148
You're so generous!

168
00:15:56,719 --> 00:15:58,242
Do you know what this is?

169
00:15:59,853 --> 00:16:02,751
A nutcracker

170
00:16:02,786 --> 00:16:04,615
Apart from cracking nuts
it's a very versatile tool

171
00:16:04,652 --> 00:16:08,709
Yeah, I also use this when I eat crabs

172
00:16:17,418 --> 00:16:19,475
San-pao, take him to the toilet

173
00:16:20,385 --> 00:16:21,975
Take off his trousers

174
00:16:22,018 --> 00:16:24,075
Crack his nuts...

175
00:16:24,118 --> 00:16:26,243
So he understands how
a depressed sex life feels like

176
00:16:26,284 --> 00:16:27,147
Take him away

177
00:16:30,852 --> 00:16:34,112
Chinese people said
blind people are usually smart

178
00:16:34,550 --> 00:16:36,981
He must be the exception

179
00:16:37,817 --> 00:16:38,874
That's right

180
00:16:41,250 --> 00:16:42,181
Come on...

181
00:16:46,649 --> 00:16:48,274
This case will determine the legitimacy
of the electronic game business

182
00:16:48,316 --> 00:16:50,646
Whether it can legally exist in Taiwan

183
00:16:53,650 --> 00:16:54,875
Welcome, welcome!

184
00:16:56,548 --> 00:16:57,912
Playing electronic game isn't gambling

185
00:16:57,949 --> 00:16:59,074
We support Mr. Chau

186
00:16:59,116 --> 00:17:00,275
Playing electronic game isn't gambling

187
00:17:00,316 --> 00:17:01,441
We support Mr. Chau

188
00:17:01,483 --> 00:17:05,346
Playing electronic game isn't gambling...

189
00:17:05,382 --> 00:17:07,315
Mr. Chau, what is your view?

190
00:17:22,648 --> 00:17:23,443
Here comes Mr. Chau

191
00:17:27,114 --> 00:17:29,478
Mr. Chau, we support you

192
00:17:29,514 --> 00:17:31,877
Thank you...

193
00:17:41,246 --> 00:17:44,338
You are invited to our restaurant
for a dinner at 6pm this evening

194
00:17:44,381 --> 00:17:45,936
As a gesture of our appreciation

195
00:17:49,579 --> 00:17:50,739
Quiet

196
00:17:50,780 --> 00:17:52,370
Please be seated

197
00:17:52,946 --> 00:17:54,572
The court's in session

198
00:18:03,978 --> 00:18:06,876
From the official report

199
00:18:06,911 --> 00:18:09,775
provided by the Education Dept

200
00:18:10,344 --> 00:18:13,106
It's said that, the electronic games
which are popular in this society

201
00:18:13,145 --> 00:18:18,337
has not categorically been
defined as gambling

202
00:18:18,710 --> 00:18:25,075
It means that we have no
legal ground for indictment

203
00:18:25,111 --> 00:18:29,043
I find the defendant
Chau Chiu-sen not guilty

204
00:18:29,276 --> 00:18:33,368
All electronic games & computer IC boards
must be returned to Mr. Chau at once

205
00:18:33,710 --> 00:18:35,608
Rumor has it that you have a very good
relationship with the Education Department

206
00:18:35,643 --> 00:18:37,666
Chiu-sen is a nice guy
he has friends everywhere

207
00:18:37,710 --> 00:18:38,675
Right?

208
00:18:38,709 --> 00:18:39,800
You are the chairman of
the Union of Electronic Game Centers

209
00:18:39,843 --> 00:18:42,207
So why do you operate
underground casinos?

210
00:18:43,510 --> 00:18:46,771
Since the definition between gambling and
electronic games isn't clearly defined yet

211
00:18:47,342 --> 00:18:49,900
Being the chairman
I have to be proactive

212
00:18:49,943 --> 00:18:52,135
So I would like to hold a public hearing

213
00:18:52,908 --> 00:18:54,931
To invite representatives
from all walks of life

214
00:18:54,975 --> 00:18:57,373
to help draw up
a standard code of practice

215
00:18:57,409 --> 00:19:00,602
Then I'll make sure our members
will follow the set rules

216
00:19:00,641 --> 00:19:02,436
Hopefully it will clear up
any misunderstandings

217
00:19:02,475 --> 00:19:06,430
You are the accused
but you are sounding like the judge!

218
00:19:11,274 --> 00:19:13,637
Excuse me, goodbye

219
00:19:22,806 --> 00:19:23,669
Excuse us...

220
00:19:23,706 --> 00:19:25,798
Chiu-sen has to rush off to officiate
an inauguration for a highway

221
00:19:25,841 --> 00:19:27,864
Please excuse us and save the questions
for some other time

222
00:19:27,907 --> 00:19:28,873
Thank you

223
00:19:32,173 --> 00:19:33,139
Ling Fei, are you alright?

224
00:19:34,539 --> 00:19:35,527
I am fine

225
00:19:58,238 --> 00:20:01,136
"Righteousness is usually late
but it'll come sooner or later!"

226
00:20:14,070 --> 00:20:15,229
Stop playing around

227
00:20:16,271 --> 00:20:18,032
Dinner is ready

228
00:20:28,370 --> 00:20:30,667
Good evening, this is your DJ

229
00:20:30,704 --> 00:20:33,260
This afternoon, I received a call

230
00:20:33,303 --> 00:20:36,928
A young man wants to
dedicate a song to his dad

231
00:20:37,069 --> 00:20:38,535
He wishes his dad to be happy forever

232
00:20:39,236 --> 00:20:40,361
The song is...

233
00:20:41,269 --> 00:20:44,291
Mei Lan-fong's Drunken Concubine

234
00:20:46,502 --> 00:20:47,468
How's business today?

235
00:20:48,902 --> 00:20:50,231
Terrible!

236
00:20:50,268 --> 00:20:54,064
You know, your dad is always
picky about whom to pick up

237
00:20:54,102 --> 00:20:55,795
Especially single girls

238
00:20:55,835 --> 00:20:57,801
If they are not suitable
to be my daughter-in-law

239
00:20:58,101 --> 00:20:59,398
I won't give them a ride

240
00:21:00,302 --> 00:21:05,665
Have you seen the picture
I gave you last week?

241
00:21:05,700 --> 00:21:08,996
The girl is pretty and well educated

242
00:21:09,034 --> 00:21:10,591
A customer you met on the street?

243
00:21:11,001 --> 00:21:13,126
A customer I chose on the street!

244
00:21:15,767 --> 00:21:17,097
Fei, I have to stop here

245
00:21:17,134 --> 00:21:19,429
A lady wants a ride

246
00:21:19,467 --> 00:21:20,763
Taxi...

247
00:21:21,401 --> 00:21:24,264
Excuse me, will you take me to Bei-tau?

248
00:21:25,632 --> 00:21:28,793
Sorry, I am in a hurry, I am sorry

249
00:22:22,163 --> 00:22:23,719
About the book report

250
00:22:23,763 --> 00:22:25,252
You haven't written a word yet

251
00:22:25,296 --> 00:22:27,785
You just go shopping everyday

252
00:22:27,830 --> 00:22:30,261
I don't know how to write it
I am not going to the meeting

253
00:22:32,229 --> 00:22:36,026
This Heritage Society is organized by
the wife of Chairman Hau

254
00:22:36,063 --> 00:22:38,323
The members are all
wives of senior officials

255
00:22:39,128 --> 00:22:41,618
I put in a lot of effort
to make you a member

256
00:22:41,662 --> 00:22:43,458
How can you refuse to go?

257
00:22:43,862 --> 00:22:45,192
Give me a reason why

258
00:22:45,628 --> 00:22:46,616
Damn it

259
00:22:46,829 --> 00:22:49,556
I am not well educated, they despise me

260
00:22:52,528 --> 00:22:54,618
I don't think
they are well educated either

261
00:22:54,661 --> 00:22:59,320
It's an excuse for them
to do some networking

262
00:22:59,860 --> 00:23:02,850
I am satisfied just to be your wife

263
00:23:02,894 --> 00:23:04,621
I don't need to be the wife of
a legislative council member

264
00:23:08,426 --> 00:23:10,017
Do you remember the days
of the First Liquidation?

265
00:23:10,860 --> 00:23:13,019
Don't you think it's enough to be kept
behind bars for five years?

266
00:23:13,793 --> 00:23:16,452
During the Second Liquidation
we were lucky to be in Hong Kong

267
00:23:16,793 --> 00:23:19,224
Who knows when the government will
launch a third liquidation?

268
00:23:23,059 --> 00:23:26,026
Now, I am rich enough to bid for a seat
in the legislative council

269
00:23:26,060 --> 00:23:27,423
It provides the best insurance

270
00:23:27,460 --> 00:23:28,890
Otherwise, how can we be sure
to have a stable life in the future?

271
00:23:28,992 --> 00:23:31,720
But you have to spend 20 to 30 million
dollars to be elected!

272
00:23:33,492 --> 00:23:36,322
You fool, don't you understand
what investment means?

273
00:23:36,359 --> 00:23:38,450
Once I have power

274
00:23:39,359 --> 00:23:42,518
I can get many times
return on my investment

275
00:23:45,624 --> 00:23:48,954
Alright, be a good girl
I'll help you write the report

276
00:23:49,725 --> 00:23:52,656
And you memorize it
and go to the meeting tomorrow

277
00:23:53,758 --> 00:23:56,246
You've ruined my dress

278
00:23:57,424 --> 00:24:00,014
Go buy another one

279
00:24:12,489 --> 00:24:13,251
Hello

280
00:24:13,290 --> 00:24:17,120
This is a live report by Ling Fei
in the Benefaction Villa

281
00:24:17,156 --> 00:24:18,179
A charity auction for ash urns
is being held right here

282
00:24:29,522 --> 00:24:32,215
Excuse me. Thank you

283
00:24:35,321 --> 00:24:37,288
Please give way...

284
00:24:38,522 --> 00:24:39,180
Sir

285
00:24:39,222 --> 00:24:41,778
Chiu-sen, I'm so glad to see you

286
00:24:49,121 --> 00:24:52,678
Please rise

287
00:24:55,787 --> 00:25:03,083
The Benefaction Villa
Supreme Sung Miu-tin

288
00:25:55,817 --> 00:26:00,216
May we have Madam Chiu
Chairlady of the Chai-sai Association

289
00:26:00,950 --> 00:26:04,212
Also Mrs. Hau
Deputy Chairman of the Council

290
00:26:04,249 --> 00:26:06,943
to host the auction for us

291
00:26:14,184 --> 00:26:18,205
The objective of this auction

292
00:26:18,248 --> 00:26:22,613
is to gather all the kind hearted people

293
00:26:22,649 --> 00:26:28,013
for those uncared

294
00:26:28,048 --> 00:26:30,639
we can now offer them free urns
and a good buried place

295
00:26:31,082 --> 00:26:34,981
Those who has done good...

296
00:26:35,016 --> 00:26:37,606
will find internal peace

297
00:26:37,648 --> 00:26:42,274
At the same time, Master Sung will offer
the donors his special spiritual blessing

298
00:26:42,848 --> 00:26:45,507
to help them to avoid evils and bad luck

299
00:26:45,548 --> 00:26:49,139
And to strengthen their luck and wisdom

300
00:26:49,581 --> 00:26:52,342
The starting price for each urn
is $300,000

301
00:26:53,114 --> 00:26:56,170
I hope all of you will
do your best to contribute

302
00:26:58,846 --> 00:27:00,506
Madam is a great lady

303
00:27:01,180 --> 00:27:05,135
I am really touched by her speech

304
00:27:06,080 --> 00:27:08,102
To show my support

305
00:27:08,145 --> 00:27:11,135
I'll buy ten urns

306
00:27:19,312 --> 00:27:22,539
The starting price for each urn is
$300,000, is that right?

307
00:27:22,578 --> 00:27:23,635
So how much is ten urns?

308
00:27:23,678 --> 00:27:24,576
3 million!

309
00:27:25,646 --> 00:27:28,804
You know how much Madam Chau paid?

310
00:27:28,844 --> 00:27:30,276
$60 million!

311
00:27:31,178 --> 00:27:32,371
How generous!

312
00:27:33,145 --> 00:27:39,543
That may be the political donation by Chau
in order to get the party's nomination

313
00:27:39,578 --> 00:27:41,271
Is that right?

314
00:27:41,311 --> 00:27:43,004
That's right It's possible

315
00:27:43,644 --> 00:27:46,906
How is the money channeled
from that charity association?

316
00:27:48,310 --> 00:27:49,207
Who knows?

317
00:27:49,577 --> 00:27:50,474
You're right

318
00:27:51,177 --> 00:27:52,870
Look at this

319
00:27:53,744 --> 00:27:56,903
On last Monday and Saturday

320
00:27:56,943 --> 00:27:59,408
Chau and the Deputy Commissioner
of the Public Works Department...

321
00:27:59,443 --> 00:28:01,500
played golf twice

322
00:28:04,943 --> 00:28:06,841
Mr. Lam is the boss of
Tak-cheung Construction Company

323
00:28:06,875 --> 00:28:09,171
He wants to bid for the construction
contract for Bin-hai Road

324
00:28:09,209 --> 00:28:10,334
But he received anonymous threats

325
00:28:10,376 --> 00:28:13,103
He suspects that it was Chau
so he came to report the case

326
00:28:16,676 --> 00:28:19,107
Now, all the government construction
contracts go to Chau

327
00:28:19,708 --> 00:28:21,469
He is a triad

328
00:28:21,507 --> 00:28:23,269
He knows nothing about construction

329
00:28:24,208 --> 00:28:26,140
Kidnapping, killing
setting fire... they are experts

330
00:28:26,175 --> 00:28:29,266
They can easily burn a building down

331
00:28:30,541 --> 00:28:33,405
But they have no idea
on how to build one

332
00:28:33,441 --> 00:28:34,873
The triads are connected
with the officials

333
00:28:35,474 --> 00:28:39,907
They share most of the gov't construction
budget with the Public Works Dept

334
00:28:39,941 --> 00:28:41,997
And allocate only a small sum
for the actual construction

335
00:28:42,040 --> 00:28:43,198
The quality of the work is
thus grossly compromised

336
00:28:43,239 --> 00:28:46,229
Even before an earthquake
the building will collapse

337
00:28:46,674 --> 00:28:50,468
Our government is collaborating
with illegal gangs

338
00:28:51,239 --> 00:28:53,797
Our construction site is being forcefully
occupied, my staffs are beaten

339
00:28:53,840 --> 00:28:58,204
It's worse than what's shown
in Hollywood movies

340
00:28:59,541 --> 00:29:02,334
They sent this to my son's school

341
00:29:03,238 --> 00:29:04,068
Open

342
00:29:04,105 --> 00:29:06,265
Paper pagoda tombs

343
00:29:07,173 --> 00:29:10,468
Two big ones and a small one
do you get it?

344
00:29:11,205 --> 00:29:12,670
How dare I report to the police?

345
00:29:12,705 --> 00:29:14,638
They are all bribed

346
00:29:14,672 --> 00:29:19,797
If I go to the police, I am just leaving
myself wide open for further danger

347
00:29:20,205 --> 00:29:24,500
I come to you just to try my luck

348
00:29:24,538 --> 00:29:27,936
God knows you are getting nowhere

349
00:29:27,972 --> 00:29:29,733
And you want me to be your undercover?

350
00:29:29,771 --> 00:29:32,066
Don't you feel ashamed even asking me?

351
00:29:33,470 --> 00:29:35,460
We serve the community in different ways

352
00:29:35,504 --> 00:29:38,026
I construct building and you beat crimes

353
00:29:38,071 --> 00:29:39,469
Are you kidding me?

354
00:29:43,071 --> 00:29:45,730
Alright, you are a nice guy

355
00:29:45,770 --> 00:29:47,292
I know you from the TV report

356
00:29:47,337 --> 00:29:49,565
You are straight

357
00:29:49,971 --> 00:29:51,436
But you'll have it do it on your own

358
00:29:51,470 --> 00:29:53,230
I can't help you at all

359
00:29:58,836 --> 00:30:00,063
What's the matter?

360
00:30:09,469 --> 00:30:12,560
Shut up!

361
00:30:20,535 --> 00:30:23,058
See what they have done to my son!

362
00:30:25,567 --> 00:30:29,125
I swear, I would take revenge for you

363
00:30:32,101 --> 00:30:32,589
Thank you

364
00:30:34,834 --> 00:30:35,800
Well...

365
00:30:37,866 --> 00:30:39,661
Nice haircut? I did it

366
00:30:40,400 --> 00:30:43,264
Be careful, someone might find out

367
00:31:30,197 --> 00:31:31,663
Competition - Tea Ceremony

368
00:31:34,164 --> 00:31:34,959
Mr. Lam

369
00:31:36,530 --> 00:31:37,893
Nice to meet you

370
00:31:37,929 --> 00:31:38,395
Me too

371
00:31:38,430 --> 00:31:39,192
Take a seat

372
00:31:39,230 --> 00:31:39,991
Thank you

373
00:31:59,428 --> 00:32:02,123
Alright, let's start the meeting

374
00:32:02,529 --> 00:32:04,290
The late comers
have given up their rights

375
00:32:05,062 --> 00:32:06,426
Who will make the tea for us?

376
00:32:08,761 --> 00:32:11,852
Come on, speak out
don't just look at me

377
00:32:11,895 --> 00:32:14,326
I am just the organizer
I don't have to be the chairman

378
00:32:19,027 --> 00:32:22,926
Mr. Chau, I am sorry, I was caught
in a traffic jam, I am sorry

379
00:32:30,127 --> 00:32:31,184
San-pao

380
00:32:33,360 --> 00:32:34,587
Move the empty chair away

381
00:32:42,459 --> 00:32:44,358
Since everyone is kind enough
to give me face

382
00:32:44,393 --> 00:32:45,824
I'll serve the tea

383
00:32:46,527 --> 00:32:48,322
Please turn off your pagers
and mobile phones

384
00:32:56,092 --> 00:32:57,717
Sorry, sorry...

385
00:32:58,426 --> 00:33:01,255
Mr. Chau, I am late

386
00:33:01,291 --> 00:33:02,848
It's because of a traffic jam

387
00:33:04,091 --> 00:33:06,853
Traffic jam? What car are you driving?

388
00:33:07,526 --> 00:33:09,650
I have a...

389
00:33:09,692 --> 00:33:11,281
Mazda

390
00:33:12,891 --> 00:33:16,585
We all drive Mercedes or Rolls Royce

391
00:33:16,625 --> 00:33:19,784
And you drive a Mazda
that's why you are late

392
00:33:20,124 --> 00:33:24,351
You are not even qualified
to join this meeting

393
00:33:26,623 --> 00:33:28,215
Find a seat

394
00:33:28,258 --> 00:33:29,655
Yes, thank you

395
00:33:35,723 --> 00:33:36,916
Can you find any?

396
00:33:38,090 --> 00:33:38,680
No

397
00:33:40,157 --> 00:33:44,020
You are 11 minutes late
that shows you don't respect this meeting

398
00:33:44,056 --> 00:33:45,647
You are despising us

399
00:33:45,989 --> 00:33:48,353
So how can you expect us
to treat you as a buddy?

400
00:33:48,922 --> 00:33:51,354
Wait for my call at home
I'll call you later

401
00:34:09,188 --> 00:34:11,746
About the Bei-hoi Road construction

402
00:34:11,789 --> 00:34:14,844
A total of 18 companies are planning to
bid for the contract

403
00:34:15,554 --> 00:34:17,247
According to my estimates

404
00:34:17,287 --> 00:34:21,151
9 companies are not big enough
to handle such a big project

405
00:34:21,521 --> 00:34:24,452
So I talked to them before this meeting

406
00:34:25,053 --> 00:34:26,952
And they gave me face too

407
00:34:26,987 --> 00:34:28,953
They decided to withdraw

408
00:34:29,353 --> 00:34:32,251
Which leaves us, the nine companies

409
00:34:32,953 --> 00:34:34,442
And one has just forfeited

410
00:34:35,219 --> 00:34:36,480
So, there are eight of us left

411
00:34:44,285 --> 00:34:45,944
We are all resourceful and strong

412
00:34:46,818 --> 00:34:49,478
But I would like to call for unity

413
00:34:50,218 --> 00:34:52,081
If we bid separately

414
00:34:52,118 --> 00:34:54,549
Will the successful bidder
end up being a winner?

415
00:34:55,319 --> 00:34:57,410
I am sure the final price will be so low
it's not worth it

416
00:34:58,285 --> 00:35:00,443
I hope we would make money together

417
00:35:00,484 --> 00:35:03,178
To share the profit from the project

418
00:35:03,218 --> 00:35:05,274
After all, it's the government's money

419
00:35:06,051 --> 00:35:07,846
Our government is very rich

420
00:35:09,851 --> 00:35:12,316
I'd like to make a suggestion

421
00:35:13,217 --> 00:35:14,512
Actually

422
00:35:15,016 --> 00:35:16,607
I would like you to do me a favor

423
00:35:17,084 --> 00:35:18,311
I'll be frank

424
00:35:18,684 --> 00:35:20,513
I want this project

425
00:35:21,317 --> 00:35:25,272
Since my business is growing rapidly
my cash flow is tight

426
00:35:26,116 --> 00:35:27,672
And here is my offer

427
00:35:27,716 --> 00:35:31,444
Firstly, the government's budget
for the construction is 1 billion

428
00:35:32,116 --> 00:35:35,014
Say I'll make 20% profit
that's 200 million

429
00:35:35,549 --> 00:35:37,242
I'll allocate 40 million

430
00:35:37,282 --> 00:35:39,078
The seven of you can share it

431
00:35:39,116 --> 00:35:41,343
That is, each of you will get
just over 5 million

432
00:35:42,482 --> 00:35:46,244
Secondly, the government will offer 3 more
contracts in the second half of the year

433
00:35:46,648 --> 00:35:47,773
I promise I won't be bidding

434
00:35:47,982 --> 00:35:49,209
I'll be satisfied with
my nominal share of the profit

435
00:35:49,248 --> 00:35:50,578
as calculated similarly to this project

436
00:35:51,114 --> 00:35:52,444
I'm finished

437
00:35:53,049 --> 00:35:55,776
Yes, or no?

438
00:36:00,848 --> 00:36:01,711
I object

439
00:36:06,913 --> 00:36:10,778
I always tell my friends that
Mr. Chau is someone I really admire

440
00:36:11,580 --> 00:36:14,171
He gets the contract and
he doesn't need to lift a finger

441
00:36:14,447 --> 00:36:16,243
You'll take half of the 1 billion

442
00:36:17,047 --> 00:36:18,308
And then subcontract out the project

443
00:36:18,346 --> 00:36:21,437
With several levels of subcontracting

444
00:36:21,479 --> 00:36:24,378
The quality of the building material
will be compromised

445
00:36:24,414 --> 00:36:27,039
Then you work with the officials
of the Public Works Department

446
00:36:27,080 --> 00:36:29,170
To build in an over-budget allowance
of 300 to 400 millions

447
00:36:30,313 --> 00:36:34,768
You will end up making at least
700 millions from the construction

448
00:36:35,879 --> 00:36:37,936
And you are offering us
such a pathetic sum of money

449
00:36:37,979 --> 00:36:39,172
You are out of your mind

450
00:36:41,945 --> 00:36:44,640
What he says makes sense

451
00:36:53,412 --> 00:36:55,537
I told my buddies not to come

452
00:36:55,577 --> 00:36:58,338
But they insisted on coming

453
00:36:59,945 --> 00:37:03,433
They are just small timers
and don't know the better

454
00:37:04,477 --> 00:37:05,966
But, Mr. Chau

455
00:37:06,011 --> 00:37:08,874
I've talked to Mr. Lau
beforehand about this contract

456
00:37:08,910 --> 00:37:10,842
We've decided to join up in the bidding

457
00:37:10,877 --> 00:37:13,435
We are determined to win

458
00:37:14,244 --> 00:37:15,971
But, after listening to
what you just said

459
00:37:16,010 --> 00:37:18,441
We find it hard to accept

460
00:37:21,076 --> 00:37:22,837
Cute!

461
00:37:24,543 --> 00:37:26,974
I am impressed

462
00:37:28,110 --> 00:37:31,904
You are not Chinese

463
00:37:32,442 --> 00:37:33,771
You're like Americans

464
00:37:34,542 --> 00:37:36,804
You are such good negotiators
you are just like the Americans

465
00:37:37,609 --> 00:37:40,665
Alright, this is my last offer

466
00:37:41,474 --> 00:37:44,668
First, each of you will get 7 million

467
00:37:45,475 --> 00:37:51,134
Second, Kiu-wu and Mr. Lau
will be my authorized subcontractor

468
00:37:52,308 --> 00:37:56,400
I'm done, yes or no?

469
00:37:56,441 --> 00:37:57,407
I object

470
00:38:06,141 --> 00:38:07,004
I agree

471
00:38:08,141 --> 00:38:09,299
I object

472
00:38:09,340 --> 00:38:13,033
No, I agree

473
00:38:13,073 --> 00:38:15,130
I agree We agree too

474
00:38:17,307 --> 00:38:18,136
Get out

475
00:38:21,673 --> 00:38:24,366
Thank you for giving me face
please go back

476
00:38:24,838 --> 00:38:27,634
Mr. Lam and I will sort out our problem

477
00:38:29,172 --> 00:38:31,502
Let's go...

478
00:38:33,472 --> 00:38:35,994
Why don't you stay a bit longer?

479
00:38:37,005 --> 00:38:38,527
Do you have your own driver?

480
00:38:44,038 --> 00:38:46,663
You have intentionally tried to
make trouble in the meeting today

481
00:38:46,704 --> 00:38:48,171
Who is backing you?

482
00:38:53,970 --> 00:38:54,959
Damn you

483
00:38:55,438 --> 00:38:57,097
Shit! Mr. Lam has got a gun

484
00:39:39,201 --> 00:39:41,360
Chau Chiu-sen, I am an upright person!

485
00:39:41,402 --> 00:39:42,958
I am not afraid of any triads

486
00:39:43,001 --> 00:39:46,058
To hell with you!

487
00:39:51,367 --> 00:39:53,163
You should know what I mean

488
00:40:12,933 --> 00:40:15,162
Help!

489
00:40:18,365 --> 00:40:19,331
Shit

490
00:42:50,957 --> 00:42:52,115
Help!

491
00:42:56,890 --> 00:42:58,412
Nicotine, turn on the taps

492
00:43:37,954 --> 00:43:39,181
You're tough

493
00:43:39,221 --> 00:43:40,084
Thank you

494
00:43:40,121 --> 00:43:42,951
You're lucky to be alive

495
00:43:47,387 --> 00:43:50,319
Last year, more than 160 people
were hurt when three projects

496
00:43:50,353 --> 00:43:52,251
Using inferior building material
resulted in collapses

497
00:43:52,287 --> 00:43:53,049
Look!

498
00:43:53,087 --> 00:43:54,483
Citizens are furious
about the triads rigging

499
00:43:54,519 --> 00:43:56,610
such biddings in collaboration
with government officials

500
00:43:56,653 --> 00:43:58,516
Director of the construction company

501
00:43:58,552 --> 00:44:00,542
Chau Chiu-sen has disappeared

502
00:44:00,587 --> 00:44:01,950
The Public Works Dept
announced today that

503
00:44:01,986 --> 00:44:04,110
the Bin-hei project
will be suspended for 3 months

504
00:44:04,152 --> 00:44:05,242
All investigation will be conducted
on the alleged collaboration

505
00:44:05,285 --> 00:44:08,411
between government officials
and bidding contractors

506
00:44:08,452 --> 00:44:10,577
Leading the investigation
is Fong Kuo-fei

507
00:44:10,619 --> 00:44:11,516
the investigator who has headed
the government's

508
00:44:11,552 --> 00:44:12,517
anti-electronic games gambling campaign

509
00:44:12,551 --> 00:44:15,040
Fong and his team of investigators...

510
00:44:15,085 --> 00:44:18,744
Are the true guardians of Taiwan

511
00:44:18,785 --> 00:44:21,751
Doing their best to
maintain its peace and order

512
00:44:21,785 --> 00:44:25,272
I am Ling Fei, reporting live

513
00:44:38,484 --> 00:44:41,109
I watched your report
you've done a great job

514
00:44:41,683 --> 00:44:44,082
Congratulations

515
00:44:44,151 --> 00:44:46,843
Thank you, I am just reporting the facts

516
00:44:46,883 --> 00:44:49,713
But my boss always criticizes me
of being too forthcoming

517
00:44:52,950 --> 00:44:53,813
You've come to buy pet's food?

518
00:44:54,083 --> 00:44:55,810
Yeah, for my daughter

519
00:44:56,949 --> 00:44:58,279
Doggie or kitty?

520
00:44:58,316 --> 00:45:00,111
Neither, I'll show you

521
00:45:03,116 --> 00:45:04,911
Look, this is Evita

522
00:45:06,682 --> 00:45:07,545
Pretty!

523
00:45:07,916 --> 00:45:08,846
Who do you mean?

524
00:45:09,649 --> 00:45:10,410
Both

525
00:45:13,916 --> 00:45:15,279
This is for you

526
00:45:18,947 --> 00:45:19,811
Thank you

527
00:45:23,814 --> 00:45:24,780
This is for you

528
00:45:25,748 --> 00:45:26,611
They are my kids

529
00:45:26,648 --> 00:45:28,045
Li, Dun, and Fei

530
00:45:55,579 --> 00:45:57,909
Welcome, Miss
do you have any reservation?

531
00:45:58,212 --> 00:46:00,110
Yes, Mr. Fong's table for two please

532
00:46:00,479 --> 00:46:02,001
This way please

533
00:46:04,279 --> 00:46:05,210
Over there

534
00:46:05,979 --> 00:46:07,171
Thank you

535
00:46:18,977 --> 00:46:21,102
He is a nuisance! A chain smoker!

536
00:46:21,144 --> 00:46:22,075
It doesn't matter

537
00:46:22,510 --> 00:46:24,136
She doesn't always dress like this

538
00:46:25,244 --> 00:46:26,437
We don't mind

539
00:46:26,678 --> 00:46:27,701
Please sit down

540
00:46:29,343 --> 00:46:30,831
They are my partners

541
00:46:30,876 --> 00:46:33,638
They insist on coming
I can't say no, I am sorry

542
00:46:33,677 --> 00:46:34,870
You are a considerate guy

543
00:46:36,410 --> 00:46:38,103
What's the matter, you don't measure up?

544
00:46:38,610 --> 00:46:39,768
But you've bigger ones

545
00:46:39,809 --> 00:46:40,968
Stop teasing me

546
00:46:42,943 --> 00:46:44,636
Mr. Fong, excuse me

547
00:46:44,676 --> 00:46:46,699
Someone ordered wine for you

548
00:46:46,743 --> 00:46:47,573
Who?

549
00:46:47,610 --> 00:46:48,667
Mr. Chau

550
00:46:49,143 --> 00:46:53,574
A gift from Mr. Chau

551
00:46:53,608 --> 00:46:55,768
This is a Petrus
This wine is worth over $60,000 NT dollars

552
00:46:57,075 --> 00:46:59,234
Please do us a favor
Please accept the wine

553
00:46:59,276 --> 00:47:01,434
Otherwise, we will be blamed

554
00:47:04,142 --> 00:47:04,539
Alright

555
00:47:04,575 --> 00:47:06,165
Please open it Thank you

556
00:47:12,407 --> 00:47:13,964
Please pick up my handbag

557
00:47:17,475 --> 00:47:18,168
Thank you

558
00:47:18,208 --> 00:47:21,502
Mr. Fong, let the wine breathe for a while
Give it 20 minutes

559
00:47:23,407 --> 00:47:26,271
I think my friend
would like to taste it now

560
00:47:28,773 --> 00:47:29,569
Sure

561
00:47:37,973 --> 00:47:39,234
The wine has gone bad

562
00:47:40,706 --> 00:47:41,501
That's highly unlikely

563
00:47:42,605 --> 00:47:43,730
There shouldn't be a problem

564
00:47:44,338 --> 00:47:45,771
I think the taste is weird

565
00:47:46,539 --> 00:47:47,562
You try it

566
00:47:47,606 --> 00:47:48,537
Sure

567
00:47:53,338 --> 00:47:54,804
Mr. Fong, I am sorry...

568
00:47:54,839 --> 00:47:56,236
Don't worry

569
00:47:56,272 --> 00:47:57,965
Send the wine back to Mr. Chau

570
00:47:58,005 --> 00:48:00,302
Tell him that
both the wine and its master are rotten

571
00:48:00,339 --> 00:48:01,804
I am sorry

572
00:48:06,537 --> 00:48:07,561
What did you drink?

573
00:48:10,771 --> 00:48:12,101
Come on, water please

574
00:48:12,138 --> 00:48:13,466
I toast you

575
00:48:14,804 --> 00:48:16,064
How can I be so stupid!

576
00:48:16,104 --> 00:48:17,899
Why didn't I take ketchup instead?

577
00:48:21,170 --> 00:48:23,160
I am sure the final price will be so low
it's not worth it

578
00:48:24,236 --> 00:48:26,429
I hope we would make money together

579
00:48:26,470 --> 00:48:28,993
To share the profit from the project

580
00:48:29,037 --> 00:48:31,026
After all, it's the government's money

581
00:48:31,937 --> 00:48:33,835
Our government is very rich

582
00:48:35,802 --> 00:48:38,428
I'd like to make a suggestion

583
00:48:41,403 --> 00:48:43,835
Recently
there are all sorts of rumor...

584
00:48:44,569 --> 00:48:46,694
Spreading all over town

585
00:48:46,736 --> 00:48:49,860
A lot of people are taking this chance

586
00:48:50,435 --> 00:48:53,924
To attack the Public Works Department
for collaborating with triads

587
00:48:53,969 --> 00:48:56,456
You are responsible, do you know that?

588
00:48:58,968 --> 00:49:00,298
The boss is mad

589
00:49:02,334 --> 00:49:05,095
What do you expect
your punishment to be?

590
00:49:06,234 --> 00:49:09,530
Don't tell me
he will withdraw my nomination

591
00:49:12,134 --> 00:49:13,430
You are right

592
00:49:16,066 --> 00:49:17,964
We decided to nominate
Ting Chun-shu instead

593
00:49:20,134 --> 00:49:21,157
At least he is obedient

594
00:49:23,667 --> 00:49:25,326
Any chance to rectify the situation?

595
00:49:26,366 --> 00:49:28,128
What do you think?

596
00:49:28,400 --> 00:49:31,093
If it's money, I can pay more

597
00:49:32,499 --> 00:49:34,489
It's not that simple

598
00:49:36,799 --> 00:49:38,230
Better forget this year's election

599
00:49:38,832 --> 00:49:40,525
Wait for the next one

600
00:49:42,733 --> 00:49:45,960
So the 60 million I paid'll be treated as
an advanced payment for the next election

601
00:49:45,999 --> 00:49:48,396
Damn you! Cut the bull shit!

602
00:49:49,832 --> 00:49:51,923
I've done enough covering up for you

603
00:49:52,632 --> 00:49:55,097
In the last few days
I've kept running around

604
00:49:55,131 --> 00:49:58,063
I didn't get enough sleep, and I drank
so much. And it's all because of you

605
00:49:58,098 --> 00:49:59,791
Why should I even bother?

606
00:50:00,898 --> 00:50:03,592
If it weren't for me
this tape would have leaked out

607
00:50:04,032 --> 00:50:06,327
For sure you won't be sitting here
watching this so comfortably

608
00:50:06,565 --> 00:50:08,427
You would have been arrested
by the investigators

609
00:50:09,596 --> 00:50:13,529
You must be crazy

610
00:50:13,564 --> 00:50:15,154
Is there something wrong
with your brain?

611
00:50:15,197 --> 00:50:16,754
Your ass is transplanted to your brain
isn't it?

612
00:50:17,763 --> 00:50:20,820
Damn it! Isn't saving your ass
worth $60 million?

613
00:50:20,863 --> 00:50:23,158
I have never demanded a cent more

614
00:50:24,296 --> 00:50:25,558
Damn it

615
00:50:26,297 --> 00:50:29,421
Bastard!
You should think before you talk

616
00:50:37,162 --> 00:50:40,594
Thank you, Chairman, thank you for your
benevolence and generosity

617
00:50:41,495 --> 00:50:42,927
It's all my fault

618
00:50:43,662 --> 00:50:45,389
I will go back
and reflect on my mistakes

619
00:50:46,528 --> 00:50:51,017
Chairman, take care
and have a good rest

620
00:50:52,361 --> 00:50:53,554
I am leaving now

621
00:51:12,793 --> 00:51:14,156
I've been cheated

622
00:51:15,093 --> 00:51:16,617
They took my 60 million

623
00:51:16,661 --> 00:51:18,592
And then turn the investigators onto me

624
00:51:18,627 --> 00:51:21,092
Actually, they have never really
considered nominating me

625
00:51:21,260 --> 00:51:22,384
Damn!

626
00:51:24,426 --> 00:51:25,687
I'll have to fight this

627
00:52:31,956 --> 00:52:32,943
Great, now that you are here

628
00:52:36,922 --> 00:52:37,751
Master

629
00:52:56,621 --> 00:52:58,087
What the hell did you feed her?

630
00:52:58,121 --> 00:53:00,518
I didn't feed her anything

631
00:53:00,554 --> 00:53:01,485
So, what's happened

632
00:53:01,520 --> 00:53:05,646
Maybe, she'd stolen the drugs
from somewhere else

633
00:53:05,687 --> 00:53:06,879
She is your disciple

634
00:53:06,920 --> 00:53:08,181
You are responsible

635
00:53:08,220 --> 00:53:09,243
Don't worry

636
00:53:09,287 --> 00:53:11,980
Leave this to me

637
00:53:12,187 --> 00:53:13,710
Is her family here?

638
00:53:13,754 --> 00:53:15,048
Don't worry

639
00:53:15,086 --> 00:53:16,109
Her family is far away from Taipei

640
00:53:16,152 --> 00:53:17,345
She has no friends or family in Taipei

641
00:53:17,386 --> 00:53:18,681
Anybody knows you are here?

642
00:53:18,719 --> 00:53:20,447
No, impossible

643
00:53:20,486 --> 00:53:22,714
I've created a double as a cover

644
00:53:27,619 --> 00:53:30,177
Ask Leung to help you
to get rid of the body

645
00:53:30,518 --> 00:53:31,415
Yes

646
00:53:31,452 --> 00:53:32,975
Can you fix it within an hour?

647
00:53:33,018 --> 00:53:33,916
Sure

648
00:53:34,720 --> 00:53:35,979
You promised

649
00:53:36,552 --> 00:53:37,245
Yes

650
00:53:37,285 --> 00:53:40,944
If not, I'll cut you up into two

651
00:53:41,852 --> 00:53:43,044
Yes

652
00:54:39,481 --> 00:54:40,913
It's fixed

653
00:54:42,147 --> 00:54:45,477
I just spent 53 minutes

654
00:54:55,817 --> 00:54:57,408
I am proud of you

655
00:54:58,415 --> 00:55:00,075
Thanks for the good work

656
00:55:01,450 --> 00:55:02,381
Thank you

657
00:55:07,383 --> 00:55:09,371
And I wish you a happy holiday

658
00:55:12,215 --> 00:55:16,614
I've approved your leave of absence

659
00:55:18,848 --> 00:55:19,814
Why?

660
00:55:21,114 --> 00:55:23,206
Cheung, please come here

661
00:55:25,948 --> 00:55:26,845
Why?

662
00:55:27,382 --> 00:55:28,938
Didn't I teach you?

663
00:55:28,981 --> 00:55:31,913
Just obey your orders

664
00:55:31,948 --> 00:55:34,742
And never ask why

665
00:55:35,481 --> 00:55:36,412
Come in

666
00:55:42,046 --> 00:55:43,376
Go to Captain Fong's office

667
00:55:43,413 --> 00:55:45,277
Collect everything about Chau Chiu-sen

668
00:55:45,314 --> 00:55:48,109
Sealed them and put them
into the confidential file

669
00:55:48,147 --> 00:55:49,204
Yes Sir

670
00:55:51,679 --> 00:55:53,111
This is signed by the Commissioner

671
00:56:05,212 --> 00:56:08,338
You should at least give me a reason

672
00:56:10,479 --> 00:56:11,808
You embarrassed me

673
00:56:12,511 --> 00:56:17,500
How dare you check the account of
the Cai-sai Association behind me?

674
00:56:19,179 --> 00:56:20,610
Is this the reason?

675
00:56:20,878 --> 00:56:22,207
Yes

676
00:56:25,610 --> 00:56:28,702
You acted without
the consent of your superior

677
00:56:28,745 --> 00:56:31,539
According to the regulations
I can sack you right away

678
00:56:35,811 --> 00:56:37,141
Any other reason?

679
00:56:38,377 --> 00:56:41,275
You better reflect
on what you've done wrong

680
00:56:44,177 --> 00:56:45,268
And learn from your mistakes

681
00:56:46,477 --> 00:56:47,272
Thank you

682
00:56:48,576 --> 00:56:49,940
I shouldn't have been your student

683
00:56:50,677 --> 00:56:52,301
You don't deserve to be a teacher

684
00:57:36,540 --> 00:57:39,665
Do you always come here
when you're unhappy?

685
00:57:40,640 --> 00:57:41,572
Yes

686
00:57:41,607 --> 00:57:44,696
I think this is the best treatment

687
00:57:55,072 --> 00:57:57,335
Don't give up, I'll support you

688
00:57:59,906 --> 00:58:00,803
Thank you

689
00:58:16,970 --> 00:58:17,732
Good morning

690
00:58:17,771 --> 00:58:18,634
Good morning

691
00:58:18,671 --> 00:58:21,660
The case against the bid rigging
is most encouraging

692
00:58:21,904 --> 00:58:24,097
Yes, but we could have done more

693
00:58:24,137 --> 00:58:26,432
But why has it stopped?

694
00:58:26,837 --> 00:58:29,065
Who told you that?

695
00:58:29,104 --> 00:58:31,763
As I know, it's still proceeding

696
00:58:31,804 --> 00:58:34,236
Is it due to a shortage of staff?

697
00:58:35,037 --> 00:58:36,467
I won't deny that

698
00:58:36,502 --> 00:58:38,559
We have always been over-worked

699
00:58:38,602 --> 00:58:40,592
We are seriously understaffed

700
00:58:40,804 --> 00:58:43,668
How do you rate Captain Fong Kuo-fei?

701
00:58:43,702 --> 00:58:45,066
He is the finest

702
00:58:45,103 --> 00:58:46,932
But, particularly in light of
the staff shortage situation

703
00:58:46,969 --> 00:58:50,332
Why is he suddenly suspended?

704
00:58:51,502 --> 00:58:53,695
I haven't received a report on this case

705
00:58:53,736 --> 00:58:55,202
So I can't answer your question

706
00:58:56,702 --> 00:58:59,462
Commissioner, when can you
give me a satisfactory answer?

707
00:58:59,501 --> 00:59:01,764
This is internal personnel affair

708
00:59:01,803 --> 00:59:04,064
I don't need to discuss it in public
good bye

709
00:59:04,502 --> 00:59:05,297
Commissioner

710
00:59:09,069 --> 00:59:09,966
Ling Fei

711
00:59:10,002 --> 00:59:11,228
Commissioner Off record please

712
00:59:11,901 --> 00:59:13,094
Is Fai your friend?

713
00:59:13,134 --> 00:59:14,759
Yes...

714
00:59:14,801 --> 00:59:16,132
Just an ordinary friend

715
00:59:16,169 --> 00:59:18,793
I didn't ask whether he is your ordinary
friend or boyfriend

716
00:59:20,700 --> 00:59:23,928
He is a special friend

717
00:59:25,767 --> 00:59:27,858
This is a letter from him

718
00:59:36,267 --> 00:59:38,199
What are you laughing at?

719
00:59:41,566 --> 00:59:44,396
Long live China
Long live our party chief

720
00:59:44,433 --> 00:59:47,365
Long live China
Long live our party chief

721
00:59:48,965 --> 00:59:51,988
I have to thank the party
for the opportunity and the trust

722
00:59:53,266 --> 00:59:55,595
A special thanks to the party chairman

723
00:59:56,398 --> 01:00:00,228
I, Ting Chun-shu would give my best...

724
01:00:03,165 --> 01:00:04,426
No matter how difficult it gets...

725
01:00:29,997 --> 01:00:32,554
Ladies and gentlemen, journalists

726
01:00:32,596 --> 01:00:35,460
Chiu-sen has an important announcement

727
01:00:38,463 --> 01:00:42,588
I, Chau Chiu-sen now declare

728
01:00:43,063 --> 01:00:45,052
From this second

729
01:00:46,229 --> 01:00:46,819
I withdraw from the party

730
01:00:46,862 --> 01:00:53,657
An independent fighting for
a national peace and prosperity

731
01:00:54,162 --> 01:00:57,617
I will enter
the Legislative Council Election

732
01:00:57,662 --> 01:01:00,753
As an independent candidate

733
01:01:00,796 --> 01:01:02,158
I would appreciate all your support

734
01:01:04,995 --> 01:01:10,757
My campaign would be fair
honorable and transparent

735
01:01:10,795 --> 01:01:14,022
And I will be a very formidable
opponent for Mr. Ting

736
01:01:16,194 --> 01:01:18,853
Behave yourself, mind your image

737
01:01:21,994 --> 01:01:22,890
Thank you

738
01:01:41,826 --> 01:01:50,725
National Prosperity and Peace

739
01:02:00,658 --> 01:02:02,123
Welcome...

740
01:02:13,991 --> 01:02:16,922
Congratulations!

741
01:02:17,424 --> 01:02:19,083
Thank you for
your taxi company's support

742
01:02:19,123 --> 01:02:19,885
My pleasure

743
01:02:19,923 --> 01:02:22,650
It's our pleasure, thank you

744
01:02:24,723 --> 01:02:27,518
Mr. Chau, congratulations on the
founding of your election headquarters

745
01:02:27,556 --> 01:02:29,385
Not only will I support you personally

746
01:02:29,423 --> 01:02:32,878
Everyone of our taxi company
will put up your election flags

747
01:02:35,989 --> 01:02:39,854
Dear fellows, Chau Chiu-sen is one of us

748
01:02:40,289 --> 01:02:43,016
He is not only our friend

749
01:02:43,056 --> 01:02:44,453
But a man of honor and integrity

750
01:02:44,488 --> 01:02:45,976
We should support him

751
01:02:46,021 --> 01:02:46,817
What would you say?

752
01:02:46,855 --> 01:02:48,150
Bravo!

753
01:02:48,321 --> 01:02:50,809
Chau Chiu-sen...

754
01:02:50,854 --> 01:02:52,218
Chau Chiu-sen...

755
01:02:58,220 --> 01:02:59,618
Miss, take my cab, Miss

756
01:02:59,654 --> 01:03:00,847
Miss, take my cab!

757
01:03:00,888 --> 01:03:01,876
Damn you!

758
01:03:01,921 --> 01:03:03,910
How dare you grab my customer?

759
01:03:03,954 --> 01:03:05,681
I arrived first

760
01:03:05,721 --> 01:03:06,209
So what?

761
01:03:06,253 --> 01:03:07,947
So what?

762
01:03:16,453 --> 01:03:26,614
Thank you...

763
01:03:26,653 --> 01:03:29,948
A driver from Pai-yun is having a fight
with a driver from Chuen-kuok

764
01:03:31,620 --> 01:03:32,381
San-pao

765
01:03:41,252 --> 01:03:42,615
Call Mr. Kwan

766
01:03:44,719 --> 01:03:45,480
Heung

767
01:03:48,584 --> 01:03:52,312
Check where the wife of the Commissioner
of the Police Dept. Will be going tonight

768
01:03:55,985 --> 01:03:58,074
Mr. Kwan, what happened?

769
01:03:58,950 --> 01:04:01,439
No big deal
it's just a small misunderstanding

770
01:04:01,484 --> 01:04:03,313
God knows how it becomes
such a massive battle

771
01:04:04,317 --> 01:04:07,374
Boss, if we can't solve it
as soon as possible

772
01:04:07,418 --> 01:04:09,974
The traffic of Sai Mun-ting
will be totally jammed

773
01:04:10,383 --> 01:04:12,315
This is a good opportunity

774
01:04:12,350 --> 01:04:13,976
You have to support me

775
01:04:14,251 --> 01:04:15,443
Anything you want, just tell me

776
01:04:16,183 --> 01:04:18,479
I want you to choose ten spots
with heavy traffic

777
01:04:18,517 --> 01:04:20,243
Ask all your drivers to start fights

778
01:04:20,282 --> 01:04:22,249
with the other company's drivers
at the same time

779
01:04:22,283 --> 01:04:24,146
I want traffic in Taipei
to come to a complete stop

780
01:04:25,282 --> 01:04:25,976
San-pao

781
01:04:26,749 --> 01:04:27,544
Boss

782
01:04:27,682 --> 01:04:28,842
Mobilize the Ten Generals

783
01:04:28,884 --> 01:04:32,337
Each of you lead three small teams to
3 spots to back up Kwan

784
01:04:32,782 --> 01:04:34,611
You lead a team to Fu Huo Bridge

785
01:04:34,648 --> 01:04:35,342
Yes

786
01:04:36,182 --> 01:04:39,545
Remember, Fu Huo Bridge
is the main battle ground

787
01:04:39,581 --> 01:04:41,444
And the rest are covers

788
01:04:41,881 --> 01:04:43,405
I get you

789
01:04:48,448 --> 01:04:51,278
Now, it's five pm, it's rush hour

790
01:04:51,314 --> 01:04:54,939
I want a complete mess in Taipei
within half an hour

791
01:04:55,914 --> 01:04:57,540
The messier the better

792
01:05:22,045 --> 01:05:24,568
Mrs. Tung will go to a ball
held by the Taipei University

793
01:05:24,611 --> 01:05:26,602
Graduates Association
at the Hyatt Hotel at 6 pm

794
01:05:27,346 --> 01:05:28,607
That's great

795
01:05:29,447 --> 01:05:30,879
Have you been invited?

796
01:05:31,146 --> 01:05:33,136
No, neither have you

797
01:05:35,028 --> 01:05:37,257
Get an invitation

798
01:05:37,296 --> 01:05:39,125
By hooks or by crooks
find a way to get in

799
01:05:39,162 --> 01:05:40,925
But I wouldn't have a seat assignment

800
01:05:43,497 --> 01:05:46,054
Keep switching tables
and chatting to different people

801
01:05:46,096 --> 01:05:48,087
Or, dance with some of the
university graduates

802
01:05:48,464 --> 01:05:51,453
You are beautiful and a good dancer

803
01:05:51,497 --> 01:05:53,326
It will be their dreams
to dance with you

804
01:05:53,564 --> 01:05:56,587
It's too late
I have no time to get changed

805
01:06:00,232 --> 01:06:01,129
Alright!

806
01:06:03,165 --> 01:06:05,098
Alert the press to
wait for further instructions

807
01:06:05,132 --> 01:06:07,597
My bedroom will be
the War-room for this operation

808
01:06:08,398 --> 01:06:12,025
To anyone else
I am drunk and have fallen asleep

809
01:06:14,166 --> 01:06:16,360
Except by you, I cannot be reached

810
01:06:17,601 --> 01:06:18,294
Go

811
01:06:25,834 --> 01:06:28,562
A fight resulted from two taxi drivers
solicitating the same customer

812
01:06:28,602 --> 01:06:31,091
Now the two taxi companies
are gathering their gangs

813
01:06:31,135 --> 01:06:32,726
After heated argument
they began fighting

814
01:06:32,768 --> 01:06:35,791
Now the heart of Taipei
is completely paralyzed

815
01:06:35,835 --> 01:06:37,994
The police is now on site
to try to solve the dispute

816
01:06:38,035 --> 01:06:40,093
If you are intending to pass through
Sai Mun-ting, please reroute

817
01:06:40,136 --> 01:06:42,863
Son, I've seen my daughter-in-law...

818
01:06:42,903 --> 01:06:45,563
Reporting on TV

819
01:06:45,904 --> 01:06:48,495
Work is important
but she can't work with an empty stomach

820
01:06:48,537 --> 01:06:50,332
I'm going to send her some food

821
01:06:50,805 --> 01:06:53,397
Dad, don't go there, it's dangerous

822
01:06:53,705 --> 01:06:57,467
Dangerous? Not compared to
what I've been through before

823
01:06:57,505 --> 01:07:01,063
When I fought the Japanese
you were not even born yet

824
01:07:02,607 --> 01:07:04,129
Cut it out, will you?

825
01:07:08,807 --> 01:07:10,500
Damn it!

826
01:07:24,175 --> 01:07:26,266
Yes

827
01:07:26,308 --> 01:07:28,899
Don't worry, I'll take care of it

828
01:07:31,576 --> 01:07:32,633
Damn you!

829
01:07:33,610 --> 01:07:36,303
I want a fight
but the Commissioner wants negotiation

830
01:07:36,343 --> 01:07:38,434
The other gang just doesn't want to talk

831
01:07:39,676 --> 01:07:40,607
Damn!

832
01:08:28,916 --> 01:08:32,575
Drivers of the 2 taxi companies
are fighting fiercely...

833
01:08:32,616 --> 01:08:33,548
under the bridge

834
01:08:33,583 --> 01:08:34,412
And we can see

835
01:08:34,450 --> 01:08:38,541
more taxies from Chuen-kuok Company
are still moving in

836
01:08:38,582 --> 01:08:41,640
The situation will definitely get worse

837
01:08:41,683 --> 01:08:44,446
Right here, we see only 20 cops

838
01:08:44,485 --> 01:08:47,609
But no one from any government dept
is on the scene

839
01:09:29,389 --> 01:09:31,786
What! Do it!

840
01:09:32,155 --> 01:09:33,053
Yes

841
01:09:34,156 --> 01:09:35,621
Kwan, go

842
01:09:55,093 --> 01:09:56,490
No shooting...

843
01:10:56,833 --> 01:10:59,264
Kuo-fei...

844
01:11:01,468 --> 01:11:04,864
It's dangerous. Leave!

845
01:11:05,166 --> 01:11:06,563
Have you seen my dad?

846
01:11:06,866 --> 01:11:07,629
What did you say?

847
01:11:08,268 --> 01:11:09,495
Have you seen my dad?

848
01:11:51,705 --> 01:11:53,535
You must leave here at once

849
01:11:54,307 --> 01:11:55,362
Leave me alone

850
01:12:02,806 --> 01:12:04,034
Run, my son!

851
01:12:17,009 --> 01:12:19,167
Push! Push!

852
01:12:28,310 --> 01:12:30,708
Son

853
01:12:30,910 --> 01:12:32,035
I'm fine

854
01:13:36,985 --> 01:13:39,347
When did you change
your hair style and dress?

855
01:13:39,384 --> 01:13:40,646
I went to the ball

856
01:13:41,085 --> 01:13:44,539
You're really something

857
01:14:03,855 --> 01:14:04,718
Commissioner

858
01:14:05,055 --> 01:14:07,418
Mr. Chau, I'm so sorry to bother you!

859
01:14:08,154 --> 01:14:10,348
We know you are not well
we have no choice but have to bother you

860
01:14:10,389 --> 01:14:11,446
Please take a seat

861
01:14:14,989 --> 01:14:19,251
If we haven't seen
Madam Chau in the ball

862
01:14:19,290 --> 01:14:20,880
I'll have no way of locating you

863
01:14:21,822 --> 01:14:24,289
My anti-riot troop
has been dispatched to the scene

864
01:14:24,323 --> 01:14:26,119
But, before any action is taken

865
01:14:26,624 --> 01:14:29,215
If they could reach an agreement

866
01:14:29,257 --> 01:14:31,779
That will avoid
a lot of unnecessary casualties

867
01:14:32,624 --> 01:14:37,613
So, I wish you would
help settle this riot

868
01:14:38,226 --> 01:14:41,487
I have been asleep for an hour
how come the world has become a mess?

869
01:14:41,525 --> 01:14:42,512
Let's go

870
01:14:44,625 --> 01:14:46,854
Mr. Chau
don't you need to change first?

871
01:14:46,893 --> 01:14:49,587
We need to save lives
time is of the essence here

872
01:14:49,627 --> 01:14:50,422
Let's go

873
01:14:53,526 --> 01:14:54,993
Give Kwan a call

874
01:15:12,929 --> 01:15:14,418
No pictures...

875
01:15:14,462 --> 01:15:15,553
Chau Chiu-sen

876
01:15:15,596 --> 01:15:17,893
candidate for the Legislative Council
Election, has effectively

877
01:15:17,930 --> 01:15:22,193
put down a riot between the taxi drivers

878
01:15:22,231 --> 01:15:25,958
Chau Chiu-sen
is willing to give assistance...

879
01:15:25,997 --> 01:15:29,328
to the injured and deceased
police and drivers

880
01:15:30,032 --> 01:15:33,225
I feel very bad about such a riot

881
01:15:33,264 --> 01:15:36,231
I can't imagine that such small fight
would end up to be a tragedy like this

882
01:15:37,998 --> 01:15:39,896
A small quarrel

883
01:15:39,932 --> 01:15:42,422
could ignite a riot in Taiwan

884
01:15:42,666 --> 01:15:45,791
Watching the guys lying on the floor
soaked with blood

885
01:15:46,199 --> 01:15:49,188
If you were their relatives
how would you feel?

886
01:15:50,066 --> 01:15:51,726
While we are threatened by
external military power

887
01:15:51,767 --> 01:15:54,199
We are still fighting
among ourselves domestically

888
01:15:54,234 --> 01:15:55,859
So much worries
both externally and internally

889
01:15:55,900 --> 01:15:57,696
is breaking our hearts

890
01:15:58,868 --> 01:16:00,766
What we don't understand is

891
01:16:00,801 --> 01:16:04,426
Why peace only
comes after severe injury?

892
01:16:10,069 --> 01:16:11,330
Please take it back

893
01:16:12,870 --> 01:16:13,699
I am leaving

894
01:16:13,870 --> 01:16:14,665
OK

895
01:16:19,903 --> 01:16:20,835
Don't look

896
01:16:53,774 --> 01:16:56,968
This is what I found
while I was being suspended

897
01:16:59,374 --> 01:17:00,534
What do you think?

898
01:17:01,841 --> 01:17:04,808
I think Chau Chiu-sen, Ting Chung-shu

899
01:17:04,842 --> 01:17:07,898
And those on the video tapes
are all criminals

900
01:17:08,609 --> 01:17:11,303
They should all be put behind bars

901
01:17:12,177 --> 01:17:15,574
I hope the Commissioner
would back me up in this mission

902
01:17:15,610 --> 01:17:18,270
You do know there are
still big bosses behind them?

903
01:17:19,977 --> 01:17:20,806
I know

904
01:17:21,910 --> 01:17:24,468
So, why do something you have
so little chance of succeeding?

905
01:17:27,444 --> 01:17:29,274
I love this land

906
01:17:29,711 --> 01:17:33,735
I can't let these scumbags mess it up

907
01:17:34,345 --> 01:17:37,403
Many years ago
they ruined Mainland China

908
01:17:37,446 --> 01:17:39,434
Our people retreated to Taiwan

909
01:17:39,478 --> 01:17:43,343
If they ruin Taiwan now

910
01:17:43,379 --> 01:17:45,140
Where can we go?

911
01:17:46,113 --> 01:17:48,579
We have our backs against the sea

912
01:17:49,947 --> 01:17:52,413
You are as tough as I was

913
01:17:52,447 --> 01:17:53,572
Very good

914
01:17:54,415 --> 01:17:57,006
We are waiting for someone
to light up Taiwan

915
01:17:57,048 --> 01:18:00,105
You are the torch we need

916
01:18:00,148 --> 01:18:02,342
Kuo-fei, go ahead and do it

917
01:18:02,381 --> 01:18:03,814
I will support you

918
01:18:04,150 --> 01:18:04,843
Thank you

919
01:18:33,053 --> 01:18:34,678
What took you so long?

920
01:18:34,719 --> 01:18:36,844
The air conditioner is out of order

921
01:18:36,886 --> 01:18:38,183
I'll go fix it right away

922
01:18:47,521 --> 01:18:48,953
Boss, something's coming up

923
01:18:49,288 --> 01:18:50,980
Take a look

924
01:18:53,821 --> 01:18:55,412
Isn't that Ting Chung-shu?

925
01:19:01,455 --> 01:19:03,751
Chairman Hau's wife is here
to collect his takes again

926
01:19:10,990 --> 01:19:12,047
No smoking

927
01:19:12,090 --> 01:19:13,215
What's up?

928
01:19:16,290 --> 01:19:17,723
Do you want to stuff this in?

929
01:19:18,058 --> 01:19:20,388
This crook is doing one of his fake
Miracle Split shot again

930
01:19:20,757 --> 01:19:23,088
His disciples are really buying his act

931
01:19:23,125 --> 01:19:25,283
Each of these photos
are selling for $5,000

932
01:19:27,558 --> 01:19:29,855
During the last few days
I have been very restless

933
01:19:29,893 --> 01:19:32,051
I can feel some evil spirit
disturbing me

934
01:19:32,092 --> 01:19:33,115
What?

935
01:19:33,159 --> 01:19:34,284
What kind of bull shit is that?

936
01:19:34,326 --> 01:19:35,349
Vice-Chairman Hau

937
01:19:35,392 --> 01:19:37,222
To make it simple

938
01:19:37,260 --> 01:19:39,782
I feel that someone has been tailing me
during the last few days

939
01:19:42,359 --> 01:19:44,155
I don't know you that well

940
01:19:44,193 --> 01:19:46,626
How come you have my phone number?

941
01:19:46,661 --> 01:19:48,422
Lease don't call me again

942
01:20:01,562 --> 01:20:02,493
Get rid of him

943
01:20:02,529 --> 01:20:04,086
Use the press against Chau Chiu-sen

944
01:20:42,300 --> 01:20:44,097
Let's go

945
01:20:44,134 --> 01:20:44,997
Got you

946
01:20:46,601 --> 01:20:47,430
Go

947
01:21:58,709 --> 01:22:00,834
What are you doing?

948
01:22:01,576 --> 01:22:03,475
Please help...

949
01:22:05,777 --> 01:22:07,106
We are trapped

950
01:22:07,143 --> 01:22:09,269
Someone tried to shoot at me
but a woman was shot instead

951
01:22:09,311 --> 01:22:10,503
Call the ambulance

952
01:23:02,883 --> 01:23:03,974
Be careful!

953
01:23:27,152 --> 01:23:28,915
Now I am in front of the noodle stall

954
01:23:30,820 --> 01:23:32,547
Now I am in front of the noodle stall

955
01:23:38,754 --> 01:23:40,380
Now I am in front of the noodle stall

956
01:24:13,559 --> 01:24:14,684
Nicotine

957
01:24:15,192 --> 01:24:17,215
Mei Li, take Nicotine away

958
01:24:20,460 --> 01:24:21,858
Come on, please hang on

959
01:24:22,993 --> 01:24:24,288
Watch out and be careful

960
01:24:24,359 --> 01:24:25,383
Get down

961
01:24:32,527 --> 01:24:33,924
Get down

962
01:24:41,328 --> 01:24:42,590
Everyone, get down!

963
01:25:12,165 --> 01:25:12,961
After them!

964
01:25:13,965 --> 01:25:14,895
Go!

965
01:25:56,237 --> 01:26:00,999
Legislative Councilor candidate
Chau Chiu-sen is rumored to be...

966
01:26:01,037 --> 01:26:05,061
Associated with the shooting of inspectors
Fong & Ngai at the Shi-lin night market

967
01:26:05,105 --> 01:26:07,593
Chau was alleged to be running
video arcaded casinos and

968
01:26:07,638 --> 01:26:09,605
is also behind the rigging of bidding
for gov't construction contract

969
01:26:09,639 --> 01:26:11,969
Fong and his team members...

970
01:26:12,006 --> 01:26:13,404
Including Wah and Mei Li are all missing

971
01:26:13,439 --> 01:26:14,769
What are you laughing at?

972
01:26:14,806 --> 01:26:16,930
You are really popular these days

973
01:26:16,972 --> 01:26:19,495
I keep seeing your face in all the media

974
01:26:19,539 --> 01:26:22,664
You have a bigger exposure
than our president

975
01:26:23,707 --> 01:26:25,435
Tell me, what's so funny?

976
01:26:25,475 --> 01:26:27,303
If you can't give me a satisfactory
explanation, I'll beat you up

977
01:26:28,073 --> 01:26:31,529
All right! I am thinking what if you
become our president one day

978
01:26:31,642 --> 01:26:32,767
It's not funny at all

979
01:26:32,808 --> 01:26:33,932
Really?

980
01:26:42,109 --> 01:26:44,098
Yesterday, I imagined how you would
look when you grow old...

981
01:26:44,142 --> 01:26:45,200
See!

982
01:26:50,409 --> 01:26:51,932
Just like our president!

983
01:26:53,077 --> 01:26:54,940
You are holy...

984
01:26:57,411 --> 01:26:58,933
Shit!

985
01:27:01,611 --> 01:27:02,804
Stop crying!

986
01:27:03,378 --> 01:27:04,810
Help!

987
01:27:13,145 --> 01:27:27,104
Chau Chiu-sen

988
01:27:27,147 --> 01:27:32,444
Murder must withdraw

989
01:27:32,481 --> 01:27:35,448
It's rumored that
a guy named Chau is involved in

990
01:27:35,482 --> 01:27:37,472
bid rigging for a gov't project

991
01:27:37,782 --> 01:27:40,304
Investigators were able to get proof

992
01:27:40,348 --> 01:27:42,008
Chau is also rumored
to be involved with the murder

993
01:27:42,048 --> 01:27:43,743
of an investigator I Chin-kuo
in Shi-lin Night Market

994
01:27:43,783 --> 01:27:48,341
Now, the focus is on Chau

995
01:27:48,616 --> 01:27:51,777
It's suspected that
it is a revenge by Chau

996
01:27:51,851 --> 01:27:52,975
My friends...

997
01:27:53,017 --> 01:27:54,949
Murder must not become
a Legislative Councilor

998
01:27:54,983 --> 01:28:00,644
The murderer should withdraw
from the election

999
01:28:00,684 --> 01:28:02,275
Damn you!

1000
01:28:02,318 --> 01:28:04,443
Shit...

1001
01:28:07,486 --> 01:28:09,975
Beat him!

1002
01:28:21,055 --> 01:28:22,576
Stop your bull shit!

1003
01:28:22,620 --> 01:28:27,519
If you have guts

1004
01:28:27,554 --> 01:28:29,077
Come with me in front of
the temple to make an oath

1005
01:28:29,122 --> 01:28:32,383
I swear
my husband never did such a thing

1006
01:28:32,421 --> 01:28:33,182
If he did

1007
01:28:33,221 --> 01:28:34,983
I, Tsui Miu-heung
will be found lying dead in the street

1008
01:28:35,022 --> 01:28:36,011
so everyone can step on me

1009
01:28:36,390 --> 01:28:37,878
But you have to make an oath too

1010
01:28:37,922 --> 01:28:39,854
If you maliciously spread
such harmful rumors

1011
01:28:39,889 --> 01:28:42,321
You'll die a horrible death with no
children bearing your family name any more

1012
01:28:47,224 --> 01:28:50,713
This is not rumor started by me
This is written in newspapers

1013
01:28:50,758 --> 01:28:51,917
This is public knowledge

1014
01:28:51,958 --> 01:28:53,548
Everyone knows it

1015
01:28:53,591 --> 01:28:57,080
Besides, I have never said
your husband is a murderer

1016
01:28:58,258 --> 01:29:02,623
I never do my watching with my ears

1017
01:29:02,659 --> 01:29:06,251
But I did see you working in a nightclub

1018
01:29:06,292 --> 01:29:08,689
as a hostess 10 years ago

1019
01:29:10,160 --> 01:29:12,217
You readily provided sexual service
to any man who asked

1020
01:29:12,260 --> 01:29:13,748
No, you liar!

1021
01:29:13,793 --> 01:29:15,156
No, I assure you it's a right fact

1022
01:29:16,626 --> 01:29:18,184
Damn you! Ting Chung-shu

1023
01:29:18,228 --> 01:29:19,420
Are you a real man?

1024
01:29:19,460 --> 01:29:20,255
You can insult me

1025
01:29:20,293 --> 01:29:21,658
But you cannot insult my wife

1026
01:29:21,695 --> 01:29:22,592
Let me handle this

1027
01:29:22,628 --> 01:29:25,116
Chiu-sen, you are a gentleman
let me say something

1028
01:29:25,161 --> 01:29:26,058
Quiet!

1029
01:29:26,094 --> 01:29:27,685
Quiet!

1030
01:29:27,728 --> 01:29:29,489
Quiet please, listen to me
let me say something

1031
01:29:30,194 --> 01:29:31,251
Quiet

1032
01:29:34,529 --> 01:29:39,485
Ladies and gentlemen

1033
01:29:40,964 --> 01:29:42,759
Yes, I worked in a nightclub

1034
01:29:43,296 --> 01:29:44,818
I have an unfortunate past

1035
01:29:44,863 --> 01:29:46,193
I never denied it

1036
01:29:47,398 --> 01:29:50,728
There are things I regret having done

1037
01:29:52,097 --> 01:29:53,996
Chiu-sen knows everything

1038
01:29:55,097 --> 01:29:57,928
But, he hasn't despised me

1039
01:29:58,798 --> 01:30:01,595
Yes, he was a triad kingpin

1040
01:30:01,633 --> 01:30:03,791
But bygone is bygone

1041
01:30:04,999 --> 01:30:07,521
I hope everyone would give him a chance

1042
01:30:08,733 --> 01:30:10,858
So that he can do something
for our country

1043
01:30:11,099 --> 01:30:13,532
Think, if he can help reform me

1044
01:30:13,567 --> 01:30:16,032
Surely he can help
reform this country as well

1045
01:33:35,690 --> 01:33:37,919
Chairman, how are you?

1046
01:33:37,957 --> 01:33:41,185
I saw your car from above

1047
01:33:41,224 --> 01:33:43,383
That's why I come to say hello

1048
01:33:44,091 --> 01:33:45,421
Chairman

1049
01:33:49,159 --> 01:33:52,592
Are you going to
Ting Chun-shu's funeral?

1050
01:33:52,626 --> 01:33:54,614
No, I am going to
attend my friend's wedding

1051
01:33:57,893 --> 01:34:00,188
When did you join the air force?

1052
01:34:00,727 --> 01:34:05,455
The traffic jam is getting worse

1053
01:34:05,492 --> 01:34:09,256
If I don't buy a helicopter
I can't control my time

1054
01:34:10,594 --> 01:34:15,185
Chairman, there are so many
social problems to be solved

1055
01:34:15,227 --> 01:34:17,523
I wish to become a councilor
as fast as possible

1056
01:34:17,561 --> 01:34:20,460
So I can work with you
to service our people

1057
01:34:25,163 --> 01:34:26,685
Do you want a ride?

1058
01:34:27,328 --> 01:34:30,353
That's great, I am in a hurry

1059
01:34:34,364 --> 01:34:35,727
This way please

1060
01:34:42,565 --> 01:34:43,962
Have you seen the TV live broadcast?

1061
01:34:43,998 --> 01:34:46,021
Chau won the election by a big margin

1062
01:34:49,498 --> 01:34:52,193
Chau has been elected councilor

1063
01:34:53,233 --> 01:34:56,096
The big surprise is
as a first time candidate

1064
01:34:56,132 --> 01:35:00,657
Mr. Chau... got 125,000 votes
a very high figure

1065
01:35:00,701 --> 01:35:03,690
With all the controversy
surrounding him lately

1066
01:35:03,734 --> 01:35:08,860
He is receiving a lot of press coverage
building awareness for him

1067
01:35:08,902 --> 01:35:11,595
What a beautiful way
to begin his political life

1068
01:35:51,339 --> 01:35:51,895
Good morning

1069
01:35:51,939 --> 01:35:52,802
Good morning

1070
01:35:53,073 --> 01:35:54,630
Time is running short

1071
01:35:55,640 --> 01:35:57,664
Soon, I will be forced to resign

1072
01:35:57,941 --> 01:36:00,736
Do what you have to do

1073
01:36:46,213 --> 01:36:48,338
The Master splits again

1074
01:36:57,881 --> 01:37:01,539
Now, you are watching
proof of your crime

1075
01:37:02,013 --> 01:37:05,674
You know you are guilty

1076
01:37:08,649 --> 01:37:12,081
My name is Sung Miu-dee
brother of Sung Miu-tin

1077
01:37:12,115 --> 01:37:15,241
Miu Tin has forced me
to be his split image cover

1078
01:37:16,016 --> 01:37:18,244
I was short and thin

1079
01:37:18,917 --> 01:37:20,883
He didn't let me do any exercise

1080
01:37:20,917 --> 01:37:24,144
And he stuffed me with food

1081
01:37:24,183 --> 01:37:26,014
He gave me plastic surgery

1082
01:37:26,151 --> 01:37:28,446
He removed half of my hair

1083
01:37:28,484 --> 01:37:31,451
Broke my knee caps to make me taller

1084
01:37:31,751 --> 01:37:34,274
He ordered me to
wear high-heel shoes everyday

1085
01:37:36,151 --> 01:37:39,243
Apart from your profitable
religious racket

1086
01:37:39,853 --> 01:37:45,443
You still sell drugs with Ting
behind your boss's back

1087
01:37:45,485 --> 01:37:49,976
Urn number 19 is the place
you hide the drugs, right?

1088
01:37:50,620 --> 01:37:55,678
You use religious healing as an excuse

1089
01:37:55,721 --> 01:37:57,550
To rape a lot of woman disciples

1090
01:37:57,587 --> 01:37:58,553
Mrs. Hau?

1091
01:37:58,587 --> 01:37:59,917
That's right

1092
01:38:01,155 --> 01:38:03,143
I'll be damned...

1093
01:38:03,388 --> 01:38:05,081
How come you have this picture?
He screwed Mrs. Hau?

1094
01:38:05,988 --> 01:38:07,544
Computer-graphic

1095
01:38:07,588 --> 01:38:08,986
I only suspected it

1096
01:38:09,389 --> 01:38:11,515
But judging from his face
I know I am correct

1097
01:38:12,090 --> 01:38:13,282
Get ready

1098
01:38:14,222 --> 01:38:16,381
Alright, time's up

1099
01:38:26,690 --> 01:38:27,747
Let him talk

1100
01:38:31,891 --> 01:38:34,618
I know I am guilty

1101
01:38:34,658 --> 01:38:38,954
Please give me a chance

1102
01:38:42,625 --> 01:38:44,523
How are you, boss?

1103
01:39:04,595 --> 01:39:05,958
Hi! Master

1104
01:39:15,031 --> 01:39:16,552
Master

1105
01:39:21,298 --> 01:39:22,820
This is for Madam Chau

1106
01:40:05,036 --> 01:40:07,127
Master Hung

1107
01:40:25,671 --> 01:40:27,160
This way please

1108
01:40:42,873 --> 01:40:47,465
May I propose a toast to the four
new Legislative Councilors

1109
01:40:48,041 --> 01:40:50,529
Welcome

1110
01:40:50,574 --> 01:40:52,870
Cheers

1111
01:40:58,209 --> 01:41:03,040
In the Legislative Council
there are 164 seats

1112
01:41:03,442 --> 01:41:08,569
Thirteen of us are from the triads

1113
01:41:08,610 --> 01:41:09,769
Now, what I have to say is this

1114
01:41:09,809 --> 01:41:12,536
We must be united

1115
01:41:12,576 --> 01:41:16,600
We must not have a Judah
betraying each other

1116
01:41:20,045 --> 01:41:23,010
I heard that the government
is preparing a 3rd liquidation

1117
01:41:23,044 --> 01:41:27,239
The code name is Chi-ping

1118
01:41:27,278 --> 01:41:33,234
That's why you are invited
We need a solution

1119
01:41:41,146 --> 01:41:43,635
May I know where the toilet is?

1120
01:41:44,013 --> 01:41:46,343
Last month you earned 87 million

1121
01:41:46,380 --> 01:41:48,574
Which is 17 million
more than the previous month

1122
01:41:48,615 --> 01:41:50,739
You are to be complimented

1123
01:41:51,347 --> 01:41:52,869
That's because Madam Chau

1124
01:41:52,913 --> 01:41:55,574
and Mr. Chau decided to
join our Board of Directors

1125
01:41:55,615 --> 01:41:56,638
It brought great

1126
01:41:56,682 --> 01:41:59,649
Fung-shui to our villa

1127
01:41:59,683 --> 01:42:00,671
Really?

1128
01:42:19,418 --> 01:42:23,874
Mr. Chau rises so rapidly

1129
01:42:23,918 --> 01:42:26,406
It's just like
he is sitting in a helicopter

1130
01:42:26,451 --> 01:42:28,974
That's because he bought a helicopter

1131
01:42:31,086 --> 01:42:35,018
We treat the government as our buddy

1132
01:42:36,586 --> 01:42:40,076
We are most obliging to their needs

1133
01:42:41,087 --> 01:42:45,213
Anything they want
we provide money, manpower

1134
01:42:46,554 --> 01:42:48,247
But, once he thinks you are useless
or gets in their way

1135
01:42:48,287 --> 01:42:49,912
He will get rid of you

1136
01:42:50,821 --> 01:42:54,548
First Liquidation and Second Liquidation
an iron fisted campaign

1137
01:42:54,588 --> 01:42:56,680
No judiciary process
instant arrest and jail sentence

1138
01:42:57,889 --> 01:43:02,220
Quite a few of us here, including me

1139
01:43:02,257 --> 01:43:03,984
were imprisoned

1140
01:43:04,022 --> 01:43:05,544
Tough life, huh?

1141
01:43:06,690 --> 01:43:09,156
As our master Tao Yu-sang said

1142
01:43:11,890 --> 01:43:14,323
The government treats you as a night pot

1143
01:43:14,791 --> 01:43:17,279
When it's no longer useful
they think you stink

1144
01:43:17,324 --> 01:43:19,314
They will just throw you under the bed

1145
01:43:22,259 --> 01:43:24,690
During the first
and the second liquidation

1146
01:43:24,726 --> 01:43:27,282
None of our buddies
were legislative councilors

1147
01:43:28,559 --> 01:43:31,424
Now, among the 164 seats

1148
01:43:31,460 --> 01:43:33,221
We occupy 10%

1149
01:43:33,926 --> 01:43:38,881
And over half of the rest
are closely associated with us

1150
01:43:39,594 --> 01:43:44,493
They include local representatives
Mayors, etc

1151
01:43:44,528 --> 01:43:46,857
Many are gangsters

1152
01:43:47,927 --> 01:43:50,689
We have over 2 million
gangsters in Taiwan

1153
01:43:52,561 --> 01:43:54,858
May I ask a question

1154
01:43:54,896 --> 01:43:58,988
Can you tell me whether the 13
legislative councilors here...

1155
01:43:59,029 --> 01:44:00,586
Are politicians or triads?

1156
01:44:00,662 --> 01:44:02,594
They've become one

1157
01:44:03,029 --> 01:44:06,792
When wise guys become politicians

1158
01:44:08,730 --> 01:44:10,195
After the process of white wash

1159
01:44:11,231 --> 01:44:13,789
From black to white

1160
01:44:15,098 --> 01:44:17,995
What exactly have we become?

1161
01:44:19,065 --> 01:44:22,896
I said, we are neither

1162
01:44:22,932 --> 01:44:24,761
We are a hybrid

1163
01:44:27,298 --> 01:44:30,890
So, why don't we organize all
our buddies all over the country

1164
01:44:30,932 --> 01:44:32,830
Dissolve all the gangs

1165
01:44:32,866 --> 01:44:34,731
And form a new party

1166
01:44:34,768 --> 01:44:36,666
I guarantee that

1167
01:44:36,701 --> 01:44:40,463
We will become the biggest party
within three years

1168
01:44:40,868 --> 01:44:43,959
We can easily be the ruling party

1169
01:44:44,535 --> 01:44:48,524
We can have our meetings
in the President House

1170
01:44:49,535 --> 01:44:53,297
We don't need to act stealthily

1171
01:44:58,935 --> 01:45:01,163
We can hold our heads up

1172
01:45:03,604 --> 01:45:06,593
Let's go to Lu-tao by helicopter

1173
01:45:07,505 --> 01:45:10,698
And turn the place into a golf course

1174
01:45:10,737 --> 01:45:12,669
Let's go play golf

1175
01:45:13,371 --> 01:45:16,360
Yeah, play golf in Lu-tao

1176
01:45:17,038 --> 01:45:19,470
Good speech!

1177
01:45:20,072 --> 01:45:22,833
Last month, we're supposed to
make a deposit into a bank account

1178
01:45:22,872 --> 01:45:24,840
held by Mrs. Hau's distant relative
a Mr. Leung

1179
01:45:24,874 --> 01:45:27,032
The sum was 3.2 million dollars

1180
01:45:27,073 --> 01:45:29,663
The man claimed
he only received 1 million

1181
01:45:29,705 --> 01:45:32,969
The signed receipt should be with you

1182
01:45:33,007 --> 01:45:34,563
I hope you can check it for me

1183
01:45:34,607 --> 01:45:36,574
So I can inform Mrs. Hau immediately

1184
01:45:36,608 --> 01:45:39,699
Alright, please wait

1185
01:45:39,741 --> 01:45:40,797
Thank you

1186
01:45:55,276 --> 01:45:58,140
Ling Fei, I would like to employ
the influence of the press

1187
01:46:15,378 --> 01:46:18,038
Master Sung is tying his shoe laces at
location 18, on the 2nd floor

1188
01:46:18,079 --> 01:46:18,942
Something's wrong

1189
01:46:33,214 --> 01:46:34,611
Arrest them

1190
01:46:58,383 --> 01:46:59,315
The master is missing

1191
01:47:22,620 --> 01:47:23,483
Run

1192
01:48:36,795 --> 01:48:39,523
Call our people from Tao-yuen
Sin-yuk, Nam-han and Tai-yuen

1193
01:48:39,561 --> 01:48:41,926
Instruct them to stop those guys

1194
01:48:41,962 --> 01:48:43,552
I'll be there in three minutes

1195
01:49:04,832 --> 01:49:06,765
This way...

1196
01:49:21,000 --> 01:49:22,693
Run!

1197
01:49:23,733 --> 01:49:24,632
Run!

1198
01:49:43,903 --> 01:49:45,732
It's too late, the press has arrived

1199
01:49:45,769 --> 01:49:47,031
What?

1200
01:50:15,641 --> 01:50:17,038
Excuse me

1201
01:50:47,943 --> 01:50:49,739
How do you find me here?

1202
01:50:51,144 --> 01:50:52,541
The boss knows everything

1203
01:50:56,911 --> 01:50:58,878
Do you have a solution?

1204
01:51:00,611 --> 01:51:01,872
What do you think?

1205
01:51:03,511 --> 01:51:05,477
I can go very high with my offer

1206
01:51:06,779 --> 01:51:07,767
How high?

1207
01:51:08,313 --> 01:51:09,710
Sky high

1208
01:51:17,113 --> 01:51:19,307
Are you willing to leave Taiwan?

1209
01:51:21,848 --> 01:51:23,711
Yes, but I wish to
come back at some point

1210
01:51:24,381 --> 01:51:26,370
The Boss has a similar idea

1211
01:51:35,483 --> 01:51:38,539
Actually
you don't even need to leave Taiwan

1212
01:51:38,582 --> 01:51:40,811
Just live in Benefaction Villa

1213
01:51:40,850 --> 01:51:42,476
Never to come out again

1214
01:53:23,495 --> 01:53:24,587
Damn it

1215
01:53:25,696 --> 01:53:27,990
Are you in a hurry?

1216
01:53:28,028 --> 01:53:29,756
Would you like me to give you a lift?

1217
01:53:58,099 --> 01:54:00,656
Brother...

1218
01:54:00,699 --> 01:54:02,961
Can we talk about it?

1219
01:54:03,600 --> 01:54:05,065
What do you think?

1220
01:54:06,266 --> 01:54:09,721
Now that we are in the air

1221
01:54:09,767 --> 01:54:12,665
Can your offer go sky high?

1222
01:54:55,406 --> 01:54:57,235
"Resignation"

1223
01:55:00,074 --> 01:55:01,766
Any news on Chau Chiu-sen?

1224
01:55:52,478 --> 01:55:56,001
This is Ling Fei reporting live

1225
01:55:56,045 --> 01:55:58,706
We are following Legislative Councilor
Chau on his escape route

1226
01:55:58,746 --> 01:56:00,473
Chau is being escorted by

1227
01:56:00,513 --> 01:56:03,946
over 30 vehicles

1228
01:56:03,980 --> 01:56:07,776
The entourage is traveling on
Jie Tung Highway heading south

1229
01:56:12,114 --> 01:56:14,978
Watch out, there are journalists ahead

1230
01:56:30,749 --> 01:56:33,182
San-pao, what is that strange noise?

1231
01:56:49,552 --> 01:56:50,643
Go for him

1232
01:57:11,856 --> 01:57:13,048
Get him

1233
01:57:46,427 --> 01:57:47,550
San Pao!

1234
01:59:23,637 --> 01:59:24,897
Heung

1235
01:59:31,170 --> 01:59:32,500
Heung

1236
01:59:39,772 --> 01:59:40,997
Chau Chiu-sen

1237
01:59:49,206 --> 01:59:50,331
Go!

1238
02:01:50,419 --> 02:01:54,910
The biggest scandal since Taiwan entered
the age of democracy has just erupted

1239
02:01:54,954 --> 02:01:58,249
Legislative Councilor Chau
has been found guilty

1240
02:01:58,287 --> 02:02:01,277
Capital punishment has been imposed

1241
02:02:01,321 --> 02:02:04,152
Master Sung Miu-tin
who turned witness for the plaintiff

1242
02:02:04,189 --> 02:02:08,781
Also the Minister Sun
were both convicted...

1243
02:02:08,823 --> 02:02:10,550
And are given jail terms
on Lu-tao Prison

1244
02:02:10,589 --> 02:02:14,147
This case has sparked off
an avalanche of scandals

1245
02:02:14,190 --> 02:02:16,418
A lot of senior government officials
has fled the country

1246
02:02:16,457 --> 02:02:21,754
The chief inspector Fong Kuo-fei
and Minister of the Legal Department

1247
02:02:21,790 --> 02:02:25,553
have both resigned under
immense pressure from society at large

