HEN RY LOUIS GATES, JR:
By the middle of the 1950s,
African Americans had
fought and died in war,
achieved success in business,
attained fame on the stage,
on screen, and on
the playing field.
But in the South, they couldn't
sit in the front of a bus
or eat a hamburger
at a lunch counter.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Nearly
a century after emancipation,
many found these
contradictions intolerable.
Out of this was born a new
determination and resolve
to stand up and fight.
At first, these defiant acts
were tiny ripples of hope,
as Robert Kennedy
once described them.
But soon, they would converge to
form a mighty current of change,
in a mass movement that would
forever alter America.
MARTIN LUTHER KING, JR.:
I have a dream this afternoon
that one day...
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by
Senegal, Africa-
The Door of No Return.
From these shores, millions
of Africans went across oceans
and continents, battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud to
sponsor "Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years of
African American history.
We believe connecting to
our past helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it.
Wi-Fi.
Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational.
Thanks.
Others, just a few minutes.
Jimmy Jones Ill.
Either way, our signal is
strong and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy of
staying in touch.
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER:
The Howard and Abby Milstein
Foundation, in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Ban k.
African American history
is an epic story--
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in
supporting your public
television station.
AN NOUN CE RI
The Coca-Cola Company,
the Ford Foundation JustFilms,
Dr. Georgette Bennett
and Dr. Leonard Polonsky,
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H. Tanenbaum,
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National Endowment
for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation for
Public Broadcasting,
and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
GATES: The prologue
to the great drama
of the civil rights movement
began in the 1940s,
in northern cities like Detroit.
Tens of thousands of African
Americans migrated here,
lured by the promise
of a better life.
Jobs in the auto industry
offered many black Americans
their first chance
to earn a living wage.
But economic opportunity
did not mean equal treatment.
My dad and 99%
of all blacks
worked in the foundry.
The foundry is
the dirtiest place
at the Ford Motor
Company you could
have at that time.
There were no unions.
There was no
vacation time.
You punched in,
you punched out,
and my father
would come home with
burns all over his face.
It was just humiliating.
GATES: And the foundry
was where they put Negroes.
And the foundry was
where they put Negroes.
GATES: As black workers
poured into Detroit,
racial tensions mounted,
over jobs, housing, even access
to public space.
And then...
MAN ON RADIO:
We interrupt this program
to bring you a special
news bulletin.
The Japanese have attacked
Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, by air...
GATES: Pearl Harbor
turned Detroit,
and the rest of America,
upside down.
MAN ON FILM: Not just another
relatively simple automobile.
GATES: Almost overnight,
the automobile industry
stopped manufacturing cars
and started making bombers.
MAN ON FILM: ...each
had to be perfect.
SECOND MAN ON FILM: And another
giant missile shows its power.
GATES: Facing labor shortages
and pressure from black leaders,
FDR integrated defense industry
assembly lines.
And with that, simmering racial
tensions in Detroit exploded.
KEITH: Detroit was basically
a segregated city.
Not only was it segregated,
it was full of hatred.
You could see the animosity
between blacks and whites.
You had this mixture
of southern whites
and southern blacks
for the first time
being integrated
because of the war efforts,
and it was explosive.
The atmosphere
that engulfed our city.
GATES: During the war,
Detroit came to be known
as the arsenal of democracy,
but it also was an arsenal
of racial conﬂict.
A race war erupted here in 1943,
and some of the worst violence
occurred on this bridge.
The riots broke out.
Everything was in chaos.
My God.
The whites came into
the neighborhood,
just start fighting
and beating us up.
They came into
your neighborhood?
Yes. Oh, sure.
The hatred and venom
in these people.
I told my mother, I said,
"I'm just prepared
to die here
to save you and our family
in the city."
GATES: By the time the two-day
riot ended,
24 African Americans were dead,
more than half killed
by the Detroit police.
But unlike earlier riots,
this time,
when the smoke cleared,
African Americans refused
to return to the status quo.
They girded themselves
for a new kind of battle.
[Explosions and gunfire]
With the advent of World War ll,
African Americans saw
a further opportunity
to press their cause.
[Man shouting indistinctly]
GATES: Hundreds of thousands
went to war,
with the expectation
that their service
would earn them equal rights
once and for all.
Black men fought in
every American war
since the American Revolution,
in return for the promise
of equality,
but they never received
the right to full citizenship.
Black servicemen
and black leaders
decided in World War ll that
they would fin ally force America
to make good on that promise.
Seizing on the spirit
of the moment,
the black press mounted
the "Double V" campaign-
victory on two fronts,
again st Hitler overseas
and against racism at home.
If we are going to rally
to the colors, we must
make larger society aware that
it is conditional this time.
[Gunfire]
Victory at home
and victory abroad
became the mantra of men
and women as they marched off.
MAN: What happened was,
they went overseas,
made a lot of difference,
because they got a greater
sense of themselves, right,
they got a greater
measure of themselves.
[Bell ringing]
[indistinct shouting]
GATES: Christopher Parker,
a Navy veteran,
has written about
black servicemen
and their fight
for equal rights.
A lot of these men
wanted to fight
because they wanted
to prove their manhood.
They wanted to prove
their patriotism, right?
They were participating
in something
that they thought
would actually
not only free them,
but also, they
were participating
in something that
was bigger than them.
They were making
the world safe
for democracy.
Exactly. And some
white troops
tried to bring Jim Crow
over there with them,
and these black men
are like, "Not today.
"We're wearing
the same uniform.
We're fighting for
the same stuff here."
And we could die.
Equally.
And so they became
accustomed to fighting
Jim Crow overseas.
It was nothing but
a thing, you know,
when they came back.
So, it was a new Negro
who returned
from the war.
Yes.
LEWIS: Soldiers who
have experienced,
who have liberated
concentration camps, even,
there is now a seriousness
of purpose.
We believed that the return
would bring us to a wand
that was men ding itself
and improving race relations.
Well, wishful thinking.
GATES: Though black soldiers
had changed,
much of the rest of the country
still had not.
Black veterans were unprepared
for the discrimination,
even violence, they faced
upon returning home.
It was February 1946.
Army Sergeant Isaac Woodard,
just back from a tour of duty
in the Pacific,
boarded a bus
in Augusta, Georgia.
At a routine stop, Sergeant
Woodard, in full uniform,
asked if he could
use the restroom.
The bus driver
cursed him and said no.
Woodard cursed him back,
demanding respect.
When they arrived
at the next stop,
Woodard was called off the bus,
where two police officers
were waiting for him.
When he tried to tell
his side of the story,
one of the officers beat him
in the head with a nightstick,
driving the end of it
into his eyes.
At 27, Sergeant Woodard
would be blinded
for the rest of his life.
African Americans mourned
the Woodard incident
within their own communities,
but now, after the war,
many white Americans
shared their shock and horror.
MAN ON RADIO: What does
it cost to be a Negro?
In Aiken, South Carolina,
it cost a man his eyes.
GATES: Film director
Orson Welles,
who hosted a weekly
political radio broadcast,
devoted an entire show
to the Woodard incident,
expressing his disgust
for the two policemen.
WELLES: ...Officer X,
all America is ashamed of you.
If there's room for pity,
you can have it,
for you're far more
blind than he.
For you're far more
GATES: But even when they
weren't evenly political,
radio broadcasts were beginning
to shake up the status quo,
especially in the South,
where you could segregate
virtually everything
but the airwaves.
MAN ON RADIO: Top of the morning
to you, my friends.
WDIA, 50,000 watts of goodwill,
invites you to join us...
GATES: In 1949, mite-owned
Memphis radio station WDIA
became an accidental agent
of social change.
Starved for listeners, it was
forced to broaden its audience.
They were losing money.
No sponsors.
They couldn't get anybody.
So, they brought in
this programming
that was directed toward
the African American--
there's 40% African Americans
in Memphis in 1948.
GATES: With little left to lose,
WDIA took a gamble.
They switched to
all-black programming.
The next year, within
a year, they're number two.
[Blues music ending]
All right. 1:34, 26 before 2:00
at AM 1070, your WDIA.
GATES: They also introduced
black DJs,
including Ford Nelson,
who'd once been a part
of B.B. King's band.
I've been looking forward
to this all the week.
GATES: 6 decades later,
he's still on the air.
Professor Henry Louis
"Skip" Gates.
Say something
to my audience.
You are a pioneer
and that's why I'm here.
62 years on the radio.
That's all right.
And I love the history
of WDIA,
"Mother Station of
the Negroes" as it was
called back in the day.
That's all right.
To our audience
and to our community,
we were a big deal.
It gave the black
community a feeling
of pride,
a feeling
of involvement,
and a feeling
of belonging.
So, we were just, like,
heroes, so to speak.
And I haven't forgotten
our new believers.
About this time on Sundays,
I like to remember-
GATES: But WDIA's contribution
went beyond community service.
Before long, white kids
began tuning in as well,
giving the station
an interracial audience
in the Jim Crow South.
So, in spite of
the fact that Memphis
is strictly segregated,
white people are
listening to black music
being played and
narrated by black DJs.
Sure. What I think
is really fascinating
is how these kids
who were coming of age
in the late 1940s
and early 1950s,
they're getting exposure
to a message
that is very much that
we are all the same.
So, subconsciously,
this is breaking down
a racial barrier.
I think it is.
[Nelson laughs on radio]
NELSON ON RADIO:
And now, folks, here we are,
smack dab at the end of another
day of broadcasting...
GATES:Across the country,
black culture
was becoming popular culture,
loosening assumptions
and quietly opening doors.
Americans watched
as Jackie Robinson
broke baseball's color line
and became the highest-paid
Dodger in history.
° when your love bird
decides to ﬂy °
°There ain't
no door that... °
GATES: 5 years later,
Dorothy Dandridge
became the first
African-American
nominated for an Academy Award
in a leading role.
° ...dream
a dream came“
GATES: While most black stars
supported civil rights,
few used their celebrity
for explicitly political ends.
° ...first thing you do... °
GATES:Actor and singer
Paul Robeson did.
° ...tell a lie... °
Free political expression is
the very essence of the defense
of our civil liberties, and
by that I shall always stand.
GATES: Robeson spoke
to audiences around the world,
condemning the United States
government
for promoting democracy abroad
while neglecting the rights
of its African American
citizens at home.
ROBESON: In attacking me,
they suggested
that when I was abroad,
I spoke out
against injustices to the Negro
people in the United States.
I certainly did.
GATES: Paul Robeson sought to
plead the cause of the Negro
right here,
at the United Nations.
In 1951, he presented a petition
entitled "We Charge Genocide:
The Crime of Government
Against the Negro People."
He chose the U.N.
because it would have
provided
a worldwide voice.
MAN: Robeson was pointing
to the fact that
in this country,
blacks were still living
in desperate circumstances,
and that
the federal government,
let alone
the state governments,
were doing almost
nothing about it.
He insisted that
economic deprivations
were just as destructive
of human life
as were the overt
policies of
a state regime,
like Hitler
and the Jews.
GATES: Robeson thought that
only a Communist revolution
could solve the problem
of racial discrimination
in America.
Most other
black leaders disagreed.
DUBERMAN: At that point in time,
the black leadership
in this country
still felt that they
had to present themselves
as good, patriotic Americans,
and there was no room for
Robeson in that scenario.
GATES: For more than a decade,
the NAACP had been mounting
a pain staking legal effort
to dismantle Jim Crow.
Robeson, to them, was
a dangerous gadﬂy.
How important do you
think Robeson was
to the creation
of the modern
civil rights movement?
Once the modem
civil rights
movement got going,
he was not regarded
as one of the great
precursors, which,
in fact, he was.
He was always
on the cutting edge
of racial justice.
GATES: Robeson introduced
a tactic that,
when the time was right,
others would repeat.
His public shaming of the United
States before the world
would prove to be a key strategy
used by others in the mass
movement to come,
a movement that would
ultimately sweep the nation,
but that began
in the American South.
The first major battle of
the civil rights movement
began on a city bus
in Montgomery, Alabama.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: On this bus,
on December 1,1955,
Rosa Parks refused to give up
her seat to a white man.
The battle over this very seat
launched a revolution,
and Rosa Parks became its icon.
Civil rights leaders
had long been looking
for the ideal candidate
to challenge segregation
on public buses.
Mrs. Parks
fit the bill perfectly.
LEWIS: She, of course,
doesn't come out of nowhere.
There had been
trial runs of 3 women
who were thought to be
not quite perfect.
So, the stars were
aligned with Rosa Parks,
a wonderfully composed
and courageous woman.
GATES: Rosa Parks'
dignified manner
masked her long history
as a tenacious activist.
LEWIS: She had gone to
the Highlander Folk School
in Tennessee,
the cockpit for
much labor organizing
and civil rights planning,
and so she had, in a sense,
already had
a dress rehearsal experience.
MAN: I heard somebody
said once that
when Rosa Parks sat down,
black people stood up.
Ha ha! That's right.
She democratized
the movement.
It became a people's
movement at all levels.
GATES: Inspired by
Parks' example,
Montgomery's black community
opted to walk to their jobs
instead of riding
the city's buses.
JORDAN:There are
many great lines
in the civil rights movement,
but there is none better
than the black maid Wm),
in the second week, said,
"My feets are tired
but my soul is rested."
That was a statement
of inspiration,
and it was
a statement saying,
"Let's get on with it."
KING: 90% at least of
the regular Negro bus passengers
are staying off the buses,
and we plan to continue
until something is done.
GATES: The boycott effort
came to be led
by an unknown young minister
from Atlanta.
26-year-old
Martin Luther King, Jr.
became a household name when,
after a year of protest,
Montgomery finally
ended segregation
on its city buses.
Do you believe
the majority
of the Negro people
of Montgomery
will now go back
to riding the buses?
Yes, I do.
We must go back
with a deep sense of
love and dedication
to the principle
of nonviolence.
GATES: King's philosophy
of nonviolent civil disobedience
was inspired by the principles
and practices
of India's Mahatma Gandhi.
The tactic was intended to
agitate segregationists,
provoking a reaction
that would elicit
widespread sympathy
from the public.
LEWIS: The way you
bring to your side
forces governmental,
religious, international
is by allowing yourself to be
so maltreated visibly
that your assailant
loses credibility.
GATES: The clash
between peaceful protests
and violent resistance
would produce images
that caused the country
to sit up and take notice.
In New Orleans, on the morning
of November 14, 1960,
federal marshals escorted
a 6-year-old gin
named Ruby Bridges to the local,
all-white elementary school.
WOMAN: I remember
turning onto the street.
I saw barricades
and police officers
and just
people everywhere.
When I saw all of that,
I immediately thought
that it was Mardi Gras.
Ha ha!
I had no idea
that they were here
to keep me out of
the school.
Ruby, were you scared?
I would have
been terrified.
I wasn't, actually,
because, you know,
it was very hard
for parents, I think,
to explain
to a 6-year-old
what was
actually happening.
They didn't say,
"it's a white school.
You're making history"?
I remember them saying
"Ruby, you're gonna go to
a new school today,
and you better behave."
GATES: But Ruby
was making history.
6 years earlier,
after decades of struggle,
the NAACP had won
a major legal victory-
Brown v. Board of Education,
in which the Supreme
Court declared
that the doctrine of
separate but equal schools
was unconstitutional.
But in many places, that triumph
did not translate into change.
For years after Brown,
much of the South
simply refused to integrate.
Now Ruby would be one of
6 New Orleans children
chosen to desegregate several
all-white elementary schools.
BRIDGES: They were
screaming and shouting
and chanting "2, 4, 6, 8,
we don't want to integrate."
[Crowd chanting] 2, 4, 6, 8,
we don't want to integrate.
2, 4, 6, 8...
MAN ON TV: The mothers of
downtown New Orleans
screaming at a Negro child
as she entered
the William Frantz
Elementary School,
first in the city
to be integrated.
BRIDGES: Once I got
into the school,
all of these people here
rushed inside of
the building.
[indistinct chanting]
BRIDGES: They were
taking out their children.
Over 500 kids walked out
of school that day.
MAN: What is your reaction
to the court's decision
continuing integration?
We don't want
the niggers going
in that school.
Well...
This is
a white school.
BRIDGES: They didn't
see a child.
They saw change,
and what they thought was
being taken from them.
They never saw a child.
WOMEN: ° if you believe °
° The faith you lost
so long ago °
° Will return upon your shore °
GATES: The image of
a 6-year-old child
heckled by an angry mob
became a powerful icon
for the young movement.
Ruby's example
soon inspired others.
[indistinct shouting]
MAN ON TV: There is still
opposition to integration here,
but integration is
being accomplished.
GATES: Nonviolent direct action
was contagious.
African American students began
crossing the color line
at historically white
colleges and universities
throughout the South.
MAN: We had one thing in mind,
and that was challenging
bigotry and Jim Crow.
We had been fit as students,
even in elementary grades,
to memorize "We hold these
truths to be self-evident,"
"that all men are created equal
and endowed with-"
not women, now,
"all men are created equal."
We saw through that.
And now here was
our moment
to challenge our
nation to recognize
that we are
hypocrites,
and this is
our opportunity
to try to make
this right.
[Crowd chanting] ...want to
integrate, 2, 4, 6, 8...
GATES: Charlayne Hunter
and Hamilton Holmes
desegregated the University
of Georgia in 1961.
[Crowd chanting] 2, 4, 6, 8,
we don't want to integrate.
We just kept
straight ahead,
kept our eyes on
the prize, you know,
and walked through
the columns.
GATES: Now, I'm trying to
think of other movements
in which the students
played such a vanguard role
Why students?
Students in one sense
have less to lose.
One of the reasons
I think so many
older black people
opposed the movement
was that they had vested
business interests.
They had to take care
of their family.
They had mortgages
to pay.
Mortgages to pay.
The parents of many
of those students
told them
not to do this.
Oh, of course.
Yeah. But they
went ahead.
And they were afraid
they were gonna
get killed, too.
Well, yeah, that,
but pan of it
was don't rock
the boat, you know.
Rock the boat. Yeah.
GATES: Soon, students
began confronting
local segregated businesses
across the South.
Diane Nash was
a student in Nashville
when, together with John Lewis,
she helped lead a campaign
to desegregate the city's
lunch counters.
GATES: When I'm
teaching my students
about the history of the
civil rights movement,
we talk
about nonviolence,
they think
it's ridiculous. Ha ha!
How long did it take you
to wrap your head around
the genius of
nonviolent,
passive resistance?
I didn't think
nonviolence would work.
The idea of guns
and power and violence
compared to nonviolence,
I thought,
no, you know, violence
would work better.
But what questions
does this raise to us
as to how we might
act nonviolently?
GATES: Nash and Lewis
attended workshops
led by the Reverend James Lawson
that trained students in
the tactics of nonviolence.
The workshops in Nashville
were the only organization
that was trying to do anything
to combat segregation.
That's why I kept going.
MAN: Now, tonight,
we have to have one major
role-playing experience.
We just didn't
wake up one morning
and say we're gonna
go and sit in.
We had role-playing.
We had social drama.
Let's send them all
back to Africa.
Why don't someone
get these niggers
out of here?
[Men talking at once]
[Clapping]
LEVERING LEWIS: The training
involved in nonviolent
passive resistance
was specific and demanding.
It takes a lot of courage
to be weak.
JOHN LEWIS, VOICE-OVER:
We had the very first
sit-in in Nashville.
I asked a waitress for
a hamburger and a Coke.
I said, "I'm sorry,
our management does not
allow us to serve
niggers in here."
JOHN LEWIS, VOICE-OVER:
In spite of all of this.
I have to keep loving the people
who denied me service.
[indistinct shouting]
GATES: The tactic
worked to perfection.
Passive resistance was
met with brutality.
WOMAN: ° We who believe
in freedom cannot rest... °
GATES: Forced to contend
with the escalating violence,
Nashville became the first
major city in the South
to desegregate
its lunch counters.
WOMAN: ° ...until it come °
° We who believe in... °
HUNTER: When you get confronted,
particularly in the way
that we were confronted,
it caused us to reach down
inside of ourselves
and find something that
we didn't know was there,
and guess what it was?
It was courage.
WOMAN: °To me °
WOMEN: ° Young people
come first °
° They come my .. °
GATES: By the end of April,
in 1960,
over 50,000 students had staged
sit-ins throughout the South.
They were becoming the vanguard
of the civil rights struggle.
But they had little
support or encouragement
from the movement's leadership,
accustomed to employing
less-aggressive tactics.
WOMAN: Activism was not
the style of the civil
rights movement.
Some of our elders thought
it was a bit much
to be putting yourself
up for jail and violence.
They certainly refused
to see young people
as a pan of
their struggle.
GATES: A little-known
56-year-old civil rights veteran
named Ella Baker
would change that.
Ella Baker,
granddaughter of slaves,
had been a grassroots organizer
all over the South
for two decades.
A quiet but radical force.
She would say,
like the turtle,
you have to put your
tail on the line,
and the students
could understand that,
and...we did put our
tails on the line.
GATES: Now together with
students less than half her age,
Baker helped found
a new organization-
the Student Nonviolent
Coordinating Committee,
known as SNCC.
NORTON: The level
at which SNCC operated
was the most dangerous level.
It was the shock troop level.
They went into towns
and the places
where segregation
ran amok.
They were in
pans of the South
that can only be
called terrorist.
Historically,
civil rights and many
other movements
are top-down.
Mrs. Baker believed
that the ultimate
source of power is at
the level where
the people are.
Up here does not
direct down here.
Down here
directs up there.
The day has come when racism
must be banished.
GATES: So many people
of your generation,
you two,
describe her as
this visionary force.
Why isn't she
a household word of the
civil rights movement?
Because the movement
was-l hate
to say this-
it was dominated
by ministers
and religious
leaders,
and they didn't
see a role
for women in
leadership position.
Until the killing of black men,
black moth er and son,
becomes as important
to the rest of the country
as the killing of
a white mother and son...
[Applause]
JOHN LEWIS: That was Ella Baker.
BAKER: We who believe in freedom
cannot rest
until this happens.
[Applause]
JOHN LEWIS: She took
the long sweep of her life
and her experiences
and poured it
into young folks.
GATES: Ella Baker and SNCC
helped the civil rights movement
broaden and gain momentum.
Up to this point, the movement
had been focused on the South.
It had not found its voice
in the North.
Here in Detroit, that began
to change in 1963.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: By then,
black people in Detroit
had lost many of
the gains they had made
during and after World War ll.
Most were underemployed
and undereducated.
But Detroit was also the home
of what would become
the most successful black-owned
business in the country.
On this street, a man
named Berry Gordy
founded a small record label
and transformed it
into a factory
of black creative genius.
WOMAN: ° ...knockin' on my... °
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
He called it Motown.
WOMAN: ° ...and you
need a friend °
GATES: Like many black
businessmen in the early 1960s,
Berry Gordy was a bit concerned
about how the militancy
of the civil rights movement
might affect his bottom line.
But all that changed
the day that
the Reverend Dr. Martin Luther
King, Jr. came to town.
Dr. King came to Detroit
in June 1963,
hoping to spread his
gospel of nonviolence
to a northern audience.
KING: Segregation is
a cancer in the body politic
which must be removed before our
democratic health
can be realized.
[Cheering and applause]
GATES: Always one
to spot a trend,
Berry Gordy stepped in
to sell the speech.
You know what that speech was?
It was the prototype
of "I Have a Dream."
KING: I have a dream
this afternoon
that one day...
[Applause]
One day little white children
and little Negro children
will be able to join hands
as brothers and sisters.
I have a dream this afternoon.
GATES: In Detroit's cavernous
Cobo Hall,
Dr. King spoke before 25,000
eager listeners.
KING: ...simply because
people want to be free.
GATES: The recording
of the speech
made it onto
the "Billboard" charts.
KING: We've come
to see the power
of nonviolence.
We’ve come to see that this
method is not a weak method.
GATES: But that same year,
a different voice
came to Detroit as well.
MAN: Revolution is bloody.
Revolution is hostile.
Revolution knows no compromise.
GATES: And a different kind
of speech was recorded.
MALCOLM X: Revolution
overturns and destroys
everything that gets in its way.
GATES: Malcolm X spent much of
his youth in northern cities
and became radicalized
by his experiences in prison.
While there, he convened
to the Nation of Islam
and embraced the concept
of armed self-defense.
X: There's no such thing
as a nonviolent revolution.
Whoever heard of a revolution
where they lock arms,
sing "We Shall Overcome"?
GATES: Malcolm X
appealed to those
impatient with
the pace of the movement
unfolding in the South.
To them, nonviolence
looked like capitulation.
Facing police brutality,
failing schools,
and widespread unemployment,
north em African Americans were
less interested in desegregation
than in economic
and racial justice.
MAN: Malcolm's appeal
on one level is with
working-class people,
with the working poor,
people who might be
what we call underclass
in contemporary America.
Now, he also has an appeal
beyond that as well, because
Malcolm is able to articulate
repressed emotions
that even the black middle class
and upper middle class feel.
Malcolm really is black
America's prosecuting attorney,
prosecuting white Americans
for what he's gonna argue
are crimes against the black
community and black humanity.
Whereas King serves as
a defense attorney
for both African Americans
and whites towards each other.
He's a mediator.
GATES: For a brief moment here
in Detroit, in June of 1963,
followers of Dr. King
and Malcolm X came together,
marching side by side in
the great walk for freedom,
the largest march for racial
equality up to that point.
KEITH: It was a tremendous,
tremendous gathering of blacks,
and seeing my people
together like this,
marching for freedom,
meant everything to me,
and it inspired me,
because I said, "My God,
"if we work together
"and realize what we
can do as a community,
we can break mesa
bankers dawn?'
WOMAN: The freedom march
helped to change
our convictions in the North.
We began to see that we could
play a role in the struggle.
GATES: Veteran activist
Grace Lee Boggs
and her husband James were
organizers of the march.
BOGGS: People were not quite
sure how to choose
between Malcolm and Martin
and to see how both
of them mattered.
GATES: So on June 23,
1963, would you say
this was a Malcolm city,
not a Martin city?
There was a lot of sentiment
in the city
that King was a little naive
and all that sort of stuff.
I mean, we were so
sophisticated.
Why was he naive?
Because he was
southern
or because of all
this nonviolence?
I don't think
we really recognized
the philosophic meaning
of nonviolence.
It took us a while
to do that.
So King was
ahead of you.
Yeah, in essence.
Ah.
But I think by '63
in Detroit,
we were much more...
infatuated with Malcolm,
and we were thin king
we had to redefine ourselves,
that we had to become
more self-reliant,
more self-determining,
that we had to create
a new dream.
[Sirens]
[Screaming and shouting]
GATES: For the next
few years, however,
Dr. King's nonviolent
civil disobedience
continued to dominate
civil rights strategy
as the movement spread
across the country.
PRESIDENT JOHNSON: I am about
to sign into law
the Civil Rights Act of 1964.
GATES: The more civil rights
protesters suffered violence
and even death,
the clearer the justice
of their cause became
and the harder it became
to ignore.
The civil rights movement
reached a climax
on March 7, 1965,
when a peaceful march
for voting rights
from Selma to Montgomery
turned into
what would become known
as Bloody Sunday.
We're marching
today to dramatize
to the nation
and dramatize to
the wand
that hundreds
and thousands of
Negro citizens
are denied
the right to vote.
I remember so well
on that particular day.
We came to the highest point
on the bridge.
Down below we saw
a sea of blue--
Alabama State Troopers--
and a man identified himself
and said,
"I'm Major John Cloud of
the Alabama State Troopers.
"This is an unlawful march.
You will not be allowed
to continue."
CLOUD: This is
Major Cloud talking.
Marching this way.
JOHN LEWIS: You saw these guys
putting on their gas masks.
[Crowd shouting]
They came toward us...
beating us with nightsticks.
I was hit in the head by a State
Trooper with a nightstick.
I thought I was going to die.
I thought I saw death.
GATES: The brutality at Selma
was broadcast on
national television.
TV ANNOUNCER: Programs
normally seen at this time
will not be broadcast.
[Crowd shouting]
GATES: 48 million people
across the country watched
as peaceful protesters were
attacked by police
with nightsticks and tear gas.
John Lewis once said that
with out television news
coverage,
the civil rights movement
would have been
like a bird without wings
or a choir
with out a song.
Do you think
that's fair?
I think this fight
for righteousness,
for justice, really for
the honor of the country--
it would have been
a longtime
for the movement
to succeed.
Television
was the instrument
that, to use
John Lewis' metaphor,
had people hear
the choir.
This is Highway
Number 80,
Selma to Montgomery,
Alabama.
Once our people
were totally and terribly
brutalized here...
GATES: By transforming
the movement
into a kind of televised
morality play,
Dr. King was able to appeal
to people of faith
across the country,
many of whom began
to join his cause.
[Crowd singing
"We Shall Overcome"]
JOSEPH: What's extraordinary
about nonviolence
is that nonviolence helps you
get the clergy leaders,
whether Catholic, Protestant,
Jewish, Muslim--
the kind of alliances
that were needed.
GATES: After Bloody Sunday,
hundreds of clergy,
including rabbis Marc Tanenbaum
and Abraham Joshua Heschel,
came to Selma
in a show of unity.
The people, most of
whose names were
barely known at the time
and long since
forgotten, who took pan
in the nonviolent
protests--
they made the civil
rights movement.
GATES: The outrage following
the brutality in Selma
incited demonstrations in over
80 cities across America.
Once again, the treatment
of its black citizens
was becoming a liability
to a nation trying to be
the face of democracy
around the wand.
The South was a national
embarrassment.
Congress and the White House
were compelled to act.
JOHNSON: It's not
just Negroes but really
it's all of us who must overcome
the crippling legacy of bigotry
and injustice.
GATES: March 15, 1965.
President Lyndon Baines Johnson
astonished the nation
by invoking the phrase that had
become the mantra
of the movement.
And we sh all overcome.
[Applause]
GATES: I watched that speech
in our living room
on our little black-and-white TV
with my parents.
JOHNSON: And the long denial...
GATES: Even then, at that age,
tears came to my eyes.
A few months later,
President Johnson would sign
our nation's first
Voting Rights Act.
Just 10 years following
the Montgomery bus boycott,
a revolution had occurred.
[Applause]
GATES: The passage
of the Voting Rights Act
was the high water mark of
a decade of struggle
for civil rights.
But despite the
legislative victory,
southern states still made it
difficult if not impossible
for black citizens
to register and vote.
In June 1966, James Meredith,
a law student,
staged a solo march
across the South
to draw attention to the issue
of voter registration.
It would be called
The March Again st Fear.
Barely two days into his march,
Meredith crossed
the Mississippi state line...
[Gunshot]
And was shot and wounded
by a sniper.
In the days following
the shooting,
the movement's elders,
led by Dr. King,
came to finish what
James Meredith had started.
But this time, they were joined
by SNCC
and its youthful leader
Stokely Carmichael.
JOSEPH: You have two
generations:
the generation that Martin
Luther King Jr. represents
and the generation that
Stokely Carmichael represents,
and Dr. King's message was
really wearing thin
in this latter half
of the 1960s,
particularly because
there's so much violence.
FORBES: As the violence grew,
the willingness
to be passive declined.
MIKE WALLACE: Do you think
you'll be able to keep it
nonviolent, Dr. King?
Yes, I think so.
I don't have any doubt
in my mind about that.
WALLACE: Mr. Carmichael,
are you as committed
to the nonviolent approach
as Dr. King is?
No, I'm not.
Why aren't you?
Well, I just don't
see it as a way
of life.
I never have.
JOSEPH: The Meredith march is
where Stokely Carmichael
becomes an icon.
No one in this
country is asking
the white community
in the South
to be nonviolent,
and that in a sense
is giving them
a free license to go
ahead and shoot us
at Mil.
MAN: ° Freedom got a shotgun °
[Crowd ch ants]
GATES: Carmichael
and the militant activists-
they're thinking that civil
rights has not gone far enough.
They want liberation
and freedom now.
MAN: ° Freedom's
gonna shoot it °
DIFFERENT MAN: I'm gonna start
out by asking you a question.
What do you want?
CROWD: Freedom!
MAN: What do you want?
MAN: When do you want it?
CROWD: Now!
MAN: How much of it
do you want?
CROWD: All of it!
MAN:That tells me that you're
gonna march with us,
and we're gonna...
MAN: We're here in the heart
of the black community
in Greenwood in the deep
pan of Mississippi.
The tensions
within the march
are starting to manifest
themselves.
Twilight was coming.
This park is filled
with the Meredith
marchers.
Stokely Carmichael gets
up to give a speech.
CARMICHAEL: We've begged
the federal government.
That's all we've been doing:
begging, begging.
It's time we stand up
and take over.
[Crowd cheers]
CARMICHAEL: Take over.
He talks about
black aspirations.
He talks about how
black is beautiful.
And he talks about
how black people
need to control
their own communities.
Every courthouse
in Mississippi
ought to be burned
down tomorrow...
GOUDSOUZIAN: So that
when he drops the slogan,
if you will,
when he
starts to say...
CARMICHAEL:
What do you want?
GOUDSOUZIAN:
What do we want?
Black power.
CROWD: Black power!
CARMICHAEL:
We want black power.
GOUDSOUZIANI
And starts
urging on the crowd,
and the next thing
you know,
he's got this
massive response.
CROWD: Black power!
CARMICHAEL: What do you want?
GOUDSOUZIAN:
That's a turning point
in African American history,
and certainly
a turning point
in the civil rights movement.
GATES: I saw it
that night on TV...
Really?
With my mother
and my father. Yeah.
What did it
feel like?
Oh, it was
electric, man.
It was-l got
gooseﬂesh.
You knew that--
it was like
the top of your head
was about to
come off.
Activists had expressed
a lot of these
ideas already,
but black power-
Not in my
living room.
[Both laugh]
I never heard it
before.
I went, like,
"Whoa, man!"
I'm like
a nuclear bomb
gone up.
Black power [indistinct]
Yeah!
JOSEPH: By the next morning,
the whole nation
is talking about black power.
MAN: It was like
the great last march
of these great
civil rights leaders.
And because of that dynamic
going on
between the different parts
of the movement,
there emerged, like it was a
process, emerged a new movement.
The new movement was
a black consciousness,
black power movement
which was not just political,
but it was a psychological
break from the past
and saying,
"We are moving to a new day,
a new change,
and we're gonna do it
on our terms."
KING: Like anybody, I would
like to live a long life.
Longevity has its place.
But I'm not concerned
about that now.
GATES: Nonviolent protest seemed
to have run its course.
The final tragic blow came
on April 4, 1968.
And I've seen...
the promised land.
[Crowd murmuring]
I may not get there with you...
Less than two years after
the March Against Fear,
the apostle of nonviolence
would be felled
by the very violence that he had
spent his life opposing.
So I'm happy tonight.
I'm not worried about anything.
I'm not fearing any man.
Mine eyes have seen
the glory
of the coming of the Lord!
[Crowd cheering]
[Gun cocking]
[Siren]
GATES: With Dr. King's
voice stilled,
black resistance would
take a new form.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by...
Senegal, Africa-
the door of no return.
From these shores, millions
of Africans went across oceans
and continents, battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud
to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years of
African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it.
Wi-Fi.
Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational.
Thanks.
Others just a few minutes.
Either way,
our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy
of staying in touch.
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER: The Howard
and Abby Milstein Foundation
in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Ban k.
African American history is
an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
AN NOUN CE RI
The Coca-Cola Company,
The Ford Foundation JustFilms,
Dr. Georgette Bennett
and Dr. Leonard Polonsky
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H. Tanenbaum,
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National Endowment
for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting,
and by viewers like you.
Next time on "The African
Americans"...
a new generation speaks up.
QUESTLOVE: Don Cornelius-
his master plan
was to change the lives
of black youth.
ANNOUNCER: And the dream
comes true.
We did it.
They said we
couldn't,
and we did.
Yeah.
ANNOUNCER:
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross."
The African American story
continues online at
pbsnrg/manyrivers
with streaming video and more.