GATES: The dawning of the
20th century brought cruel
repression to the
African American people,
but the strategies they
employed to fight back led to
profound transformations
in American society,
as Black people
reinvented themselves.
The migrants ﬂeeing the South
realigned the racial composition
of virtually every
city and town in the North
and the Midwest, and in
the process, Black culture
experienced a renaissance,
an unprecedented economic
and political growth.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by
Senegal, Africa-
The Door of No Return.
From these shores, millions
of Africans went across oceans
and continents, battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud to
sponsor "Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey through
500 years of
African American history.
We believe connecting to
our past helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it.
Wi-Fi Settings?
May I, Mr.Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
Thanks.
Others, just a few minutes.
Jimmy Jones Ill.
Either way, our signal is
strong and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy of
staying in touch.
AN NOUN CE R:
The Howard and Abby Milstein
Foundation, in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Ban k.
African American history
is an epic story--
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in
supporting your public
television station.
AN NOUN CE RI
The Coca-Cola Company,
the Ford Foundation JustFilms,
Dr. Georgette Bennett and
Dr. Leonard Polonsky,
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H. Tanenbaum,
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National Endowment
for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation for
Public Broadcasting,
and by
viewers like you.
Thank you.
GATES: As the 19th century drew
to a close, nearly 8 million
African Americans still
lived in the South.
LANGSTON HUGHES: "I pick up my
life and take it on the train
to Los Angeles, Bakersfield,
Seattle, Oakland, Salt Lake...
any place that is North
and West and not South."
[Boat whistle blows]
GATES: Just 30 years after
the end of slavery, life for
most African Americans
had become
increasingly harsh.
HUGH ES: "I am fed up with
Jim Crow laws, people who are
"cruel and afraid,
who lynch and run,
"who are scared of
me and me of them.
So I pick up my life and take
it away on a one-way ticket."
GATES: With "separate but
equal" the law of the land,
enforcing segregation could
be a brutal enterprise.
Consequently, many African
Americans were beginning to
look for a way out
of the South.
Starting in the 1890s, African
Americans began to migrate
north and west--
first as a trickle,
then as a ﬂood.
It would come to be known as
the Great Migration, and it
would last for
generations to come.
By the time it ended, it would
arguably be the largest exodus
of people in American history.
But it began with a
slow stream of pioneers.
What was happening in
the South that made
the migration occur?
The late 19th century,
that was a period of time when
things were getting pretty
tough in the South, and anyone
who had a political
opinion, expressed it,
really had to leave.
GATES: African Americans carried
with them much more than their
meager possessions.
They carried their hopes,
their dreams,
and their culture.
How in the world did all
those people...travel?
Any way they could!
Ha ha ha!
Mobility is such an important
part of freedom, you know?
That's at the core
of it, isn't it?
Of course, with the Great
Migration, there was also
another opportunity for
self-realization, to find
themselves, to get the
boot off their neck.
GATES: The boot on the neck of
African Americans belonged to
Jim Crow, the set of legal
and extra-legal measures that
tried to keep them
thoroughly in their place.
WOMAN: From the moment they
woke up until the moment they
went to sleep, every aspect
of their lives was controlled
and determined by an
artificial hierarchy that
replicated aspects
of enslavement.
There were Black and White
bibles to swear to tell
the truth on in court.
It was actually against the
law for Black people and White
people to even play
checkers together.
And that had an overlay over
every single thing that they
could do and everything
that they could imagine
themselves being.
GATES: Jim Crow was not just a
system of laws excluding Black
people from public
accommodations; it was a code
of conduct that relegated
African Americans to
second-class citizenship.
MAN: To reach your maturity as
a male at this time, you were
expected to step
off sidewalks.
Your eyes were never to gaze
directly into those
of a White person.
Perish the thought that
any eye contact
with a female occur.
This was the policing
of a population.
Life was one of
saturated oppression.
GATES: Lynchings were fast
becoming the weapon of choice
for enforcing Jim Crow
and reinforcing the notion
of white supremacy.
By the tum of the century,
as many as 3 lynchings
occurred each week.
Some were widely advertised
and drew large crowds,
picnic basket in tow.
LEWIS: Figure, if you will,
some community 50 miles away
from an advertised event
of retribution, a lynching,
would pack bags and get on
the buggy and hurry there.
Multiply that 10-fold,
and then you have hundreds
of people there to witness,
and indeed, to leave
with souvenirs of the ﬂesh
and bone of the victim.
This was a barbarism that
should have placed the South
beyond the pale.
GATES: These grisly
events spared no one-
man, woman, or child-
and they didn't always
involve a rope and a tree.
In Memphis, here at a place
called the Curve stood the
People's Grocery, a food co-op
own ed by a well-respected
African American, Thomas Moss.
[Bell ringing]
The success of Moss' store
threaten ed a White competitor.
To put him out of business,
a mob attacked.
Moss and his partners took
up arms to defend themselves.
When the smoke cleared,
several of the attackers lay
wounded, while Moss and
his defenders were hauled
off to jail.
Before long, a lynch mob came,
pulled them from their cells,
and dragged them to
the outskirts of town.
There, before a group of local
reporters, Thomas Moss was
asked if he had
anything left to say.
He answered, "Tell
my people to go west.
There is no justice
for them here."
So this is
where he's buried.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, look.
They put "At Rest."
That's horrible.
"At Rest."
it really brings back the
manner of his death,
which was so brutal.
They were making
a statement.
They replicated the injuries
of Whites that had been shot
in this melee, and the
Whites had been shot, one man
in the eye and
cheek and throat.
And that's how
they shot him?
And that's how they
shot the 3 men.
Oh, that's horrible!
That's terrible.
Yeah, yeah.
GATES: The Moss case
attracted the attention
of many African Americans
in the South,
largely due to Moss'
friendship with
journalist Ida B. Wells.
In a series of provocative
editorials published in her
newspaper, the "Memphis Free
Speech," Wells condemned
the Moss killings and the
practice of lynching.
GIDDINGS:
When Ida B. Wells
hears about the lynching,
she doesn't know
what she's going to write
about it, but then she
remembers Thomas Moss' last
words, and she decides to say,
there's only one thing we
can do: save our nickels
and dimes.
Leave Memphis, a place
that will not protect us
and murders us in cold blood.
GATES:
With that, Ida B. Wells,
born into slavery,
became our country's leading
anti-lynching crusader.
Her words en raged her White
neighbors, who destroyed her
newspaper offices.
She was threatened with
lynching if she ever returned
to Memphis.
GATES: In this editorial,
she spoke the unspeakable.
GIDDINGS: She spoke
the unspeakable. Talk
about truth to power.
Truth to power.
And the interesting thing
about her, she knew how
explosive it was,
but she was just determined
to follow what
she calls the logic
of lynching to its end.
She said, "The heavens
might fall," but I'm
going to tell
the truth about lynching.
GATES: The truth about
lynching, according to Wells,
was that it was an
"unjustifiable act"
of economic jealousy and
sexual anxiety, an instrument
of terror and control.
In the weeks and months
following, thousands of Black
people from Memphis joined
the early migration
out of the South.
Their exodus
created a problem.
The Southern economy was still
largely agrarian, dependent
upon African Americans to do
the jobs no one else wanted
at a wage few
others would accept.
LEWIS: People are leaving the
South, and indeed, curiously
enough, there is a pushback
on the part of many Whites
in the South, who say,
"Wait a minute.
"We have to calibrate
our bestiality.
"I mean, if we start
losing these people,
why, that's not
the game plan."
GATES: Who would cook...
clean...
and care for the children?
Till the fields,
harvest the crops?
WILKERSON:The
interaction between the
former slaveholders
and those who had been
enslaved had not changed
fundamentally
when it came to
interpersonal interactions
and the expectations of
how one should behave.
And economic
exploitation.
It's incredible, isn't it?
It was like
a bad marriage.
Yeah.
The Emancipation
Proclamation had not
lived up to its name.
People had not
truly been free.
The Great Migration is
really about freedom.
It's about identity.
It's about claiming
one's citizenship,
one's American-ness,
and it's ultimately
about agency.
GATES: While some Black
leaders advocated leaving the
South behind, there were other
inﬂuential voices urging
African Americans to resist
the siren song of the North
and to stay right
where they were.
GATES: Born a slave himself,
Booker T. Washington
believed that former slaves
and their masters
shared a common
role in the creation
of the New South--
to help transform
it economically.
If the South was ever going
to leave that antebellum
plantation mentality behind,
it would require the mutual
cooperation of Black people
and White people alike.
WOMAN: Booker T. Washington
was a very practical man,
because he was a person
who could see
the wand as it is.
He's saying to the
Black people, you don't
need to leave.
You don't need to go North.
You can stay here.
GATES: As a practical man,
Washington argued that
political rights for African
Americans could only be won
from a position of economic
strength and self-sufficiency.
WOMAN: He believed that
eventually, White people
would come to realize
the value
of Black workers.
He saw himself as a mediating
figure between the White South
and the Black South.
GATES: The product of a
vocational education himself,
Washington argued that
by learning a trade,
African Americans
would hold the key
to their own advancement.
He went on to found the
Tuskegee Institute, which
trained African Americans in
vocational and technical skills
and advocated self-help.
Tuskegee was not alone.
The Negro Women's Club
movement created far-reaching
social networks that
promoted racial uplift.
Black churches and benevolent
societies lent money to
entrepreneurs starting
out in business.
A washerwoman named Sarah
Breedlove relied on just
such a network.
After changing her
name to Madam C.J. Walker,
she launched a hair
product company and was hailed
as the first self-made female
millionaire, Black or White.
Fueled in part by the
hardships of Jim Crow,
these success stories were a
by-product of a system of laws
that forced Black people to
live in their own world.
Necessity became the
mother of invention.
African Americans made
a way out of no way.
HIGGINBOTHAM: Our
people didn't give up.
You know, they didn't say,
we're overwhelmed
and overcome, and
therefore, we will just
turn on ourselves.
They looked to their own
institutions, their churches.
Out of those churches,
they will build schools,
they will build
insurance companies,
they will build banks.
It's just amazing, all
that is happening.
GATES: While Black
land ownership was on the rise
and a small Black middle
class was emerging, another,
more sinister phenomenon was
taking root to counteract
these gains.
And in those days, it took
little more than a trip to
the mailbox to see it.
MAN: This is our row of
caricatures-
the picaninny, the Tom,
the coon, the tragic mulatto,
the Jezebel, the savage.
All groups, all racial
and ethnic groups,
in this country
have been caricatured.
None of them has been
caricatured as often or in as
many ways as have
Africans and their
American descendants.
GATES: David Pilgrim
is the founder of the
Jim Crow Museum
at Ferris State University
in Michigan, home to
the largest collection
of racist memorabilia
in the country.
PILGRIM: You could take any
piece that you see in here,
and they do Mo things.
The first thing is,
they reﬂect existing
attitudes toward Black people.
But the other thing, and maybe
more important, is they shaped
future attitudes
toward Black people.
LEWIS: The redefinition of the
African American takes place
in this period of time.
The African American in
antebellum times was,
the stereotype held,
reliable, faithful,
hardworking, malleable--
indeed, one entrusted one's
children, one's property
to such people.
Now of a sudden, the African
American becomes demonized,
a threat, a lascivious beast
roaming the countryside
of the South, people loosed
by the end of slavery and now
upon us like locusts.
Well, this was an absurdity.
GATES: A massive propaganda
campaign demeaning
African Americans
and legitimizing
violence against them
was fundamental to
reinforcing Jim Crow.
PILGRIM:And that is one of
the most vulgar depictions
of African American children
that we have in here.
GATES: Well, they're
not human. They're bait.
That's right.
They look like a litter.
This is a postcard?
Yeah, that was a postcard.
Actually, what that
one says is, "Dear
Aunt Libby, this is
what they do to the bad
people in Delaware."
And the significance here is
that it shows a Black person
being beaten matter-of-factly.
It's the normalizing of
violence against Blacks.
And look at
this kid's face.
Not only does that teach
something about violence--
against Blacks, in this case-
but it's also teaching him.
Oh , yeah.
It's horrible.
David, if Black people were
so subjugated, why did
White America
need to create
millions and millions
of images of our
ancestors' subjugation?
New generations had to be
taught those same lessons
about, this is the way we
need to treat Black people.
Because our people never
were fully subjugated.
They were never--
that's right.
MAN: ° Come listen,
all you gals and boys,
I'm just from Tuckahoe °
° I'm gwine to sing a little
song, My name's Jim Crow°
GATES: While these
images were shaping negative
perceptions of Black people at
home, an altogether different
view of African Americans
made its way to Europe.
At the 1900 World's Fair,
a most unusual display drew
crowds of curious onlookers.
Called the American Negro
Exhibit, it featured
a collection of nearly
500 images of dignified,
well-dressed
African American men,
women, and children.
LEWIS: Here, these fine images
of African Americans of every
color, every shape, every
size, every professional pursuit
show graphically
that this is a small nation
of people on the march.
GATES: The exhibit was the
brainchild of the leading
Black intellectual of
the time, William Edward
Burghardt Du Bois.
Du Bois earned his first
Bachelor degree from
Fisk University in
Nashville, Tennessee,
and soon became a leader
among the emerging African
American intellectual elite.
LEWIS: There's a wonderful
image of Du Bois arriving
in Pan's in top hat and tails,
looking like the Edwardian
man quintessential.
He sees 1900 as a wonderful
opportunity to give a counter
narrative to the stereotype
view of the African American
that has really gone global.
GATES: The Paris exhibition
embodied Du Bois' philosophy
about African American
leadership.
Unlike his contemporary
Booker T. Washington,
Du Bois believed
that the masses of former
slaves in the South, largely
uneducated, had little chance
of achieving
liberation on their own.
They needed to
be shown the way.
HIGGINBOTHAM: How do we
understand how a group
of people who are
oppressed rise?
There's one idea that says
you need talented leaders,
you need extraordinary,
exceptional, educated--
you know, the highest leaders,
your great thinkers.
That was the Talented Tenth.
GATES: Du Bois was the first
African American to earn
a doctoral degree
from Harvard.
He believed it was the
responsibility of his
intellectual cohort to
lead the fight
for full citizen ship.
HIGGINBOTHAM: Du Bois told
Black people that they could
not wait to be citizens,
that they were
already on the books.
We have a Constitution.
It was signed and sealed in
blood during that Civil War
and during Reconstruction,
and we were already citizens
of the United States.
You couldn't postpone
fighting for justice.
For Du Bois, you comprise
something too great to wait
and to say "one day."
GATES: Du Bois waged his
battle for justice
on several fronts.
First, he established the
Niagara Movement, whose
Declaration of Principles
would provide the basis
of the modem civil
rights movement.
And then he co-founded the
NAACP, the country's oldest
and largest
civil-rights organization.
He also believed that if
African Americans were going
to achieve equal rights,
they had to prove their worth
on the cultural
front, as well,
as creators of a unique
artistic tradition.
LEWIS: Du Bois was saying that
literature can be an agency
for profound change.
I call it civil
rights by copyright.
GATES: Du Bois and his
colleagues aspired to set
in motion a Black literary
movement that would compete
on the highest levels
of New York society.
"We just left slavery 40,
50 years ago, and you're
"talking about publishing house
contracts with Alfred Knopf
and Horace Liveright,
when lynching still goes on?"
"Yes," they said.
"Absolutely.
We're going to write
ourselves just straight
across this problem."
In 1910, Harlem was
an upper-middle-class
White community, but
by 1925, it was known as
the Mecca of the New Negro.
African Americans came to New
York, just as they did to many
of the great cities of the
North, seeking opportunity.
During the first World War,
their numbers swelled when
labor shortages made
better-paying jobs
available for migrants.
[Bell rings]
Those who came to Harlem found
a place where they were free,
for the first time, to express
themselves in ways that seemed
inconceivable before.
WILKERSON: Many of these
people had not been able to
pursue their art, had not been
able to pursue the opportunity
to become a novelist,
to become a jazz musician.
It simply was not available
and possible for them
in the restricted caste system
that they were consigned to
in the South.
Suddenly, here, in New York,
finally, finally, finally,
we can be the people that
we imagine ourselves to be.
[Jazz playing]
GATES: It would explode into
one of the most artistically
fertile periods in
African American history.
MAN: The Harlem Renaissance
represents, above all,
Black people, really for the
first time, making a claim
on being modem as a people...
to say that we are here,
and this is our contribution.
GATES: Here, on 136th Street,
in the heart of Harlem,
some of the most talented
newcomers found a temporary home
in a rooming house which
its residents humorously
nicknamed Nigeratti Manor.
EDWARDS: Some of the
people that lived there
included Eric Walrond,
the Caribbean novelist
and short-story writer,
Zora Neale Hurston
passed through there,
Langston Hugh es
spent time there.
They all ended up putting
together a kind of salon.
It was right here.
Who invented this
crazy term, "niggerati"?
Zora Neale Hurston, playing
with the term "literati"
and saying,
"if they're the literati
downtown, we must be
the niggerati uptown."
GATES: Out of Niggerati
Manor came one of the most
provocative publications
of the renaissance--
a literary journal
called "Fire!!"
EDWARDS: In that
single issue of "Fire!!"
the first story in there
is Wallace Thurman's
"Cordelia the Crude."
[Both chuckle]
It's about a prostitute.
Richard Bruce Nugent's
sexually exploratory vignettes
"Smoke, Lilies and Jade"--
in terms of exploring a kind
of queer eroticism, it's one
of the stories in the
renaissance, one of the few,
that does that,
that goes there.
[Jazz music playing]
Harlem came to represent
a kind of oasis
of permissibility.
There were things that could
go on in Harlem that could not
go on elsewhere.
GATES: Harlem's reputation
spread through out the country.
Outsiders were drawn to
its clubs and cabarets.
Races could mingle here in
ways that were illegal in much
of the rest of the country.
EDWARDS: Let's say
you get out of the
show at Connie's Inn
or at the Cotton Club.
Something else happens when
you can go to the speakeasy
after hours and be sitting
next to an Ethel Waters
or a Duke Ellington.
Were they segregated,
these speakeasies?
They were not segregated.
You had to know where it
was and know how to get in.
[Buzzer sounds]
For all of them, you had
to know the code.
So there's one you would
knock 3 times and cough.
Ha ha ha!
And if you didn't
cough right, you
weren't gonna get in.
And if you’re thinking
about the attraction
to a White audience,
it's not just the attraction
of seeing what was
then American popular music,
the coolest stuff around,
but you also get
a kind of proximity
and everything that
goes along with that-
communication, seduction,
various kinds of interaction
that's not always
predictable.
You're on top of each other.
Literally
and figuratively.
Literally and figuratively.
You're going to be jammed
up with people sweating
and drinking and having
a good time all night
till the next morning.
It adds something
to the evening.
Ha ha ha!
GATES: The Harlem Renaissance
spotlighted African American
artists, both as purveyors of
cool and as major contributors
to American culture.
Ironically, the most sublime
of these contributions wasn't
widely embraced at the time
by the Black elite.
[Jazz playing]
To them, jazz,
which had made its way north
with many of the
southern migrants,
was unsophisticated,
even vulgar, but in time,
jazz would be recognized as
the most quintessentially
American an form.
[Applause]
EDWARDS: Jazz is significant
because it represents some
of the best potentials that
are inherent in the American
conception of democracy...
making sure that everyone has a
place to have their own say...
and creating, out of a fabric
of individual contributions,
a greater whole, a more
beautiful whole.
[Applause]
GATES: Meanwhile, a new
medium was emerging that would
revolutionize popular culture
and offer another opportunity
for African Americans
to redefine their image.
Before Hollywood was even
Hollywood, Oscar Micheaux,
once a Pullman porter,
became the first Black
in dependent filmmaker.
GATES: Micheaux films--
were they shown in Black
theaters or in White?
Black theaters. I mean,
sometimes White-own ed
theaters,
but as with some of
the others of that period,
Micheaux didn't really see
boundaries for himself.
GATES: Oscar Micheaux managed
to make more than 40 films
in a career that
spanned 4 decades.
What is different about them
than other films coming out?
Well, the fact that you are
seeing a whole range of Black
characters on the screen,
assertive, articulate,
often sophisticated African
American men who are strong
characters who are trying to
do something for themselves
and the community.
The idea was, there's
a Black audience out
there that wasn't
yet begin serviced and wanted
to be entertained and wanted
to learn something as much
as any other audience.
GATES: Black audiences would
see new images of themselves
on film, many of them
for the first time.
Micheaux's films walked a fine
line between entertainment
and social commentary.
Tackling taboo subjects
like miscegenation
and the brutality of rape,
Micheaux chose to articulate
harsh, largely unspoken
truths about black life
through his an.
BOGLE: In this film, "Within
Our Gates," there was this
sequence when the leading lady
of the film, she is in a sort
of cabin, and there's an
older white man who's
about to rape her.
And he goes after her,
and there is a struggle,
and somehow her blouse is
ripped open, and she's got
a birthmark, and he realizes
that actually he had
impregnated a black woman
years before, and this
is his daughter.
Oh, my God.
You know, you think of the
women in the slave cabins
at night, when the White
masters came out and got them.
I mean,
all of that is sort
of part of a kind of
subtext in the movie.
Now, this is heavy stuff.
GATES: In its portrayal of
the hidden causes of racial
violence, Micheaux's film
was a bold rebuttal to one
of the most celebrated and
racist American films ever made,
"The Birth of a Nation."
FILM ANNOUNCER:
D.W. Griffith's "Birth
of a Nation."
GATES: Released in 1915 to
widespread critical acclaim,
"The Birth of a Nation" was
picketed by the NAACP for its
vicious portrayals
of African Americans.
BOGLE: In "The Birth of
a Nation," major Black
characters
were played by
Whites in blackface-
Of course.
Which made them
all the more grotesque,
and these Black men
lusting after White women.
GATES: With its searing
depiction of black men as
sexual predators, "The Birth
of a Nation" helped revive
the Ku Klux Klan, which had
been largely dormant
since Reconstruction.
Organized to defend White
supremacy, the Klan's
membership ﬂuctuated over
the decades and tended to peak
when competition for
jobs triggered violence.
On occasion, Klan activities
were fueled by resentment
of a thriving Black
middle class,
like in Tulsa, Oklahoma.
WOMAN: My grandfather,
he has seen
a lot in this life,
and he shared some of
those things with me.
GATES: Wes Young was only
4 years old when a single
accusation ignited
the city of Tulsa.
He told me, when he was a
little boy, that something
really bad happened, told me
how he was woken up by his mom
in the middle of the night-
"We have to go."
GATES: Young's family lived
in the Black section of town
known as Greenwood, where
black-owned businesses
thrived, creating an oasis
at the height of Jim Crow.
MAN: In the early pans of
the 20th century in Tulsa,
African Americans, they said,
"OK, we have to be separate,
"and we're going to show that
separate but equal is not
"gonna stop us from
being successful.
"We can build our
own businesses.
We can support
our own industry."
And in fact, the black dollar
circulated 26 times before it
left that community, which meant
it went from the barbershop
to the butcher
to the supermarket.
GATES: This area was once known
as the Negro Wall Street--
prosperous, self-sufficient,
all-Black world, a model
of progress and achievement.
But prosperity for some was
a provocation to others.
On May 31, 1921, Dick Rowland
was accused of assaulting
Sarah Page in an elevator.
He was Black.
She was White.
Both were teenagers.
Mm-hmm.
In the elevator?
In the elevator.
GATES: As allegations spread
that a Black boy had molested
a White gin, a White mob
headed to the jailhouse where
Dick Rowland was being held.
GATES: Black men
from Greenwood got their guns
and protected Dick Rowland
from being lynched,
but what happened afterward
went beyond their control.
MAN: A large white mob
came over the railroad tracks
into the Greenwood community,
shooting and burning
and looting.
There were over 1 ,250
structures in Greenwood
that were destroyed.
These were homes
and businesses.
Because of the fires,
the whole area
was wiped out--
36 square blocks.
Wiped out
in 24 hours?
Really wiped out in
less than 24 hours.
My God. Just think of what
this would have been today.
OGLETREE: This was an
effort to stop the success
of the community and
Greenwood, and there was
a message from Tulsa.
The message was, if you try to
be successful, we're going to
bring you down.
GATES: The exact number of
African Americans killed
during the massacre
may never be known.
GATES: I mean,
until you see it, the
enormity of the thing--
it's never hit me
until right now.
Oh , yeah.
GATES: Property damage
to Greenwood's homes
and businesses was
estimated at $2 million.
That would be the equivalent
of almost $26 million today.
But they didn't
burn the spirit.
GATES: The Tulsa riots were
not an isolated incident.
Throughout the country, racial
conﬂicts had been ﬂaring.
Wand War I had just ended.
Black and White soldiers were
returning home from the front,
competing with
immigrants for scarce jobs.
The mere sight of a Black man
in uniform could be enough to
provoke bloodshed from those
who saw his proud assertion
of citizenship as a threat.
In 1919, an outbreak of
violence in Charleston,
South Carolina, spread
like a virus to some
two dozen cities.
It was known
as Red Summer.
LEWIS: And by the time it's
over, it has swept north
and south and west.
Hundreds of people are dead.
Cities are smoldering.
Young Colonel MacArthur
brings the troops in to
quell the disturbance.
This Red Summer
presented a dilemma.
We're not making progress.
We've left the cotton fields,
but it looks like a dead end
may confront us.
GATES: This racial violence
dampened the wartime optimism
of many African Americans,
causing them to reexamine
their relation ship to this
country, as they had
so many times before.
For those wondering "Where now,"
a man emerged with an answer.
Marcus Garvey, a Jamaican
immigrant with a keen sense
of pageantry and a mesmerizing
oratorical voice, appealed to
those who saw no future for
themselves in mainstream
American life.
A Pan-Africanist, Garvey
believed in the fundamental
unity of Black people
throughout the world.
WOMAN: Garvey emerges
at a time when African
Americans are coming
back from war determined to
fight and get their rights.
He appeals to this sense of
Black pride in a moment in our
history where White
supremacy is riding unbound,
and the response
is phenomenal.
GATES: At its height, Garvey's
organization, the Universal
Negro Improvement Association,
was the largest black mass
movement in American history.
MAN: Garvey becomes one of
the era's biggest black-
nationalist organizers.
He is a fan and admirer of
Booker T. Washington
and thinks that
this idea of bootstrapping,
pulling yourself up,
is the way to go.
GATES: The UNIA started its
own businesses, including
a printing press that
publish ed the widely
circulated "Negro
Wand" newspaper.
MAN: Garvey has a
messianic vision of himself.
He's going to say that Black
people are worthwhile people.
They've been kings
and queens in Africa.
He wants to repatriate to
Africa and establish a colony
that's under African American
leadership in Liberia.
GATES: Garvey created a
shipping company called the
Black Star Line to transport
those of his followers who
wanted to move to Africa.
But Garvey's dream was
as leaky as his boats.
LEWIS: Turned out to be
a rather unfortunate
acquisition.
Those huge tubs leaked,
and their boilers had to be
repaired and all that, but for
one gorgeous day, marching
down to the Brooklyn pier to
see the "Frederick Douglass"
sail to Africa--
boy, what a charge, that.
GATES: When Garvey mailed
ads for the sale of shares
in a ship he did not own,
the FBI used this as an excuse
to arrest him on
charges of fraud.
Ultimately, he was tried and
convicted of the charges,
sewing nearly 3 years of a
5-year sentence before making
one last bargain.
[Ship horn blows]
In one of the cruelest ironies
of African American history,
President Calvin Coolidge
commuted Garvey's sentence,
under one condition--
that he would be deported
from right here, at the
port of New Orleans
not back to Africa,
but to his home in Jamaica.
On a December day in 1927,
Garvey's most devoted
followers came to
bid him farewell.
JOSEPH: His lasting legacy
is that all blacks who are
descended from Africa, whether
they're in Brazil or Brooklyn,
Harlem or Haiti,
are one people.
GATES: As Garvey's ship
sailed away at the height
of the Roaring Twenties,
no one could imagine
the devastating economic
downturn that was to come.
During the Great Depression,
African Americans reached new
depths of despair.
Pushed out of the unskilled,
largely menial jobs that they
had once held, Black people
saw unemployment rise above
50% in some pans of the
country, twice that
of White Americans.
In the South, searing poverty
made the lie of "separate
but equal" all the more
glaring, especially
in education.
At the height of the
depression, a lawyer named
Charles Hamilton Houston set
out to expose the inequities
of Jim Crow.
SULLIVAN: Charles Hamilton
Houston took a camera and went
into South Carolina and did
a visual documentation
of separate and unequal.
GATES: With this visual
evidence, Houston began
building a legal case against
Jim Crow, showing just how
unequal education was between
Black and White students
in America.
SULLIVAN: They would
film a Black sch col.
Often, they'd be
in just shacks.
I mean,
you know, places that had
cracks in the walls,
and children crowded onto
benches, no desks.
Then he would go to the
White school, neighboring
White school--
2-story,brick,
basketball courts.
So here is this astounding
visual essay, and he used it
to inform people around the
country and to help mobilize
Black people to fight for
their children's futures.
GATES: After serving as
a commissioned officer
in World War I,
Houston entered law school.
He emerged a soldier
of another kind.
SULLIVAN: While he was in
law school, he developed this
notion about the kind of role
a Black lawyer should play
in the fight for civil rights.
He says the Black lawyer is
a soldier, taking the battle
into the courtroom, sewing
as an advisor to the people.
The courtroom became the
place where you asserted
your citizenship.
GATES: As his legal career
ascended, Houston began a slow
assault on Jim Crows
"separate but equal" doctrine.
SULLIVAN: As Dean at Howard
Law School, he is determined
that he will train the best
constitutional lawyers, and he
imbues in them the power that
they have, and he transforms
the law school.
It becomes the West Point of
the civil rights movement.
GATES: Houston and his law
students at Howard University
would forge an army of
their own, bringing a series
of cases testing the legality
of "separate but equal"
throughout the South.
OGLETREE: American
wasn't 't ready for the en d
of segregation when he
started pushing these cases
in the 1930s.
As he argued cases before the
Supreme Court, he also noticed
that one justice actually turned
his back on him, wouldn't even
listen to him, because he was
a black man articulating what
it was all about.
At the Supreme Court?
At the Supreme Court.
The justice just turned his
back, didn't want to hear
a black man arguing,
but Charles Houston won
case by case, statute by
statute, section by section,
and his whole effort
was to make sure that
the races were treated equal.
GATES: Though he wouldn't live
to argue the case himself,
Houston's efforts eventually
led to the landmark 1954
Supreme Court
ruling "Brown vs.
Board of Education."
The court reached the decision
to overturn segregation
in public schools just 4 years
after Houston's death.
In the 1930s, however, the
end of segregation was still
decades away.
African Americans would have
to find ways to cope with the
many challenges posed by Jim
Crow, like where to eat or
drink, sleep, stand, or where
to stop and rest after
along drive.
The sheer inconvenience and
indignity of it all was enough
to overwhelm, so in 1936,
a Harlem postal employee
offered a solution.
"The Negro Motorist
Green-Book."
What in the wand was that?
WILKERSON: It was created
by Victor Hugo Green.
Ha ha! My man,
Victor Hugo Green.
So, it was green.
The book was green.
He was Green.
His name was Green.
And he set out to create a
listing of where one might go
if you were African American,
and you could be assured
of being able to get service.
So in other words,
how not to get arrested
or rebuffed while
you're driving that new
car that Mr. Ford made.
Yes.
But it also represented so
much more than just listings.
It was insurance
again st indignity.
GATES: With the Great Depression
in their rear view mirror,
Black people were
once again on the move,
and the automobile was now
one of the most viable means
of transportation.
But being on the road was not
such an easy thing back then.
Isabel, it's so enormously
complicated and fraught.
What went into a Black
family planning a trip
north in a car?
They would need to know,
where is it safe to stop,
where would there be
proprietors
that would permit us
to have a room for the
night, where we could
get gas.
So we couldn't get gas
at any gas station?
You couldn't assume that
you could get anything
from anyplace.
All these things added
to the uncertainties of
being on the road.
GATES: By turning the
uncertainties
of the road into something
more reliable, the "Green-Book"
would direct Black travelers
to accommodations
like this.
WILKERSON: People had to drive
far longer than they otherwise
might have because they had
to get to the one place that
might have accepted them.
And they found creative
ways to tell the children,
"We don't want to stop there,
anyway," or, "We're gonna go
and wait till we get
to auntie's house."
They cushioned the blow
of reality
of the segregated America.
Yes , yes .
Was this migration one of
the first massive exercises
of free will of the
African American people?
Absolutely. In fact, I call
it the overground railroad.
That's a good way to put it.
That this migration was a
first step that the nation's
servant class ever
took without asking.
This is the first time
that they made a decision
for themselves as to who
they would be and where they
would be it.
GATES: Among other things,
it was indignity that
African Americans
were escaping
in the Great Migration-
and indeed, throughout
much of their history.
Perhaps the "Green-Book"
helped in some small way to
reaffirm their humanity.
Another book
certainly did, and it, too,
went with them
on their journey.
That book was the Good Book,
the Holy Bible.
WILKERSON: It was the
reminder of what was
at stake
when they were going
into these lonely
stretches where
there was no guarantee
of what might happen,
and so this is
what carried them through.
"I raise my eyes
toward the mountains.
"From where will
my help come?
My help comes from
the Lord, the maker
of heaven and earth..."
GATES: "God will not allow
your foot to slip; your
guardian does not sleep.
"By day,
the sun cannot harm you,
"nor the moon by night.
"The Lord will guard you from
all evil, will always
guard your life.
The Lord will guard your
coming and going, both now
and forevermore."
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by
Senegal, Africa-
The Door of No Return.
From these shores, millions
of Africans went across oceans
and continents, battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud to
sponsor "Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years of
African American history.
We believe connecting to
our past helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it.
Wi-Fi Settings?
May I, Mr.Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational.
Thanks.
Others, just a few minutes.
Jimmy Jones Ill.
Either way, our signal is
strong and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy of
staying in touch.
AN NOUN CE R:
The Howard and Abby Milstein
Foundation, in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Ban k.
African American history
is an epic story--
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in
supporting your public
television station.
AN NOUN CE RI
The Coca-Cola Company,
the Ford Foundation JustFilms,
Dr. Georgette Bennett and
Dr. Leonard Polonsky,
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H. Tanenbaum,
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National
Endowment for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation for
Public Broadcasting,
and by
viewers like you.
Thank you.
Next time on "The African
Americans," a change
is going to come.
MAN: We had one thing in mind,
and that was challenging
bigotry and Jim Crow.
We saw through that.
MAN: I said, "My God.
If we work together as a
community, we can break these
barriers down
AN NOUN CE RI
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross."
The African American
story continues online
at pbsnrg/manyrivers,
with streaming video and more.