[Birds chirping]
With the outbreak
of the Civil War in 1861,
African Americans,
like the country itself,
were plunged into chaos.
Their freedom at stake, they
risked everything for victory.
5 years later, slavery was over,
but what would freedom
really mean?
Reconstruction brought another
period of roiling uncertainty,
but never did African Americans
relinquish their quest
for the real prize-freedom
and the rights of citizenship.
The lengths they would go
and the price they would pay
make this one of the most
inspiring stories
in American history.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by...
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER:
Senegal, Africa-
the Door of No Return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah. They have it.
Wi-Fi. Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: Others
just a few minutes.
Either my, our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community,
the simple joy
of staying in touch.
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER: The Howard
and Abby Milstein Foundation,
in partnership with Hoover
Milstein and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
ANNOUNCER: The Ford Foundation
Just Films...
...and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
GATES: In the early morning
of April 12,1861,
South em cannons opened fire
on Fort Sumter,
A federal garrison
in Charleston Harbor.
The North and South were at war.
When the Civil War began,
more than 3.9 million slaves
faced a terrible choice--
to be forced to aid
a Confederate army they despised
or gamble everything on escape.
Half a million chose
to break and run.
Not only would they change
the tide of war,
they would change its meaning,
turning a war about union
into a war about slavery.
One of my favorite stories
of the Civil War happened
right here at the battery
just a year
after the outbreak of the war
over at Fort Sumter.
As Charleston slept,
a young black man, a slave,
plotted his escape
aboard a ship.
Robert Smalls
was a 23-year-old slave
pressed into service
for the Confederacy
aboard a warship called
the Planter.
For nearly a year,
he quietly observed
the movements of the ship
and its crew.
Just before dawn
on May 13, 1862,
Smalls took his chance.
While the ship's officers
slept ashore,
he and his fellow slave crewmen
pulled anchor
and eased the Planter
into Charleston Harbor.
MAN: They had prearranged
to meet their family members
and to pick them up,
and then come back
down the peninsula
and they begin the process,
and this is in the wee
hours of the morning
of sailing out of
the harbor.
They are embarked now on
an extremely dangerous journey.
GATES: Smalls knew these waters
like the back of his hand,
but he also knew the risks
that lay ahead--
4 Confederate checkpoints:
Castle Pinckney, Fort Ripley,
Fort Johnson,
and Fort Sumter.
Isn't Smalls afraid
of being caught?
How in the world
is a black slave
gonna pull this off?
He's extremely afraid
of being caught.
He disguises himself
as the captain
and also mimics
the captain's gait
as he walked back and forth
across the wheelhouse.
GATES: Smalls slipped past the
first 3 checkpoints undetected.
The most dangerous
checkpoint remained--
Fort Sumter,
with its mighty guns
and fearsome cannons.
Discovery would mean
certain death.
As dawn broke,
the crew urged Smalls
to take a wide berth,
but changing course
could arouse suspicion.
Smalls gave the signal.
[Steam whistle blowing]
A few seconds later,
the countersignal came back.
[Steam whistle blows]
"Pass on by."
So they're safe, right?
They're free?
Well, they're not
completely free
because now we have
this situation where
a Confederate-ﬂagged
vessel is sailing out,
and it begins
to approach the vessels
of the Union naval
blockading force.
GATES: Fortunately,
the vessel was not fired on.
As astonished Union officers
boarded the Planter,
Smalls stood at attention,
saluted, and spoke.
POWERS: "I am delivering
this war materiel,
"including these cannons,
and I think
Uncle Abraham Lincoln
can put them to good use."
Ha ha ha!
Smalls was ready with
his line for history.
That's right.
GATES: "I don't know exactly
what you are now,"
the officer told Smalls,
"but you're certainly
no longer slaves."
Robert Smalls' escape
personified a new,
more determined attitude
among Southern slaves.
Before the war, his bold act
would have been in vain.
The Fugitive Slave Act of 1850
decreed that runaway slaves
were to be hunted down
and returned to their masters
in chains,
but all that changed
on May 23,1861,
less than a year
before Smalls' escape,
when 3 runaway slaves made it
here to Fort Monroe,
a Union-held outpost
in Confederate Virginia.
The slaves were taken before
Union Major General
Benjamin Butler.
Defying the law, Butler refused
to return the fugitive slaves
to the Confederacy.
Instead, he invented
a new status for them.
They were contraband of war,
illegal property now forfeited
to the North.
Butler could have no idea
how wide a door he had opened.
MAN: The Contraband Act
doesn't legally free them,
but if you're a slave
on the ground
and you reach Union lines,
that act says
that the officer
is required
to retain you,
put you to work.
In practice, you're ﬂee.
GATES: The word went out
through the slaves' grapevine,
and all these Negroes
descend upon Fort Monroe.
I bet the Army didn't
know what hit them.
No, they didn't, and they
didn't know what to do.
Hundreds came over here,
and they were located
in and around the fort.
So there were all these
makeshift camps everywhere.
Dysentery was very common,
tuberculosis,
all kinds of diseases.
It was a horrendous
situation.
GATES: Neither slave nor free,
the contraband
had found sanctuary,
but were little more
than refugees,
a burden to the war effort
in the eyes of some
Northern soldiers.
We can't imagine,
I don't think, the cost,
the courage,
the difficulty
of making that journey
and getting there
and some commander saying,
"OK, we have to take them in,
"but don't give them food
because that will
make them lazy."
GATES: Still, the escaped slaves
kept coming
in a great upsurge
of hope and courage.
Although their status remained
as uncertain at the war itself,
the contraband sought to live
as fully free men and women.
Even in the midst
of squalid camps,
they pursued a privilege
long denied to slaves-
learning to read and write.
Some contraband began
their education here
on what is today the campus
of Hampton University,
one of the country's oldest
black colleges.
It was all made possible
by a visionary teacher
named Mary Peake.
For Peake,
an educated woman of color,
liberating the mind was as
important as freeing the body.
Before the war,
she had taught slaves in secret,
Defying the law,
but in Union-occupied
Hampton, Virginia,
those laws no longer applied.
Peaks conducted her lessons
beneath the branches
of this oak tree,
which, incredibly,
still stands today.
No one even knew
at the beginning of the war
if a Union victory
would even lead
to the abolition
of slavery.
GLYMPH: No.
GATES: So why
would she do it?
GLYMPH: I think that,
like a lot of blacks,
she saw this
as an opportunity.
She was passionate
about using her skills,
her talents
and abilities
to help uplift
the community.
GATES: Mary Peake's
contraband students
let nothing keep them
from learning.
GLYMPH : There was
a mother and a daughter.
They were living
in this tent.
They had one dress
between the two of them,
and so, during the day,
the daughter
would wear the dress
and go to school
and then come back
afierschooL
and the mother would
then do some work
and then go
to night school.
Hmm.
So they shared
a single dress
between the two of them.
How quickly does
her school grow?
It starts
with a handful,
but then quickly,
there are 50.
Then there are
a hundred.
Mm-hmm.
She ended up
with 900 students.
900 students.
What she
was trying to do
was to prepare
people
to really be
full citizens.
GATES: Escaped slaves
were changing their own lives,
but they were also transforming
the fate of the nation.
By the summer of 1862,
President Lincoln
faced a dilemma.
Not only was the North
losing the war,
but runaway slaves were forcing
him finally to confront
the question of slavery itself.
Lincoln's first objective
in the war
had been to save the Union.
"I have no purpose,"
he had proclaimed,
"to interfere with
the institution of slavery."
But now, military necessity
converged
with the moral imperative
of ending slavery.
GATES: This was
the country in 1862.
GLYMPH: It was, and,
therefore, for Lincoln,
a place he could escape to.
He came here pretty often
in the summer
of '62, which is
his critical summer
where he was writing
the Proclamation.
This is Camp David.
This is his Camp David.
As he wrote
and made the journey
to this cottage,
he would have seen
black refugees camped out
all over the city.
What do you do with them?
Do you just keep ignoring them?
Enslaved people were
making the war their war.
They were making
the war about freedom
and emancipation.
STAUFFER: African Americans
are arguing,
the easiest way
to win the war
is to emancipate slaves,
and they make
a brilliant point
that eventually the Lincoln
Administration accepts,
that "You need us.
If you want to win
this war, you need us."
GATES: Lincoln knew
he could no longer avoid
committing himself
and the nation
to slavery's eradication.
On September 22,
Lincoln showed his cabinet
the outlines of a bold plan-
emancipate the slaves
in enemy territory
and encourage them to find
safety behind Union lines.
On January 1, 1863,
he issued the final draft
to the nation.
"From that day on," it read,
"any slave within
a rebellious state
"shall be then, thenceforward,
and forever free."
Though the Proclamation
didn't abolish slavery,
nor declare all slaves free,
it was a powerful statement,
redefining the war's purpose
as ending slavery.
For African Americans,
enslaved or free,
the Emancipation Proclamation
was their Declaration
of lndependence.
NEWBY-ALEXANDER:
When you read the words
in the Emancipation
Proclamation that say,
"thenceforward
and forever free,"
You don't read
or hear the words
"the exceptions,
the limitations
that follow."
You hear
that you're free,
and that was all
that was needed.
That snowball was
on that steep cliff,
it just got kicked off, and
there was not stopping it.
GATES: The Proclamation
encouraged slaves
to abandon their plantations,
but it couldn't help them do so.
They would have to run
that risk themselves
in a gamble for freedom.
GLYMPH:The Union military
is constantly on the move.
You've got to make
a decision
knowing that you will have
to navigate enemy territory.
The amazing thing is that
these half a million people,
they took that chance.
They left...
They left.
everything
that they knew
under the hope
that they were pan
of this age
of emancipation
and age of freedom.
And age of freedom.
GATES:The Proclamation
held one more surprise.
It granted black men the right
to fight for the Union.
Imagine...
knowing that
they could now
actually take up legally
arms in their own defense.
Mmm, revolutionary.
Revolutionary.
That has to be
the most important thing
about the Emancipation
Proclamation.
Without a doubt.
A white man could be
legally killed
by a black man.
A slaveholder could be
legally killed
by his former slave.
That's everything.
GATES: Neaﬂy 200,000
African Americans
enlisted in the military
during the war,
including my great-granduncle.
They fought for themselves,
they fought for each other,
and they fought for those
who had been left behind.
But most of all, they fought
for a future with hope,
a future of freedom
and equal rights.
Their stories are honored here
at the African American
Civil War Memorial and Museum
in Washington, DC.
GATES: Hari, given the
fact that the military
today is so black,
my students find it
extraordinarily
difficult to believe
that black men had
to fight for the right
to fight,
as it were.
Why?
It's like the 1940s
and 1950s
and the arguments that
African Americans, the Negro,
cannot play basketball
because it requires
too much of the intellect.
Ha ha!
Well, that's the argument
during the Civil War.
They're just not
intelligent enough.
They don't have
the agility,
the courage,
the determination
to be a good soldier.
GATES: While
the Emancipation Proclamation
gave African American men
the right to fight,
it did nothing to guarantee
their equal treatment.
Northern white soldiers were
skeptical of black soldiers.
Southern soldiers
simply reviled them.
Confederate President
Jefferson Davis made it clear.
All black Union soldiers
would be treated
as slaves in rebellion.
JON ES: Jeff Davis would
come out with a proclamation
stating that if a colored
soldier is captured,
he will be returned
to his owner.
If the owner could not be
found, the state would take
the responsibility
and they would be put
to hard labor.
But the Confederate soldiers
would behave not according
to protocol, in many cases.
GATES: Perhaps the Confederate
Army's worst atrocities
against African American troops
came at the Battle
of Fort Pillow, Tennessee,
in 1864.
As defeat loomed,
African American soldiers
attempted to surrender.
Confederate troops
massacred them.
JONES: 255 African American
soldiers were given no quarters.
No quarters means
that when you're captured
as a prisoner of war,
they do not take you
through the regular protocol.
What you're saying is,
they wouldn't allow
black soldiers to surrender.
They just killed them.
You do not allow them
the honor of being a soldier.
GATES: 255 black soldiers
were killed in cold blood.
It was the Confederacy's
brutal reminder
to African Americans of
the price they would pay
for rising up against slavery.
Only 6 months later,
black soldiers
would have their revenge.
It was September 29, 1864.
Union troops assembled
in New Market Heights,
a small town
right outside of Richmond,
the capital of the Confederacy.
They were led
by Benjamin Butler,
the same Benjamin Butler
who, eany in the war,
had refused to return
fugitive slaves to the South.
At New Market Heights,
he commanded black troops
to lead the assault.
JON ES: Butler,
before the assault,
he rides around through
the troops and tells them,
"You go in crying,
remember Fort Pillow."
They're up against
veteran Texas troops,
and to take New Market Heights,
capture the closest position
to Richmond,
you want to send troops
who have the determination,
that won't back down.
[Gunfire]
They're under strict orders
not to stop to fire,
and their comrades
are falling consistently
as they're moving forward,
and the 4th and 6th
United States Colored Troops,
They get almost wiped out.
[Cannon fire]
So it's the next wave,
but it's not easy
for the next wave, either.
They don't stop.
They just keep coming.
Confederates are hearing
this "Remember Fort Pillow,"
and they withdraw
from the position.
We read some scholars
who would say,
"Well, they just decided
they'd defend another position."
Ha ha ha!
That's always
interesting to me.
Yeah, the position
that's called
Cover My Ass.
[Laughter]
That's why the performance
of United States Colored Troops
in these battles is
so important, because
they don't stop.
They don't just say,
"We captured New Market Heights
and we're partying,
the game's over."
They continue.
It's only a matter of time
before Richmond falls.
So that's it.
The cake's all dough,
as my daddy would say.
[Birds crowing]
GATES". By Apr“,
he m: ms over,
and with it,
the promise of the end
of nearly 3 1/2 centuries
of American slavery.
The human cost
was unprecedented--
nearly 750,000 lives lost,
40,000 of them
African Americans--
more deaths than in all other
American wars combined.
As the country entered the
period known as Reconstruction,
the massive federal effort
to rebuild a new South,
the future of the former slaves
was anything but clear.
Their chains had been struck,
but would they realize
their hope for new lives
as free and equal citizens?
We're heading to Edisto Island,
which was the home of
the famous Sea Island cotton,
finest cotton in the world.
Legend has it that even the Pope
wanted his garments,
his vestments,
made out of Sea Island cotton
because this was the place
where black people
actually got a chance
to take their pan
in the promise of America.
The promise of America
was always land,
the right to own property.
Who understood that better
than people
who had served
as property themselves?
Can you imagine
what that must have been like
to farm this island,
producing this rich sea cotton
for all those years,
back-breaking labor,
and then
having the opportunity
to farm that land for yourself?
It must have been one
of the most exhilarating moments
in the history
of the African American people.
All over the South,
that heady promise,
Some land of your own,
filled African Americans
with optimism.
As the federal government
set about reconstructing,
African Americans waited eagerly
to receive their own plots.
Their optimism was born in pan
from a remarkable pledge made
to freed slaves just
a few months before war's end.
Today, the phrase
"40 acres and a mule"
has an ironic connotation,
but for newly freed slaves,
it represented
a tangible manifestation
of their new stake in America.
In fact, the idea came
from the black community itself.
In January 1865,
20 black ministers were summoned
to a meeting in Savannah
with Major General
William Tecumseh Sherman
and Secretary of War
Edwin M. Stanton.
The general and the secretary
wanted some advice.
What did former slaves
most desire when the war ended?
Garrison Frazier,
the 67-year-old Baptist minister
chosen to lead the group,
responded unequivocally.
"The best way we can take care
of ourselves,"
Frazier told them,
"is to have land
"and turn it and till it
by our own labor."
"We want to be placed on land
until we are able to buy it
and make it our own."
"I would prefer to live
by ourselves,
"for there is a prejudice
against us in the South
that will take years
to get over."
GATES: Give the former
slaves land
and let them be self-governing,
and that was the birth
of 40 acres and a mule.
4 days later, Sherman issued
Special Field Order 15.
Some 400,000 acres
of confiscated lands
would be doled out
in 40-acre tracts
to the heads
of former slave families.
As a bonus,
Sherman threw in
some broken-down mules
left over from the war.
Here on Edisto Island,
black women and men,
who had once worked
this land as slaves,
could now claim
their own 40 acres
as ﬂee people.
So, Bernard,
set the scene for me.
They come back with all
that expectation.
They're gonna get land
for the first time.
They're gonna get
their 40 acres.
Yet this would
have been
a very difficult
time for them.
They were more free
than they had ever
been before,
but now they would
be faced with
the prospect
of trying to recraft
and reconstruct
their lives,
and it wasn't
absolutely certain
what the parameters
of their freedoms
were going
to be like.
They would have
subsisted off
of Army rations,
but nevertheless,
I think,
with all of this
deprivation
that they were
surrounded by,
there was the hope
of a new day.
GATES: Well, look
at the wallpaper.
POWERS:
Yeah, that's right.
Newspapers and magazines.
That's right.
They were only given
what were called
promissory titles,
not permanent titles,
but they expected
to receive clear
and free title to
the land down the road.
GATES: But the former slaves
never did get their titles.
Less than a year later,
Lincoln was dead.
His successor, Andrew Johnson,
began to dismantle the plan
for Reconstruction,
starting with
40 acres and a mule.
All confiscated lands were
returned to their former owners.
For African Americans,
President Johnson's order was
a crushing disappointment.
Still, they had little choice
but to keep going,
placing their hopes in
a reconstructed South.
GATES: It's something
I wonder about and think,
"Jesus, how could you
survive every day
and have hope, build
a family, fall in love?"
That's right,
and I guess
that's all you have,
is hope, right?
Hope did, in fact, bring
these people through,
and it gave them
a firm foundation upon
which to visualize
their future.
GATES: If hope was to be
the foundation
of the former slaves' new lives,
love and family would be
its brick and mortar.
GLYMPH: Thousands of people
have lost their kin,
and thousands
of people are very keen
To find members,
family members, and fiends
who have been sold away.
GATES: In freedom,
they set out to rebuild families
shattered by slavery.
They filled newspapers
with information-wanted ads
seeking long-lost
family members.
GLYMPH: The ads captured
the loss that slavery brought
in terms of having your child
torn from your arms.
There would not be
as many reunions
as there had been separations,
but it didn't stop people
from yearning
and trying to imagine
what that babe of 4 months old
looked like 20 years hence,
how had your child fared.
GATES: Freedom promised a future
where black women and men
would have control over their
most fundamental decisions.
They got married,
they took new names,
and they worshipped freely
in their own churches.
For the first time,
African American women and men
could define the terms
of their families' labor.
GLYMPH:
A black mother could say,
"I will not stay
overnight anymore,
"and my 10-year-old daughter
who comes to work with me
"every day will now be going
to school for 3 months,
and when she is not
in school, she won't be
coming here with me."
It meant reclaiming
your right as a human being.
GATES: The social changes
former slaves experienced
were not matched
by economic progress.
One aspect of Southern society
remained fixed--
Old King Cotton still reigned.
Without land of their own,
many freed slaves
went back to work
on cotton plantations,
some for their former masters,
who did their utmost
to impose poor wages
and working conditions.
But once in a great while,
a freed slave
seized a chance
for something more.
One such man
was Benjamin Montgomery,
who had been the favorite slave
at the Davis Bend plantation,
the crown jewel of Mississippi's
planter aristocracy.
WOMAN: Benjamin Montgomery
purchased this land,
and he purchased it from
his former slave-own er,
Joseph Davis.
Joseph Davis,
the brother
of the President
of the Confederacy.
GATES: When Union forces
closed in,
Joseph Davis had ﬂed
the plantation.
After the war ended,
the elderly Davis made
a bold and surprising choice.
He gave his former slave a loan
to buy the property
that he and his brother
Jefferson once shared.
These brick columns are
all that remain
of the house that Jeff built.
Standing here,
I try to picture
what it was like
in Davis' heyday--
a rambling, 8-room home
with a front and back porch,
from which dozens of slaves
could be seen tilling the soil.
Now, one of them,
Benjamin Montgomery,
owned the home built
by the President
of the Confederacy.
And soon, he began to recruit
his fellow former slaves
to join him at Davis Bend.
FIELD: He would rent out
the land to them, and together,
they would build
a successful cotton crop
that would ultimately bring
profits to all of them.
GATES: And profit they did.
FIELD: In 1870,
Benjamin Montgomery was
the third-largest
cotton planter
in the state
of Mississippi.
And that's a lot
of cotton.
Right,
and Mississippi,
of course, is
the largest producer
in the country,
so that makes him,
arguably, the
third-largest
planter in the country
at that time.
It was not just
the quantity of cotton,
it was also
the quality of it.
He was winning awards
left and right,
and he was
widely regarded and
widely respected
by fellow Mississippi
planters,
most of whom were white.
If this were
a Spike Lee film,
the Ku Klux Klan
would have come
galloping down that hill
through the river valley...
Yeah.
Roasted Benjamin Montgomery
and his new plantation.
Right.
But that didn't happen.
Why not?
Local white Southerners,
and white planters
in particular, were
willing to allow him
to carry on with
his economic activities,
as long as he stayed out
of the limelight,
or at least that was
his perception.
He's doing
a lot of work,
culturally and socially,
to kind of keep people
happy with him,
white people,
in particular.
GATES: Montgomery was playing
a delicate and dangerous game,
appeasing whites
so he could continue
to profit from his land.
It was a gamble,
but it was paying off.
Ultimately,
African American s knew,
if they were going to protect
and extend the freedoms
they had gained in the South,
they couldn't depend on
the largesse of whites.
They needed political power
of their own.
To get it, they needed
the right to vote.
STAUFFER: African Americans
were very, very sensitive
and great, in a sense,
historians.
They understood that this
social revolution should be
a revolution about equality
under the law for all people.
If you're African American
and you have the vote,
you have a voice,
you have a public voice
that whites had
long sought to suppress.
GATES: Their struggle
for the vote took place
in a larger political context.
Northern Republicans feared
that the freed African
American population
might play into the hands
of their enemies,
the Southern Democrats.
POWERS:
The Three-fifths Clause,
which was the formula
used for determining
how many Congressmen
any state was entitled to.
The“ was over Mm new,
and so, Kama: ma“ $15
of the slaves being counted,
now it was the total
free population,
and so that really was
a political boon
to the South,
and it would have been
used against the North.
GATES: But if African Americans
were given the vote,
they could create alliances
with Northern Republicans
to forge an unstoppable
political force.
The Republican-controlled
Congress grabbed the chance,
passing the 14th Amendment,
granting full citizenship
and equal protection
under the law to anyone born
in the United States,
regardless of race.
And in the 15th Amendment,
they gave black men
the right to vote.
For the first time,
blacks in many communities
did have
equal representation.
You had black legislators
in Mississippi, in Alabama,
in South Carolina.
GATES: Even South Carolina,
the state that fired the first
shots in the Civil War,
saw black men--former slaves--
elected to office.
One of them was Robert Smalls,
the same man who had
narrowly escaped from slavery
on a boat in Charleston Harbor.
In 1868,
Smalls was elected by the voters
of Beaufort County
to the South Carolina House
of Representatives.
All told, some 2,000
African Americans
would hold office
between 1868 and 1876.
There were sheriffs,
justices of the peace,
EVEN mayors.
The first African Americans
would be elected
to the United States Senate
and the House
of Representatives.
These politicians promised
to use the Reconstruction period
to transform the South
politically,
economically, and socially.
POWERS: This would have
demonstrated, I think,
the virtually unlimited
possibilities of the future.
GATES: But the transfer
of political power in the South
triggered a violent backlash
among whites,
who saw their way
of life threatened.
The small window of opportunity
for freed southern blacks
was slammed shut, as all levels
of white society reacted.
Eutaw, Alabama--
Southern Democrats
assault a rally
of black and white Republicans,
4 black men murdered.
Colfax, Louisiana--
300 armed white men
attack African American s
over the contested outcome
of the local election,
100 black men massacred.
MAN: What's happening
during Reconstruction
is the possibilities,
right, of racial
equality are emerging.
Black people become
a threat to,
you know,
white supremacy.
STAUFFER: Most Southern
whites could not envision
a society in which
blacks had rights,
in which blacks
were treated as humans.
They just assumed
that black supremacy
would replace
white supremacy,
it would be one
or the other.
Mm-hmm.
And that fueled
their desire to do
anything possible
to prevent that
from happening.
They would particularly pursue
people who had achieved
what they saw
as unreasonable success.
The image of a man
with his own wagon
or carriage on the street,
these became kind of rallying
cries for white supremacy.
STAUFFER: You identify
the leading African Americans
and you just murder them.
Ideally, you'd do so
in public to send a message
and a warning:
"Know your place."
GATES: As the violence
escalated,
Northern Republicans began
to reassess their support
for South em blacks.
Political alliances
were one thing;
a second Civil War was another.
"There is a feeling
in this country,"
one African American
observer wrote,
"that the Negro has got
about as much
as he ought to have."
The final betrayal came in 1876.
With the presidential
election deadlocked,
and both political parties
claiming victory,
Republican Rutherford B. Hayes
cut a cynical back-room deal
with South em Democrats.
In return for the presidency,
Hayes promised to remove
the final few thousand
federal troops lingering
in the South.
For African Americans,
the meaning of that symbolic
gesture was all too clear:
Reconstruction was over.
STAUFFER:
By 1876, let's face it.
Most conservative
and moderate whites
had lost whatever
sympathy they had had
for African Americans,
and they rationalized it
by saying, "Well, look what
we've already done for them.
"We've passed the 13th,
14th, 15th Amendment.
"We've given them
everything they need.
Hey, it's time they figure
it out on their own."
250 years of slavery,
10 years of freedom...
Yes.
"Yuma an yum awn.“
BROWN: Southern Democrats
take back the South from
the Republican party and
from all these black people
who have occupied positions
in Southern legislatures.
So you have
the establishment
of white supremacy,
you know, brick by brick in
these Southern territories.
You know, brick by brick in
GATES: Once again,
African Americans in the South
can only depend on
their own tenacity and hope.
Isaiah Montgomery had helped
his father Benjamin
run a successful cotton empire
on his master's former
plantation, Davis Bend,
only to lose the land when
the economically volatile years
after Reconstruction left
the family mired in debt.
Now, Isaiah was determined to
build a haven for black people
in a remote corner
of Mississippi.
FIELD: The Delta was
a majority-black region
that was largely unsettled.
Isaiah Montgomery saw
himself as improving
upon his father's dream,
and he improved upon it
by making this
a paradise
for black landowners.
GATES: Isaiah would call
his new town Mound Bayou.
It was a self-contained,
all-black wand.
FIELD: The idea of having
your own grocery stores,
your own sidewalks
to walk down,
free from the kind
of constant harassment
and the constant threat
of violence that pervaded
most Southern towns
by this point
is simply unimaginable.
GATES: Mound Bayou residents
today remember with awe
the kind of respect
their relatives were afforded,
especially by white Southerners.
MAN: There's a story
of my granddad.
He went to the local
tractor shop there
in Cleveland, Mississippi,
and he stood in the back.
There was this young guy
that not long had been
working behind the counter,
and he saw my granddad
standing there,
and he said, "Nigger,
take your hat off!"
And so my granddaddy
just stood there,
and before he could
say it the next time,
he said, "Nigger- ♪
Said, "Come here,"
they said,
"That's not a nigger.
He's from Mound Bayou."
[Both laugh]
GATES: Isaiah believed
that only by living apart
from white people could
black Southerners thrive.
But his all-black town also
appeased white Southerners
increasingly determined
to impose racial segregation
on the South.
White America did not
fear Mound Bayou.
Mm-mmm.
Montgomery had already
made clear in various ways
that he had no intentions
of being a political problem.
That is, he had no intention
of claiming his rights
beyond the confines
of building his business
and his world
in Mound Bayou.
GATES: In 1890, Isaiah was
the only black delegate
to the Mississippi State
Constitutional Convention.
Hoping to protect Mound Bayou
from violence,
he reluctantly voted in favor
of literacy tests,
knowing that they would
effectively bar black men
from voting in Mississippi.
It was a bargain that would
reverberate across the South
for decades to come.
He said, "I'm willing
to sacrifice 123,000 men
in order that
white people will give us
some breathing room."
Mm-hmm.
"We will stand back
"and let you have
the political arena.
"We will let you have
the franchise.
Just give us a little bit
of room so that we can,
you know, do a few things."
Isaiah himself acknowledged
that it was a compromise,
but on the other hand,
you have to understand
the South and, particularly,
Mississippi at the time.
There is a lynching
in the South every--
it's either third day
or fourth day.
Mmm.
He needs to do everything
he can to ensure
that whites aren't
gonna get outraged
and have a reason
for torching
and burning his community.
Mm-hmm.
And one reason is to say,
"OK, I'll accept your
disenfranchisement.
I just want to
retain my autonomous
black community."
So...was it possible?
Was there a scenario
that you imagine
where their logic
made sense?
In the United States
of America,
which purports to be
a democracy, the notion
that you would have
to give up your freedom
to become ﬂee, it just
doesn't make any sense.
Or that you can bargain
away the future freedoms
of people by giving up
current rights,
I think it was...
like a devil's pact.
You can do it
and hope that, "OK,
you know, we accommodate some,
they'll treat us better,"
but they won't,
and they did not.
But they won't,
GATES: As Southern legislatures
mounted a relentless assault
on their hard-won rights,
African Americans devised
new strategies
to hold on to the gains
they had made
during Reconstruction.
On June 7,1892,
Homer Plessy strode
through the streets
of his native New Orleans
toward the train station.
[Train bell clanging]
This was no idle stroll.
He was about to test
the 14th Amendment's promise
of equal protection
under the law.
He would board
a white passenger car
and refuse to move
to the black one.
GATES: OK, June 7,1892,
the Press Street depot.
What is Homer Plessy
doing there?
Homer Plessy is
attempting to be
arrested, booked,
and tried
for violating the
segregation laws
of 1890.
I don't think he was
very confident
that he wouldn't be
hung that day
because there was
a serious plan in effect
to actually orchestrate
his arrest.
Mm-hmm.
[Bell clan gs]
GATES: Conceived by a group
of black Republicans,
Plessy's gambit was a calculated
act of civil disobedience--
breaking Louisiana's law
in the hope of landing the case
in the United States
Supreme Court.
The group had chosen
Homer Plessy
for one overriding reason:
he was so light-complexioned
that he was indistinguishable
from whites.
GATES: Why did they need
a guy light and bright
and damn-n ear white?
BROWN: What they wanted
to do is to tell the courts
that, you know, you're
putting someone on there
whose race has
to be determined by
a train conductor.
How can this be
the basis of law
when every
train conductor has
to look carefully,
right, at people's skin
and look and say,
"Oh, l think this person
is a Negro"-
Negro reader.
Yeah, exactly, right?
As if they would have
a Negro meter or
something like that.
It's patently absurd.
Plessy gets his ticket,
he goes right past
the colored car,
sits in the white car,
and that's when a
plain-cloth es officer
warns him to get off
the train and, when he
doesn't move,
arrests him
and takes him off.
GATES: The case did make it all
the way to the Supreme Court,
but the Justices didn't do what
Plessy and his backers hoped.
In a momentous decision
that would shape
the next half-century,
they upheld Louisiana's
segregation law.
The Supreme Court decided
that separate but equal
was the law of the land.
Justice might be blind,
but the United States
Constitution
would no longer be
color-blind.
The Plessy decision dealt
the final blow
to the brief, ﬂickering hope
of Reconstruction.
Now, the law relegated
African Americans
to the margins
of white society.
Free? Yes.
Equal? No.
BROWN: That drastically reduces
the horizons for black people.
So what they begin to do is
they begin to live
within the limitations set by
the federal government
and the state governments.
It doesn't mean
the traditions
of struggle end.
Throughout
the darkest days of
Jim Crow segregation,
the black
freedom struggle
never goes away.
GATES: The poet Langston Hughes
would compare the extraordinary
experience of Reconstruction
to a telescope of dreams.
Seen through one end,
the dream "looms larger,
so much larger, it seemed,
than truth can be."
"Turn the telescope
around," he tells us,
"and wonder why what
was so large
becomes so small again."
As the 20th century dammed,
the African American people
could only ask themselves,
"Where has all
our freedom gone?"
facing the bitter irony
of winning their freedom in war,
only to lose their rights
under the law.
Could they summon
the strength for a new fight?
Could they ever reach
that elusive promised land?
[Bird screeches]
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
"Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by...
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER:
Senegal, Africa-
the Door of No Return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah. They have it.
Wi-Fi. Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: Others
just a few minutes.
Either my, our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community,
the simple joy
of staying in touch.
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER: The Howard
and Abby Milstein Foundation,
in partnership with Hoover
Milstein and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
ANNOUNCER: The Ford Foundation
Just Films...
...and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
Next time on
"The African Americans"...
Jim Crow laws offer
new challenges.
We're going to show
that separate but equal
is not going to stop us
from being successful.
ANNOUNCER:And they take
the fight to the Supreme Court.
WOMAN: He says,
"The black lawyer is a soldier
taking the battle
into the courtroom."
ANNOUNCER:
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross."
"The African Americans"
story continues online
at pbsnrg/manyrivers
with streaming video and more.