[Bells ringing]
HENRY LOUIS GATES JR;
The American Revolution
was an inspiration
to black people.
They hoped the words
of the patriots
would apply equally to them,
but they were wrong.
When the armies left the fields,
we were a country of farmers
founded on notions of freedom,
and our largest farms
were worked by slaves.
There were 700,000 slaves in
the United States at its birth.
They had no rights and no power,
yet they were determined
to hold America to its ideals.
Their struggle would last
for generations,
and that struggle would
fundamentally reshape
the character of our nation.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by...
DIFFERENTANNOUNCER:
Senegal, Africa-
the Door of No Return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah. They have it.
Wifi. Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: others
just a few minutes.
Either my, our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community,
the simple joy
of staying in touch.
DIFFERENTANNOUNCER: the Howard
and Abby Milstein Foundation
in partnership
with Hoover Milstein
and Emigrant Bank...
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
ANNOUNCER: the Ford Foundation
Just Films...
and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
GATES: Sheffield, Massachusetts.
At the time
of the American Revolution,
this was slave country.
Slavery was legal here,
just as it was
in each of the 13 colonies...
but the Revolution brought
new laws to this land,
and here in this farmhouse,
one slave began
to test those laws.
Her name was Mum Be“.
For decades, she served meals
in these rooms.
Then she heard talk
around the table
Of a new Constitution that said
all men were ﬂee.
So Mum Bett decided to act.
She ran away to the nearby town
of Stockbridge,
where she convinced
a young lawyer
to help her file a suit.
Other slaves had sued
their masters before,
but this case was different.
Mum Bett was challenging
the very existence
of slavery in Massachusetts.
Her argument was that slavery
violated
The most basic principle
of the American Revolution,
that all human beings
were created equal.
It was a powerful argument,
and she won.
Mum Ben's victory echoed
across the young nation.
Within two decades,
every state in the North
was on the road to abolition,
and this political
transformation
was accompanied
by a religious one
as an evangelical revival
spread across the country
proclaiming that all races
were equal in the eyes of God.
MAN: You have these big,
outdoor preaching sessions
where people gather
in large numbers
to hear a charismatic preacher
give the word of God.
MAN: ° Didn't my Lord
deliver Daniel °
° Daniel, Daniel? °
BROWN: A lot of it
is the language of Exodus,
which is something that's very
dangerous for s slave society
because when people begin
to read the story of Exodus
and think about the delivery
of God's chosen people
from bondage in Egypt,
they begin to think
about their own delivery,
and they begin to interpret that
as God's mandate
for them to become
abolitionists,
and so that becomes very
important in a white awakening
to the evil of slavery.
MAN: ° Didn't my Lord, Daniel °
° Why not every man? °
GATES: The evangelical movement
also offered opportunities
to black people,
among them a young slave
named Richard Allen.
[Rooster crows]
Allen grew up on a Delaware farm
much like this.
In the woods nearby,
he heard traveling preachers
say that slavery
was a mortal sin,
and Allen hatched the plan
to make his master listen.
His master
was religious,
but not in any kind
of intensive way.
Richard Allen really
tried to cultivate that.
Sounds like Richard Allen
was a bit of a trickster.
Allen was a quietly
intensive man
who was always plotting
to gain his freedom.
So once he gets
his masters trust,
he convinces these
antislavery preachers
to visit his
master's house,
and when they do that,
he know what
they're gonna say.
They're gonna convince
Allen's master
that he is sinning
and is gonna go to hell
unless he emancipates.
Allen put the
kajunga on him, man.
Well, as he puts it
in his autobiography,
soon after the preachers
visited his house,
"my master allowed us
to buy our freedom."
So he knew
what he was doing
every step of the way.
GATES: Now free, Richard Allen
set out to share his faith
with the world.
He soon became a preacher
himself,
spreading the message
of equality,
and in the winter of 1786,
he arrived here in Philadelphia.
[Horse neighs]
At the time, Philadelphia
was the largest city
in the United States
and home to a burgeoning
abolitionist movement...
[Gavel bangs]
That opposed slavery
on religious grounds.
It was also a magnet for
a steadily growing population
of free black people.
NEWMAN: Philadelphia,
it's the Harlem
of early America.
This is where people go
to make their way
in culture, to find
new job opportunities,
to bond
in a social way.
GATES: Allen was invited
to preach in a white church
that was caught up
in the spirit of the time.
It must have seemed like
he'd reached the Promised Land,
but Allen soon faced
a hard fact.
Freedom was one thing.
Equality was something else.
NEWMAN: Race rears
its ugly head.
White preachers there
separate black
Congregationalists.
By the 1790s there's
gonna be a black pew
which is separate
and above the white pew,
and Richard Allen thinks
that this violates
everything he learned.
GATES: Emboldened,
Allen made a decision
that would change history.
He and his friends decided
to stage America's first sit-in.
NEWMAN:They gonna
march into the church.
They're not gonna sit
in the Negro pews.
They're gonna go down
into the front
of the church,
and they're gonna sit
with other congregants.
So Richard Allen
is praying.
His great friend
Absalom Jon es
is praying next to him.
White preachers come up,
tapped him on
the shoulder, and say,
"You got to get
out of here,"
and after prayers
are over,
Richard Allen,
together with all
the other black
congregants, get up,
march out of the
church in a body,
and, as he says,
"We never returned."
GATES:Allen resolved
to start his own church,
an African American church,
the first of its kind
in the United States.
His efforts began humbly.
He bought a blacksmith's shop,
dragged it onto a vacant lot,
and set up a temporary parish.
Then he spent the next 23 years
struggling to make it permanent.
[Organ playing
UH
Allen's church,
the African Methodist
Episcopal Church,
still thrives today.
<> Holy, holy, holy °
GATES: This is just one
of its 7,000 congregations
around the globe.
Got to tell you, you all look
wonderful down here.
° Holy, holy, holy... °
MAN: To a person
from the eany 19th century,
Richard Allen
would have been
like what
President Barack Obama
is to us today.
He did what nobody
thought was possible.
And he showed that black
people could create
and sustain their
own institution.
Oh, absolutely.
You look at the modem
civil rights movement,
really, the blueprint
was laid here.
It started here,
indeed.
I mean, for example,
Rosa Parks.
Here she is,
an AME member,
a stewardess in
an AME church in Alabama,
and I am convinced
that having heard the story
of Allen's walkout
all of her life,
that as she sat
on that bus, deep down,
she knew that she
was not stepping out
into uncharted
territory.
°All need the Bible °
° You need the Bible °
GATES: Allen's church
was a powerful rebuke
to the very existence
of slavery.
If black people
could build a place like this,
what couldn't they do?
For one hopeful moment
at the end of the 18th century,
that question hung
over the entire nation,
North and South.
Some Southerners began
to free their slaves.
Small ﬂee black communities
began to spring up
in Southern cities,
and it brieﬂy seemed
as if America might actually
live up to the promise
of its Revolution...
but the moment didn't last.
The agrarian South was simply
too dependent upon slave labor.
Southern lawmakers began
to erect enormous obstacles
in front of masters
who wanted to free their slaves.
It was a crushing blow
to the African Americans
still held in bondage,
but some refused to accept it.
But some refused to accept it.
On Sunday, August 10, 1800,
a group of slaves
gathered near this creek
on the outskirts
of Richmond, Virginia.
Sunday was their day off,
but this Sunday,
they'd come to plot a revolt,
summoned by a young blacksmith
named Gabriel.
Here's a guy Wm),
if he lived
in Mum Bett's
Massachusetts,
things would
be different.
He's got a skill.
He's literate.
He's respected, but he's
tied to the plantation.
GATES: Gabriel recruited
followers from miles around,
armed them with homemade swords,
and organized them for battle.
His plans called for 3 separate
slave armies
to seize the Virginia capital
and kidnap its governor.
Slavery was to be ended
by negotiation,
but it never happened.
[Thunder]
On the day of the uprising,
a violent storm hit Richmond.
Trees fell,
and bridges were washed away.
[Thunder]
Gabriel decided to postpone...
But when the storm broke,
two slaves panicked
and told their masters.
The rebels were rounded up,
tried, and sentenced to death.
In the end,
in your judgment,
was Gabriel a patriot?
He believed in what
the Founding Fathers
claimed were
American ideals.
He believed in freedom
for all people.
He didn't
want to kill people
for the sake
of killing people.
He wanted to kill
a handful of people
to free several
hundred thousand
enslaved Virginians,
and that, I think,
makes him a patriot.
GATES: Slaveholding Virginia
took a different view
of Gabriel.
He and his fellow rebels
were marched down this path
to a gallows.
Then they were executed
and buried in unmarked graves
beneath this field.
In a sense, their deaths marked
the end of one era
and the start of another.
NARRATOR: Cotton is king.
In 1781 , a New England farm boy
named Eli Whitney
put together a few boards
and rollers.
GATES: Many of us learned
this story as children.
Eli Whitney, a Yankee tinkerer,
invented a machine
that launched
the Industrial Revolution.
What we didn't learn was that
Whitney's cotton gin
also launched a new phase
of American slavery,
a phase in which ideas
about black freedom
were overwhelmed by the need
for black labor.
It would be the nadir
of African American history...
And it all started
with a simple, white plant.
MAN: It was economically
unfeasible to grow cotton
before the cotton gin
because it took one individual
about 10 hours
to produce
one pound
of usable cotton.
One individual,
10 hours, one pound...
Right.
of clean cotton.
Right, clean cotton,
and so even the
first primitive gin
could produce
about 50 pounds
of cotton in one day,
and very quickly,
they'd grow until
eventually producing
thousands of pounds
of cotton a day.
And this is the greatest
economic boom
in the history
of the United States.
Oh, sure.
The whole country is
benefiting from this.
Yeah.
GATES: What made cotton
so desirable?
A perfect storm.
In the 1790s,
America's oldest crops,
like tobacco,
were depleting farmland
and dropping in value.
At the same time,
the textile industry
in Great Britain was exploding,
creating enormous
international demand
for cotton clothing.
Eli Whitney's gin
merely provided the motor
for a global economic machine,
and slavery was its fuel.
DEYLE: Everybody was
getting a piece of it-
all these Northern bankers
and marketing people,
folks who owned
the ships
that transported
the cotton.
Everybody was getting
a piece of the pie.
GATES: Cotton utterly
transformed the United States,
making fertile land
from Georgia to Texas
extraordinarily valuable.
The fact that Native Americans
lived on these lands
was a temporary inconvenience
solved by a policy
of Indian removal,
the massive replacement
of Native populations
with slave plantations.
It's a pan of our
troubled history
that can still be seen
from the air.
DEYLE: if we were ﬂying
over this prior
to European settlement,
we would've seen
large fields of corn
and beans,
trees, and squash.
When the first English
began moving in here,
they begin chopping down
the trees
and expanding the fields
available for cotton.
GATES: The enormous
profitability of cotton
undermined the principles
of the American Revolution
and forever altered black life.
The more money the planters made
from growing cotton,
the more cotton
the planters wanted to grow,
and that took more slaves.
Slaves in the Upper South
became incredibly more valuable
as commodities because
of this demand for them
in the Deep South.
They were sold off in droves,
and that created
a second Middle Passage,
and, in many ways,
the second Middle Passage
was just as devastating
as the first.
To feed King Cotton, more than
a million African Americans
were carried off
into the Deep South.
That's 2 1/2 times the number
that were brought
to the United States
from Africa.
It was the largest
forced migration
in American history...
and it filled the countryside
with a haunting sight-
slaves chained together
marching south.
[Chains rattling]
WOMAN: You'd hear
the clanking of chains
as the enslaved people
walked through here.
Like a prison gang.
Exactly, exactly.
The men usually
were in front,
and they were always
chained by the necks
and by the wrists.
Hmm.
Women weren't
always chained,
but sometimes
they were.
I always
tell people
to think about
the 5 senses
when you talk
about slavery.
So what do you hear?
What do you think?
What do you taste?
What do you smell?
You'll hear weeping
and sobbing and wailing,
and oftentimes when
families were separated,
you'll have slave
narratives talk about
how they heard
their mothers screaming
up until the distance,
until the wagon was gone,
or even when
the wagon was gone,
they could still
hear the screams,
screams
from the mothers.
Do you have
nightmares about it?
Do you dream
about it?
Yes , yes .
It's the stories about
women and being raped.
Here they are, walking 200,
300 miles' joumey, tired.
Then at night,
they were being raped.
I can't imagine
the kind of shame
that enslaved
people felt,
and if there was
a partner around,
to have to witness that,
somebody putting their hands
on their partner like that,
must have been really difficult.
It must have been
a nightmare.
Yeah.
GATES:The second Middle Passage
lasted roughly 70 years,
from 1790 right up
to the Civil War.
For black people in the South,
that meant 70 years
of near-constant upheaval.
Slave families that had been
stable for generations
were suddenly and irrevocably
shattered.
Every time
somebody was sold,
people would come
out of the fields
to say good-bye to the
people who were leaving,
and they had certain hymns
that they would sing
about seeing each other
again in heaven,
and so that music
and paying homage
to those people was
really a way of saying
they did have bonds
and then when those
were being broken,
they had to have
some kind of way
of saying good-bye.
CHORUS: ° Look down °
° Look down °
° “m mug, mug, {am road °
° Where you and I-- °
° I must 90°
GATES: The rise of cotton
affected every African American,
even those who were free.
This was especially true
for the free black people
who remained in the South
struggling to build lives
within a slave economy.
Some made decisions
that are difficult for us
to understand today.
This cemetery holds the remains
of the Brown Fellowship Society,
an elite organization
of ﬂee black men
in Charleston, South Carolina.
They came together
to promote
their common goals,
their common purposes,
mutual elevation,
social advancement, but...
GATES: The Society's members
were craftsmen and tradesmen.
Many of their clients
were white slave owners,
and some chose to buy slaves
for themselves,
but their motives
were complex.
We can't shy away
from the fact
that you had ﬂee blacks
that owned slaves
and used them in the same way
that whites did,
but we also know
that you had people
who were free who were--
quote, unquote--"married"
to a slave spouse,
and what they might do
is purchase
the enslaved spouse,
but now the law would not allow
them to emancipate the person,
and so they end up
holding the individual,
who's really their
husband or wife, as a slave.
Why didn't they challenge
the status quo?
They didn't
challenge the status quo
because they understood how
precarious their freedom was.
GATES: Try to imagine having
to purchase your own spouse.
That was the reality
for some ﬂee black people
in the South.
They existed on the margins
of the largest slave society
in the history of the world.
In the history of the world.
The white planters
who stood above them
were making more money
than any other group in America.
They set the political course
of our nation
by controlling its wealth,
crafting a new landscape
with new centers of power...
like Natchez, Mississippi.
In 1800,
this was a trading post.
50 years later,
there were more millionaires
here per capita
than anywhere else in America,
and in their day,
money ﬂowed from a place
just nearby.
This is called
Forks of the Road.
It's the dividing point
on a rural highway
right outside Natchez.
It may look like
a sleepy intersection,
but this was once
the second largest slave market
in the United States,
a place where black people
from the Upper South
were brought to be sold
into the Deep South.
This was
a specialty market.
You go to certain
places you know
where you can
get what you want.
Mm-hmm.
That was this place.
If you wanted a field hand,
you can find them here.
If you wanted somebody
with more technical skills,
you can find them here--
builders, carpenters,
any and everything
you were looking for.
This was like
a shopping center.
What is was was like
going to Costco or Walmart,
but the product
that was being sold...
Were human beings.
GATES: Tens of thousands
of slaves were sold
at Forks of the Road,
and the planters who bought them
weren't just buying workers
for their cotton fields.
They had a very specific
interest in women.
WHITE: You wanted men
for the heavy labor,
and you particularly
may have had an interest
in females for their
ability to reproduce
the next generation
of enslaved people
for your particular
plantation.
GATES: The high cost of
purchasing even a single slave
meant that most masters tried
to breed their own labor force,
and some went to great lengths
to make it happen,
from forced pairings
of slave couples to rape.
Of all the major slave societies
in the New World,
only in the United States
did the slave population
naturally increased over time.
The 400,000 people
that we imported from Africa
had become nearly 4 million by
the outbreak of the Civil War.
The numbers are staggering,
and so was the violence required
to keep them all under control.
This small museum
in Walterboro, South Carolina,
holds evidence of that violence,
objects that seemed to come
from the Middle Ages.
Oh, man, look at that.
Yeah, for the neck.
A whip.
Right.
They would pour salt
in the wounds of people
after they
had been whipped--
men, women,
children whipped.
Slave muzzle. Mm.
What had
that person said?
Why was that person
being muzzled?
What always strikes me when
I look at items like this,
probably some
enslaved blacksmith
created these items.
Mm. He had to make
the instruments
for your own
oppressor.
Exactly, exactly.
What choice
do you have?
The shackles...
Mm...
BROWN: You have all these
implements of torture
which are tools for
punishing people, right,
who don't do what
they're supposed to do,
but they're also
symbolic, right?
So if you see someone
muzzled or whipped
in your community,
you're warned
what not to do.
It creates this
pervasive sense
of fear and terror.
Slave doesn't
have to mean
that you're whipped
every day,
you're raped every day,
that you're tenured
every day
to be incredibly
destructive
to one's spirit
and soul and being.
You just have to commit
such shocking violence
upon the bodies
of a few examples
that nobody else would
dare to think about it.
Now, the funny thing is,
people still do dare,
right, right?
You still do have
people saying,
"Well, whatever
they got,
it's got to be
better than this."
GATES: Early on the morning
of August 22,1831,
a group of slaves crept
into the plantation house
that once stood
on these Virginia fields.
They killed the planter
and his wife.
Then they killed the children.
The bloodiest slave revolt in
American history was underway.
Over the next two days, more
that 60 white people would die.
WOMAN: They go house to house,
and as they go,
they pretty much kill
every man, woman, and child
that they can find.
It was in credibly
personal.
The people that
these rebels were killing
were often people whom
they've grown up with,
whose parents
had enslaved their parents.
GATES: The slaves were led
by a man named Nat Turner,
a self-styled prophet
who claimed that God
had told him to slay
his enemies.
In hindsight, his motives
seemed much simpler.
GATES: Why did he do it?
Why him? Why here?
Why then?
He did it because
slavery was awful.
Slavery was horrible.
He did it because daily
he was watching
communities
be torn apart.
He did it because
he knew the stories
of women abused
by slave owners.
He knew the stories
of how, from farm to farm,
being split up
was horrible...
Mm-hmm.
And he knew
the constant threat
of being shipped away.
GATES: Turners revolt
was crushed on this field
by a local militia.
Looking back, it's easy
to see it as a suicide mission,
the desperate act
of a people pushed too far,
but it was more than that.
Turner made real the secret
hopes of millions of slaves,
And he sent shockwaves
across slaveholding America.
BROWN: The Nat Turner
revolt happens
in an international context
where not only
are the abolitionists
in the North beginning
to gear up their agitation
against slavery,
but also in the British Empire,
slavery is on its last legs.
In 1838, it's over,
and slavery has ended
in the British Empire.
South em planters
are overwhelmingly
concerned with this.
They know that if slavery
is not defended aggressively,
it's gonna be over, right,
and Nat Turner is just
one warning signal among many
that they're on the losing side
of a global battle
GATES: In the wake
of turner's revolt,
Southern planters defended
themselves
by launching an intense
ideological campaign
projecting an image
of happy slaves
and benevolent masters,
arguing that their way of life
was beneficial to both races.
MAN: There were some
proslavery writers who argued
that what slavery really was
was the possibility of
perfecting the human condition.
It's like Americans have been
given this gift of Africans.
These were people who came
to see slavery
as something not just good,
but natural, permanent,
possibly the way you create
the ideal community,
the ideal wand.
GATES: Scientists even tried
to prove that black people
were pan of
a different species,
a species suited for slavery
by nature.
BERRY: They would actually
start measuring
the size
of black people's skulls,
and they would talk about how
they were not as intelligent
because of the shapes
of their heads,
the size of their brains,
and then they would look
at things like
how robust they were
in terms of not their brains,
but their bodies,
and they'd say, "Well, look
at their physical bodies.
They're made
for this kind of work."
GATES: Even in the North, these
racist attitudes held sway.
Newspapers brimmed
with grotesque caricatures
of free black people.
Laws were written
to restrict their rights,
and racial violence
became commonplace.
BROWN: There are a lot
of white people in the North
who are just plain racist and
don't want black people around,
and so black people find
that they're restricted
to certain jobs
and certain industries.
They find they're restricted
to certain places within a city.
They find they're only allowed
to bury their dead, right,
in burial grounds
for black people.
BLIGHT: Free blacks,
North or South,
were this kind
of an American caste set apart.
They lived insecure lives,
threatened lives,
and we know this because
of certain mobs, riots.
A black orphanage
in New York City was bu med.
Black schools
were sometimes attacked.
They were always
weak in cohesion,
weak in wealth, weak in power,
but, nevertheless,
they were survivors,
and they had leaders.
GATES: Despite all
they had endured,
free black people
refused to be intimidated.
They had been in America
too long
and invested too much
to back down.
In their families,
churches, and jobs,
they showed that they were fully
capable American citizens...
and they understood that as long
as slavery continued to exist,
no black person
could be truly ﬂee.
So they began to agitate for
abolition with increasing force.
They allied themselves
with a few sympathetic whites
in the North in order to raise
a chorus of voices
against the slaveholding South.
Perhaps the more powerful voice
came from a young man
who simply told his own story.
Who simply told his own story.
Frederick Douglass was raised
by his grandmother Betsy Bailey
in a cabin near
these Maryland woods.
For the first 6 years
of his life,
Betsy was the only family
he really knew,
but then one morning, Betsy
led him away from their home.
She had been told to deliver him
to work on a plantation
12 miles away.
Douglass had no idea
what was happening,
but Betsy did.
She had brought him here
for one reason
and one reason only,
this boy that she
had raised and loved,
and that was to abandon him.
When they reached this house,
Betsy told him to go play
with some other children.
Then she slipped away.
He never saw her again.
BLIGHT: The way he remembers it
in the autobiographies
is as a childhood trauma,
laying on the ground crying,
and for a 6-year-old it was
as though his world had ended.
GATES: Douglass would spend
the next 14 years in slavery,
yet he refused to be broken.
He kept trying to escape,
and on his third try,
he succeeded.
BLIGHT: He takes a train.
He takes, actually, two trains,
3 ferry boats,
goes through Philadelphia,
crosses the Susquehanna,
the Hudson.
So it was highly planned
down to the moment
he would jump on the train.
GATES: Douglass ended up here
in the whaling town
of New Bedford, Massachusetts,
home to a small
ﬂee black community
and central to the burgeoning
abolitionist movement.
This is the place
where he
discovered himself
in many ways.
How do you mean?
Well, he was,
like many others,
simple
an escaped slave,
and he discovered
a voice, a role
to be an antislavery
agitator,
to be a revolutionary,
if you will.
One of the first
speeches he made
was in the church.
GATES: Douglass found work
on these docks,
joined the black church
in the town,
and began to speak out
against slavery.
Soon, he caught the attention
of white abolitionists
who desperately needed
black voices.
MAN: White abolitionists
could be militant and committed,
but in their voices the slave
experience would be abstract,
whereas with Douglass,
he was a manifestation
of the principal charges
that the abolitionists
were making against
the slave regime,
especially
its destruction
of the family life
of slaves.
He could speak
directly to that
in terms of
his own family.
GATES: In the summer of 1841,
Douglass came here
to Nantucket, Massachusetts,
to speak
at an antislavery convention.
In the audience sat
William Lloyd Garrison,
the leading white
abolitionist of the day.
Douglass was just 23 years old,
but he was about
to alter history.
HOLT: It was his first speech
before an integrated audience.
So he was very nervous.
Douglass finishes
his speech.
Garrison leaps up and
says to the audience,
"Do we have here
a chattel,
or do we have a man?"
and the audience
responds, "A man."
"And should this man be
return ed to slavery?"
and the audience
roared no.
Frederick Douglass
was launched.
Yes. He was
invited to join
the Anti-Slavery Society
as a lecturer.
They hired him
on the spot.
on the spot, man.
GATES: Douglass began to travel
the North giving speeches,
living proof of our nation's
fundamental hypocrisy,
showing audiences
that a black person
was every bit the equal
of a white person.
BLIGHT: Frederick Douglass
gave us a critique
of the United States
that's unique and as powerful
as any we've ever had.
He's speaking to history,
to the nation, to the world
about the meaning
of the United States
and how it has betrayed
its promise.
There's no better voice
of that story and that pain
and that promise than Douglass.
I mean, he's the
Martin Luther King and then some
of the 19th century.
GATES: Douglass
and his allies in the North
forced slavery
into national politics,
making it an issue
of intense debate.
In the South, slaves pressed
the issue themselves
by running away whenever
and however they could.
Their stories filled
a growing abolitionist press,
giving rise to rumors
of a vast network for escapees
soon called
the Underground Railroad.
Pan folklore, pan propaganda,
the Underground Railroad
was never as large
as we often imagine,
but it was real.
A loosely organized network of
safe houses in the border states
helped more than 20,000 runaways
make their way to freedom.
The network was run
by free blacks
and sympathetic whites,
and it required
immense courage from them all.
This is one of the few
documented safe houses
on the Underground Railroad
and the site
of at least one
remarkable escape.
WOMAN: Mary Corbett
heard a knock on the door
and it was an enslaved man
who was ﬂeeing,
and the sheriff
was after him,
and he pleaded to her
to help him.
So, she brings him
into the house
and they go all the way
up to the attic area,
and she points to
a very, very, very small,
little door in the eaves
and suggests that he try
to crawl in there
and hide himself.
LARSON, VOICE-OVER:
There's a pounding on the door.
The sheriff and his posse
are with him,
and she opens the door
and lets them in,
and she tells them they're
welcome to search
any room in the house.
Stop.Tum around.
And here's the cupboard
that Sam hid in.
That?
Yes. Mary Corbett
brought him up here
and he--
and he squeezed himself
in there.
My God.
It's just so tiny.
LARSON: And the sheriff
decided not to look,
because they didn't think
that a man could
fit in there.
They would've
just caught me.
Ha!
I'm too claustrophobic
to go in there.
I just said, "Look,
let's make a deal."
But if the sheriff
is after you with
his dogs and guns,
you might
find a way.
That's incredible.
No wonder they
didn't look there.
Right.
Amazing.
GATES: infuriated by
all the runaways,
southerners pushed for
harsh laws to stanch the ﬂow,
culminating in the notorious
Fugitive Slave Act of 1850,
a watershed moment
in American history.
The law required northerners
to help capture
anyone even accused of
being a runaway slave...
turning the north into
a police power for the south.
It also placed every free black
person in terrible danger.
WOMAN: Every time you
walked on the street,
you were subject to being
claimed as a slave.
You're living every day afraid
and watching over your shoulder
to make sure that you're
not being watched by someone
who was looking for you
or someone else
and would happily take you
if they can't find
the someone else.
GATES: As bounty hunters
ﬂooded northern cities,
black people began
to look for freedom
in ever-more-distant places.
Small numbers had been
running away to Canada
since the Revolutionary War.
Now they began to come here--
to Niagara Falls on
the Canadian border-in droves.
Why Canada?
No slavery.
And no slavery meant
no slave catchers.
In Canada, a black person
could serve on a jury.
A black person could vote.
A black person
could own property.
A black person could
become a citizen.
Canada was for black people
what the United States was
for white people--
the land of the free,
the home of the brave.
Over 10,000 African Americans
ﬂed to Canada in the 1850s,
including the most
well-known conductor
of the Underground Railroad-
Harriet Tubman.
Tubman settled here, in the tiny
town of St. Catharines,
and joined this church, which
became a hub for runaways.
There are black families
still living in this town
who trace their roots
back to those runaways,
people whose ancestors took
an almost unimaginable risk.
WOMAN: Here is
just one portion of
the descendant wall
from 1838 all the way
to today.
This is portions of
the Cassiel family...
You had to get
out of the south,
and you were
on your own.
What did you have?
You didn't have a map,
you didn't have
the education,
you had nothing.
So, you had to be
able to rely on
the north star,
and yourself.
I want to point out
my immediate family.
So, this is all
my mother's side.
This is
the home team.
Yeah.
This is
my mom's mom.
And then,
bounty hunters
are after you.
So, there was
a lot at risk,
and not many would do it
and those that did,
I mean,
it's documented--
you had to be
a little bit bent.
You had to be...
ha ha ha!
You had to be
totally crazy.
Yeah. Ha! Yeah.
When I was a youngster,
we knew of the stories,
but I never appreciated
any of it,
never looked back or
even thought about it,
until I was grown,
and then it's like,
"My God, my people
did that?
That's how we got here?"
GATES: The very existence
of these families,
an entire community of people
descended from escaped slaves,
is a testament
to their strength.
BROWN: When I think about
the Underground Railroad,
it makes me want to claim
slaves, right, as my ancestors,
because they were genius
in order
to pull something of like this.
I think about this and I think,
wow, you know,
slavery is not a shame on me,
because my ancestors
were some of the most
creative, resourceful people
in the history of
the United States.
That's a shame
on the slaveholders.
But there's no stigma
that I bear
by being descended from people
who could do something
like that, you know,
who could pull something
like that off.
GATES: Unfortunately,
the Underground Railroad
was out of reach
for almost all slaves.
Only a fraction ever
made it to freedom.
Their stories are inspiring,
but their experience
was not typical.
As the Civil War drew near,
almost 4 million slaves
remained trapped in a nation
still struggling to resolve its
most fundamental contradictions.
Their lives were desperate,
and the choices they faced
are hard to contemplate.
Covington, Kentucky--
the north em border
of the slaveholding south.
In January of 1856,
an enslaved woman
named Margaret Garner
lived here on a farm.
Margaret was 22, she was
married, with 4 children.
Freedom lay just 5 miles away,
so she and her husband
decided to run.
They traveled by night
and made it here,
to the banks of the Ohio River,
at dawn.
This was the barrier between
slave Kentucky and free Ohio.
It was a quarter-mile wide
and frozen solid.
WOMAN: They got here
just before sunrise.
GATES: They must have been
exhausted and terrified.
And-and cold.
And cold, yeah,
and they look over there,
and there's
nothing but ice.
Frozen solid.
A natural foot bridge.
A natural
foot bridge
to freedom.
GATES: The Gamers
walked across the river,
risking their lives
with every step.
And then, they arrived
at a small house in Ohio,
owned by a ﬂee black man.
But their triumph
was short-lived.
Within hours, federal marshals
had tracked the family down.
They got a big
block of wood
and start
ramming in the door.
They try to go
into the windows,
and outside, a crowd
is gathering,
just to see this
scene taking place.
Inside,
there's mayhem,
there's alarm.
People
were hysterical
at the thought
that they were so
close to freedom,
and had only enjoyed
it for two hours,
and now, you know,
it looks like
they're gonna
be returned
into bondage.
Nightmare.
Yes.
GATES: Barricaded in the house,
Margaret Gamer did
something unthinkable.
TAYLOR: As the marshals were
battering in the house,
Margaret Garner decided,
rather than return to slavery,
she would kill her children.
[Door creaks]
GATES: When the marshals
finally broke in,
they were confronted
by a horrible scene.
Margaret had slashed the throat
of her daughter Mary.
Mary lay on the ﬂoor dead.
Hiding in the next room
were her two young sons,
still alive, but
bruised and bleeding.
Margaret, knife in hand,
was quite clear about
what she'd done and why.
The only
direct quote we have
from Margaret Garner
about the murder
was she says,
"I did the best that
a mother could do,
"and I would've done
better and more
for the rest.
We done
the best I could."
Meaning "I would've
killed them all...
Right.
If I could've."
And for her, she said,
she said this to
a couple of visitors
who saw her
when she was in jail,
that this was freedom.
She called her
deceased toddler a bird
for having
ﬂown into freedom.
GATES: Margaret Garner
quickly became a legend,
celebrated and condemned
across the country.
What she had done became fodder
for both sides of
the slavery debate.
South em whites claimed
that Margaret showed
that black people were subhuman,
capable of monstrous deeds,
and in need of their masters
paternal care.
Abolitionists claimed
that Margaret revealed
the essential inhumanity
of bondage.
Margaret Garner stood for
powerful ideas, images
on both-all sides,
and perhaps not enough
for her own side.
Just like "I'm not
a poster child for abolitionism
"and I'm not a defective mother,
"but I am a woman who knows
what it feels like, looks like,
means to be a slave, and I don't
want that for my children."
GATES: Margaret Gamers story
had a final tragic turn.
An Ohio court ruled that
as a slave, she was property,
and couldn't be
tried for murder.
So, she was given back
to her owner.
And here, on a riverboat
heading south,
Margaret made one last decision
about her family.
She let her
infant daughter Celia
slip into the icy water
and drown.
If Celia had only lived 9 more
years, she would've been ﬂee,
but Margaret couldn't have
possibly known that.
Margaret preferred to kill
her own children
rather than to allow them
to live the social death
of slavery.
It was a horrifying decision,
but it tells us something
about the America of its time.
Slavery was so deeply embedded
in the nation
that violence seemed
the only way to end it.
And much more violence
was coming.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
"Many Rivers to Cross"
was made possible by...
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER:
Senegal, Africa-
the Door of No Return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah. They have it.
Wi-Fi. Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: Others
just a few minutes.
Either my, our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community,
the simple joy
of staying in touch.
DIFFERENT ANNOUNCER: The Howard
and Abby Milstein Foundation,
in partnership with Hoover
Milstein and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
ANNOUNCER: The Ford Foundation
Just Films...
...and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
Next time on
"The African Americans"...
The country erupts in civil war.
Lincoln would've
seen black refugees
camped out
all over the city.
ANNOUNCER: But what
would freedom bring?
What's happening during
Reconstruction is
black people
become a threat
to white supremacy.
ANNOUNCER:
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross."
"The African Americans"
story continues online
at pbsnrg/manyrivers
with streaming video and more.