HENRY LOUIS GATES, JR.:
I've spent much of my life
Searching for the stories
of the African American people.
MAN: Our first notation
of Anthony Johnson
essentially defines him as
"Antonio the Negro."
GATES: I've always wanted
to tell their history:
5 centuries in the making.
It's a living history,
and I've traveled
around the country...
and across the globe
to chronicle it.
As-Salaam-Alaikum.
Did any of you
receive wealth
inherited from
the slave trade?
GATES: Black people changed
American society.
America probably wouldn't have
much of a popular culture
without black people.
We blackified it.
We took everything
and made it, like,
made it better.
Mmm. You're a good
cook, man.
GATES: Black people redefined
the American dream.
Robert Smalls
epitomizes America.
Come from nothing
and to be a success.
GATES: They held
the country to its ideals,
even when it abandoned them.
[Sirens]
In these 6 hours,
I'll tell the stories
of some of the people,
places,
and events...
WOMAN: Free Huey.
GATES: that made black
history...
MAN: We want black power!
We want black power!
GATES: stories of courage...
determination...
and the power of hope.
MAN: Are you prepared to
take the oath, Senator?
I am.
JIMMY CLIFF:
° Many rivers to cross °
CHORUS: ° Rivers
to cross °
° But just where to begin... °
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was provided by...
Senegal, Africa--
the door of no return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud to
sponsor "Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it--
WiFi.
Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
MR. JON ES: Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: others,
just a few minutes.
Julian Jones Ill.
ANNOUNCER: Either way,
our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community
The simple joy
of staying in touch.
The Howard and Abby
Milstein Foundation,
in partnership
with Hoover Milstein
and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
And by the following...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting
and by viewers like you.
[Sea gulls cawing]
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
The African American story
begins here,
on the Atlantic Ocean.
Africans crossed these waters
with the very first
European explorers.
And their stories show that
right from the start,
the black people who came
to this land
nurtured aspirations
and dreams...
dreams that would never
disappear,
even in the long night
of slavery...
dreams that would help them
endure and overcome.
Florida. The first known
African in America
came here with Spanish
explorers in 1513.
His name was Juan Garrido.
He was free, and he left
his mark on the New World.
Garrido helped Cortez
take Mexico.
Then he headed for California,
searching for gold.
20 years later,
a black man struggled to
cross this Texas desert.
He was called Esteban the Moor.
He was one of just 4 survivors
of a Spanish expedition
that went horribly wrong.
Esteban served as a guide
and a translator
for his companions, negotiating
their way to safety
across this forbidding
landscape.
By the year 1536, they had
walked 15,000 miles.
They had seen more of
the North American continent
than any explorers would
until Lewis and Clark.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Garrido and Esteban
were among the first Africans
in our country.
They found hope
and opportunity here.
But things changed quickly.
Jamestown, Virginia--
the first British colony
in what became
the United States.
In 1619, this was
the ultimate frontier town,
crude fortifications bordering
a muddy malarial swamp.
Then one morning in August,
a ship appeared-
the "White Lion."
It was a pirate ship
carrying African slaves.
Roughly 20 of them
were traded here for food.
That's how slavery began
in the English colonies.
Plantations, as we imagine them,
didn't exist yet.
This was just a fragile outpost
in the wilderness.
MAN: Lives in
colonial Virginia
were very precarious.
They were really stuck
at the edge of survival.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
I've come here,
just a few miles from Jamestown,
to look for traces of a man
named Anthony Johnson,
a man whose life shows how
slavery evolved in Virginia.
SWEET: Our first notation
of Anthony Johnson
is from the early Virginia
muster roll,
which essentially
defines him
as Antonio the Negro.
So his blackness
was pan of his name,
his title.
Exactly.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Despite his skin color,
Johnson found opportunities
in Jamestown.
He worked side by side
with his owner
and forged a bond
based on necessity
SWEET: In order for
the master to survive,
he needed Anthony Johnson.
To make a farm in this
kind of environment,
it was all about
manual labor,
so Anthony Johnson
earned his way
to his own freedom,
and his master actually
provided him with son of
a start-up, if you will.
He gave him a little
cash, some land?
Yeah, some land,
it seems. Yes.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Anthony Johnson soon
began to prosper.
He owned a 250-acre
tobacco farm,
he had white indentured
servants,
and he even had an African
slave of his own.
But as Johnson prospered,
so did Virginia.
Within decades, Jamestown
had become the center
of a booming tobacco economy
that was desperate for labor,
and this transformed slavery
from a loose, informal
arrangement
into a rigid racial system,
a system in which
a life like Anthony Johnson's
would be inconceivable.
SWEET: Johnson's blackness,
his African-ness,
these things define him,
mark him as an outsider.
The stigma
of blackness.
of blackness,
and the fact that
the status was tied
to that observable
trait was one which was
very difficult to surmount.
GATES: After Johnson died,
a noun ruled that he
was "a negroe"
and by consequence an "alien."
And then the colony of Virginia
seized his family's land.
Johnson's story marked a new era
in the British colonies.
From this point on, slavery
would be solely based on race,
and the acquisition of slaves
would be central
to the acquisition of wealth.
In effect, the British were
simply trying to do
what many Europeans
had already done.
By the time Anthony Johnson
arrived in Jamestown
in the early 1620s, more than
half a million enslaved Africans
had already been spread
across the New World
into Brazil, Mexico,
and the Caribbean.
The free labor of these slaves
was making fortunes
for the Portuguese
and the Spanish.
Now the British wanted
to get in on the action.
SWEET: Most of the largest
cities of the Americas
were dominated
by Africans.
There were more Africans
in those cities
than there were Europeans.
SWEET: Here I'm talking about
places like Mexico City, Lima,
Panama City, Havana.
So when Jamestown is founded,
all of those colonists
understood
a wold in which Africans
were the primary labor force
for producing wealth for Europe.
I think it's important
to understand
that the British
are not innovating
when they settle Jamestown.
They're trying to catch up.
BROWN: American historians
sometimes treat
the emergence of slavery
as a mystery
where all of a sudden people go,
"How did all these
Africans get here?"
The real mystery would have been
if slavery had not
developed in Virginia.
GATES: A brutal equation
ruled the New World:
black equaled slave.
And to fulfill
their hunger for slaves,
the British turned to the place
that many other Europeans
had turned already: Africa.
Had turned already: Africa.
Sierra Leone was once
a major hub for the slave trade.
More than 300,000 people
were taken from here
and shipped to the New World
in bondage.
But the first slave traders
in this place weren't Europeans.
They were other black Africans.
Africans practiced slavery
long before they ever
saw a white person.
All across this continent,
slaves were pan of a system
based not on race,
but on ethnic difference
and brute power,
a system involving
an enormous array
of monarchs, merchants,
and mercenaries.
WOMAN:African kingdoms were at
war with one another.
War was a theme in Africa,
and actually Europe as well,
for many, many years, and so
as a pan of these wars,
as a result of these wars,
people were taken hostage
and made into slaves.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
I've come to Port Loko,
a river town in Sierra Leone,
and the longstanding home
of the Temne people.
For centuries, the Temne here
collected captives
who had been taken in wars.
They tied them, packed them
into small boats,
and sailed them downstream,
where they were sold
to Europeans for profit.
We sometimes romanticize Africa.
We think that Africa was idyllic
until the white man came.
But there were deep tensions
between ethnic groups here.
Black Africans didn't
necessarily feel the bonds
of skin color any more strongly
than, say, white Europeans did.
MAN: Slavery was ongoing
before the Europeans came.
It was just
a common business.
They come here
on this wharf.
Here is the landing
pad for the boats.
Who were
the slave traders?
BANGURA: The slave traders
were great warriors,
strong men, chiefs.
They do it as business.
GATES: A lot of misery
loaded on these boats.
Yes, but people were
not thinking about misery.
It was a lucrative
business.
Mm-hmm.
[Children shouting]
GATES:
As-Salaam-Alaikum.
Ha ha!
[Speaks African
language]
Professor Gates.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: I was
surprised to find out
that in Port Loko today,
there are still many families
whose ancestors profited
from the trade,
and some of them were
willing to tell me about it.
Good. Speak
from your heart.
[Translator speaking
African language]
GATES: Did any of you
receive wealth
inherited from
the slave trade?
500?
500.
[Whistles]
My God. So he
was very rich.
Yes. Yes, our people
were rich.
Would chiefs wage war
just to get slaves?
Oh, yes.
In America,
we think black men
were selling
black people
to the white man,
but when you see it,
do you see it as
Temne were
buying Loko--
Mende were buying
Temne, at cetera.
Is there
a difference?
Well--
Were all black
people black?
[Speaking
African language]
TRANSLATOR:
[indistinct] who are black.
We don't speak
the same language.
I don't like
what you like.
You know, we don't
just live in harmony.
GATES: Though some find it
difficult to face,
the crucial role of Africans
in the slave trade
is now well-documented.
Historians estimate that
the overwhelming majority
of the slaves
shipped to the New World
were captured and sold
by African kingdoms.
By African kingdoms.
But Africans did not
invent slavery.
It existed everywhere,
dating back to the most
ancient civilizations.
Nor did Africans
envision slavery
as something that
would be passed on
from one generation
to the next,
something based
exclusively on race.
That was a European innovation.
BROWN: Europeans had actually
developed an idea,
Over several centuries,
that they should not
enslave each other.
They could kill each other,
torture each other,
fight each other in wars,
but Europeans did not
enslave other Europeans
because Christians did not
enslave other Christians.
The great advantage of Africans
is that they were outside
the European community,
and so it was possible
to use race as away
of providing a marker
of who's enslavable
and who's not.
GATES: Sailing in ships
of radical new design,
armed with new weapons
and new technologies,
Europeans transform slavery
into a business far larger
and far crueler than anything
the Africans had ever done.
Of course, it didn't
happen overnight.
The dehumanization
of an entire race
was a process requiring
many steps.
One occurred here.
This beautiful island
shrouded in fog
is home to what was once
a fortress built by the British
in the 1670s.
WOMAN: Out there is
the mouth of the
Port Loko Creek.
African middlemen used
to bring their slaves
and goods down
the Port Loko Creek
through the mouth
of the Port Loko Creek
out there
all the way to this
beach here.
So they came
right through
that gap right there.
Yes, sir. Yes.
GATES: They would
bring them here.
They'd march them
straight up there
and sell them.
Up this hill up on to
the trading area.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Though its
walls have long crumbled,
I could still get a sense of how
this place once worked.
SMITH: This was
the main entrance
into the fort.
It had a double
folding door
with a little
[indistinct] patch
on top.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: British
officers lived here,
in a lavish two-story mansion.
SMITH: That's
a fireplace,
a fake fireplace because
there is no flue.
This is the tropics.
We don't need a fire
in the tropics.
But it was an attempt
by the slave traders
that lived here
at elegance.
GATES: A little
touch of home.
SMITH: A little
GATES, VOICE-OVER: The British
enjoyed parties here,
even a small golf course.
Slaves, meanwhile, were
herded like cattle.
SMITH: In here is the
women's and children's
slave yard.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: They were
branded, then held in pens
for shipment to the New World.
So the men were
over there,
and the women
and children were
right here.
So they could hear
each other's cries.
Definitely.
They could have heard
each other's cries,
but they could not
help each other.
In fact, let me show you
the men's slave yard.
It's right through
these doors.
By the time
they got here,
they were very
terrified,
and then they were
examined like cattle--
their eyes, teeth-
and then when the slaves
were taken out
to be put on board
the slave ships,
they were branded
with the letter "s"
on their left breast
to denote that they
came from Sierra Leone.
GATES: This place
was not unusual.
There were dozens
of forts like this
up and down the African coast.
We're not even sure exactly
how many slaves passed
through this island-
50,000 at least.
We know the names of a handful
and the stories
of a precious few.
In 1756, a British ship
named the "Hare"
set sail for Charleston
carrying 80 African slaves-.
One of them was
a 10-year-old girl.
We don't know where
she was from.
We don't know
her parents' names.
But we do know the name
that her master gave her:
Priscilla.
SINGERS: "Wade °
° In the water °
n Wade n
° In the water, children °
° In the water..."
GATES: Priscilla was at
the start of a journey
that would change
her life forever:
the dreaded Middle Passage.
SINGERS: ° The water °
WOMAN: The entire experience
is so horrific
and so just brutalizing in ways
that are just unimaginable
for a contemporary audience.
You have public floggings.
You have decapitation.
Being immersed in your own
bodily excrement.
[Baby crying]
It is complete loss
of control over your life
in every way possible.
Think about an 8-, a 9-,
a 10-year-old.
It is something that you're
never going to forget,
and it's going to be etched
in your memory.
GATES: Women on the ship, even
girls as young as Priscilla,
faced an added danger:
they were completely at
the mercy of the male crew.
MUSTAKEEM: Women were considered
to be available prey
at any given moment
for the entire ship crew
throughout the passage,
so some women would
commit suicide,
and some women did decide that
"I don't want to bring a child
into this world,"
so they inserted some
son of piece of wood
or nail or something to,
you know, cause violence
upon their body, and you will
also find that some women
would actually die
from these attempts.
GATES: Priscilla spent
10 weeks on the ship.
She saw 13 of her fellow
Africans die along the way,
their corpses thrown
into the ocean.
Death was so common
on slave ships
that sharks followed
in their wake,
feasting on the dead bodies.
[Thunder]
As the ship drew close to shore,
the slaves were rubbed with
a mixture of gunpowder and oil
to make them look healthier,
hiding the wounds
from their beatings and chains.
Then Priscilla stepped
into a new world.
Charleston, South Carolina.
This was once the center
of the slave trade
in the 13 colonies.
Over 40% of all the slaves
who entered our country
came through this city.
In Priscilla's time, South
Carolina had more black slaves
than white citizens.
In fact, it was called
"Negro country."
[Whip cracks]
[Stamping]
[Church bell rings]
GATES: Slave auctions were held
on the streets of Charleston
almost every day.
Priscilla was bought
at one of these auctions
by a rice planter
named Elias Ball.
MAN: We're on the way
to the Ball plantation,
which consisted of
1/2 of Comingtee plantation
and about 25 African
American slaves.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Edward Ball
is the fifth great-grandson
of the man who purchased
Priscilla.
He's brought me to the land
where his family ran
rice plantations
for almost two centuries.
...the landlord
with a thousand acres.
So this would have
been maybe one little
road running through it.
Yeah. The rice fields
were off the river.
They were
right around here.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Ball told me
he had spent years
wrestling with
his family's past.
Priscilla is just
one of 4,000 people
that they owned.
My dad used to talk
about the plantations
and Elias Ball
and all of the--
the prosperity
that our family
had lived through,
but he never talked
about the slaves.
He said, "There are
5 things we don't
talk about
"in the Ball family:
religion, sex, death,
money, and the Negroes."
[Gates laughs]
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Priscilla
arrived herein July 1756.
She was 10.
BALL: She came
as an orphan--
no parents,
no language, no home.
This was her
introduction
to the rest
of her life.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Priscilla's new life
centered around this house and
the white family that owned it.
Though a ruin today, the Ball
plantation was once thriving,
thanks to the labor
of its slaves.
BALL: The second Elias,
who bought Priscilla,
bought 6 children,
none of them older
than 10.
He liked buying children.
In fact, he wrote
a little memoir
in which he said,
"Due two things
with your money:
buy land and buy
young slaves."
GATES: Hmm. Why?
BALL: Better
long-term investment.
The white folks lived here.
The black folks lived
about 1/4 mile away.
The rice fields were about
half a mile down that road,
and that's where
all the work
of producing the money
took place.
GATES: Rica-that's why
Priscilla was here.
Rice fields like these
were making a fortune
for slave-owners.
Don't let their beauty
fool you.
These places were death traps.
The swamp ground was
covered with snakes.
The tropical air was filled
with malarial mosquitoes.
1/3 of South Carolina's slaves
died within a year
of their arrival,
and nearly 2/3 of all children
were dead before they turned 16.
But Priscilla beat the odds.
She and her family survived.
BALL: The Balls were
fanatical about
keeping records.
They had books
that listed
the birthdays
of all the slave
children,
books that listed
the deaths of all
the slave adults,
and all of this stuff
is collected in an archive
of about 10,000 pages.
My God.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Edward Ball spent 3 years
poring over
his family's records,
here in the South Carolina
Historical Society.
Hampshire. Gambia.
Ditto, ditto, ditto.
All of these men
and women from Gambia.
London.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Ball was
trying to piece together
the stories of
his family's slaves.
For most, he found
no story at all.
They survived only as
names on a page.
BALL: Christmas...
GATES, VOICE-OVER: People
consumed by the brutality
of slavery.
BALL: Sampson...
There was an ordinance
where if you ran away
and you were caught,
you had to have
two toes amputated.
If you ran away again
and you were caught,
you had to have
your ears amputated.
And if you ran away
a third time,
the punishment
was castration.
Oh, man.
Law of the land.
They were not
joking.
kidding around. Yeah.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: As Ball
scanned page after page,
he began to see
one name repeated.
Priscilla's 10 years old
when she comes to
Comingtee Plantation,
and 10 years later,
she's having
her own children.
Monimia, Priscilla's
daughter, was born,
and Monimia becomes
the matriarch
and her grandchildren
have children.
GATES: Ball was able to trace
Priscilla's family tree
down generations,
stretching from the 1750s
all the way to today.
For an African American,
this is extraordinarily rare.
GATES: Now, how are you
related to Priscilla?
She is my great-great-
great-great-
great- grandmother:
Through your mother--
Through my father.
My father. Mm-hmm.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
This is Thomalind Polite.
She and her husband Antoine
are carrying on a family line
that began in Sierra Leone
more than 250 years ago.
I was 19 years old
when I first found out.
It really hit me like,
"Oh, my gosh."
You know, this was my
fifth grandmother. Yeah.
But she had
to be tough.
She had to be.
I got some of that
from her...
[Laughter]
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Thomalind is remarkably lucky.
She actually knows the name of
her original African ancestor.
I don't know anyone else
who can do this.
For nearly all
African Americans, including me,
our original ancestors
will remain
forever anonymous and invisible.
This was not an accident.
VINCENT BROWN: Removing people
from genealogy
is very important
to making a slave.
So, if I only call you
by your first name
and never by a family name,
I'm indicating
to everybody, right,
that you have no family.
Right? You're just Jimmy.
You're just Sam.
You’re just Sarah, right?
So, they'll occupy a station
that everybody will
publicly recognize is at
the lowest rung of society.
Publicly recognize is at
GATES: Masters
worked methodically
to erase the identities
of their slaves
so that they would
be more productive.
And these tactics
were quite effective.
Slaves built this country.
They built roads and bridges,
factories and farms,
towns and cities,
but they built
something else as well,
something all their own--
a culture.
SWEET: As much as slave masters
tried to control
the worlds of their slaves,
they were vastly unsuccessful.
There was a persistence in
history and culture and names
that went across the Atlantic
despite the best efforts
of Europeans.
We tend to assume that
the slave is a cipher, right,
because that's ideology,
that's the ideology of slavery.
That the slave is simply an
extension of the master's will.
That's the plan,
that's the idea,
but that's not really what you
can ever do to a human being.
Human beings always find a way
to assert
their own prerogatives.
So, black people create
new kinds of cultural patterns
they didn't obtain in Africa
that weren't those of the whites
but were something new
in the Americas.
MAN: This garden
signifies crops that
enslaved African Americans
would have grown...
GATES, VOICE-OVER: One of
the most enduring expressions
of any culture is food.
Even today, we can try to access
the world of our ancestors
by tasting it.
GATES: What do we
have here, Michael?
MICHAEL: Well, you
have a late 18th-,
early 19th-century
feast, without the
okra, just for you.
Ha ha!
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Michael Twitty is
a food historian.
We have cala au congri,
which are basically
black eyed pea fritters
from New Orleans,
and then a lot of people
in this region had
3 salt herrings a week.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: He's
cooked me an 18th-century meal
to show how slaves from
different pans of Africa
crafted a distinct
African American cuisine.
So, you get a taste.
Hominy or mush,
ash cakes,
hoecakes, at cetera,
would have been the
staple of your diet.
How about some Hoppin' John?
Oh, you gotta
have that.
Mm. You're
a good cook, man.
Thank you, sir.
This came out of
my garden
yesterday afternoon.
Wow.
From Spartanburg,
South Carolina.
But all those
recipes there,
right out of
history books.
...great.
Mm-hmm.
Ha ha ha!
TWITTY, VOICE-OVER: When
in the history of humankind
has an enslaved people
revolutionized
the way the people
who enslaved them
ate, drank, believed, the way
Africans did in the Americas?
GATES: That's sorghum?
Yeah.
This is the first time
I've ever seen it.
Well, you see it
looks just like corn.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Twitty has
traced the roots of foods
that connect Africa,
the Caribbean, and the Americas
in a vast
black Atlantic culture,
a culture the slaves
even propagated
among their white masters.
It amazed me,
one reference
was one of the
former governors
of Virginia,
his wife said that
no one bakes a ham
better than a big,
fat Negro mammy.
Oh, really?
And you think
about this.
Ham as a food
was not invented
in Africa.
No.
But somehow,
we got our hands
on the sugarcane.
And our ancestors
blackified it.
We blackified it.
We took--
we took everything
and made it, like,
made it better
and made it--
made it
more soulful,
if you will.
Said, "Let's put
a little pineapple,
cherries on there..."
Exactly,
and brown sugar.
Now, you know, maple
syrup, we don't
do maple syrup.
Excuse me.
Brown sugar, brown sugar.
And it's
a Creolization process.
So, while the okra soup
and the black eyed peas
and the Hoppin' John
and the red rice
and jambalaya
And gumbo,
blah blah blah,
is going to
the master's house,
those cooks are bringing
European western dishes
into the slave quarters.
The ﬂow is going
both ways.
both ways,
and what we have
to recognize is
everybody puts
their stamp on it.
GATES: Food was not
the only thing
flowing throughout
the Atlantic world.
So were ideas.
Ideas about music,
dance, religion.
But especially
ideas about freedom,
even if the masters
wished otherwise.
GORDON-REED: Black people
knew they were people,
whether whites
thought it or not.
They knew they were people,
and so if you hear words about
liberty and freedom,
things that they wanted,
of course they would think
it would apply to them.
GATES: St. Augustine, Florida.
This is the oldest city
in the United States.
Built by the Spanish
in the 1560s
and held by Spain almost
continuously until 1821.
This beautiful place has special
meaning for African Americans.
Because as slavery's
grip tightened
in the British colonies,
Spain declared that runaway
slaves could come here
and be free.
Why? Politics.
Colonial Spain was locked
in a ferocious rivalry
with colonial England.
So, they welcomed
any fugitive slaves
who would convert
to Catholicism,
swear loyalty
to the Spanish crown,
and serve in
the colonial militia.
Suddenly, slaves
in the British colonies
Simply had to make it
across the St. Mary's River
into Spanish Florida,
and they would be free.
LAN DE RS: They knew
the geopolitics
of the region,
that the English
and the Spaniards
were enemies.
Enemy of my enemy
is my friend
son of thing.
And we often find
that they get
their information
from the Indian groups,
Hmm.
Who have gone
back and forth.
So, the Indians say,
"Hey, you black people,
"if you get on the boat
you get down to a place
called St. Augustine,
you'll be cool,
you'll be free."
Well, they wouldn't
have known that,
but they'd have known
where St. Augustine was
and they would've known
the Spaniards and the
English were at war.
Mm-hmm.
That the Spaniards
didn't like the English
being there,
and they took their
lives in their hands.
Mm-hmm.
They get in a boat
and they make it.
GATES: Soon, there were so many
black people in St. Augustine
that the Spanish built them
their own town,
called Fort Mose, just a few
miles to the north.
Nothing remains of Fort Mose.
It is sunk entirely into the
swamps of the Atlantic coast.
But this was the first
all-black settlement
in what would become
the United States.
An outpost of freedom
in a slave land.
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
I'm trying to imagine
what it must have felt like
to arrive here after traveling
through swamps, across rivers,
and through the wilderness,
finally gaining your freedom
at Fort Mose.
Slavery breeds dreams of freedom
in every human breast.
African American culture
is full of references to
the day of jubilee, to making it
to the promised land.
Well, for African slaves,
Fort Mose was the promised land,
and crossing St. Mary's River,
well, that was like
crossing the River Jordan.
So many slaves tried to run here
that the British started
executing them in public
to stanch the flow.
But even that
couldn't stop them.
300 miles north of Fort Mose,
just outside of Charleston,
runs the Stono River.
When word of the fort
reached this place,
it inspired one of
the biggest slave revolts
in the history of
the British colonies.
It all started right here-
the site of what was
once a general store
called Hutchinson's.
[Rattling]
Sunday morning,
September 9, 1739.
Hutchinson's Store
had been looted.
Its guns and ammunition
had been stolen.
Two shopkeepers lay dead,
their severed heads lying
on the steps of the store.
Plantations on either side
of the river were burning.
An army was on the move-
an African army.
They were headed for Fort Mose.
They set out before dawn,
a group of roughly 20 men.
Their tactics were simple.
They surrounded plantations,
then burned them to the ground.
The ringleaders came from
the kingdom of Congo,
a powerful African state.
Some had military training,
and they had a plan.
POWERS: The slaves marched
over to Pon Pon Road,
which was a road that,
if you took it south,
it would take you
down into Georgia,
down into Savannah,
and ultimately all the way
down to Florida.
[Drumbeat]
They were beating drums.
Now, the beating of the drums
is terribly important, because
that shows us that
they were attempting
to draw other Africans
into their midst.
GATES: By afternoon,
the rebel army had grown
to nearly 100,
and they kept moving south,
along what today
is this highway,
which still leads
from South Carolina to Florida.
But they didn't make it.
Just 20 miles
outside of Charleston,
an armed militia
caught up with them
in a clearing in these woods.
The survivors faced
a gruesome fate.
POWERS: A number of
the people who were--
were captured,
they'd be beheaded.
Beheaded.
They would be beheaded
by the militiamen,
and as was
a usual practice
during the time period,
their severed heads were
placed on top of posts
along the highway.
So, right along here,
Yeah.
We would've
seen the heads
Yes.
Of these rebels.
Yes. That's right.
And that was meant
to instill fear.
Mm.
And to teach
a lesson
to all who observe
to try to
discourage people
from-from
rebelling.
This must have been
the planters
worst nightmare.
It was. Absolutely.
Worse than
the worst thing.
They couldn't imagine
that these Congo Africans
knew anything about
guns and ammunition.
That's right.
That's right
Absolutely right.
This was
the worst
insurrection
to occur
in 18th-century
British
colonial
North America.
Huh.
GATES: In the wake
of the rebellion,
South Carolina imposed
harsh new slave laws.
They banned drumming
and literacy,
and set drastic punishments
on runaways.
But no laws ever
could force the slaves
to accept their fates.
Slaves plotted revolts
all over the Atlantic world.
In Jamaica, in Virginia,
Barbados and Georgia,
even in New York City.
Most of them failed.
But that didn't stop
the slaves from trying.
They were always searching
for a chance at freedom.
And as time passed, freedom
seemed to be drawing near.
The American Revolution brought
immense hope to the slaves.
They heard the patriots
talk of liberty and equality,
and it ignited their own dreams.
But for the most pan,
those dreams were ignored.
Even the greatest
champion of freedom
was hesitant to extend it
to black people.
This is Mount Vernon,
George Washington's estate.
For so many of us, an icon of
American independence.
But for more than
100 African Americans,
this was a plantation,
where from sunup to sundown,
they toiled as slaves.
The father of our country
was also one of its
largest slave owners.
Slaves tended his fields
and watched over his every need.
One worked in these stables,
a groomsman named
Harry Washington.
Harry heard the talk
around Mount Vernon
about liberty and independence,
but he sensed it wasn't
meant for slaves.
So, like many black people,
he decided to take his chances
with the British.
Once the war comes, there are
enslaved men and women saying,
"Hey, we'd love to help you out
"if you would help us out.
"We'd be happy
to help you suppress
"this rebellion in Massachusetts
if you will grant
our freedom in return."
GATES: Harry joined
a loyalist regiment
called the Black Pioneers,
and he wasn't the only one.
Roughly 20,000 slaves
ran away to the British lines,
far more than joined
the patriot cause.
There were a lot of Harry
Washingtons in the British army.
In fact, it's probably
fair to say that especially
in the southern colonies,
the British army effort
could not have been
as successful as it was
for a time
without the assistance
of former slaves-.
GATES: Unfortunately, most of
these black loyalists
were ravaged by the war.
GORDON-REED: Many of them died.
Many of them
contracted smallpox.
They met terrible fates,
many of them,
but you can understand
why they opted for it.
That gives you a measure
of what slavery was like,
that people would take
that kind of risk.
GATES: Harry Washington
was one of the lucky few.
In the waning days of the war,
the British put him on a ship
and evacuated him to Canada.
GORDON-REED: The British
definitely wanted to use
the black to help them in their
struggle against the colonists,
but they did not want to--
had no intention of
actually making them,
you know, equal to them
and bringing them
and making them
pan of British society, so,
dropped them off there
and let them make their way.
GATES: Harry didn't
stay long in Canada.
He and his fellow
black loyalists
were barred from voting
and exploited by local whites.
So, when the British set up
a colony for former slaves
back in Sierra Leone,
Harry was among
the first to emigrate.
He ended up near here,
one of the very few slaves
who ever made it back to Africa.
Harry didn't necessarily
want to go back to Africa.
You know what Harry wanted?
He wanted his old master
George wanted-freedom.
The right to do as he pleased.
Unfortunately, he did not
find it here.
The British government
in Sierra Leone
tried to limit the property
rights of the black settlers.
Harry fought back and was
banished for insubordination.
After that, he disappeared.
Harry was a rebel to the end,
and it's probably best that
he turned his back on America,
because he wouldn't have liked
what America became.
The founding fathers built
a country committed to slavery.
The site of Washington, DC
was chosen as our capital
in order to appease southern
slave owners, and why not?
They held an enormous
amount of power.
CHRISTOPHER BROWN: None of it
exists without slavery.
There are no settlements.
There is no 13 colonies
without slavery.
There is no United States
There's no independence movement
without slavery.
The whole thing is
built upon slavery.
That's why they didn't
abolish it.
GATES, VOICE-OVER: Slavery was
a part of American society
from the very beginning.
When the Declaration of
Independence was signed,
slavery was legal in each
of the 13 colonies.
And take this building here-
our magnificent Capitol.
Slaves quarried and cut
its oldest stones.
Its innermost bricks
were laid by slaves.
And you see the statue of
the Native American on top?
Symbol of freedom?
One of the people who cast it
was a slave.
But even if the ideals
of the American Revolution
were perverted by slavery,
the ideals themselves endured.
They lingered in the hearts
of black people
and they spread throughout
the Atlantic world.
Saint-Domingue. At the close
of the American Revolution,
this was a French colony.
It was the world's largest
producer of coffee and sugar.
And it had the largest
concentration of slaves
in the Western Hemisphere.
Almost twice as many Africans
were brought here
as were brought to
the entire United States.
In essence, this was
the epicenter of slavery
in the New World.
But in August of 1791,
this colony began to collapse
as the slaves rose up against
their hated masters.
Inspired by the same ideals
as the American patriots,
they fought off European armies
and founded a new nation--
Haiti, the world's first
black republic.
Never before in history had
slaves overthrown their masters.
The Haitian Revolution
becomes this
great beacon of
hope, right,
for what's possible.
Another world is possible
Slavery can end.
How in the world would a slave,
completely illiterate,
stuck on a plantation,
hear about
the Haitian Revolution?
Well, illiterate doesn't
mean ignorant, right?
That's the first thing
we have to understand.
Which is that news is
traveling all around
aboard ships, right?
So, sailors,
they're spreading news
about what's going on,
and then the slaves
hear ideas about
freedom and equality
and liberty
that are
incredibly important
to black people.
And so they raise hopes
to an extremely
high level.
GATES: Unfortunately, here in
the United States,
those hopes were dashed.
African Americans had to wait
almost a century
for their freedom.
But even so, Haiti had
a profound impact.
For generation after generation,
Haiti was a source
of immense pride.
A free black nation
in a world that thought
black people were fit
only to be slaves.
That pride can still
be seen today,
if you know where to look.
[Drumbeat]
These men are pan
of a celebration
that stretches back
almost two centuries,
a celebration of our living
connection to Haiti.
They get up before dawn
on Mardi Gras morning
and parade through New Orleans,
waking the city to celebrate
with a Haitian vodooan tradition.
MAN: Enjoy your life.
SECOND MAN: I can dig that.
You never know--you might
not wake up tomorrow.
That's right.
So, they make sure that
everybody wake up
on Mardi Gras Day.
If they don't wake up,
they're dead.
If they don't wake
up, they're dead.
[Laughs]
That's the message.
If you don't wake
up, you're dead.
Ha ha ha!
That's their job,
to wake everybody up
and make sure
that you enjoy
Mardi Gras.
GATES: They've been doing this
since 1819,
soon after a group
of Haitian refugees
came to New Orleans via Cuba
and started the tradition.
It's one of the oldest
parts of Mardi Gras,
and a living reminder that
African American history
isn't limited to the story
of the United States.
It's pan of a much
wider history--
the history of a people
scattered like sand
throughout the Atlantic world.
VINCENT BROWN: The way
we think of history
is in national terms,
so, U.S. history is
U.S. history
and it's discrete
from Jamaican history
or Haitian history or
British history or
French history.
And it turns out
that national history
really emerges in these
Atlantic cross-currents,
right?
That involve Africa,
the Caribbean,
South America, Europe,
and North America.
° I've been through ashes..."
"You better stand up
before you... °
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
African American culture
was born in the mixing
of people and ideas
from all over
the Atlantic world.
° ...it's too late to cry... °
GATES, VOICE-OVER:
Mixing made us strong.
It gave us hope.
It sustained us.
° .-.before you die
you better... °
GATES: Less than a mile
from the Mardi Gras parades
runs the mighty
Mississippi River.
In the decades after
the Haitian revolution,
this river became
the sight and symbol
of a new phase
in American slavery-
the violent rise
of the deep South.
But the memory of Haiti
was never forgotten.
It was mixed into the fabric
of African American culture.
It became an inspiration
for countless numbers
of black people
who dared to dream
of their freedom.
They would need that inspiration
in the harsh and dreadful
years to come.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross"
was provided by...
Senegal, Africa--
the door of no return.
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields, racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America is proud to
sponsor "Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it--
WiFi.
Settings?
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
ANNOUNCER: Some connections
are generational...
MR. JON ES: Thanks.
ANNOUNCER: others,
just a few minutes.
Julian Jones Ill.
ANNOUNCER: Either way,
our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community
The simple joy
of staying in touch.
The Howard and Abby
Milstein Foundation,
in partnership
with Hoover Milstein
and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
And by the following...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting
and by viewers like you.
Next time on
"The African Americans,"
the struggle for
freedom continues.
The Underground Railroad
makes me want to claim slaves
as my ancestors.
Here's the cupboard
that Sam hid in.
My God.
This is so tiny.
ANNOUNCER:
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross."
The African Americans story
continues online at
pbsorg/manyrivers
with streaming video and more