GATES: By 1968,
the Civil Rights Movement
had achieved stunning victories
both in the courts...
and in the Congress.
But would African Americans
finally be allowed
to achieve genuine
racial equality?
In the decades
that followed,
some attained
undreamed-of success...
while others struggled
with ever-greater challenges,
opening a deep divide
in the black community.
As the African
American people
confronted obstacles
old and new,
could their efforts
be sustained
by the dream that they,
as a people,
could reach
the mountaintop?
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross,"
was made possible by...
"Senegal, Africa,
The Door of No Return."
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it-
"Wifi, settings."
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
Some connections are
generational...
others just a few minutes.
Either way,
our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy
of staying in touch.
The Howard and Abby
Milstein Foundation,
in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Ban k.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
AN NOUN CE RI
The Coca-Cola Company,
the Ford Foundation
Just Films,
Dr. Georgette Bennett
and Dr. Leonard Polonsky
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H.Tanenbaum...
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National Endowment
for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting,
and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
[Siren]
KENNEDY: I have some
very sad news for all of you
and I think sad news
for all of our fellow citizens
and people who love peace
all over the world.
And that is that
Martin Luther King
was shot and was killed tonight
in Memphis, Tennessee.
[Onlookers gasping and shouting]
GATES: On April 4, 1968,
the tragic assassination
of Dr. King,
beloved symbol
of the civil rights struggle,
shattered African Americans'
faith that racial equality
could ever be won
through peaceful protest.
JACKSON: There were those who
never believed in nonviolence,
because they never
understood the depth
of that method of solving
problems in the world.
To some extent,
Dr. King has been a buffer
the last two years
between the black community
and the white community.
The white people
do not know it,
but the white people's
best friend is dead.
NEAL CLEAVER:
Once King was assassinated,
the politics of nonviolence
lost their relevance
for a large number
of people.
Everyone had some
very deeply visceral response
of what they unwanted to do,
and what many people
wanted to do was just go bum.
NEWSMEN: 6 days of rioting in
a negro section of Los Angeles.
Race riots rocked
New Jersey's largest city.
It's as if
a ﬂight of bombers
has passed over Detroit.
GATES:
Across the country,
some African Americans
who had patiently withstood
injustice for decades
now set their cities on fire
in a spontaneous outpouring
of despair and anger.
But in Oakland,
California,
people had
somewhere else to tum-
the Black Panther Party,
a militant group
started in 1966
to defend the city's
black community.
People jammed
the Black Panther offices
saying, "We want guns.
We want guns.
We have to do something
about this."
GATES: By April 1968,
the Panthers had gone
from promoting self-defense
to advocating
revolutionary change.
NEAL CLEAVER: lf you
consider a civil right
a right protected
by the government
in terms of legislation,
civil rights were accomplish ed.
Mm-hmm.
Obviously, something
hadn't happened
to make black people
equal, available,
and have access
to the resources.
So that's power.
That's where the Black Panther
Party came in.
It's for the people
who want to bring about change.
GATES: 22-year-old
Kathleen Neal
was working
for racial justice
through the Student Nonviolent
Coordinating Committee,
but the rising call
for black power
awakened her desire
for something more radical.
After meeting Panther
Minister of Information
Eldridge Cleaver,
Kathleen moved west,
married Cleaver,
and took charge
of communications
for the Party.
NEAL CLEAVER: The question
is not will it be
nonviolence versus violence,
but whether a human being
can practice his God-given right
of self-defense.
GATES: The Panthers
came up with
their own bold new solution
to the longstanding problem
of police harassment
in the ghetto-
armed community patrols.
BROWN: They just assumed
their Second-Amendment rights
and said, "We have the right
to defend ourselves
"under this Constitution,
and we're going to do it
openly and publicly."
NEAL CLEAVER: We would have
power to determine
the destiny
of our own community.
We would not be subjected
to police brutality.
And that was
a pretty direct take
in the streets
with their weapons
patrolling the police.
It was something
that the Oakland police
had never encountered.
GATES: Their
in-your-face attitude
infuriated the authorities,
but it thrilled
young people
impatient with the slow progress
toward racial equality.
Th e Panthers
summoned the people
they called
"the brothers on the block"
to realize the goal defined
by their Black Nationalist
forbearers
like Marcus Garvey
and Malcolm X-
black self-empowerment.
JOSEPH: The Panthers
are really saying
they want guns
and butter-
guns to defend
the community.
The butter
is community programs.
MAN: Way over 6,000
bags of groceries
are being given away ﬂee.
JOSEPH:
Free breakfast programs,
ﬂee sickle cell anemia
programs, health clinics.
NEAL CLEAVER: Raised our own
money. We didn't take grants.
It was a community-based popular
radical black organization
completely in dependent,
and we didn't have to answer
to anyone.
What kind of future
for the African American people
did the Panthers envision?
A brilliant future.
GATES: The Black Panthers
were not alone.
The black power movement
inspired a whole generation
who had stopped
asking for freedom
and were now demanding it.
WOMAN:
What is freedom?
Freedom is black power.
Calling all black people.
GATES: Black power
took many forms,
including black feminism,
black theology,
a black ans movement,
and a new ideology
called cultural nationalism,
which encouraged Black Americans
to reconnect with the culture
of their ancestors
By learning Swahili,
taking African names,
and wearing African cloth es.
Maulana Karenga
and his organization Us
called for black unity
through cultural revolution.
Cedric, would
you tell us
what umoja is?
Umoja is unity.
GATES: To that end,
in 1966,
he invented an African
American holiday--Kwanza.
I created it
as a way to reaffirm
our rootedness in our own
culture, African culture.
Malcolm said it-Until we have
a cultural revolution
to un-brainwash
a whole people,
we cannot break the bonds
of white supremacy,
because it begins first
in the mind.
You've got to
decolonize the mind.
10 years before, you could
have had the same idea,
and it would have
fallen ﬂat.
You know that
as well as I.
But what was it
about this moment
that let the seeds
that you planted blossom?
Remember, this is
the black power movement,
and black was sacred.
Ha ha ha ha!
It became
a movement holiday,
and as the movement grew,
it grew.
Wearing my natural
gives me more power
within myself.
Isn't it beautiful?
MAN: What are you?
I'm black and beautiful.
ROSE: "Black is beautiful"
was an effort
to sort of throw off
the shackles of
the way white supremacy
constructed black bodies-
they're not as intelligent,
they're not human,
they're not as beautiful,
they're not valued.
So to undo that,
one has to directly attack
that ideology.
GATES: "Black is Beautiful"
came out of
the black power movement...
Right on, brother.
But it quickly permeated the
American cultural mainstream.
Blackness, or soul,
became the epitome of cool...
Right on.
In popular films, music,
and advertising.
By 1969, there were
black characters
on 21 prime-time TV shows.
But more than
any other program,
the syndicated television show
"Soul Train,"
created and hosted by visionary
entrepreneur Don Cornelius,
helped spread the idea
that black was beautiful.
"Soul Train" brought black
music, dancing, and fashion
into homes across America.
For African American youth,
it was a revelation
to see kids like themselves
on national television.
THOMPSON: "Soul Train"
was pretty much the obsession
in every household
in my neighborhood.
I guess you could say
"Soul Train" was kind of
the first non-minstrel-based
black entertainment
that, you know,
America really got.
GATES:And it was more
than just music and dancing.
"Soul Train"
and its sponsors
advertised products
for black consumers
in ways that appealed to
their new pride and identity.
THOMPSON: Don Cornelius
used the commercials to educate
and promote afrocentricity,
which was something that was
absolutely not heard of.
There's one
with Frederick Douglass.
Teaching you
how to...yeah.
"My brother, you can't
go out looking like that."
Well, Mr. Douglass,
you know, times have changed.
We wear the natural now.
You call that a natural?
That's a mess.
THOMPSON: Kids used to tease you
by saying, "You're African."
"No, I'm not. I'm..."
You know, that was
the reason for a fight.
Someone called me African,
I'm beating somebody up.
Don Cornelius,
his master plan
was to change the lives
of black youth
without them knowing it.
I don't mean it lightly
when I say that
self-love was probably
the most important lesson
that was taught
on the sh ow.
[indistinct]
GATES: "Soul Train" made
black culture truly national
and kept it accessible
to the African Americans
who were moving out of their old
segregated neighborhoods
and integrating white suburbs
for the first time.
°Ashes, ashes,
we all fall down °
Professional opportunities
were opening up,
both in civil service
and in the private sector,
spurring the growth
of the black middle class.
The American dream was finally
coming within reach for some
thanks to a new idea
called Affirmative Action,
which prescribed
concrete policies
to end historic
discrimination.
You cannot explain
the significant increase
of middle-class blacks
in professional positions
and in colleges
and universities
without taking account
of these civil rights acts
and Affirmative Action programs.
It definitely
improved their life.
You and I
are prime examples.
Precisely, yeah.
GATES: In September 1969,
I drove to New Haven,
Connecticut,
a world away from my hometown,
Piedmont, West Virginia.
I was one of the lucky
96 black students
starting at Yale that fall,
a huge leap
from the 6 black men
who had graduated
in the class of '66,
just 3 years earlier.
Yale's president,
Kingman Brewster,
who had made
the bold decision
to open up
admissions policies,
greeted us with a speech
I'll never forget.
He said,
"Welcome to Yale.
"You're among
the intellectual elect.
"You are one of the 1,000
male leaders
brought into
the freshman class."
Our goal,
our revolutionary action
would be to integrate
the white power elite.
The other black students
I met at Yale were brilliant,
including future neurosurgeon
Dr. Ben Carson,
future United States
Congresswoman
Sheila Jackson Lee,
and Kurt Schmoke,
who would go on to become
the first black mayor
of Baltimore.
SCHMOKE: I thought of
our class coming in
as pan of what Dr. King
was talking about,
certainly what my grandmother
would wish for,
you know, that these
institutions were opening up
to African Americans.
Uh, somewhere in here.
Where's the mark?
There you go.
Affirmative Action,
for us,
was the first chance
we had to compete
with white boys,
our peers,
on a level
playing field.
You know, I never
considered myself
as being unqualified.
Right.
This was all about
inclusion.
This was about me being
a pan of and not apart from.
GATES: Integrating
the power elite
was just the beginning.
For us, black power meant
shaping Yale to meet our needs,
forming a black
student alliance,
and demanding new classes
emphasizing African American
history and culture.
But off campus,
the assertive stance
of the black power movement
had aroused fears,
fears that began to take
tangible form.
Calling the Panthers
"the greatest threat
to the internal security
of the country,"
the FBI launched
a secret campaign
of surveillance, infiltration,
and disinformation
aimed at seeding conﬂict
between the black power groups.
Were you aware of this
counterintelligence program
as it was going on?
We thought
they wanted to kill us.
What we didn't understand
is really
what they wanted to do
was confuse us,
to make us think our friends
were our enemies,
to make us lose confidence
in what we were doing.
Why would the FBI care
about the handful
of black people wearing berets
and the handful of
black people in dashikis?
You know, these
were not mass movements
where 20 million
black people,
you know, lined up
to join them.
Nobody really was threatened
by the Panthers.
Let's be honest.
Hoover wasn't
afraid of them,
and he wasn't
afraid of us.
He feared us
in our unity,
the potential of a unified
black movement,
self-conscious and armed.
GATES: In March 1972,
over 8,000 people,
including Cultural Nationalists,
Black Panthers, representatives
of the black arts movement,
mainstream civil rights
activists,
and elected officials
come together
in Gary, Indiana, intent on
defining a unified agenda
through the first national
black political convention.
What was the idea
behind this meeting?
There was a recognition that
protect politics wasn't enough.
You actually have to
struggle for power.
MAN: All right,
please, please, please.
In the interest--
Please. Now let's go.
KELLEY: One of the things
that Gary did reveal, though,
is that unity
is a hard thing.
MAN:The political agenda
that comes out
of this convention
has to be a nearly
unanimous document.
If it's not, it will
simply be ignored
by the major
political parties.
"Why is it that you all
don't agree?"
Yeah.
We have never had that
in the black community,
and it has never been true
in the white community.
But only we are
asked about it.
Ha ha ha.
Going and participating
did not necessarily mean
that you agree
with everything,
but not to be there
to witness this
and to be a pan of it
would have been,
for me, irresponsible.
All in favor
of adopting
the National Black Agenda
please signify
by raising your hands!
GATES: The participants united
across ideological lines
around the black community's
most crucial issue,
the longstanding
economic inequality
that the civil rights movement
hadn't been able to eradicate.
JACKSON: Now we find ourselves
with the right
to move in any neighborhood
in America,
and we can't pay the note.
We have the right to go
to any school in America.
We can't pay the tuition.
We've got the right
to buy any car in America.
But we can't stop it
from being repossessed.
We are not arguing about
our Constitutionality.
We are raising
a basic question--
when will we get paid for
the work we have already done?
[Cheering and applause]
BLACKWELL: In the Seventies,
we really had
a tale of three cities.
We have a few African Americans
who have achieved
real greatness
in terms of education,
in business, in politics.
Then you had
a black middle class
that had middle-class status,
middle-class ideals,
did not quite have
middle-class stability,
but middle class nonetheless.
And then you had a huge swath
of the black community
that was poor,
and its poverty
was worse
than the poverty
that preceded it.
GATES: During that time,
larger economic forces
were reshaping
the American landscape.
Industries were moving out
of the inner cities.
White people
and African Americans
who had made it
into the middle class
followed the jobs
to the suburbs.
The black poor
were left behind.
There's a big
difference, Skip,
between neighborhoods
in which a majority
of the adults are working,
like was the case,
say, back in 1950...
Mm-hmm.
And neighborhoods
in which a significant
majority of the adults
are not working.
Joblessness triggers problems
in a neighborhood-
family breakups,
drug trafficking, gangs.
What you're describing
is a perfect storm
for disaster
for the poorest element
of the African
American community.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, what strikes me
as a paradox
is that all this
occurred
precisely as black
people were gaining
increasing political
power and efficacy
in the cities.
Being mayor of Gary
has not made it possible
for me to control
things like jobs
and the economic conditions
of black people.
[Applause]
The unemployment rate
is 4 and 5 times greater
than the national unemployment
rate during the Depression.
[Applause]
Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.
GATES: When my old friend from
Yale, Kurt Schmoke, was elected,
he, like the country's
other black mayors,
inherited a city
in decline
and abandoned
by the Federal government.
SCHMOKE: When I became mayor,
it was clear that we had
significant problems in
the African American community
that weren't being faced
in the white community.
I didn't realize,
however,
that the other thing
that I was gonna face
was the negative impacts
of the war on drugs.
NEWSMAN: President Reagan signed
a stiff new anti-drug law
authorizing $1.7 billion
to fight drug abuse.
REAGAN : The American people
want their government
to get tough
and go on the offensive,
And that's exactly
what we intend.
ALEXANDER: From the outset,
the war on drugs
had relatively little to do
with genuine concern
about people struggling with
drug addiction and drug abuse...
ANNOUNCER: This is
your brain on drugs.
And much to do
with politics...
Just say no.
Racial politics,
using racially coded get-tough
political peals on issues
of crime and welfare
in order to appeal to poor
and working-class whites
who are anxious about
and resentful of
many of the gains
of African Americans
in the civil rights movement.
GATES: That war on drugs
would be waged
in African American
neighborhoods
like Harlem's Wagner Houses,
where Terrence Stevens grew up.
Were you aware
that the government
had declared
a war on drugs?
I knew that there was
a war on drugs
in the street
with law enforcement
because I remember,
as a kid,
we'd just be hanging out
in front of our buildings,
and the police
would come
and just throw everybody
up on the wall
and started
checking everybody.
They're running up
in these apartment buildings
with their guns out.
It had a devastating effect
on the black community.
GATES: In the mid-1980's,
inner-city neighborhoods
like Terrence's,
which were already struggling
to combat poverty and decay,
suffered a staggering blow.
STEVENS: Crack stole
the sh ow.
Crack just like
killed the game.
It was indescribable,
the level of hardships
and whatnot
that, you know,
people was experiencing.
They would be smoking
crack cocaine in a park.
You know, people
literally stealing TV's
out of your house,
you know.
Crack really hit
Harlem heavy.
The war on drugs
is focused on crack.
Let's go.
[Men shouting]
Police!
ALEXANDER: When crack
hit the streets,
The Reagan administration
seized on this development,
actually hiring staff
whose job it was
to publicize
inner-city crack babies...
Crack kids.
Crack dealers...
Get down
on your hands!
In an effort
to bolster public support
for a drug war
they had already declared.
NEWSMAN: The plan,
an all too familiar one.
It's an other night,
another crack raid.
ALEXANDER: There was such
a frenzy associated with
a fear of crack,
it served the function
of deflecting attention
away from problems of poverty,
of joblessness
in these communities...
Open n!
To crack.
MAN: Police are now arresting
more than 35 people a day
on drug charges,
but almost all
of these arrests
are taking place
in black neighborhoods.
ALEXANDER: Even at the height
of the crack epidemic,
the majority of crack users
were white.
But once it became
sensationalized in the media
as a black drug,
a wave of punitiveness
swept over.
We saw a whole generation of
young black men in particular
being swept into
prisons and jails.
How old are you, son?
15 years old.
It's like
it was a trap,
and it was a trap
by design.
GATES: In 1990, Terrence
was traveling to Buffalo.
Police searched
the bus he was riding
and found 5 ounces
of cocaine.
STEVENS: I was arrested,
you know, as a result
of drugs that someone else
had in their bag,
and I was sentenced
as a first-time, low-level,
nonviolent offender
to 15 years to life.
I was locked up with some guys
that committed murder.
They raped kids.
And they got
under 10 years.
MAN: When your gate
opens up,
you will strip down
for the officer.
ALEXANDER'. Before
the war an drugs,
The most severe sentence
for drug possession
under Federal law
was one year.
Congress and State legislators
began passing
ever harsh er mandatory
minimum sentences
for minor drug offenses.
Prisons exploded
almost overnight.
What's happening, man?
You're getting big, kid.
You'll be growing up,
and you'll wonder why
you ain't seen the person,
and unfortunately,
if you end up in prison,
the person will be there.
You know, they go, "Mike!"
They go, "Bob!"
They go, "Uncle..."
you know, and it's like
the prisons were an extension
of the community.
[indistinct conversation]
GATES: As their communities
came under assault
or languished in neglect,
young people were looking
for a way to express their rage
and hopes about what was
going on around them.
BROWN: You had
a lot of confusion
on what was gonna get
America out of
really kind of like
a depression for black folks.
V. BROWN: The gutting
of the urban labor force,
the rise
of the prison economy,
the ﬂooding of these
neighborhoods with drugs,
you have the withering
of the state,
so schools are being
increasingly defunded,
an programs go 8%'!-
Out of the ashes
rose the phoenix of hip-hop.
ROSE: Kids just
did it themselves.
Deejays take
the electrical power sources
from the city, you know,
and attach them to turntables
and massive
homemade speakers.
The idea of a block party
was just reinvigorated
in hip-hop with nothing.
GATES: Those kids created
an entire culture
with its own music,
dance, visual art,
style, and attitude.
° Don't push me
'cause I'm close to the edge °
GATES: Rap songs
like "The Message"
shed a vivid new light
on the experience
of people
who felt invisible.
° It makes me wonder
how I keep from going under°
It's like a jungle sometimes.
It makes me wonder
how I keep
from going under.
That black male especially,
it made us like, yeah, you know.
"This person
is speaking for me
"because I can't say
these things.
I ain't being heard."
And hip-hop just came out
and just said,
"Yes. Yes.
Exactly, you know."
And it's riding a beat.
Very powerful for a person
going from 17 to 26,
when I started making
my first records.
° Fight the power °
GATES: Chuck D had grown up
with the black power movement.
With his group
Public Enemy,
he revived the message
of black resistance
in the language
of a new generation.
CHUCK D: "Fight the power“
was a call
to be looked upon
as equal people,
yelling for your rights.
And if you can speak and yell
and then rap for your rights,
then, you know, it just follows
in the footsteps
of the legacy
of black musicians
that spoke to
a forward movement.
GATES: As hip-hop's
popularity grew,
its lyrics and music videos
didn't shy away from portraying
issues like poverty,
hardship, and police brutality.
CHUCK D: Rap was
black America's CNN
because it was able to give
direct commentary
on what was going on.
13 years into the recorded
hip-hop idiom
comes what it's been
saying all along.
GATES: In 1991,
a home video
captured the vicious beating
of Rodney King,
an unarmed black man
by Los Angeles police officers.
Those images
shocked a nation
largely unaware
of police practices
in America's inner cities.
When the officers in the King
video went on trial,
black Los Angeles
waited for the verdict.
On April 29, 1992,
the 4 officers
were cleared
of all charges.
They don't represent
the people no more!
It's terrible.
ALEXANDER: After being denied
for so long,
any validation, acknowledgment
of the pain and the suffering
and the anger,
it exploded.
A black man didn't put
these scars on my head!
A black man didn't do this!
The police did this!
I got scars on my head
for the rest of my life!
[Chanting "Africans unite!"]
MAN: Today Mayor Tom Bradley
urged everyone in Los Angeles
to remain home,
to stay off the streets.
He also suggested they might
want to watch "The Cosby Show'
because he believes and we
believe we need this time,
a bit of a cooling-off period,
giving us some breathing space,
maybe a time to remember
what Thursday nights were like
before all this madness
began in Los Angeles.
Theo!
GATES: While Los Angeles burned,
millions of people
of all races tuned in
to "The Cosby Shaw's"
final episode
to say goodbye
to the black characters
they had loved and laughed with
with 8 years.
America's most popular sitcom
had offered viewers
a celebration
of black achievement,
an afﬂuent, wholesome family
who unapologetically embraced
black traditions and culture
from historically
black colleges...
I haven't seen this
since I was 8 years old.
To black an and music.
V. BROWN: Through
the Eighties and Nineties,
that black middle class
finds its voice, too,
people beginning to express
what's happening
for black middle-class people
who can go to college,
uh, and who are entering
professional life,
um, and who begin to take their
place in the nation's elite.
GATES: I watched "The Cosby
Show" with my Mo daughters.
The wand it depicted
reﬂected the lives
of our own family
and our friends,
a black reality
that looked nothing
like what was going on
in America's ghettos.
My daughters
were accustomed
to seeing African Americans
as icons
of main stream American culture.
But it still amazed me
that black celebrities
were becoming so popular
with audiences of all colors.
COBB: We started
to see acceptance
for exceptional black people,
but in some ways,
people were measuring
the rest of black America
by the success of a handful
of exceptional individuals,
and it made it possible
to ignore
the ongoing structural dynamics
that made it very difficult
for other people to attain
a reasonable living.
JOSEPH: These people
who find themselves
very, very successful,
they've managed to escape.
That's what
they've managed to do.
You may think to yourself
like, "Wow! Things are great.
You know, I've made it."
But if you go back
to where you're from,
you're gonna see
that all these people
that were left behind
are still there,
and you might have
thought to yourself that
"since I made it,
somehow they all got ﬂee..."
In America,
that's not the case.
MAN: We've got
major ﬂooding here.
GATES: On August 29, 2005,
Hurricane Katrina struck
the city of New Orleans.
In the ﬂoods
that followed,
about 1,500 people
lost their lives.
Hundreds of thousands
of people lost their homes.
These members
of the Black Men of Labor,
a cultural organization,
stayed in New Orleans
throughout the disaster.
Things were so hectic
that, you know,
guys just couldn't
arbitrarily go out
on their own
for fear of being
arrested
or maybe being
fired upon.
So we banded together.
GATES: When aid
didn't come fast enough,
they went outwith a boat
to rescue people
stranded by the ﬂoods.
Do you have nightmares
about what you saw?
Where these three--
they were sisters and brothers.
They were all dressed in white.
I'll never forget that.
And they were pouring water
down his mouth
and telling him,
"We're gonna make it.
We're almost there.
We're almost there."
They were bringing him
to the bus.
And I couldn't
take that either.
I couldn't take it.
Excuse me.
Shouldn't the government
have been doing
what you guys
were forced to do?
You can wait for government
if you want,
but, I mean,
lives were at stake.
So you did what you knew
you could do.
MAN: So many of these people,
almost all of them that we see,
are so poor,
and they are so black,
and this is gonna raise
lots of questions
for people who are watching
this story unfold.
GATES: For many
African Americans,
no matter how rich or poor,
the painfully in adequate
relief effort
reopened a deep racial wound.
The landscape
of the city
has changed dramatically,
tragically,
and perhaps
irreversibly.
George Bush doesn't
care about black people.
COBB: There are hundreds
of deceased people
literally ﬂoating
down the street,
overwhelmingly
African American,
and the official response
is that the President
is on Air Force One,
and they fly lower
so that they can
survey the damage.
People kept saying,
"This is not about race."
But for African American s,
it was hard to conceive
that there could be
800 white people dead
and hundreds,
thousands more
who are desperately
in need of assistance,
and what they get
is a ﬂyover.
BLACKWELL: The government's
failure to respond
I don't think was just because
people were black
or just because
people were poor.
People were left
in that crisis
because they were
black and poor.
It was strictly because
they did not matter.
GATES: A few days
after the ﬂoods,
an official delegation visited
Katrina evacuees
sheltered in
the Houston Astrodome.
Among them was the sole
African American
in the United States Senate,
Barack Obama,
the junior Senator
from Illinois.
OBAMA: The people of New Orleans
weren't just abandoned
during the hurricane.
They were abandon ed
long ago
to murder and mayhem
in their streets,
to substandard schools,
to dilapidated housing,
to inadequate health care,
to a pervasive sense
of hopelessness.
Now, that's the deeper shame
of this past week.
Thank you, everybody.
God bless you.
GATES: Just a year
and a half later,
Obama announced
that he would seek
the Democratic nomination for
the United States Presidency.
It was an audacious decision
for any first-term Senator,
but especially
for an African American.
One day there may be
a black President,
but there will never be a black
President named Barack Obama.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that's too black.
When I did the joke,
I really didn't believe
he could be President.
It was about me
sort of just saying
the country wasn't ready.
GATES: Many African Americans
simply didn't believe
that Obama could
persuade white voters
to elect a black man
to the nation's highest office.
[Cheering]
Oh, I think
that's a good one!
That's a good one!
But as the months went by,
his unprecedented confidence
began to pay off.
This fall, we owe the American
people a real choice.
[Cheering and applause]
GATES: The campaign's
freshest face
has now emerged
as its frontrunner.
What do we really know
about Barack Obama?
MAN: The reason that he's
considered such a big deal
is simply
because he's black.
Do we really want somebody
like that in the White House?
Here's a candidate
who claims to be a unifier,
and yet he belongs
to a church
where they specialize
in denouncing whites.
GATES: In March 2008,
the media discovered
the fiery sermons
of Obama's pastor,
Reverend Jeremiah Wright.
The government
gives them the drugs,
builds bigger prisons,
passes a 3-strike law,
and then wants us to sing
"God Bless America"?
No, no, no!
Not "God Bless America."
"...Damn America!"
I wouldn't sit in a church where
a pastor said that. Would you?
Why does Senator Obama?
Commitment to
the black community.
Commitment to the black family.
Adherence to the black
work ethic.
If every time
we said "black,"
if it was a church,
and those words were "white,"
wouldn't we call
that church racist?
GATES: Although Obama
had avoided emphasizing
the issue of race
during the campaign,
the media frenzy
that ensued
forced him to confront
the topic head-on.
The path to a more perfect Union
means acknowledging
that what ails
the African American community
does not just exist
in the minds of black people.
Working together,
we can move beyond
some of our old
racial wounds
and that, in fact,
we have no choice.
We have no choice if we are
to continue on the path
of a more perfect Union.
GATES: By reassuring
many Americans
that he understood
both sides
of the country's longstanding
and painful racial divide,
Obama inspired voters
to do something
that many considered
impossible.
NEWSMEN: Pennsylvania
has gone to Obama.
Senator Obama will carry
the State of Massachusetts.
Ohio is gone for Obama.
We can report history.
You are looking at the 44th
President of the United States.
The celebrations begin.
[Cheering "Yes, we can!"]
POWELL: We did it.
They said we couldn't,
and we did it.
Yeah.
I cried.
I still do.
[Cheering]
JORDAN: My eyes
filled with tears,
but they were not
my tears.
They were the tears
of my parents
and my grandparents.
They were the tears
of all of those black people
who toted that cotton
and lifted that bale.
Did you think
America was ready
to elect a black
President?
It doesn't matter.
It happened.
[Cheering]
Change has come
to America.
[Cheering]
GATES: As people all over
the world rejoiced,
we, too, could
once again believe
in the promise
of America.
COBB: So there's
always been
this double vision
of America-
America, the land
of opportunity,
and also America,
the land that has
a rigid racial
hierarchy.
What Obama's election did
was offer the country
at least a moment
in which it could
renew that creed,
the land where everything
is possible.
Congratulations,
Mr. President.
Thank you, sir.
[Cheering and applause]
GATES: Against
the greatest odds,
America sent a black man
to the White House.
In the euphoria that followed,
some even dared to wonder
was this the end
of racism?
Could 500 years
of race relations
be transformed
by the election of one man?
The idea that one
black President ended racism-
like...Aah!
Like, it was just like,
that's all it takes?
I think people
wanted to buy it.
And there was so much good
feeling around Barack
at that point
that we wanted to believe
that he was--you know,
it's the extension
of the magical negro
in the movies.
And that good feeling
led to claims
that somehow we had
turned a corner,
that we were
so-called post-racial.
America was founded
on racism.
The only way
we get to be post-racial
is the way that we got to be
post-dinosaur.
You know what I mean?
Like, a meteor has to hit
and just sort of wipe
everything out,
and then something else
has to replace America.
BLACKWELL: Attitudes are
improving about race.
All the polls show it.
The American people
actually feel better
about people
who are different.
They feel better
about black people.
They have less racism.
But those personal attitudes
don't translate into change,
because the racism now
is institutionalized.
It's structural.
COBB: This African America
who is in the White House
occurs at a point
where there's
nearly a million black men
who are incarcerated,
at a point where
black unemployment
is routinely double that
of white unemployment,
at a point where there are
all these enduring indicators
of social, economic
inequality.
GATES: After almost a decade,
in a maximum-security prison,
an eternity
for Terrence Stevens,
who suffers from
muscular dystrophy,
the governor of New York
granted him clemency,
allowing him
to come home at last.
Today is Terrence day, baby.
Yippy-yi-yay!
8 1l2 long years.
I guess it's like 58 it seemed
like to him in his condition.
Getting ready to lift now.
Let's go.
I'm thinking about
writing a book
when I get out, too.
Well, you're out now.
Yeah, I'm out now.
Yeah, right.
"When I get out."
He's saying...
I'm so used to being in.
[Laughter]
Yeah, it's a beautiful
morning, though.
Ha ha ha!
It's funny, man.
I was locked up so long
that when I finally
got released...
I...l had a little phobia
about going outside,
because outside seemed
so huge, you know.
It seemed so huge.
GATES: Although he was
no longer incarcerated,
Terrence discovered
that as a convicted felon,
he was not yet ﬂee.
There was a lot of things
that I couldn't do.
You know, I couldn't vote.
Having to report
to parole once a week.
Parole officers coming
to your house.
You have a curfew.
A lot of people, when they go
and apply for jobs,
they want to know
do you have a conviction,
and you write down, yes,
you have a conviction,
and now the employer
don't want to employ you.
Even after prison,
you're kind of still
under prison guidelines,
you know.
WOMAN: Put your right foot
back up, please.
Put that against
your stomach.
ALEXANDER: I refer to the
system of mass incarceration
as a new Jim Crow,
because it is
a comprehensive system
that serves to lock
a group of people,
defined largely
by race and class,
into a permanent
second-class status.
Our racial stereotypes...
fears, and anxieties
have driven the birth
of this system
and sustained the idea
that some people are a problem
to be dealt with harshly.
WOMAN: Sean Bell died
the same day
he was supposed
to get married.
[Gunshot]
MAN: Grant was
fatally wounded.
GATES: As a President
of a nation
eager to disavow
its racial past,
Obama had steered clear
of discussing race
while in the White House.
But during his second term,
an all too familiar story
moved him to break his silence
about the persistent
demonization
oi young mack men .
WOMAN: We, the jury, find
George Zimmerman not guilty.
Oh,no!
[Chanting "Whose streets?
Our streets!"
OBAMA: When Trayvon Martin
was first shot,
I said that this
could have been my son.
Uh...
Another way
of saying that is
Trayvon Martin
could have been me, uh...
35 years ago.
V. BROWN: My first though twas
it could have been me, too.
This is something that all
black men know in this country.
Anybody out of place,
anybody in the wrong location--
Can I just say it?
Anybody off their plantation...
Right?
Is already suspected to be
a criminal of some son,
and the society around
is empowered
to do something
about that.
How you doing, bro?
The big question is
can the nation
be something else?
And that's a question
we all have to ask together.
STEVENS: I knew that
when I returned home,
I had to do
something significant,
I had to do something
that was major,
and I had to contribute
to my society in a huge way.
I came up with this idea
of starting a foundation
where we would actually
reach out
to children who lost
their mothers and fathers
to incarceration.
We provide tutoring,
mentoring.
I'm gonna ask that each one of
you guys get up and scream out,
"I am somebody!"
We connect them
with a positive role model.
And we transport them up
to these correctional facilities
so that they can
reestablish the bond
with their parents.
How long your dad
been in prison?
Like, 6 years.
5 Years?
When was the last time
you seen your dad?
Like...2 years ago.
It's a crying shame
that, you know,
mass incarceration
had taken over the community
the way it did, you know.
And I remain hopeful
that they will soften up
some of these policies.
Hopefully some of these parents
can return home
and, you know, become,
you know, parents again.
GATES: Terrence's efforts
to help these children
break the cycle
of incarceration
connects him to the most
important unifying thread
that runs through
black history--
the enduring will
both to survive
and to carve out
a better future
for those who follow.
KARENGA: Everybody benefited
from our movement.
Native Americans, Latinos,
Asians, Women, Gays, Seniors
built on
our conversation.
That's true.
In Africa...
In China...
In the Palestinian struggle,
they sang our songs,
used our phrases--
"Million Man March,
We shall overcome," all of that
and posed our struggle
as a model to emulate.
GATES: Th at struggle
is far from over.
I have a dream today.
GATES: The African
American people
have played a central role
in building this country
since before its inception...
Never losing sight
of the dream
that one day the United States
would finally achieve
that more perfect Union.
Looking back
on the last 500 years
reminds us that when
the weakest members of society
take history
into their own hands,
they can change
the world.
The journey from the slave ship
to the White House,
from bondage
to full equality
has been long
and arduous,
replete with despair
but full of joy as well.
It's a journey
still in progress,
one that we are
continuing together.
ANNOUNCER: Funding for
"The African Americans:
Many Rivers to Cross,"
was made possible by...
"Senegal, Africa,
The Door of No Return."
From these shores,
millions of Africans
went across oceans
and continents,
battlefields,
racial barriers,
and constitutional divides.
Bank of America
is proud to sponsor
"Many Rivers to Cross,"
an epic journey
through 500 years
of African American history.
We believe connecting
to our past
helps us all create
a better future.
Yeah, they have it-
"Wifi, settings."
May I, Mr. Jones?
Please.
Some connections
are generational...
others just a few minutes.
Either way,
our signal is strong
and deeply rooted
in the community.
The simple joy
of staying in touch.
The Howard and Abby
Milstein Foundation,
in partnership
with HooverMilstein
and Emigrant Bank.
African American history
is an epic story,
our American story.
We're proud to fund
this important program.
Please join us in supporting
your public television station.
ANNOUNCER:
The Coca-Cola Company,
the Ford Foundation
Just Films,
Dr. Georgette Bennett
and Dr. Leonard Polonsky
in memory of
Rabbi Marc H.Tanenbaum...
Richard Gilder,
the Hutchins Family Foundation,
the National Endowment
for the Humanities,
the W.K. Kellogg Foundation,
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting,
and by viewers like you.
Thank you.
° Many rivers to cross °
° But I can't seem to find °
° My way over”
° Wandering, I am lost °
° As I travel along °
° The white cliffs of Dover °
ANNOUNCER:
The African American story
continues online
at pbsnrg/manyrivers
with streaming video
and more.
° Because of my pride °