1
00:00:25,526 --> 00:00:27,736
<i>At the outbreak of World War II</i>

2
00:00:28,153 --> 00:00:32,115
<i>Germany increased its U-boat
production by 1000%.</i>

3
00:00:32,324 --> 00:00:35,536
<i>Mass producing 17 new U-boats a month.</i>

4
00:00:36,995 --> 00:00:40,040
<i>Hitler knew the key to winning
the war in Europe...</i>

5
00:00:40,249 --> 00:00:42,000
<i>was to control the Atlantic.</i>

6
00:00:45,045 --> 00:00:47,130
<i>And control it, they would.</i>

7
00:00:57,015 --> 00:01:01,311
<i>By the end of 1942,
German U-boats working in groups...</i>

8
00:01:01,353 --> 00:01:05,691
<i>known as "wolfpacks",
sunk over 1,000 allied ships.</i>

9
00:01:11,321 --> 00:01:14,741
<i>This success gave Germany
a decisive advantage.</i>

10
00:01:19,454 --> 00:01:22,875
<i>They were winning the war,
and if this trend continued...</i>

11
00:01:23,000 --> 00:01:24,960
<i>all of Europe would fall.</i>

12
00:01:25,085 --> 00:01:26,545
IN ENEMY HANDS

13
00:01:28,505 --> 00:01:33,635
<i>In January 1943, President Roosevelt,
and Prime Minister Churchill...</i>

14
00:01:33,927 --> 00:01:37,472
<i>declared that stopping the U-boats
would be their top priority.</i>

15
00:01:40,309 --> 00:01:44,563
<i>With the US fully committed to the war,
and new advances in technology...</i>

16
00:01:44,688 --> 00:01:46,773
<i>the allies strike back.</i>

17
00:01:48,650 --> 00:01:52,070
<i>After losing an average
of only five U-Boats a month...</i>

18
00:01:52,196 --> 00:01:56,366
<i>Germany suffers its greatest losses
in what would be known as Black May.</i>

19
00:02:00,537 --> 00:02:04,291
<i>That month, allies sink
and destroy 41 U-Boats.</i>

20
00:02:05,542 --> 00:02:08,879
<i>8 out of every 10 U-boat sailors died.</i>

21
00:02:12,633 --> 00:02:17,304
<i>The rain of the wolfpack was
rapidly drawing to a close.</i>

22
00:02:20,015 --> 00:02:22,935
Dept. of the Navy
June 3, 1943

23
00:02:23,769 --> 00:02:25,020
I've known you your whole life.

24
00:02:25,062 --> 00:02:27,231
I'm not going to embarrass you
with the details.

25
00:02:27,856 --> 00:02:29,316
Your father was a good man.

26
00:02:29,399 --> 00:02:30,859
A great soldier.

27
00:02:31,068 --> 00:02:32,653
Thank you, Sir.

28
00:02:33,070 --> 00:02:36,490
It's out of respect for him that
I just assume you didn't do this.

29
00:02:41,411 --> 00:02:43,288
We're not here to chase ghosts.

30
00:02:43,997 --> 00:02:45,874
Our job is to pursue an enemy...

31
00:02:46,083 --> 00:02:47,125
and defeat it.

32
00:02:48,794 --> 00:02:50,254
You certain that's what you wanna do?

33
00:02:50,587 --> 00:02:51,839
Absolutely.

34
00:02:54,967 --> 00:02:56,093
When do you ship out?

35
00:02:56,218 --> 00:02:57,261
In two weeks.

36
00:02:57,344 --> 00:02:58,720
Monday after next...

37
00:02:58,804 --> 00:03:00,597
we'll be ready.

38
00:03:00,889 --> 00:03:02,349
Have you met your C.O.B. yet?

39
00:03:02,391 --> 00:03:05,185
No Sir, Nate Travers, not yet.

40
00:03:05,394 --> 00:03:08,188
Nathan Travers, a good man.

41
00:03:09,439 --> 00:03:12,568
You might actually learn something from him
if you're interested in that sort of thing.

42
00:03:17,072 --> 00:03:19,658
- Give 'em hell, Commander.
- Oh, I plan to, Sir.

43
00:03:20,200 --> 00:03:21,743
- That's an order.
- Yes, Sir.

44
00:03:28,333 --> 00:03:31,336
I'm just waiting for some things
hanging on the line to dry.

45
00:03:31,962 --> 00:03:34,464
And your mom wants you
to call her before you go.

46
00:03:34,882 --> 00:03:38,135
Don't go without calling her because I'm
the one who's gonna have to deal with it...

47
00:03:38,427 --> 00:03:40,220
everyday until you get back.

48
00:03:41,138 --> 00:03:43,015
I love her, but she's your mother.

49
00:03:43,223 --> 00:03:44,391
You deal with her.

50
00:03:45,017 --> 00:03:46,476
I'm gonna take this.

51
00:03:48,353 --> 00:03:49,688
I'm taking this with me.

52
00:03:51,481 --> 00:03:53,442
I'll stick it right above my bunk.

53
00:03:54,276 --> 00:03:56,486
It'll be the last thing
I see when I go to bed...

54
00:03:57,821 --> 00:03:59,823
and the first thing
I see when I wake.

55
00:04:01,074 --> 00:04:03,785
Oh, dammit.
Why do you go and do that?

56
00:04:03,869 --> 00:04:05,954
- What?
- You know what.

57
00:04:06,163 --> 00:04:09,416
Now you got me started,
and I can't stop once I get started.

58
00:04:10,125 --> 00:04:10,959
Sorry.

59
00:04:11,793 --> 00:04:13,045
You're not sorry.

60
00:04:14,505 --> 00:04:15,881
I love you.

61
00:04:19,009 --> 00:04:21,178
- Promiss me something Nate Travers.
- Anything.

62
00:04:24,515 --> 00:04:27,976
Promiss me you won't get yourself
killed trying to be a hero.

63
00:04:29,228 --> 00:04:30,896
You think you can get rid
of me that easily?

64
00:04:30,979 --> 00:04:32,147
No, I'm serious.

65
00:04:33,690 --> 00:04:35,275
Honey, don't start that.

66
00:04:35,776 --> 00:04:38,070
Promiss me you'll come home.

67
00:04:38,820 --> 00:04:40,072
I promiss.

68
00:04:40,989 --> 00:04:42,783
Swear it.

69
00:04:45,369 --> 00:04:48,413
I swear... I'll come home to you.

70
00:04:49,665 --> 00:04:50,499
Okay.

71
00:05:07,599 --> 00:05:10,602
Two Months later
August 2nd 1943

72
00:05:11,228 --> 00:05:14,147
Mid-Atlantic Convoy Route
600 miles off the U.S. Coast

73
00:05:43,468 --> 00:05:47,222
- Heinrich!
- Turn off the air-intake!

74
00:05:51,268 --> 00:05:57,649
- Stubborn bastards, those Americans.
- All ahead, 15 degrees starboard.

75
00:06:11,288 --> 00:06:14,958
- They're leaving.
- They're leaving.

76
00:06:15,167 --> 00:06:22,466
Periscope depth. We'll teach them
who the stubborn ones are.

77
00:06:34,019 --> 00:06:41,026
- 286 degrees, 15 knots.
- Distance: 2,700 meters.

78
00:06:42,277 --> 00:06:45,822
Ready tubes 3 and 4.

79
00:06:54,790 --> 00:06:55,916
Ready.

80
00:06:56,124 --> 00:07:00,212
- 112 degrees.
- Torpedo ready?

81
00:07:00,420 --> 00:07:02,506
3 and 4 ready.

82
00:07:05,425 --> 00:07:06,468
Ready.

83
00:07:09,263 --> 00:07:10,931
Fire.

84
00:07:32,536 --> 00:07:33,996
Yes! We got her!

85
00:07:36,790 --> 00:07:37,958
We got her!

86
00:07:38,166 --> 00:07:44,840
- A good yankee is a dead yankee.
- We dive.

87
00:07:55,976 --> 00:07:59,521
U.S.S. Swordfish
Balao-Class Attack Submarine

88
00:08:22,586 --> 00:08:24,963
- All ahead two thirds.
- All ahead two thirds.

89
00:08:25,714 --> 00:08:27,049
Make ready to dive.

90
00:08:27,090 --> 00:08:28,509
Make ready to dive.

91
00:08:28,634 --> 00:08:30,719
Shut 'em down, we're switching
to battery power!

92
00:08:30,761 --> 00:08:33,305
Come on! Move it! Let's go!

93
00:08:33,514 --> 00:08:36,141
Knock it off, come on!
And get your hands off your pecker!

94
00:08:36,183 --> 00:08:38,227
- Giddy up!
- Yeah, yeah!

95
00:08:38,644 --> 00:08:41,772
- Green board, pressure in the boat.
- Take her to 60.

96
00:08:42,397 --> 00:08:44,483
Take her to 60, five degree down-angle.

97
00:08:44,525 --> 00:08:46,568
60 feet, five degree down-angle, aye.

98
00:08:55,619 --> 00:08:56,662
Fuck!

99
00:09:08,674 --> 00:09:09,591
60 feet, Sir.

100
00:09:10,759 --> 00:09:12,719
- Zero bubble?
- Zero bubble, Sir.

101
00:09:13,345 --> 00:09:14,930
Zero bubble at 60, Sir.

102
00:09:15,013 --> 00:09:15,848
Scope up.

103
00:09:16,056 --> 00:09:17,224
Scope up!

104
00:09:20,018 --> 00:09:21,186
Time?

105
00:09:21,395 --> 00:09:22,437
64 seconds.

106
00:09:23,272 --> 00:09:24,606
64 seconds.

107
00:09:25,649 --> 00:09:27,025
64 seconds.

108
00:09:28,485 --> 00:09:30,237
Prepare to surface, exercise complete.

109
00:09:30,362 --> 00:09:32,114
Prepare to surface, exercise complete.

110
00:09:32,656 --> 00:09:33,907
Chief, in my quarters.

111
00:09:34,825 --> 00:09:36,201
Periscope going down!

112
00:09:39,621 --> 00:09:40,873
Not again!

113
00:09:42,541 --> 00:09:44,334
Maybe I should just go for a swim.

114
00:09:44,418 --> 00:09:45,460
Can I join you?

115
00:09:45,669 --> 00:09:47,129
- Now, Chief.
- Be right there, Sir.

116
00:09:49,131 --> 00:09:51,216
You look like crap,
you should see the medic.

117
00:09:51,425 --> 00:09:52,968
There's a lot of things I should do.

118
00:09:53,510 --> 00:09:59,349
Three months. Three months in the water
and the men become compleasant and sloppy.

119
00:09:59,641 --> 00:10:01,226
If you were in my shoes,
would that trouble you?

120
00:10:01,518 --> 00:10:02,895
Yes, Sir.

121
00:10:03,187 --> 00:10:05,606
Today's dive time was 64 seconds.

122
00:10:06,106 --> 00:10:08,108
3 days ago it was 58 seconds.

123
00:10:08,817 --> 00:10:10,277
6 seconds, Chief.

124
00:10:10,402 --> 00:10:11,528
We're in the Atlantic now...

125
00:10:11,653 --> 00:10:14,031
we can't afford to give the
Germans a six second advantage.

126
00:10:14,364 --> 00:10:15,282
I'll speak to the men.

127
00:10:17,367 --> 00:10:18,952
See that you do.

128
00:10:22,581 --> 00:10:23,540
Chief.

129
00:10:24,458 --> 00:10:26,251
You may have more experience...

130
00:10:26,543 --> 00:10:30,088
but I've been preparing for this for
a long time and I do know what I'm doing.

131
00:10:30,714 --> 00:10:32,090
I don't doubt that, Sir.

132
00:10:32,799 --> 00:10:34,468
So, what's on your mind, Chief?
Let's have it.

133
00:10:37,387 --> 00:10:39,181
I was thinking about
the men's morale.

134
00:10:39,389 --> 00:10:41,475
They're frustrated by these
constant exercises...

135
00:10:41,517 --> 00:10:43,644
and it's clearly not helping
their performance.

136
00:10:45,312 --> 00:10:48,565
What is it? You and the men are
disappointed we haven't seen any action?

137
00:10:49,274 --> 00:10:51,777
No, it's not that.

138
00:10:51,985 --> 00:10:54,696
Then what is it, Chief?
What is it?

139
00:10:55,113 --> 00:10:56,782
I was thinking...

140
00:10:56,907 --> 00:10:58,575
to keep spirits up,
maybe we could...

141
00:10:58,659 --> 00:11:00,869
give 'em a little more latitude...

142
00:11:01,161 --> 00:11:02,538
little less exercise.

143
00:11:04,206 --> 00:11:05,874
That's not your decision.

144
00:11:06,500 --> 00:11:07,960
And I've made mine.

145
00:11:08,043 --> 00:11:10,128
The crew's performance is
not what it needs to be.

146
00:11:10,546 --> 00:11:12,548
And the drills will
continue per my orders.

147
00:11:13,048 --> 00:11:14,216
Understood?

148
00:11:14,633 --> 00:11:15,551
Aye, Sir.

149
00:11:16,176 --> 00:11:17,219
Is that all?

150
00:11:18,679 --> 00:11:20,055
Yeah, that's all.

151
00:11:20,764 --> 00:11:21,723
You're dismissed.

152
00:11:28,689 --> 00:11:34,945
- How is Heinrich?
- Concussion. He'll be okay.

153
00:11:35,153 --> 00:11:38,198
Good, I'll check in on him later.

154
00:11:42,452 --> 00:11:46,540
- Good move.
- You always win anyway.

155
00:11:47,666 --> 00:11:51,753
- Do you know what your problem is?
- My queen is in a bad position.

156
00:11:52,045 --> 00:11:54,673
You always underestimate yourself.

157
00:11:54,882 --> 00:11:59,761
You should have been a commander yourself,
instead of hanging around with me.

158
00:12:03,223 --> 00:12:07,186
I thought that you would be more cheerful,
after we sunk that cruiser.

159
00:12:10,522 --> 00:12:16,361
We sink one, they sink 30.
We're lucky that the torpedo exploded.

160
00:12:17,404 --> 00:12:22,618
- The Americans joined the war.
- It didn't go so well last night.

161
00:12:22,910 --> 00:12:28,248
It'll all be better soon.
With a little luck...

162
00:12:28,457 --> 00:12:32,628
With a little luck,
we'll make it home in one piece.

163
00:12:55,859 --> 00:13:00,364
- What is it, Bauer?
- Look at this.

164
00:13:10,582 --> 00:13:13,794
Always when you least expect it.

165
00:13:16,296 --> 00:13:20,259
- How many moves do I have left?
- Two.

166
00:13:20,467 --> 00:13:23,095
Check...

167
00:13:24,638 --> 00:13:26,014
...mate.

168
00:13:26,223 --> 00:13:31,854
Good, I hate chess.
I get worse in every new move.

169
00:13:33,188 --> 00:13:39,152
- Sorry to disturb you, Captain. Mr. Cremer.
- We're finished.

170
00:13:42,489 --> 00:13:46,660
We got a message...
from home.

171
00:13:47,578 --> 00:13:49,246
Give it to me.

172
00:14:04,178 --> 00:14:08,140
Jonas... what does it say?

173
00:14:13,145 --> 00:14:16,064
I need a moment alone.

174
00:14:24,615 --> 00:14:28,577
They bombed Hamburg. The school his
daughters attend is completely destroyed.

175
00:14:28,785 --> 00:14:31,914
No survivors.

176
00:14:44,092 --> 00:14:45,469
All right, don't be stingy.

177
00:14:46,512 --> 00:14:47,638
Thanks.

178
00:14:47,846 --> 00:14:50,766
How many dress rehearsals is that?
Twenty seven, twenty eight maybe?

179
00:14:50,974 --> 00:14:53,810
I don't know... I don't care.

180
00:14:54,311 --> 00:14:55,896
I figured as much from you.

181
00:14:56,104 --> 00:14:56,939
I mean...

182
00:14:56,980 --> 00:14:58,190
It's not like we've
never done it before?

183
00:14:58,398 --> 00:15:00,359
I just don't get why he
doesn't find some krautsto pester...

184
00:15:00,400 --> 00:15:02,361
instead of jerking
our chains and fuckin' us.

185
00:15:02,444 --> 00:15:04,029
Yeah, I mean, what's he trying to prove?

186
00:15:04,112 --> 00:15:06,949
The least he could do is, whenever
it's not real, he could tell us.

187
00:15:07,032 --> 00:15:08,408
So we don't shit
our pants everytime.

188
00:15:09,034 --> 00:15:12,162
That would explain the complaints
I've been getting from laundry services.

189
00:15:16,416 --> 00:15:17,251
Chief.

190
00:15:19,336 --> 00:15:22,381
The reason we've conducted twenty
seven exercises Mr. Miller...

191
00:15:22,589 --> 00:15:26,218
is for you to become so accustomed
to your task, so masterful in your skills...

192
00:15:26,343 --> 00:15:30,514
that you do not shit yourself when
this boat comes under attack.

193
00:15:31,557 --> 00:15:32,808
I understand, Chief.

194
00:15:35,102 --> 00:15:39,356
Wanna talk some trash? Save it for
those nazi sons of bitches...

195
00:15:39,398 --> 00:15:42,484
crawling up and down our East Coast
looking to blow us out of the water.

196
00:15:44,695 --> 00:15:45,821
Anyone seen the XO?

197
00:15:46,154 --> 00:15:49,074
Oh, yeah. I think I saw
him go into the head, Chief.

198
00:16:11,805 --> 00:16:13,765
You're all right in there, Sir?

199
00:16:14,600 --> 00:16:15,559
Fine, Chief.

200
00:16:15,642 --> 00:16:17,102
I'll be out in a minute.

201
00:16:19,104 --> 00:16:20,606
U 281
Two days later

202
00:16:20,647 --> 00:16:21,899
290 miles northeast of Bermuda

203
00:16:30,657 --> 00:16:33,577
British Merchant Vessel Achilles

204
00:16:38,290 --> 00:16:40,250
Torpedoes... Fire.

205
00:16:41,001 --> 00:16:42,878
How do you lose an entire convoy?

206
00:16:46,423 --> 00:16:48,383
Increase speed to 18 knots.

207
00:16:57,684 --> 00:16:59,853
The Achille's last
radio contact, here.

208
00:17:00,062 --> 00:17:02,981
That's where the closest allied
vessel had been ordered to take a look.

209
00:17:03,315 --> 00:17:06,652
There's been no report of U-Boat
activity in that area for several weeks.

210
00:17:06,735 --> 00:17:08,320
That does not mean
they're not there.

211
00:17:08,946 --> 00:17:10,072
Chief...

212
00:17:10,197 --> 00:17:11,448
no drill this time.

213
00:17:11,657 --> 00:17:12,991
I'll inform the men.

214
00:17:13,408 --> 00:17:15,494
Confirm coordinates, let CINCLANT
know that we're on our way.

215
00:17:15,536 --> 00:17:16,537
Aye, Captain.

216
00:17:34,680 --> 00:17:37,724
We have to surface.

217
00:17:41,353 --> 00:17:45,107
Jonas, it's night.
We have to surface.

218
00:17:46,483 --> 00:17:50,445
- Yes, prepare for surfacing.
- Ready for surfacing.

219
00:17:51,071 --> 00:17:52,197
Who's in there?

220
00:17:53,991 --> 00:17:56,076
I've been waiting for too long.

221
00:17:58,161 --> 00:17:59,621
Hey, open up.

222
00:18:01,707 --> 00:18:03,792
- Oh, shit!
- Who is it?

223
00:18:04,209 --> 00:18:06,295
The XO, let's get him
to the medic. Come on.

224
00:18:12,759 --> 00:18:13,886
Flu?

225
00:18:14,636 --> 00:18:15,762
Not sure.

226
00:18:15,971 --> 00:18:17,431
Could be a reaction
to something he ate.

227
00:18:17,973 --> 00:18:19,224
How long have you
been feeling like this?

228
00:18:19,725 --> 00:18:22,019
A week maybe, since Panama.

229
00:18:22,352 --> 00:18:24,646
Hey, Chief. The Captain needs you.

230
00:18:24,730 --> 00:18:26,190
I think it's important.

231
00:18:26,732 --> 00:18:28,275
I need to come too.

232
00:18:28,692 --> 00:18:31,403
- You're not going anywhere.
- You wish you could order me around.

233
00:18:31,612 --> 00:18:32,571
I can.

234
00:18:33,697 --> 00:18:35,991
Keep the liquids coming,
and let me know of any changes.

235
00:18:36,116 --> 00:18:37,367
Yes, Sir.

236
00:18:37,784 --> 00:18:39,453
There's Cooper at your service.

237
00:18:46,627 --> 00:18:49,129
We need to keep him here,
away from the rest of the crew.

238
00:18:49,254 --> 00:18:52,799
Until I have a chance to check on the others
to see if they have any of the same symptoms.

239
00:18:53,300 --> 00:18:54,468
Is that serious?

240
00:18:55,511 --> 00:18:56,970
It could be meningococcus.

241
00:18:57,679 --> 00:18:58,931
English?

242
00:18:58,972 --> 00:19:01,558
It's a form of meningitis,
it's highly contagious...

243
00:19:01,642 --> 00:19:04,061
and in some cases it can be fatal.

244
00:19:12,194 --> 00:19:15,405
We couldn't stop the bleeding
in the brain.

245
00:19:17,074 --> 00:19:20,202
How old was he? 18?

246
00:19:22,829 --> 00:19:26,166
Heinrich wanted to show
what he could do.

247
00:19:26,375 --> 00:19:28,669
From the first day.

248
00:19:28,961 --> 00:19:34,091
You couldn't do anything.
You couldn't stop it.

249
00:19:35,008 --> 00:19:37,845
No...

250
00:19:38,053 --> 00:19:41,598
That's the problem.

251
00:19:48,689 --> 00:19:49,940
Anything?

252
00:19:50,148 --> 00:19:50,983
No, Sir.

253
00:19:53,485 --> 00:19:56,196
Chief, glad you could join us.
Put the men on full alert.

254
00:19:56,488 --> 00:19:57,447
Yes, Sir.

255
00:19:58,282 --> 00:19:59,616
Where's the XO?

256
00:20:00,242 --> 00:20:01,910
In a sick room, Sir,
he's taken ill.

257
00:20:02,870 --> 00:20:04,538
Have Mr. Goodman standing by.

258
00:20:07,457 --> 00:20:09,960
Sir, the XO can barely stand.

259
00:20:11,211 --> 00:20:12,546
He's got a rash, and the med--

260
00:20:12,588 --> 00:20:16,717
Chief, we're in hostile waters, the XO
is breathing, I want him at his post.

261
00:20:17,551 --> 00:20:18,510
Aye, Sir.

262
00:20:37,988 --> 00:20:40,699
U 821
Two days later

263
00:20:44,995 --> 00:20:46,955
Captain...

264
00:20:59,176 --> 00:21:01,762
Glenn Miller?

265
00:21:04,056 --> 00:21:06,475
Good.

266
00:21:19,279 --> 00:21:23,242
<i>That's music by Glenn Miller,
from the spacious Café Rouge...</i>

267
00:21:23,283 --> 00:21:26,161
<i>of the Hotel Pennsylvania
in New York City.</i>

268
00:21:26,578 --> 00:21:30,749
<i>Where the young at heart come from
far and near to watch and hear...</i>

269
00:21:30,874 --> 00:21:35,879
<i>the orchestra that has given America
some of the most beautiful sounds ever.</i>

270
00:21:46,390 --> 00:21:47,558
Captain!

271
00:21:47,599 --> 00:21:50,686
Captain! I've got something
at 3-4-0, 4,000 feet.

272
00:21:51,728 --> 00:21:53,272
Sounds... sounds like music.

273
00:21:57,359 --> 00:21:58,610
You dirty dog!

274
00:21:59,236 --> 00:22:02,990
Mr. Goodman, set torpedo
depth at 10 feet.

275
00:22:03,198 --> 00:22:05,576
Set torpedo depth 10 feet.

276
00:22:05,909 --> 00:22:08,203
- Depth set!
- Depth is set!

277
00:22:08,704 --> 00:22:10,080
Ready tubes one and two.

278
00:22:10,122 --> 00:22:11,623
Ready bow tubes one and two.

279
00:22:11,832 --> 00:22:12,875
Come on.

280
00:22:13,000 --> 00:22:14,543
- Gyro angle?
- 349.

281
00:22:14,585 --> 00:22:16,211
Gyro angle 349.

282
00:22:16,253 --> 00:22:17,254
- Set?
- Set.

283
00:22:17,296 --> 00:22:18,297
Fire one.

284
00:22:18,338 --> 00:22:19,339
Fire one.

285
00:22:19,381 --> 00:22:20,382
Fire one!

286
00:22:23,427 --> 00:22:24,052
Fire two.

287
00:22:24,094 --> 00:22:24,761
Fire two.

288
00:22:24,887 --> 00:22:25,929
Fire two!

289
00:22:29,141 --> 00:22:31,351
- Torpedoes!
- Damn!

290
00:22:31,643 --> 00:22:35,105
All ahead full. Dive!

291
00:22:40,527 --> 00:22:41,987
They were hit, Sir,
but are still up.

292
00:22:42,029 --> 00:22:43,530
Goddamn it! Prepare to attack again.

293
00:22:43,739 --> 00:22:44,573
Prepare to attack again!

294
00:22:44,615 --> 00:22:46,158
Set torpedo depth to 12 feet.

295
00:22:46,241 --> 00:22:47,826
Set torpedo depth to 12 feet.

296
00:22:47,910 --> 00:22:49,578
- Depth is set!
- Depth is set!

297
00:22:49,786 --> 00:22:51,163
Ready bow tubes three and four.

298
00:22:51,246 --> 00:22:53,040
Ready bow tubes three and four.

299
00:22:53,081 --> 00:22:55,417
Where the hell is he?

300
00:23:00,130 --> 00:23:04,301
Two subs.
One of ours, the other is American.

301
00:23:04,510 --> 00:23:08,555
- Distance?
- 4,000 meters.

302
00:23:09,932 --> 00:23:11,058
Angle? Angle?

303
00:23:11,683 --> 00:23:12,518
351.

304
00:23:12,935 --> 00:23:15,145
351, are we set? Mr. Goodman, set?

305
00:23:16,897 --> 00:23:18,357
Gyro angle 351.

306
00:23:18,899 --> 00:23:19,608
Tube three ready.

307
00:23:19,733 --> 00:23:20,651
Tube three ready!

308
00:23:20,776 --> 00:23:21,401
Set!

309
00:23:21,485 --> 00:23:22,236
Fire three!

310
00:23:22,319 --> 00:23:23,362
Fire three!

311
00:23:25,781 --> 00:23:30,577
- She's right in front of us.
- Distance 400 meters. Fire!

312
00:23:41,004 --> 00:23:42,256
Captain!

313
00:23:48,095 --> 00:23:50,055
- She's cooked alright! Well done!
- Yeah!

314
00:23:51,014 --> 00:23:52,558
Good work, boys! Good work!

315
00:23:52,975 --> 00:23:53,809
We got 'em!

316
00:23:56,854 --> 00:23:58,522
How does it feel to have
your cherry popped?

317
00:23:58,605 --> 00:24:01,024
- Oh, God! Even better than the first time.
- First time?

318
00:24:05,404 --> 00:24:07,364
That's what it's all about, all right?

319
00:24:11,243 --> 00:24:12,369
He's dead.

320
00:24:12,786 --> 00:24:13,954
Screw in the water!

321
00:24:14,580 --> 00:24:16,665
Right full rudder
all ahead flank, now! Move!

322
00:24:16,874 --> 00:24:18,750
Right full rudder all ahead flank.

323
00:24:35,309 --> 00:24:37,394
I need damage reports, Chief!
Damage reports!

324
00:24:37,936 --> 00:24:39,897
Mr. Right, I need damage reports!

325
00:24:46,904 --> 00:24:48,989
It's no use, he's gone.

326
00:24:51,909 --> 00:24:53,660
- Miller!
- Yes, Sir!

327
00:24:53,994 --> 00:24:56,079
Blow bow bouyancy. Surface!

328
00:24:56,371 --> 00:24:57,623
Surface! Surface!

329
00:25:14,515 --> 00:25:15,682
Help me!

330
00:25:19,436 --> 00:25:20,979
- Who's in there?
- Nobody!

331
00:25:21,313 --> 00:25:23,190
They're all dead in there,
Chief. Come on!

332
00:25:26,109 --> 00:25:27,778
Listing 10 degrees port, sir.

333
00:25:27,819 --> 00:25:30,489
Forward torpedo and forward
barrack taking on water, Sir!

334
00:25:30,989 --> 00:25:32,574
We've lost the engines, Captain!

335
00:25:32,783 --> 00:25:35,077
We're not gonna make it,
Captain. She's going down.

336
00:25:40,165 --> 00:25:42,876
- Captain, you gotta--
- Don't tell me what I have to do, Chief.

337
00:25:44,336 --> 00:25:45,796
I know what I have to do.

338
00:25:51,552 --> 00:25:53,220
This is your captain speaking...

339
00:25:53,720 --> 00:25:55,097
Abandon ship.

340
00:25:55,722 --> 00:25:58,851
I repeat, abandon ship.

341
00:26:03,856 --> 00:26:04,982
Abandon ship.

342
00:26:19,705 --> 00:26:24,918
Captain! There's nothing more you can do!
She's going down, come on!

343
00:26:25,127 --> 00:26:27,838
Tend to the others, Chief.
That's an order.

344
00:26:30,424 --> 00:26:32,634
Come on, Chief!
We gotta hurry!

345
00:26:52,946 --> 00:26:55,574
Come on. Captain,
we gotta get out of here!

346
00:26:55,782 --> 00:26:57,743
- Not till the crew's out.
- No. Listen to me.

347
00:26:57,951 --> 00:27:01,705
They're all dead. This is a casket.
We gotta get out of here.

348
00:27:30,067 --> 00:27:34,363
<i>You made me love you...</i>

349
00:27:34,571 --> 00:27:37,574
<i>I didn't wanna do it...</i>

350
00:27:37,783 --> 00:27:42,579
<i>I didn't wanna do it...</i>

351
00:27:42,621 --> 00:27:48,335
<i>You made me love you...</i>

352
00:27:48,627 --> 00:27:52,297
<i>And all the time you knew it...</i>

353
00:27:52,714 --> 00:27:55,843
<i>I guess you always knew it...</i>

354
00:27:56,468 --> 00:27:59,888
<i>You made me happy...</i>

355
00:28:00,222 --> 00:28:03,767
This has been the best
thanksgiving ever.

356
00:28:04,893 --> 00:28:06,895
I do get holidays.

357
00:28:08,856 --> 00:28:10,649
You just wait till Christmas.

358
00:28:13,569 --> 00:28:14,611
Kiss me.

359
00:28:47,144 --> 00:28:51,315
Follow me. Now!

360
00:28:51,523 --> 00:28:54,109
Come.

361
00:29:11,960 --> 00:29:13,879
Move!

362
00:29:13,921 --> 00:29:17,257
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.

363
00:29:37,694 --> 00:29:39,780
It's okay, Captain. You got it.

364
00:29:40,322 --> 00:29:41,573
You got it.

365
00:29:41,615 --> 00:29:43,659
Move it!

366
00:29:45,619 --> 00:29:49,581
You're not scared of a few Americans?

367
00:29:49,790 --> 00:29:52,918
I'm worried about supplies.

368
00:29:53,126 --> 00:29:57,422
We'll be at the supply vessel in a week.
We have enough supplies.

369
00:29:57,631 --> 00:30:00,133
There's nothing to worry about.

370
00:30:00,551 --> 00:30:04,304
When we get there, we'll turn
over the Americans for interrogation.

371
00:30:05,973 --> 00:30:08,684
Klaus, could you give us a moment?

372
00:30:10,853 --> 00:30:12,104
As you wish.

373
00:30:17,317 --> 00:30:19,820
What is it?

374
00:30:21,405 --> 00:30:26,201
You said it yourself - the war is ending.
Why risk everything now?

375
00:30:29,746 --> 00:30:34,209
Make sure my orders are followed, Ludwig.

376
00:30:36,712 --> 00:30:39,131
Yes, Captain.

377
00:30:44,845 --> 00:30:47,472
- Everybody all right?
- Yeah.

378
00:30:49,433 --> 00:30:51,935
I don't know about you guys,
but I don't wanna go to Germany.

379
00:30:53,103 --> 00:30:54,771
You know what they do
to prisoners in Germany?

380
00:30:55,397 --> 00:30:58,734
They torture them, and then
they gas them or they burn them alive!

381
00:30:58,817 --> 00:30:59,860
Shut up!

382
00:31:00,485 --> 00:31:01,320
Shut up.

383
00:31:01,445 --> 00:31:03,322
That's what those officers
in Panama said they did...

384
00:31:03,363 --> 00:31:05,199
to all those jews!
They just cooked them!

385
00:31:05,282 --> 00:31:07,910
- They cooked them like meat.
- Calm down, Miller.

386
00:31:07,993 --> 00:31:09,369
That's an order, sailor.

387
00:31:10,621 --> 00:31:11,955
We gotta hold it together.

388
00:31:12,581 --> 00:31:14,374
We panic now,
we're as good as dead.

389
00:31:14,666 --> 00:31:16,752
They were supposed to
just let us drown, Captain.

390
00:31:17,294 --> 00:31:19,171
Why didn't they just
let us fucking drown?

391
00:31:35,854 --> 00:31:36,772
Chief...

392
00:31:37,105 --> 00:31:38,857
We're going to break up
into three groups.

393
00:31:39,483 --> 00:31:41,693
I'll head up a team to
search for food and supplies.

394
00:31:41,735 --> 00:31:43,862
I want you to radio
CINCLANT our position.

395
00:31:43,987 --> 00:31:47,533
Find out what our orders are.
Tell them we contacted the enemy.

396
00:31:47,950 --> 00:31:49,618
Understand? Understand?

397
00:31:50,869 --> 00:31:51,912
But, Captain...

398
00:32:01,380 --> 00:32:02,756
Take it easy... easy.

399
00:32:03,048 --> 00:32:04,091
Come here!

400
00:32:06,718 --> 00:32:08,178
Come on.

401
00:32:09,221 --> 00:32:10,138
I got it.

402
00:32:14,434 --> 00:32:16,520
You should have let me
die on my boat, Chief.

403
00:32:17,980 --> 00:32:19,731
You should have let me
die on my boat.

404
00:32:38,917 --> 00:32:40,377
Is he dead?

405
00:32:46,133 --> 00:32:47,593
What are we gonna do Chief?

406
00:32:49,970 --> 00:32:51,972
What are you looking at me for?
The captain--

407
00:32:52,181 --> 00:32:53,849
The Captain ain't the Captain no more.

408
00:32:56,435 --> 00:32:58,103
He's gone off his mind, Chief.

409
00:32:58,937 --> 00:33:00,939
He ain't gonna be able
to help us now.

410
00:33:03,442 --> 00:33:10,324
- Why the hell did he bring them onboard?
- There are rules in war.

411
00:33:11,658 --> 00:33:16,872
Not when they just sunk one of ours.
The entire crew was killed.

412
00:33:17,080 --> 00:33:22,294
- Our Comrades!
- Are you questioning him?

413
00:33:26,173 --> 00:33:30,969
I don't doubt the Captain's
orders. Neither should you.

414
00:33:31,178 --> 00:33:35,557
Mr. Cremer, he puts us in danger.

415
00:33:39,937 --> 00:33:43,482
That's what war is about.

416
00:33:48,070 --> 00:33:50,447
I counted at least 20 of them pricks.

417
00:33:50,572 --> 00:33:52,032
There's probably twice that many.

418
00:33:52,115 --> 00:33:53,909
Yeah, and they got guns too.

419
00:34:06,505 --> 00:34:08,715
Eat.

420
00:34:11,718 --> 00:34:14,555
They don't understand a word.

421
00:34:20,060 --> 00:34:23,397
Here you go.
I hope you like it.

422
00:34:23,814 --> 00:34:25,482
Piss off, you damn kraut!

423
00:34:26,859 --> 00:34:27,901
Hey, come on.

424
00:34:27,985 --> 00:34:30,821
Leave it.

425
00:34:43,542 --> 00:34:44,877
What the hell is this?

426
00:34:45,294 --> 00:34:49,381
My guess is... pig balls and
chicken guts if we're lucky.

427
00:34:49,464 --> 00:34:50,632
Give me one for the Captain.

428
00:34:55,929 --> 00:34:57,514
How do we know they
didn't poison it, Chief?

429
00:34:57,556 --> 00:34:59,057
How do we know they
didn't do that?

430
00:34:59,266 --> 00:35:01,351
Cause if they wanted us dead,
they would have let us drown.

431
00:35:02,394 --> 00:35:04,897
Besides, we're gonna need all
the strenght we can get, so...

432
00:35:05,939 --> 00:35:06,982
Eat up.

433
00:35:24,082 --> 00:35:25,459
You should try to eat something.

434
00:35:27,336 --> 00:35:29,213
You said that Goodman had a rash.

435
00:35:30,547 --> 00:35:32,007
What did the medic think it was?

436
00:35:34,510 --> 00:35:35,761
Meningitis.

437
00:35:43,185 --> 00:35:44,645
What did it look like?

438
00:36:01,745 --> 00:36:03,288
I want you to keep this
between us, Chief.

439
00:36:03,413 --> 00:36:05,290
I don't wanna startle
the men, understand?

440
00:36:27,271 --> 00:36:28,522
Hey!

441
00:36:28,856 --> 00:36:30,190
Hey, someone's coming!

442
00:37:02,931 --> 00:37:05,017
Who is of highest rank?

443
00:37:09,313 --> 00:37:12,941
- It's alright.
- It's okay, okay, okay!

444
00:37:22,951 --> 00:37:24,411
What's your position?

445
00:37:25,787 --> 00:37:26,914
Chief of Boat.

446
00:37:31,627 --> 00:37:34,630
What happened to your Captain,
Chief of Boat?

447
00:37:36,089 --> 00:37:37,257
He didn't make it.

448
00:37:39,426 --> 00:37:40,802
He went down with the ship?

449
00:37:41,428 --> 00:37:42,679
Yeah, he did.

450
00:37:50,062 --> 00:37:51,647
These are your men.

451
00:37:52,564 --> 00:37:55,609
They do as you tell them,
and we do not have a problem.

452
00:38:02,699 --> 00:38:04,368
What's the matter with him?

453
00:38:05,702 --> 00:38:07,579
He was injured, trying to get out.

454
00:38:08,539 --> 00:38:10,499
He'll be needing medical assistance.

455
00:38:12,709 --> 00:38:16,672
You'll split in half.
Smaller groups, more comfortable...

456
00:38:18,340 --> 00:38:19,800
for all of us.

457
00:38:21,677 --> 00:38:25,013
Chain them, and give him medicine.

458
00:38:25,305 --> 00:38:29,601
- Let him die.
- Do as I say!

459
00:38:59,298 --> 00:39:02,134
Take his handcuffs off.

460
00:39:10,267 --> 00:39:11,935
Mind your fucking head.

461
00:39:14,229 --> 00:39:16,940
For him.

462
00:39:24,531 --> 00:39:26,325
How can anybody sleep like that?

463
00:39:26,950 --> 00:39:30,078
Got clobbered in the head,
probably has a concussion.

464
00:39:30,704 --> 00:39:32,247
Well, should we wake him first?

465
00:39:32,372 --> 00:39:33,624
Shit, I wouldn't.

466
00:39:36,210 --> 00:39:37,878
Oh, man. Look at that.

467
00:39:38,504 --> 00:39:39,755
Hey, Right, don't touch that.

468
00:39:39,963 --> 00:39:41,340
Right, don't fucking touch it!

469
00:39:41,423 --> 00:39:43,008
Why? Why not?

470
00:39:44,134 --> 00:39:46,637
Shit. Guys, that's not a wound,
that's a rash.

471
00:39:48,096 --> 00:39:50,307
- What?
- My sister got it when she was a kid.

472
00:39:50,599 --> 00:39:52,684
Meningitis I think,
I don't know exacly.

473
00:39:52,893 --> 00:39:54,478
She got it from
the water in our well.

474
00:39:54,895 --> 00:39:56,021
How long does it last?

475
00:39:56,230 --> 00:39:57,272
About a week.

476
00:39:57,481 --> 00:39:59,566
Okay, so how do you treat it?
I got a bunch of stuff...

477
00:39:59,691 --> 00:40:00,526
You don't, Right.

478
00:40:00,609 --> 00:40:02,611
So, what, it just goes away?

479
00:40:02,653 --> 00:40:03,445
No.

480
00:40:04,071 --> 00:40:06,365
- You said it lasted a week.
- Yeah, I said about a week.

481
00:40:08,659 --> 00:40:09,910
And then we buried her.

482
00:40:11,453 --> 00:40:12,829
Christ, Abers!

483
00:40:13,247 --> 00:40:14,498
Abers, is it contagious?

484
00:40:15,749 --> 00:40:18,544
Well, I didn't get it.
But, yeah.

485
00:40:19,086 --> 00:40:21,588
Oh, great! Great!

486
00:40:22,089 --> 00:40:23,882
The krauts won't kill us,
the Captain will.

487
00:40:34,184 --> 00:40:37,312
What are you looking at, rat?

488
00:40:41,400 --> 00:40:42,734
What are you doing?!

489
00:40:43,694 --> 00:40:48,282
Not only are you eating our food,
I also have to look at you.

490
00:40:48,699 --> 00:40:51,076
- What is he saying?
- Oh, come on! What the hell are you doing?

491
00:40:53,161 --> 00:40:55,789
That's enough.

492
00:41:06,216 --> 00:41:07,050
Are you all right?

493
00:41:22,357 --> 00:41:24,443
Three days later
August 10th

494
00:41:24,484 --> 00:41:27,070
450 miles off the U.S. Coast

495
00:42:12,824 --> 00:42:18,163
I hurt everywhere,
and it's difficult to breathe.

496
00:42:18,372 --> 00:42:23,043
I'll give you something for the pain.
Get some rest.

497
00:42:23,252 --> 00:42:26,171
You'll be well soon.

498
00:42:49,528 --> 00:42:55,158
- How many?
- Eight sick. Others have the symptoms.

499
00:42:55,367 --> 00:42:58,203
Captain, come here, please.

500
00:42:59,538 --> 00:43:03,625
We're almost there,
but the supply vessel isn't here.

501
00:43:03,917 --> 00:43:08,630
- What do you mean?
- They aren't answering our radio signals.

502
00:43:08,839 --> 00:43:12,259
- Are we in the right position?
- Yes.

503
00:43:12,467 --> 00:43:15,387
Damn! Up periscope.

504
00:43:28,108 --> 00:43:31,987
An American destroyer. Damn!

505
00:43:38,744 --> 00:43:41,872
- Distance?
- 2,500 meters.

506
00:43:42,080 --> 00:43:43,665
2,500.

507
00:43:57,429 --> 00:43:59,306
Captain?

508
00:44:12,110 --> 00:44:16,281
What's your command?
We must act.

509
00:44:22,663 --> 00:44:26,625
- How many torpedoes do we have?
- Two front, one stern.

510
00:44:26,834 --> 00:44:31,839
Ready one and two.
Set torpedo depth at 5 meters.

511
00:44:43,809 --> 00:44:45,394
Chief, they prepare to attack.

512
00:44:45,477 --> 00:44:46,728
We gotta do something.

513
00:44:47,980 --> 00:44:53,193
1800 meters.

514
00:44:53,819 --> 00:44:56,321
Otto, come here.

515
00:45:04,246 --> 00:45:06,665
- Torpedoes ready.
- Ready.

516
00:45:39,698 --> 00:45:40,741
Now!

517
00:45:58,884 --> 00:46:01,386
Captain, torpedoes ready.

518
00:46:16,401 --> 00:46:21,406
- The Americans escaped!
- I told you it would happen!

519
00:46:23,283 --> 00:46:26,537
- Stop the launch!
- I'm on it!

520
00:46:38,090 --> 00:46:40,092
We've got company!

521
00:46:42,177 --> 00:46:44,054
Ox, a little help!

522
00:46:46,640 --> 00:46:47,891
How are you gonna know
which one is which?

523
00:46:48,100 --> 00:46:49,685
I was born to fire
torpedoes, don't matter...

524
00:46:49,726 --> 00:46:51,854
if it's German, jap or
portuguese for that matter.

525
00:46:52,062 --> 00:46:53,105
Do it fast!

526
00:47:04,283 --> 00:47:05,409
Got it! I got it!

527
00:47:09,288 --> 00:47:10,622
Cooper!

528
00:47:10,664 --> 00:47:11,582
No!

529
00:47:22,092 --> 00:47:23,760
Stop! Stop it right now!

530
00:47:26,054 --> 00:47:27,723
Don't shoot, don't shoot.

531
00:47:32,853 --> 00:47:34,730
Right, full rudder.
Take evasive action.

532
00:47:35,147 --> 00:47:36,481
Get me a location on that thing.

533
00:47:36,523 --> 00:47:39,818
Dive!
Depth: stern minus 20, bow minus 30.

534
00:47:48,076 --> 00:47:53,081
- Quick!
- Everybody to the front!

535
00:47:53,373 --> 00:47:56,418
Hurry! Quick!

536
00:48:01,089 --> 00:48:02,674
What was that?

537
00:48:12,267 --> 00:48:14,228
50 meters.

538
00:48:20,609 --> 00:48:23,612
Fool... You've killed us all.

539
00:48:25,072 --> 00:48:31,036
If you pull that trigger now, you might just
pin a bull's eye on the side of this boat.

540
00:48:33,413 --> 00:48:35,707
Captain, is it over?

541
00:48:37,709 --> 00:48:39,253
It hasn't even started.

542
00:49:11,285 --> 00:49:13,370
Back!

543
00:49:16,290 --> 00:49:19,001
Don't shoot! Captain! Captain!

544
00:49:19,293 --> 00:49:24,298
Captain! Captain!

545
00:49:24,423 --> 00:49:27,551
Captain! Captain!

546
00:49:44,234 --> 00:49:45,569
Captain's dead.

547
00:49:57,581 --> 00:50:03,712
- We have to get rid of the Americans.
- Here? A mass execution?

548
00:50:03,921 --> 00:50:10,093
I want to get rid of them as well. But we
can't get rid of the bodies.

549
00:50:10,302 --> 00:50:12,679
I can live with the smell.

550
00:50:14,765 --> 00:50:19,144
- What is it, Bauer?
- There's something you have to see.

551
00:50:19,353 --> 00:50:23,440
Wilhelm was the first to
get the symptoms. Here.

552
00:50:32,407 --> 00:50:37,829
The Americans are like The Plague.
And we have them here onboard.

553
00:50:46,463 --> 00:50:48,131
Look at him!

554
00:50:48,882 --> 00:50:51,385
- What is it?
- I'm not sure.

555
00:50:55,764 --> 00:50:58,350
A medic thought it might
be meningitis.

556
00:51:00,018 --> 00:51:01,061
Contagious?

557
00:51:01,895 --> 00:51:03,272
Very.

558
00:51:08,277 --> 00:51:09,319
Is there a cure?

559
00:51:10,654 --> 00:51:12,531
I'm not a doctor.

560
00:51:23,166 --> 00:51:27,254
- The crew must not know.
- What? But the Americans...

561
00:51:27,462 --> 00:51:32,467
That is an order!
And you will obey.

562
00:51:58,202 --> 00:52:02,289
Everybody must wear the breathing apparatus,
until we can surface.

563
00:52:02,497 --> 00:52:08,003
- The Americans can't have any.
- Everybody must wear the breathing apparatus.

564
00:52:11,340 --> 00:52:17,596
Yes, Captain.
How long are we staying down here?

565
00:52:17,804 --> 00:52:20,933
As long as we can.

566
00:53:04,643 --> 00:53:06,812
Abers.

567
00:53:06,854 --> 00:53:09,523
- I'm here.
- When you get out...

568
00:53:10,899 --> 00:53:12,985
don't you tell my mother
that I died this way.

569
00:53:17,447 --> 00:53:23,495
Tell her that I went quick.
No pain.

570
00:53:28,709 --> 00:53:30,169
No pain.

571
00:54:33,899 --> 00:54:36,068
August 13th

572
00:54:36,109 --> 00:54:38,695
380 miles off the U.S. Coast

573
00:54:50,791 --> 00:54:52,334
<i>Don't quit!</i>

574
00:54:53,585 --> 00:54:55,587
<i>Don't quit on me, Nate.</i>

575
00:54:56,213 --> 00:54:57,756
Rachel.

576
00:55:03,720 --> 00:55:06,431
I've never seen you
like this before.

577
00:55:08,308 --> 00:55:11,520
My men are dying.
We're near the end.

578
00:55:12,354 --> 00:55:14,356
I can't accept that.

579
00:55:16,024 --> 00:55:17,276
I'm sorry.

580
00:55:17,693 --> 00:55:19,570
Never be sorry.

581
00:55:19,987 --> 00:55:21,655
What am I supposed to do, hun?

582
00:55:22,281 --> 00:55:24,241
You're supposed to come home to me.

583
00:55:24,867 --> 00:55:26,034
How?

584
00:55:27,578 --> 00:55:29,663
I don't have any fight left.

585
00:55:30,414 --> 00:55:31,123
I don't--

586
00:55:31,164 --> 00:55:34,459
I'm not going to be one
of those wives, Nate Travers.

587
00:55:34,668 --> 00:55:38,839
I'm not back there waiting for some
telegram to tell me that my husband is dead.

588
00:55:39,798 --> 00:55:41,675
I won't let you do that to me.

589
00:55:45,429 --> 00:55:47,181
You made me a promiss.

590
00:55:48,015 --> 00:55:50,017
Oh, God, I miss you.

591
00:55:51,268 --> 00:55:53,228
Then come back to me.

592
00:55:59,484 --> 00:56:04,615
- Is she still there?
- Perhaps.

593
00:56:04,823 --> 00:56:08,577
"Perhaps" is not good enough.

594
00:56:14,499 --> 00:56:19,004
- Ready to surface.
- We'll be an easy target.

595
00:56:19,296 --> 00:56:23,800
What would you prefer?
Dying here or up there?

596
00:56:24,092 --> 00:56:27,554
At least we have a chance up there.

597
00:56:28,263 --> 00:56:30,682
Surface.

598
00:57:08,011 --> 00:57:11,139
We're clear!

599
00:57:15,102 --> 00:57:18,313
Transmit emergency signal.

600
00:57:22,609 --> 00:57:25,112
It's fresh air.
The hatch is open.

601
00:57:27,614 --> 00:57:29,283
It means we lost our navy.

602
00:57:35,122 --> 00:57:39,334
Family?

603
00:57:39,376 --> 00:57:42,212
Yeah. That's my family.

604
00:57:42,838 --> 00:57:45,632
That's Vivian, and...
and Ol' Danny Jr.

605
00:57:45,841 --> 00:57:48,343
- Looks like me, huh?
- Give it a rest, will ya?

606
00:57:48,677 --> 00:57:50,012
They don't care.

607
00:57:50,345 --> 00:57:52,014
They don't care about your family.

608
00:58:01,273 --> 00:58:02,524
Is this your son?

609
00:58:02,566 --> 00:58:06,278
Yes, my son. Peter... Jr.

610
00:58:12,868 --> 00:58:18,290
Never forget this is the enemy.

611
00:58:18,582 --> 00:58:21,919
Take care of your own men.
Out.

612
00:58:26,507 --> 00:58:27,466
Eat!

613
00:58:29,843 --> 00:58:32,679
And?

614
00:58:33,305 --> 00:58:36,934
Every second is precious.

615
00:58:37,976 --> 00:58:43,524
We must do something about the Americans.

616
00:58:58,121 --> 00:59:01,124
Take off his handcuffs.

617
00:59:09,258 --> 00:59:10,843
That is all.

618
00:59:18,767 --> 00:59:20,853
Your men, they follow
your orders, do they not?

619
00:59:21,353 --> 00:59:22,312
They do.

620
00:59:22,729 --> 00:59:23,981
Would they follow mine?

621
00:59:26,775 --> 00:59:29,069
I've lost two thirds of my men.
Your navy is not far away...

622
00:59:29,194 --> 00:59:32,406
and our distress calls have failed,
I've no option left.

623
00:59:33,448 --> 00:59:36,785
Between all of us we have just enough
hands to make this boat operational.

624
00:59:37,536 --> 00:59:41,081
If you and your men join my men,
we might have a chance.

625
00:59:42,624 --> 00:59:44,084
You want us to help you?

626
00:59:44,501 --> 00:59:45,961
I want you to help yourselves.

627
00:59:49,214 --> 00:59:50,465
And if we refuse?

628
00:59:52,968 --> 00:59:54,303
We all die.

629
00:59:55,888 --> 01:00:00,893
That he's speaking to them - that alone
is treason.

630
01:00:01,101 --> 01:00:05,355
You've seen how he behaves.
He's insane.

631
01:00:07,149 --> 01:00:10,903
This is insane.

632
01:00:11,111 --> 01:00:15,365
- What do we do?
- I refuse to obey him.

633
01:00:15,574 --> 01:00:18,702
I hope
that you will do the same.

634
01:00:19,244 --> 01:00:20,787
What exactly are you proposing?

635
01:00:22,456 --> 01:00:25,375
Our diesel is nearly exhausted
and the fuel line has been damaged.

636
01:00:26,126 --> 01:00:28,295
But if we're efficient,
we should be able to make 500...

637
01:00:28,420 --> 01:00:29,963
maybe 600 kilometers.

638
01:00:30,506 --> 01:00:34,259
You can't really expect my men
to help you deliver them into custody.

639
01:00:36,011 --> 01:00:39,139
We travel submerged by day,
making up time on top at night.

640
01:00:39,973 --> 01:00:41,850
If my calculations are correct...

641
01:00:42,601 --> 01:00:43,936
we should be able...

642
01:00:44,770 --> 01:00:46,647
to make landfall in three days.

643
01:00:46,688 --> 01:00:48,649
UNITED STATES

644
01:00:48,732 --> 01:00:49,900
Jonas!

645
01:00:53,111 --> 01:00:55,197
You're serious?

646
01:00:55,405 --> 01:00:58,116
Once we're close to shore
we deploy the life-rafts...

647
01:00:58,158 --> 01:00:59,368
we evacuate the men and...

648
01:00:59,409 --> 01:01:00,536
we scuddle the boat.

649
01:01:00,577 --> 01:01:03,455
You understand I will not allow my boat
to fall into your country's hands.

650
01:01:04,581 --> 01:01:08,126
In return for this, I surrender myself to
you and ask for consideration for my men.

651
01:01:08,961 --> 01:01:13,131
- You can't just surrender.
- It's my duty to save the men.

652
01:01:13,340 --> 01:01:16,802
Don't surrender us to them!

653
01:01:18,262 --> 01:01:22,307
- We can manage without them.
- If only we could.

654
01:01:23,976 --> 01:01:25,561
Ludwig!

655
01:01:28,564 --> 01:01:30,566
I need your hand, Sir.

656
01:01:32,442 --> 01:01:35,445
I can't make any guarantees
once you're in US custody.

657
01:01:36,071 --> 01:01:37,239
I understand.

658
01:01:38,073 --> 01:01:41,076
All I ask for is that you report
to your superiors what I've done.

659
01:01:41,618 --> 01:01:44,955
So, when this war is over,
they save my men like I saved yours.

660
01:01:47,249 --> 01:01:48,917
I'll need to speak to my men first.

661
01:01:49,001 --> 01:01:50,252
All of them.

662
01:01:52,045 --> 01:01:53,380
You've two minutes.

663
01:01:54,214 --> 01:01:56,091
You want us to team-up
with the Jerries?

664
01:01:56,216 --> 01:01:58,177
I don't like it, Chief... no siree.

665
01:01:58,385 --> 01:02:01,305
I'm with them on this one.
I don't trust these kraut bastards...

666
01:02:01,430 --> 01:02:02,764
as far as I could throw 'em.

667
01:02:03,098 --> 01:02:04,433
Why don't, why don't
we just wait 'em up?

668
01:02:04,558 --> 01:02:06,643
They're dropping like flies...
we wait until enough...

669
01:02:06,685 --> 01:02:08,604
of them are infected and
then we take the boat.

670
01:02:09,646 --> 01:02:10,480
Why not?

671
01:02:10,606 --> 01:02:12,065
How long are you gonna wait?

672
01:02:12,149 --> 01:02:14,359
Romano's already dead.
How long before you are infected?

673
01:02:15,402 --> 01:02:17,988
We don't have time. None of us
are in the clear on this thing.

674
01:02:18,030 --> 01:02:20,407
Chief, we've been taught since
day one to hate these guys...

675
01:02:20,449 --> 01:02:22,576
and now you want us
to work with them?

676
01:02:22,701 --> 01:02:23,535
Shit!

677
01:02:24,036 --> 01:02:26,038
I don't like it either,
but this is our best shot.

678
01:02:29,249 --> 01:02:30,918
I made a promiss to my wife.

679
01:02:31,043 --> 01:02:33,003
That I'd get home without
getting myself killed.

680
01:02:33,128 --> 01:02:34,463
It's a promiss I wanna keep.

681
01:02:40,219 --> 01:02:41,136
It's time.

682
01:03:21,301 --> 01:03:22,344
Okay, listen up.

683
01:03:22,845 --> 01:03:24,221
- Miller.
- Yeah.

684
01:03:24,638 --> 01:03:26,098
You stick with Officer Cremer.

685
01:03:26,306 --> 01:03:27,641
He'll help you to get
a hand along things.

686
01:03:27,850 --> 01:03:30,352
- Okay, Chief.
- And remember, we're metric now.

687
01:03:30,686 --> 01:03:35,899
Ox, I want you to... hmm.
It's Hans, right?

688
01:03:36,191 --> 01:03:37,568
Your name is Hans?

689
01:03:39,027 --> 01:03:39,736
Good.

690
01:03:40,070 --> 01:03:42,781
I want you to follow Hans
to the engine room.

691
01:03:43,198 --> 01:03:47,452
We'll run on one engine only,
I wanna conserve as much diesel as we can.

692
01:03:47,870 --> 01:03:49,955
Go to hell.

693
01:03:51,623 --> 01:03:52,791
Make it happen.

694
01:03:52,875 --> 01:03:54,334
All right. What else?

695
01:03:54,543 --> 01:03:55,502
A planesman.

696
01:03:57,254 --> 01:03:58,297
Abers.

697
01:03:59,548 --> 01:04:00,799
Think you can fly this boat?

698
01:04:03,010 --> 01:04:04,136
Yeah...

699
01:04:04,344 --> 01:04:06,013
All right, Virgil...

700
01:04:06,054 --> 01:04:09,892
- Have we surrendered captain?
- Shut up! This is my boat!

701
01:04:10,100 --> 01:04:13,228
I make the decisions.

702
01:04:15,939 --> 01:04:19,484
We won't make it home, not in this boat.

703
01:04:19,693 --> 01:04:23,447
If you want to die, we all die.

704
01:04:24,573 --> 01:04:29,786
But if you want to make it back home alive
this is our only chance.

705
01:04:40,422 --> 01:04:41,465
Let's continue.

706
01:04:58,482 --> 01:05:00,984
Come on!

707
01:05:12,246 --> 01:05:13,705
Come on, Jerry!
Let's get this over with!

708
01:05:13,747 --> 01:05:14,748
Cooper!

709
01:05:15,249 --> 01:05:17,334
Hang on, all right?
Can't you see the man's praying?

710
01:05:23,715 --> 01:05:24,842
Coming up.

711
01:05:36,645 --> 01:05:39,356
Ahead, half speed.

712
01:05:39,648 --> 01:05:40,899
Ahead one half.

713
01:06:00,711 --> 01:06:03,213
Confirm course.

714
01:06:04,673 --> 01:06:06,884
285.

715
01:06:07,092 --> 01:06:08,552
Bearing 285.

716
01:06:10,637 --> 01:06:11,680
Bearing 285.

717
01:06:17,102 --> 01:06:19,479
All ahead, full.

718
01:06:30,115 --> 01:06:31,366
All ahead full.

719
01:07:05,567 --> 01:07:06,818
Hey, come on.

720
01:07:50,112 --> 01:07:52,197
We must do something.

721
01:08:26,607 --> 01:08:27,733
Nah.

722
01:08:28,483 --> 01:08:31,069
Used to smoke... two packs a day.

723
01:08:31,695 --> 01:08:32,946
Down here...

724
01:08:34,531 --> 01:08:37,868
two packs need
to last you two months.

725
01:08:44,833 --> 01:08:48,587
Nah, I... Okay.

726
01:08:57,262 --> 01:09:01,934
Your men, are good.
You've trained them well.

727
01:09:02,267 --> 01:09:04,353
Oh, it wasn't just me,
but thank you.

728
01:09:09,858 --> 01:09:12,486
Maybe this crazy plan can work.

729
01:09:15,197 --> 01:09:16,448
Maybe.

730
01:09:23,330 --> 01:09:24,456
Captain.

731
01:09:25,707 --> 01:09:26,959
Yes?

732
01:09:28,001 --> 01:09:31,255
Sun's coming up soon,
I suggest we prepare to dive.

733
01:09:33,340 --> 01:09:34,591
Of course.

734
01:09:40,305 --> 01:09:41,890
I've lost them.

735
01:09:43,767 --> 01:09:45,936
Captain has lost
the respect of his men.

736
01:09:46,687 --> 01:09:50,941
Well, they'll respect you later.
When you save their lives.

737
01:09:52,609 --> 01:09:54,403
If the situation were reversed...

738
01:09:55,445 --> 01:09:56,572
Would you do the same?

739
01:09:56,989 --> 01:10:00,325
I'm not a Captain,
I couldn't make that call.

740
01:10:01,368 --> 01:10:02,744
Just pretend.

741
01:10:08,250 --> 01:10:12,129
In the grand scheme of things,
what's one boat?

742
01:10:13,589 --> 01:10:17,217
This war is gonna end. It doesn't
mean we have to end with it.

743
01:10:20,679 --> 01:10:22,347
There's one thing
we haven't discussed.

744
01:10:24,516 --> 01:10:26,935
What do we do if we
come across a German boat?

745
01:10:28,061 --> 01:10:30,147
You mean,
do I throw away our plan?

746
01:10:30,355 --> 01:10:32,566
You go back to being prisoners,
maybe killed?

747
01:10:33,192 --> 01:10:34,651
And we go back to Germany?

748
01:10:35,277 --> 01:10:36,737
Crossed my mind.

749
01:10:37,779 --> 01:10:39,948
What if we come across
an American warship?

750
01:10:40,365 --> 01:10:42,576
What stops you from having
me and my men killed?

751
01:10:49,875 --> 01:10:51,543
These items belong to your men.

752
01:10:59,760 --> 01:11:00,719
Thank you.

753
01:11:01,845 --> 01:11:02,888
You're married?

754
01:11:03,722 --> 01:11:04,681
Yeah.

755
01:11:05,516 --> 01:11:07,392
To the only woman
who would have me.

756
01:11:08,644 --> 01:11:09,478
You?

757
01:11:09,895 --> 01:11:10,729
Yes.

758
01:11:11,438 --> 01:11:12,189
Kids?

759
01:11:13,524 --> 01:11:16,985
Three. I have three girls.

760
01:11:18,654 --> 01:11:20,948
Well, even more reason to
get through this thing alive.

761
01:11:22,616 --> 01:11:24,701
Do you know why I picked up
you and your men?

762
01:11:26,662 --> 01:11:29,915
It's protocol for a sub commander
after sinking an enemy vessel...

763
01:11:30,415 --> 01:11:32,709
to arrest only the Captain and Chief.

764
01:11:33,126 --> 01:11:35,212
Hitler himself made that
a standing order.

765
01:11:35,337 --> 01:11:36,797
If that's the case, then...

766
01:11:37,214 --> 01:11:38,257
why the others?

767
01:11:39,508 --> 01:11:42,010
We hold positions of power,
Mr. Travers.

768
01:11:42,219 --> 01:11:43,971
Men look to us for leadership.

769
01:11:45,013 --> 01:11:46,682
Saving you and your men...

770
01:11:47,516 --> 01:11:51,395
was the first time in all my years
of service I actually felt powerful.

771
01:11:53,564 --> 01:11:56,066
To save a life instead
of taking it away.

772
01:11:57,234 --> 01:11:58,360
That's power.

773
01:11:59,820 --> 01:12:01,405
I'm tired of this war.

774
01:12:02,531 --> 01:12:04,533
This can no longer be about sides.

775
01:12:04,950 --> 01:12:06,410
We are now on the same side.

776
01:12:08,912 --> 01:12:09,746
So...

777
01:12:10,581 --> 01:12:12,541
what happens if, and when...

778
01:12:13,375 --> 01:12:16,003
we come across an American
or a German boat?

779
01:12:17,045 --> 01:12:21,091
We do what we have to, to make sure
that our men come home alive.

780
01:12:23,385 --> 01:12:25,262
August 17th

781
01:12:25,387 --> 01:12:27,764
78 miles from the U.S. Coast

782
01:12:29,141 --> 01:12:31,852
What's going on in here?
Where's Hans?

783
01:12:34,146 --> 01:12:36,440
What is it with you guys?
Lovers' spat?

784
01:12:40,402 --> 01:12:41,528
Help!

785
01:13:05,302 --> 01:13:07,095
What the hell are you doing?

786
01:13:24,071 --> 01:13:25,239
Got him?

787
01:13:30,452 --> 01:13:32,621
Stop at once!

788
01:13:40,879 --> 01:13:43,590
Since first met, never liked.

789
01:13:47,845 --> 01:13:51,098
You will get what you deserve!

790
01:13:51,515 --> 01:13:52,975
All of you!

791
01:14:01,400 --> 01:14:04,862
- What's happening?
- We're being attacked. Hurry!

792
01:14:10,284 --> 01:14:11,410
What's going on, Chief?

793
01:14:17,666 --> 01:14:21,336
No, leave it.
Put down the phone.

794
01:14:21,545 --> 01:14:27,676
- The torpedo will explode! Are you mad?
- You can ask the captain about that.

795
01:14:29,761 --> 01:14:33,640
Go up there. Go!

796
01:14:34,558 --> 01:14:37,269
Put down the gun!

797
01:14:38,103 --> 01:14:40,814
Hands up!

798
01:14:41,023 --> 01:14:44,985
Traitor! I will not let
you surrender the boat.

799
01:14:45,194 --> 01:14:49,990
- Are you going to kill us all?
- I'd rather die with my honor intact!

800
01:14:50,199 --> 01:14:53,660
- No more talk now. The war is over.
- Exactly.

801
01:15:08,967 --> 01:15:10,344
Go to...!

802
01:15:50,801 --> 01:15:52,344
Jonas!

803
01:16:04,147 --> 01:16:06,525
It's your boat now.

804
01:16:08,527 --> 01:16:11,738
Get the crew home.

805
01:16:22,374 --> 01:16:25,002
He sold us out, Chief.
The bastard sold us out.

806
01:16:25,502 --> 01:16:26,753
We're so damn close, Chief.

807
01:16:28,005 --> 01:16:29,256
Do we know what was sent?

808
01:16:30,299 --> 01:16:32,801
At best, our position,
at worse, our situation.

809
01:16:33,760 --> 01:16:34,803
Well, then...

810
01:16:35,637 --> 01:16:36,763
we don't have much time.

811
01:16:36,972 --> 01:16:37,723
All right.

812
01:16:37,931 --> 01:16:38,640
You're in charge.

813
01:16:39,683 --> 01:16:40,642
What do we do?

814
01:16:51,778 --> 01:16:53,780
Periscope depth.
We're going up.

815
01:16:53,989 --> 01:16:55,657
Periscope depth.
Let's take it up.

816
01:16:55,866 --> 01:16:57,117
Let's move guys.

817
01:17:07,544 --> 01:17:08,879
What's our depth?

818
01:17:09,004 --> 01:17:10,756
Straight and level at 12 meters.

819
01:17:11,173 --> 01:17:12,007
Periscope up.

820
01:17:12,132 --> 01:17:13,467
Periscope up!

821
01:17:19,640 --> 01:17:20,974
Hey, hey, I've got something.

822
01:17:21,517 --> 01:17:24,937
Bearing 1-8-0. 2,300 meters.

823
01:17:29,525 --> 01:17:30,734
Damn.

824
01:17:30,776 --> 01:17:32,027
Have a look.

825
01:17:34,738 --> 01:17:35,989
It's an American destroyer.

826
01:17:36,949 --> 01:17:39,117
2,400 meters, Chief.
She's moving away.

827
01:17:39,326 --> 01:17:41,537
Wherever she's going,
she's in one hell of a hurry.

828
01:17:42,162 --> 01:17:44,331
- 2,600 meters.
- Think she saw us?

829
01:17:44,540 --> 01:17:45,791
No, but...

830
01:17:46,625 --> 01:17:48,710
- What?
- She may be the one.

831
01:17:48,919 --> 01:17:50,796
- The one what?
- You think you can reach her?

832
01:17:51,004 --> 01:17:53,006
Yeah, if she's got her ears on,
I can reach her, Chief.

833
01:17:53,215 --> 01:17:54,883
- What do you wanna do?
- We show our hand.

834
01:17:55,717 --> 01:17:56,969
I don't understand "show our hand".

835
01:17:57,010 --> 01:17:58,846
We make radio contact.
We surface.

836
01:17:58,887 --> 01:18:00,973
If we surface, they can attack.

837
01:18:01,014 --> 01:18:02,683
What's he saying?

838
01:18:03,934 --> 01:18:05,602
If we surface,
they blow us out of the water.

839
01:18:05,727 --> 01:18:07,396
They can blow us out
of the water anyway.

840
01:18:10,399 --> 01:18:12,484
It's an American boat.

841
01:18:13,735 --> 01:18:14,570
It's your call.

842
01:18:14,695 --> 01:18:16,572
Blow all ballast.
Prepare to surface!

843
01:18:17,614 --> 01:18:20,117
Prepare to surface.

844
01:18:21,577 --> 01:18:25,205
Whoa! Chief, I think
she's turning around.

845
01:18:25,747 --> 01:18:28,041
- Virgil?
- I'm working on it, Chief!

846
01:18:29,585 --> 01:18:31,044
2,400 meters, Chief.

847
01:18:32,713 --> 01:18:33,547
I got it!

848
01:18:34,590 --> 01:18:35,841
2,300 meters.

849
01:18:37,926 --> 01:18:38,969
C.O.B., you're on!

850
01:18:40,012 --> 01:18:42,723
This is Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers,
of the U.S.S. Swordfish.

851
01:18:43,473 --> 01:18:47,519
I repeat, this is Chief of Boat,
Nathan Travers, of the U.S.S. Swordfish.

852
01:18:48,061 --> 01:18:50,772
I am onboard the U 429
with my surviving crew.

853
01:18:50,814 --> 01:18:53,567
We're in control of this boat.

854
01:18:53,984 --> 01:18:55,861
Sir. Sir, you should hear this.

855
01:18:58,071 --> 01:19:00,782
Hold all fire, we will surface in--

856
01:19:02,242 --> 01:19:03,702
What's going on? What is that?

857
01:19:04,328 --> 01:19:05,370
We're being jammed.

858
01:19:06,079 --> 01:19:07,456
No, no. There's gotta be a mistake.

859
01:19:07,748 --> 01:19:10,375
No, Sir. He said his name was
Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers.

860
01:19:10,876 --> 01:19:13,504
- We've got company.
- Boat in the water, 800 meters and closing.

861
01:19:13,712 --> 01:19:15,047
- Whose is it?
- I can't tell.

862
01:19:20,594 --> 01:19:21,845
It's a German boat.

863
01:19:24,139 --> 01:19:27,976
I fear he sent more than
a simple distress signal.

864
01:19:32,898 --> 01:19:36,735
Ready one and two.
Sink the traitor!

865
01:19:40,822 --> 01:19:43,408
- Another U-boat, Sir.
- Shit!

866
01:19:43,534 --> 01:19:45,619
That's it! Give me CINCLANT, now!

867
01:19:45,702 --> 01:19:46,537
Yes, Sir.

868
01:19:47,788 --> 01:19:49,164
We should stay in the course.

869
01:19:49,373 --> 01:19:50,832
And head straight for the U-boat?

870
01:19:50,916 --> 01:19:53,544
Well, if we go that way,
we run right into that destroyer.

871
01:19:53,627 --> 01:19:55,003
I'll take my chances with the sub.

872
01:19:55,420 --> 01:19:56,129
Why?

873
01:19:56,255 --> 01:19:57,381
'Cause I got you.

874
01:19:57,422 --> 01:19:58,340
Fire!

875
01:20:01,260 --> 01:20:02,094
She's firing.

876
01:20:02,177 --> 01:20:03,220
On whom?

877
01:20:03,554 --> 01:20:04,680
Eel in the water!

878
01:20:05,305 --> 01:20:07,516
Turn to diesel,
turn to battery, and dive!

879
01:20:25,242 --> 01:20:26,159
Battlestations!

880
01:20:26,702 --> 01:20:27,744
GENERAL ALARM

881
01:20:47,556 --> 01:20:48,807
- Depth!
- Yeah!

882
01:20:48,849 --> 01:20:49,725
50 meters!

883
01:20:49,766 --> 01:20:51,101
- Take her to 70.
- No!

884
01:20:51,727 --> 01:20:53,061
That's exactly what he expects.

885
01:20:53,187 --> 01:20:54,938
Trust me, we've played
this game many times.

886
01:20:55,480 --> 01:20:56,815
Take her up.

887
01:20:57,858 --> 01:20:59,234
You heard that, take her up.

888
01:21:14,333 --> 01:21:21,131
All ahead, full. 110 starboard.Torpedoes
3 and 4 reload. Ready one for fire.

889
01:21:21,965 --> 01:21:24,134
Chief, we can't take
much more of this.

890
01:21:24,176 --> 01:21:25,177
We have to fight back.

891
01:21:25,302 --> 01:21:26,553
No! We can do this.

892
01:21:26,637 --> 01:21:28,639
We can do this!
I need damage reports!

893
01:21:28,931 --> 01:21:29,890
Fire!

894
01:21:32,059 --> 01:21:33,435
- Incoming.
- Incoming!

895
01:21:36,647 --> 01:21:39,149
- Shit! What?
Right rudder!

896
01:21:43,237 --> 01:21:45,739
Goddamn, seems all hell's
broken lose out there.

897
01:21:45,948 --> 01:21:48,325
I'd like to know what the hell
is going on, is that too much to ask?

898
01:21:50,619 --> 01:21:51,995
Give it to me.

899
01:21:56,458 --> 01:21:58,544
No, there.

900
01:21:58,752 --> 01:22:03,131
Cease fire! Cease fire! There's Germans
onboard and we're in control.

901
01:22:03,340 --> 01:22:09,096
- Cease fire!
- Prepare for combat.

902
01:22:11,181 --> 01:22:15,644
- Next time we're dead.
- It's our countrymen.

903
01:22:15,853 --> 01:22:19,273
They're going to kill us!

904
01:22:19,314 --> 01:22:21,066
I can't fire my own!

905
01:22:22,025 --> 01:22:24,111
They don't seem to have
a problem firing on you.

906
01:22:26,613 --> 01:22:29,408
I can't make this decision.

907
01:22:30,450 --> 01:22:33,370
You have to.
You're the Captain now.

908
01:22:44,423 --> 01:22:46,508
We've one shot to do this.

909
01:22:46,633 --> 01:22:47,759
How's that?

910
01:22:47,885 --> 01:22:49,428
We have only one torpedo left.

911
01:22:50,804 --> 01:22:52,764
Ready three and four.

912
01:22:53,098 --> 01:22:55,475
Chief, U-boat 220 meters.

913
01:22:55,809 --> 01:22:56,935
She's turning around.

914
01:22:57,269 --> 01:22:58,395
She's right in front of us.

915
01:22:58,437 --> 01:22:59,771
She's getting into firing position.

916
01:22:59,980 --> 01:23:01,857
Destroyer 1,800 meters.

917
01:23:02,149 --> 01:23:05,485
You let me worry about the destroyer,
just stay on that sub!

918
01:23:06,028 --> 01:23:07,571
Our lone torpedo is in the stern...

919
01:23:07,905 --> 01:23:09,656
Ok, on my mark, all ahead, full.

920
01:23:11,325 --> 01:23:14,036
On my command, all ahead, full.

921
01:23:14,453 --> 01:23:16,747
Load rear torpedo tube, uh...

922
01:23:16,872 --> 01:23:18,332
- Six.
- Six.

923
01:23:40,646 --> 01:23:42,189
Ready when you are, Chief.

924
01:23:43,232 --> 01:23:44,691
Ready? Hold on everybody.

925
01:23:44,900 --> 01:23:45,651
Now!

926
01:23:45,734 --> 01:23:46,485
Now!

927
01:23:48,362 --> 01:23:50,656
Dive!

928
01:23:52,533 --> 01:23:54,409
We're right on top of her.

929
01:24:07,756 --> 01:24:08,882
35 meters.

930
01:24:09,007 --> 01:24:11,385
- We need more speed.
- Come on, you piece of junk.

931
01:24:11,510 --> 01:24:12,553
50 meters.

932
01:24:15,764 --> 01:24:16,932
75 meters.

933
01:24:18,058 --> 01:24:20,894
Hold on, Coop. We only got one shot,
let's make it a good one.

934
01:24:20,978 --> 01:24:22,354
I will not disappoint you.

935
01:24:23,063 --> 01:24:24,648
- 90 meters.
- Wait.

936
01:24:25,065 --> 01:24:25,983
Hold on.

937
01:24:28,819 --> 01:24:30,571
- 120 meters!
- Fire!

938
01:24:31,113 --> 01:24:31,947
Fire!

939
01:24:42,666 --> 01:24:43,709
It's a dud, Chief.

940
01:24:44,668 --> 01:24:45,919
Hit but didn't detonate.

941
01:24:53,302 --> 01:24:55,095
Fire!

942
01:25:01,768 --> 01:25:02,477
Fire!

943
01:25:14,781 --> 01:25:15,616
Incoming!

944
01:25:16,033 --> 01:25:17,284
Crash-dive!

945
01:25:31,256 --> 01:25:32,925
- You all right?
- Yeah.

946
01:25:33,550 --> 01:25:34,593
I can't hear.

947
01:26:00,369 --> 01:26:02,246
Hey! Hey! Chief, we're open!
We're open!

948
01:26:02,538 --> 01:26:03,997
Put him on the speaker.

949
01:26:04,414 --> 01:26:05,666
You're on.

950
01:26:05,999 --> 01:26:08,585
This is Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers,
of the U.S.S. Swordfish.

951
01:26:08,710 --> 01:26:11,630
Hold your fire. I repeat,
hold your goddamned fire.

952
01:26:18,929 --> 01:26:22,975
<i>Chief Travers, this is the U.S.S. Logan,
we read you loud and clear.</i>

953
01:26:23,600 --> 01:26:26,019
<i>Chief Travers, glad to hear
you and your men are alive.</i>

954
01:26:27,062 --> 01:26:29,231
This is Captain Samuel Littleton.

955
01:26:29,273 --> 01:26:34,027
You are to secure the enigma decoding
device, and any and all documents.

956
01:26:34,444 --> 01:26:37,364
<i>I'm sending an armed boarding
party over. Do you copy?</i>

957
01:26:38,949 --> 01:26:41,660
We're taking on water fast, Sir.

958
01:26:41,702 --> 01:26:43,829
There's a... there's
a crack in the hull.

959
01:26:44,162 --> 01:26:46,665
We're going down fast,
abandoning ship.

960
01:26:47,916 --> 01:26:49,042
<i>Chief! Chief!</i>

961
01:26:49,376 --> 01:26:51,879
<i>Listen to me, you are to secure
those items.</i>

962
01:26:52,296 --> 01:26:53,755
<i>- That's an order!
- Chief?</i>

963
01:26:55,215 --> 01:26:56,884
We're not sinking.

964
01:26:57,301 --> 01:26:59,052
Yeah, we are. Yeah.

965
01:26:59,803 --> 01:27:02,306
It's a big damn crack.
Runs the length of this hull.

966
01:27:02,347 --> 01:27:03,640
Don't you see it?

967
01:27:07,603 --> 01:27:10,105
Guys, don't you see the crack
going through the hull?

968
01:27:11,148 --> 01:27:11,982
Abers?

969
01:27:13,984 --> 01:27:15,027
Yes, Chief.

970
01:27:15,527 --> 01:27:17,738
- Big crack.
- That's right, a big one.

971
01:27:17,946 --> 01:27:20,115
So let's open all the vents
and scuddle this boat.

972
01:27:20,324 --> 01:27:21,158
Open them, now!

973
01:27:23,785 --> 01:27:25,329
A promiss is a promiss.

974
01:27:35,464 --> 01:27:40,135
U.S.S. Logan, did not copy last
transmission, you're breaking up.

975
01:27:40,260 --> 01:27:42,012
Did not copy last transmission.

976
01:27:43,472 --> 01:27:44,640
Chief!

977
01:27:45,057 --> 01:27:45,682
Dammit.

978
01:28:01,406 --> 01:28:03,200
- All clear, Chief.
- Up you go.

979
01:28:05,494 --> 01:28:07,037
Ho-hoo, we're going home!

980
01:28:09,748 --> 01:28:11,124
After you.

981
01:28:13,001 --> 01:28:15,379
I'm still the highest ranking
officer on this boat.

982
01:28:16,755 --> 01:28:17,673
After you.

983
01:28:49,788 --> 01:28:52,207
<i>- But, Sir, you don't--
- No, Nate, I do.</i>

984
01:28:52,291 --> 01:28:54,710
- I understand entirely what you're saying.
- But, Sir--

985
01:28:54,793 --> 01:28:57,004
I just hope that you can appreciate
that, as prisoners of war...

986
01:28:57,045 --> 01:28:58,755
it makes the situation
somewhat delicate.

987
01:28:58,797 --> 01:29:01,675
Sir, had it not been for their
actions, six American lives...

988
01:29:01,800 --> 01:29:03,760
including my own,
would have been lost.

989
01:29:03,886 --> 01:29:06,597
But they're Germans.
And we're still at war here.

990
01:29:16,481 --> 01:29:18,150
I'm sorry, Nate.
My hands are tied.

991
01:29:18,483 --> 01:29:19,610
It is impossible.

992
01:29:22,654 --> 01:29:23,906
I hope you understand that.

993
01:29:29,119 --> 01:29:29,953
Nate.

994
01:29:32,456 --> 01:29:34,208
I realize what these
men did for you.

995
01:29:34,416 --> 01:29:36,627
And I'm gonna do anything
in my power to see to it...

996
01:29:36,710 --> 01:29:38,712
that they're as well taken
care of as possible.

997
01:29:39,963 --> 01:29:40,881
Thank you, Sir.

998
01:29:45,594 --> 01:29:47,888
I was dead, several times.

999
01:29:49,556 --> 01:29:50,807
I...

1000
01:29:52,893 --> 01:29:55,395
I gave up all hope
of ever coming home.

1001
01:29:57,064 --> 01:29:59,233
I wish I could have
been there for you.

1002
01:30:01,860 --> 01:30:05,697
You were. In more ways than one.

1003
01:30:09,576 --> 01:30:11,328
I don't know what
I'd do without you.

1004
01:30:14,998 --> 01:30:16,041
What?

1005
01:30:16,542 --> 01:30:18,752
You think you can get
rid of me that easily?

1006
01:30:51,159 --> 01:30:55,873
Camp Cooke, California
German P.O.W. Compound

1007
01:31:06,925 --> 01:31:08,260
Thank you.

1008
01:31:09,219 --> 01:31:10,345
Hello.

1009
01:31:12,431 --> 01:31:14,725
This is my wife, Rachel.
She wanted to meet you.

1010
01:31:16,393 --> 01:31:17,561
It's my pleasure.

1011
01:31:18,687 --> 01:31:21,315
None of us would have made it
had it not been for your husband.

1012
01:31:24,318 --> 01:31:25,694
You've a brave man there.

1013
01:31:26,403 --> 01:31:28,197
He says the same about you.

1014
01:31:32,576 --> 01:31:35,913
A telegram...
was sent to my house...

1015
01:31:37,164 --> 01:31:39,541
it said that my husband's
boat was missing.

1016
01:31:40,083 --> 01:31:41,960
They had lost contact...

1017
01:31:42,169 --> 01:31:43,837
and the crew was presumed dead.

1018
01:31:47,883 --> 01:31:49,051
Thank you.

1019
01:31:56,975 --> 01:31:58,852
I'll let you two talk.

1020
01:32:01,563 --> 01:32:02,898
I'll be right there.

1021
01:32:08,111 --> 01:32:09,279
She's beautiful.

1022
01:32:10,197 --> 01:32:12,908
I can't take credit for that,
but... thanks.

1023
01:32:17,412 --> 01:32:18,455
Here.

1024
01:32:20,207 --> 01:32:21,375
My cigarettes!

1025
01:32:22,835 --> 01:32:24,169
How did you get these?

1026
01:32:24,211 --> 01:32:25,963
You don't wanna know.

1027
01:32:26,672 --> 01:32:27,714
Thank you.

1028
01:32:28,465 --> 01:32:29,508
How are the men?

1029
01:32:31,593 --> 01:32:33,679
The food is good, clean rooms...

1030
01:32:35,347 --> 01:32:37,850
The Captain was unrealistic
in his demands.

1031
01:32:39,184 --> 01:32:41,603
I suspect he even knew
this'd be our fate.

1032
01:32:43,355 --> 01:32:45,023
He didn't want you
to end up here.

1033
01:32:47,442 --> 01:32:48,902
He wanted us to live.

1034
01:32:51,822 --> 01:32:53,156
He succeeded.

1035
01:32:54,199 --> 01:32:55,576
We succeeded.

1036
01:32:57,452 --> 01:33:00,038
- The war will be over soon.
- Yeah.

1037
01:33:03,375 --> 01:33:06,003
We will return home.

1038
01:33:11,008 --> 01:33:15,053
If that torpedo had detonated...

1039
01:33:15,888 --> 01:33:17,973
I... I don't know.

1040
01:33:18,515 --> 01:33:19,641
I know.

1041
01:33:24,563 --> 01:33:26,106
Good to see you, my friend.

