At the outbreak of World War II
Germany increased its U-boat
production by 1000%.
Mass producing 17 new U-boats a month.
Hitler knew the key to winning
the war in Europe...
was to control the Atlantic.
And control it, they would.
By the end of 1942,
German U-boats working in groups...
known as "wolfpacks",
sunk over 1,000 allied ships.
This success gave Germany
a decisive advantage.
They were winning the war,
and if this trend continued...
all of Europe would fall.
IN ENEMY HANDS
In January 1943, President Roosevelt,
and Prime Minister Churchill...
declared that stopping the U-boats
would be their top priority.
With the US fully committed to the war,
and new advances in technology...
the allies strike back.
After losing an average
of only five U-Boats a month...
Germany suffers its greatest losses
in what would be known as Black May.
That month, allies sink
and destroy 41 U-Boats.
8 out of every 10 U-boat sailors died.
The rain of the wolfpack was
rapidly drawing to a close.
Dept. of the Navy
June 3, 1943
I've known you your whole life.
I'm not going to embarrass you
with the details.
Your father was a good man.
A great soldier.
Thank you, Sir.
It's out of respect for him that
I just assume you didn't do this.
We're not here to chase ghosts.
Our job is to pursue an enemy...
and defeat it.
You certain that's what you wanna do?
Absolutely.
When do you ship out?
In two weeks.
Monday after next...
we'll be ready.
Have you met your C.O.B. yet?
No Sir, Nate Travers, not yet.
Nathan Travers, a good man.
You might actually learn something from him
if you're interested in that sort of thing.
- Give 'em hell, Commander.
- Oh, I plan to, Sir.
- That's an order.
- Yes, Sir.
I'm just waiting for some things
hanging on the line to dry.
And your mom wants you
to call her before you go.
Don't go without calling her because I'm
the one who's gonna have to deal with it...
everyday until you get back.
I love her, but she's your mother.
You deal with her.
I'm gonna take this.
I'm taking this with me.
I'll stick it right above my bunk.
It'll be the last thing
I see when I go to bed...
and the first thing
I see when I wake.
Oh, dammit.
Why do you go and do that?
- What?
- You know what.
Now you got me started,
and I can't stop once I get started.
Sorry.
You're not sorry.
I love you.
- Promise me something Nate Travers.
- Anything.
Promise me you won't get yourself
killed trying to be a hero.
You think you can get rid
of me that easily?
No, I'm serious.
Honey, don't start that.
Promise me you'll come home.
I promise.
Swear it.
I swear... I'll come home to you.
Okay.
Two Months later
August 2nd 1943
Mid-Atlantic Convoy Route
600 miles off the U.S. Coast
- Heinrich!
- Turn off the air-intake!
- Stubborn bastards, those Americans.
- All ahead, 15 degrees starboard.
- They're leaving.
Periscope depth. We'll teach them
who the stubborn ones are.
- 286 degrees, 15 knots.
- Distance: 2,700 meters.
Ready tubes 3 and 4.
Ready.
- 112 degrees.
- Torpedo ready?
3 and 4 ready.
Ready.
Fire.
Yes! We got her!
We got her!
- A good yankee is a dead yankee.
- We dive.
U.S.S. Swordfish
Balao-Class Attack Submarine
- All ahead two thirds.
Make ready to dive.
Shut 'em down, we're switching
to battery power!
Come on! Move it! Let's go!
Knock it off, come on!
And get your hands off your pecker!
- Giddy up!
- Yeah, yeah!
- Green board, pressure in the boat.
- Take her to 60.
Take her to 60, five degree down-angle.
60 feet, five degree down-angle, aye.
Fuck!
60 feet, Sir.
- Zero bubble?
- Zero bubble, Sir.
Zero bubble at 60, Sir.
Scope up.
Scope up!
Time?
64 seconds.
Prepare to surface, exercise complete.
Chief, in my quarters.
Periscope going down!
Not again!
Maybe I should just go for a swim.
Can I join you?
- Now, Chief.
- Be right there, Sir.
You look like crap,
you should see the medic.
There's a lot of things I should do.
Three months. Three months in the water
and the men become compleasant and sloppy.
If you were in my shoes,
would that trouble you?
Yes, Sir.
Today's dive time was 64 seconds.
3 days ago it was 58 seconds.
6 seconds, Chief.
We're in the Atlantic now...
we can't afford to give the
Germans a six second advantage.
I'll speak to the men.
See that you do.
Chief.
You may have more experience...
but I've been preparing for this for
a long time and I do know what I'm doing.
I don't doubt that, Sir.
So, what's on your mind, Chief?
Let's have it.
I was thinking about
the men's morale.
They're frustrated by these
constant exercises...
and it's clearly not helping
their performance.
What is it? You and the men are
disappointed we haven't seen any action?
No, it's not that.
Then what is it, Chief?
What is it?
I was thinking...
to keep spirits up,
maybe we could...
give 'em a little more latitude...
little less exercise.
That's not your decision.
And I've made mine.
The crew's performance is
not what it needs to be.
And the drills will
continue per my orders.
Understood?
Aye, Sir.
Is that all?
Yeah, that's all.
You're dismissed.
- How is Heinrich?
- Concussion. He'll be okay.
Good, I'll check in on him later.
- Good move.
- You always win anyway.
- Do you know what your problem is?
- My queen is in a bad position.
You always underestimate yourself.
You should have been a commander yourself,
instead of hanging around with me.
I thought that you would be more cheerful,
after we sunk that cruiser.
We sink one, they sink 30.
We're lucky that the torpedo exploded.
- The Americans joined the war.
- It didn't go so well last night.
It'll all be better soon.
With a little luck...
With a little luck,
we'll make it home in one piece.
- What is it, Bauer?
- Look at this.
Always when you least expect it.
- How many moves do I have left?
- Two.
Check...
...mate.
Good, I hate chess.
I get worse in every new move.
- Sorry to disturb you, Captain. Mr. Cremer.
- We're finished.
We got a message...
from home.
Give it to me.
Jonas... what does it say?
I need a moment alone.
They bombed Hamburg. The school his
daughters attend is completely destroyed.
No survivors.
All right, don't be stingy.
Thanks.
How many dress rehearsals is that?
Twenty seven, twenty eight maybe?
I don't know... I don't care.
I figured as much from you.
I mean...
It's not like we've
never done it before?
I just don't get why he
doesn't find some krautsto pester...
instead of jerking
our chains and fuckin' us.
Yeah, I mean, what's he trying to prove?
The least he could do is, whenever
it's not real, he could tell us.
So we don't shit
our pants everytime.
That would explain the complaints
I've been getting from laundry services.
Chief.
The reason we've conducted twenty
seven exercises Mr. Miller...
is for you to become so accustomed
to your task, so masterful in your skills...
that you do not shit yourself when
this boat comes under attack.
I understand, Chief.
Wanna talk some trash? Save it for
those nazi sons of bitches...
crawling up and down our East Coast
looking to blow us out of the water.
Anyone seen the XO?
Oh, yeah. I think I saw
him go into the head, Chief.
You're all right in there, Sir?
Fine, Chief.
I'll be out in a minute.
U 281
Two days later
290 miles northeast of Bermuda
British Merchant Vessel Achilles
Torpedoes... Fire.
How do you lose an entire convoy?
Increase speed to 18 knots.
The Achille's last
radio contact, here.
That's where the closest allied
vessel had been ordered to take a look.
There's been no report of U-Boat
activity in that area for several weeks.
That does not mean
they're not there.
Chief...
no drill this time.
I'll inform the men.
Confirm coordinates, let CINCLANT
know that we're on our way.
Aye, Captain.
We have to surface.
Jonas, it's night.
- Yes, prepare for surfacing.
- Ready for surfacing.
Who's in there?
I've been waiting for too long.
Hey, open up.
- Oh, shit!
- Who is it?
The XO, let's get him
to the medic. Come on.
Flu?
Not sure.
Could be a reaction
to something he ate.
How long have you
been feeling like this?
A week maybe, since Panama.
Hey, Chief. The Captain needs you.
I think it's important.
I need to come too.
- You're not going anywhere.
- You wish you could order me around.
I can.
Keep the liquids coming,
and let me know of any changes.
Yes, Sir.
There's Cooper at your service.
We need to keep him here,
away from the rest of the crew.
Until I have a chance to check on the others
to see if they have any of the same symptoms.
Is that serious?
It could be meningococcus.
English?
It's a form of meningitis,
it's highly contagious...
and in some cases it can be fatal.
We couldn't stop the bleeding
in the brain.
How old was he? 18?
Heinrich wanted to show
what he could do.
From the first day.
You couldn't do anything.
You couldn't stop it.
No...
That's the problem.
Anything?
No, Sir.
Chief, glad you could join us.
Put the men on full alert.
Yes, Sir.
Where's the XO?
In a sick room, Sir,
he's taken ill.
Have Mr. Goodman standing by.
Sir, the XO can barely stand.
He's got a rash, and the med--
Chief, we're in hostile waters, the XO
is breathing, I want him at his post.
Aye, Sir.
U 821
Two days later
Captain...
Glenn Miller?
Good.
That's music by Glenn Miller,
from the spacious Café Rouge...
of the Hotel Pennsylvania
in New York City.
Where the young at heart come from
far and near to watch and hear...
the orchestra that has given America
some of the most beautiful sounds ever.
Captain!
Captain! I've got something
at 3-4-0, 4,000 feet.
Sounds... sounds like music.
You dirty dog!
Mr. Goodman, set torpedo
depth at 10 feet.
Set torpedo depth 10 feet.
- Depth set!
- Depth is set!
Ready tubes one and two.
Ready bow tubes one and two.
Come on.
- Gyro angle?
- 349.
Gyro angle 349.
- Set?
- Set.
Fire one.
Fire one!
Fire two.
Fire two!
- Torpedoes!
- Damn!
All ahead full. Dive!
They were hit, Sir,
but are still up.
Goddamn it! Prepare to attack again.
Prepare to attack again!
Set torpedo depth to 12 feet.
- Depth is set!
Ready bow tubes three and four.
Where the hell is he?
Two subs.
One of ours, the other is American.
- Distance?
- 4,000 meters.
Angle? Angle?
351.
351, are we set? Mr. Goodman, set?
Gyro angle 351.
Tube three ready.
Tube three ready!
Set!
Fire three!
- She's right in front of us.
- Distance 400 meters. Fire!
Captain!
- She's cooked alright! Well done!
- Yeah!
Good work, boys! Good work!
We got 'em!
How does it feel to have
your cherry popped?
- Oh, God! Even better than the first time.
- First time?
That's what it's all about, all right?
He's dead.
Screw in the water!
Right full rudder
all ahead flank, now! Move!
Right full rudder all ahead flank.
I need damage reports, Chief!
Damage reports!
Mr. Right, I need damage reports!
It's no use, he's gone.
- Miller!
- Yes, Sir!
Blow bow bouyancy. Surface!
Surface! Surface!
Help me!
- Who's in there?
- Nobody!
They're all dead in there,
Chief. Come on!
Listing 10 degrees port, sir.
Forward torpedo and forward
barrack taking on water, Sir!
We've lost the engines, Captain!
We're not gonna make it,
Captain. She's going down.
- Captain, you gotta--
- Don't tell me what I have to do, Chief.
I know what I have to do.
This is your captain speaking...
Abandon ship.
I repeat, abandon ship.
Captain! There's nothing more you can do!
She's going down, come on!
Tend to the others, Chief.
That's an order.
Come on, Chief!
We gotta hurry!
Come on. Captain,
we gotta get out of here!
- Not till the crew's out.
- No. Listen to me.
They're all dead. This is a casket.
We gotta get out of here.
You made me love you...
I didn't wanna do it...
And all the time you knew it...
I guess you always knew it...
You made me happy...
This has been the best
thanksgiving ever.
I do get holidays.
You just wait till Christmas.
Kiss me.
Follow me. Now!
Come.
Move!
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
It's okay, Captain. You got it.
You got it.
Move it!
You're not scared of a few Americans?
I'm worried about supplies.
We'll be at the supply vessel in a week.
We have enough supplies.
There's nothing to worry about.
When we get there, we'll turn
over the Americans for interrogation.
Klaus, could you give us a moment?
As you wish.
What is it?
You said it yourself - the war is ending.
Why risk everything now?
Make sure my orders are followed, Ludwig.
Yes, Captain.
- Everybody all right?
- Yeah.
I don't know about you guys,
but I don't wanna go to Germany.
You know what they do
to prisoners in Germany?
They torture them, and then
they gas them or they burn them alive!
Shut up!
Shut up.
That's what those officers
in Panama said they did...
to all those jews!
They just cooked them!
- They cooked them like meat.
- Calm down, Miller.
That's an order, sailor.
We gotta hold it together.
We panic now,
we're as good as dead.
They were supposed to
just let us drown, Captain.
Why didn't they just
let us fucking drown?
Chief...
We're going to break up
into three groups.
I'll head up a team to
search for food and supplies.
I want you to radio
CINCLANT our position.
Find out what our orders are.
Tell them we contacted the enemy.
Understand? Understand?
But, Captain...
Take it easy... easy.
Come here!
Come on.
I got it.
You should have let me
die on my boat, Chief.
die on my boat.
Is he dead?
What are we gonna do Chief?
What are you looking at me for?
The captain--
The Captain ain't the Captain no more.
He's gone off his mind, Chief.
He ain't gonna be able
to help us now.
- Why the hell did he bring them onboard?
- There are rules in war.
Not when they just sunk one of ours.
The entire crew was killed.
- Our Comrades!
- Are you questioning him?
I don't doubt the Captain's
orders. Neither should you.
Mr. Cremer, he puts us in danger.
That's what war is about.
I counted at least 20 of them pricks.
There's probably twice that many.
Yeah, and they got guns too.
Eat.
They don't understand a word.
Here you go.
I hope you like it.
Piss off, you damn kraut!
Hey, come on.
Leave it.
What the hell is this?
My guess is... pig balls and
chicken guts if we're lucky.
Give me one for the Captain.
How do we know they
didn't poison it, Chief?
didn't do that?
Cause if they wanted us dead,
they would have let us drown.
Besides, we're gonna need all
the strenght we can get, so...
Eat up.
You should try to eat something.
You said that Goodman had a rash.
What did the medic think it was?
Meningitis.
What did it look like?
I want you to keep this
between us, Chief.
I don't wanna startle
the men, understand?
Hey!
Hey, someone's coming!
Who is of highest rank?
- It's alright.
- It's okay, okay, okay!
What's your position?
Chief of Boat.
What happened to your Captain,
Chief of Boat?
He didn't make it.
He went down with the ship?
Yeah, he did.
These are your men.
They do as you tell them,
and we do not have a problem.
What's the matter with him?
He was injured, trying to get out.
He'll be needing medical assistance.
You'll split in half.
Smaller groups, more comfortable...
for all of us.
Chain them, and give him medicine.
- Let him die.
- Do as I say!
Take his handcuffs off.
Mind your fucking head.
For him.
How can anybody sleep like that?
Got clobbered in the head,
probably has a concussion.
Well, should we wake him first?
Shit, I wouldn't.
Oh, man. Look at that.
Hey, Right, don't touch that.
Right, don't fucking touch it!
Why? Why not?
Shit. Guys, that's not a wound,
that's a rash.
- What?
- My sister got it when she was a kid.
Meningitis I think,
I don't know exacly.
She got it from
the water in our well.
How long does it last?
About a week.
Okay, so how do you treat it?
I got a bunch of stuff...
You don't, Right.
So, what, it just goes away?
No.
- You said it lasted a week.
- Yeah, I said about a week.
And then we buried her.
Christ, Abers!
Abers, is it contagious?
Well, I didn't get it.
But, yeah.
Oh, great! Great!
The krauts won't kill us,
the Captain will.
What are you looking at, rat?
What are you doing?!
Not only are you eating our food,
I also have to look at you.
- What is he saying?
- Oh, come on! What the hell are you doing?
That's enough.
Are you all right?
Three days later
August 10th
450 miles off the U.S. Coast
I hurt everywhere,
and it's difficult to breathe.
I'll give you something for the pain.
Get some rest.
You'll be well soon.
- How many?
- Eight sick. Others have the symptoms.
Captain, come here, please.
We're almost there,
but the supply vessel isn't here.
- What do you mean?
- They aren't answering our radio signals.
- Are we in the right position?
- Yes.
Damn! Up periscope.
An American destroyer. Damn!
- Distance?
- 2,500 meters.
2,500.
Captain?
What's your command?
We must act.
- How many torpedoes do we have?
- Two front, one stern.
Ready one and two.
Set torpedo depth at 5 meters.
Chief, they prepare to attack.
We gotta do something.
1800 meters.
Otto, come here.
- Torpedoes ready.
- Ready.
Now!
Captain, torpedoes ready.
- The Americans escaped!
- I told you it would happen!
- Stop the launch!
- I'm on it!
We've got company!
Ox, a little help!
How are you gonna know
which one is which?
I was born to fire
torpedoes, don't matter...
if it's German, jap or
portuguese for that matter.
Do it fast!
Got it! I got it!
Cooper!
No!
Stop! Stop it right now!
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
Right, full rudder.
Take evasive action.
Get me a location on that thing.
Dive!
Depth: stern minus 20, bow minus 30.
- Quick!
- Everybody to the front!
Hurry! Quick!
What was that?
50 meters.
Fool... You've killed us all.
If you pull that trigger now, you might just
pin a bull's eye on the side of this boat.
Captain, is it over?
It hasn't even started.
Back!
Don't shoot! Captain! Captain!
Captain! Captain!
Captain's dead.
- We have to get rid of the Americans.
- Here? A mass execution?
I want to get rid of them as well. But we
can't get rid of the bodies.
I can live with the smell.
- What is it, Bauer?
- There's something you have to see.
Wilhelm was the first to
get the symptoms. Here.
The Americans are like The Plague.
And we have them here onboard.
Look at him!
- What is it?
- I'm not sure.
A medic thought it might
be meningitis.
Contagious?
Very.
Is there a cure?
I'm not a doctor.
- The crew must not know.
- What? But the Americans...
That is an order!
And you will obey.
Everybody must wear the breathing apparatus,
until we can surface.
- The Americans can't have any.
- Everybody must wear the breathing apparatus.
Yes, Captain.
How long are we staying down here?
As long as we can.
Abers.
- I'm here.
- When you get out...
don't you tell my mother
that I died this way.
Tell her that I went quick.
No pain.
August 13th
380 miles off the U.S. Coast
Don't quit!
Don't quit on me, Nate.
Rachel.
I've never seen you
like this before.
My men are dying.
We're near the end.
I can't accept that.
I'm sorry.
Never be sorry.
What am I supposed to do, hun?
You're supposed to come home to me.
How?
I don't have any fight left.
I don't--
I'm not going to be one
of those wives, Nate Travers.
I'm not back there waiting for some
telegram to tell me that my husband is dead.
I won't let you do that to me.
You made me a promise.
Oh, God, I miss you.
Then come back to me.
- Is she still there?
- Perhaps.
"Perhaps" is not good enough.
- Ready to surface.
- We'll be an easy target.
What would you prefer?
Dying here or up there?
At least we have a chance up there.
Surface.
We're clear!
Transmit emergency signal.
It's fresh air.
The hatch is open.
It means we lost our navy.
Family?
Yeah. That's my family.
That's Vivian, and...
and Ol' Danny Jr.
- Looks like me, huh?
- Give it a rest, will ya?
They don't care.
They don't care about your family.
Is this your son?
Yes, my son. Peter... Jr.
Never forget this is the enemy.
Take care of your own men.
Out.
Eat!
And?
Every second is precious.
We must do something about the Americans.
Take off his handcuffs.
That is all.
Your men, they follow
your orders, do they not?
They do.
Would they follow mine?
I've lost two thirds of my men.
Your navy is not far away...
and our distress calls have failed,
I've no option left.
Between all of us we have just enough
hands to make this boat operational.
If you and your men join my men,
we might have a chance.
You want us to help you?
I want you to help yourselves.
And if we refuse?
We all die.
That he's speaking to them - that alone
is treason.
You've seen how he behaves.
He's insane.
This is insane.
- What do we do?
- I refuse to obey him.
I hope
that you will do the same.
What exactly are you proposing?
Our diesel is nearly exhausted
and the fuel line has been damaged.
But if we're efficient,
we should be able to make 500...
maybe 600 kilometers.
You can't really expect my men
to help you deliver them into custody.
We travel submerged by day,
making up time on top at night.
If my calculations are correct...
we should be able...
to make landfall in three days.
UNITED STATES
Jonas!
You're serious?
Once we're close to shore
we deploy the life-rafts...
we evacuate the men and...
we scuddle the boat.
You understand I will not allow my boat
to fall into your country's hands.
In return for this, I surrender myself to
you and ask for consideration for my men.
- You can't just surrender.
- It's my duty to save the men.
Don't surrender us to them!
- We can manage without them.
- If only we could.
Ludwig!
I need your hand, Sir.
I can't make any guarantees
once you're in US custody.
I understand.
All I ask for is that you report
to your superiors what I've done.
So, when this war is over,
they save my men like I saved yours.
I'll need to speak to my men first.
All of them.
You've two minutes.
You want us to team-up
with the Jerries?
I don't like it, Chief... no siree.
I'm with them on this one.
I don't trust these kraut bastards...
as far as I could throw 'em.
Why don't, why don't
we just wait 'em up?
They're dropping like flies...
we wait until enough...
of them are infected and
then we take the boat.
Why not?
How long are you gonna wait?
Romano's already dead.
How long before you are infected?
We don't have time. None of us
are in the clear on this thing.
Chief, we've been taught since
day one to hate these guys...
and now you want us
to work with them?
Shit!
I don't like it either,
but this is our best shot.
I made a promise to my wife.
That I'd get home without
getting myself killed.
It's a promise I wanna keep.
It's time.
Okay, listen up.
- Miller.
- Yeah.
You stick with Officer Cremer.
He'll help you to get
a hand along things.
- Okay, Chief.
- And remember, we're metric now.
Ox, I want you to... hmm.
It's Hans, right?
Your name is Hans?
Good.
I want you to follow Hans
to the engine room.
We'll run on one engine only,
I wanna conserve as much diesel as we can.
Go to hell.
Make it happen.
All right. What else?
A planesman.
Abers.
Think you can fly this boat?
Yeah...
All right, Virgil...
- Have we surrendered captain?
- Shut up! This is my boat!
I make the decisions.
We won't make it home, not in this boat.
If you want to die, we all die.
But if you want to make it back home alive
this is our only chance.
Let's continue.
Come on!
Come on, Jerry!
Let's get this over with!
Cooper!
Hang on, all right?
Can't you see the man's praying?
Coming up.
Ahead, half speed.
Ahead one half.
Confirm course.
285.
Bearing 285.
All ahead, full.
All ahead full.
Hey, come on.
We must do something.
Nah.
Used to smoke... two packs a day.
Down here...
two packs need
to last you two months.
Nah, I... Okay.
Your men, are good.
You've trained them well.
Oh, it wasn't just me,
but thank you.
Maybe this crazy plan can work.
Maybe.
Captain.
Yes?
Sun's coming up soon,
I suggest we prepare to dive.
Of course.
I've lost them.
Captain has lost
the respect of his men.
Well, they'll respect you later.
When you save their lives.
If the situation were reversed...
Would you do the same?
I'm not a Captain,
I couldn't make that call.
Just pretend.
In the grand scheme of things,
what's one boat?
This war is gonna end. It doesn't
mean we have to end with it.
There's one thing
we haven't discussed.
What do we do if we
come across a German boat?
You mean,
do I throw away our plan?
You go back to being prisoners,
maybe killed?
And we go back to Germany?
Crossed my mind.
What if we come across
an American warship?
What stops you from having
me and my men killed?
These items belong to your men.
Thank you.
You're married?
Yeah.
To the only woman
who would have me.
You?
Yes.
Kids?
Three. I have three girls.
Well, even more reason to
get through this thing alive.
Do you know why I picked up
you and your men?
It's protocol for a sub commander
after sinking an enemy vessel...
to arrest only the Captain and Chief.
Hitler himself made that
a standing order.
If that's the case, then...
why the others?
We hold positions of power,
Mr. Travers.
Men look to us for leadership.
Saving you and your men...
was the first time in all my years
of service I actually felt powerful.
To save a life instead
of taking it away.
That's power.
I'm tired of this war.
This can no longer be about sides.
We are now on the same side.
So...
what happens if, and when...
we come across an American
or a German boat?
We do what we have to, to make sure
that our men come home alive.
August 17th
78 miles from the U.S. Coast
What's going on in here?
Where's Hans?
What is it with you guys?
Lovers' spat?
Help!
What the hell are you doing?
Got him?
Stop at once!
Since first met, never liked.
You will get what you deserve!
All of you!
- What's happening?
- We're being attacked. Hurry!
What's going on, Chief?
No, leave it.
Put down the phone.
- The torpedo will explode! Are you mad?
- You can ask the captain about that.
Go up there. Go!
Put down the gun!
Hands up!
Traitor! I will not let
you surrender the boat.
- Are you going to kill us all?
- I'd rather die with my honor intact!
- No more talk now. The war is over.
- Exactly.
Go to...!
Jonas!
It's your boat now.
Get the crew home.
He sold us out, Chief.
The bastard sold us out.
We're so damn close, Chief.
Do we know what was sent?
At best, our position,
at worse, our situation.
Well, then...
we don't have much time.
All right.
You're in charge.
What do we do?
Periscope depth.
We're going up.
Let's take it up.
Let's move guys.
What's our depth?
Straight and level at 12 meters.
Periscope up.
Periscope up!
Hey, hey, I've got something.
Bearing 1-8-0. 2,300 meters.
Damn.
Have a look.
It's an American destroyer.
2,400 meters, Chief.
She's moving away.
Wherever she's going,
she's in one hell of a hurry.
- 2,600 meters.
- Think she saw us?
No, but...
- What?
- She may be the one.
- The one what?
- You think you can reach her?
Yeah, if she's got her ears on,
I can reach her, Chief.
- What do you wanna do?
- We show our hand.
I don't understand "show our hand".
We make radio contact.
We surface.
If we surface, they can attack.
What's he saying?
If we surface,
they blow us out of the water.
They can blow us out
of the water anyway.
It's an American boat.
It's your call.
Blow all ballast.
Prepare to surface!
Prepare to surface.
Whoa! Chief, I think
she's turning around.
- Virgil?
- I'm working on it, Chief!
2,400 meters, Chief.
I got it!
2,300 meters.
C.O.B., you're on!
This is Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers,
of the U.S.S. Swordfish.
I repeat, this is Chief of Boat,
Nathan Travers, of the U.S.S. Swordfish.
I am onboard the U 429
with my surviving crew.
We're in control of this boat.
Sir. Sir, you should hear this.
Hold all fire, we will surface in--
What's going on? What is that?
We're being jammed.
No, no. There's gotta be a mistake.
No, Sir. He said his name was
Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers.
- We've got company.
- Boat in the water, 800 meters and closing.
- Whose is it?
- I can't tell.
It's a German boat.
I fear he sent more than
a simple distress signal.
Ready one and two.
Sink the traitor!
- Another U-boat, Sir.
- Shit!
That's it! Give me CINCLANT, now!
Yes, Sir.
We should stay in the course.
And head straight for the U-boat?
Well, if we go that way,
we run right into that destroyer.
I'll take my chances with the sub.
Why?
'Cause I got you.
Fire!
She's firing.
On whom?
Eel in the water!
Turn to diesel,
turn to battery, and dive!
Battlestations!
GENERAL ALARM
- Depth!
- Yeah!
50 meters!
- Take her to 70.
- No!
That's exactly what he expects.
Trust me, we've played
this game many times.
Take her up.
You heard that, take her up.
All ahead, full. 110 starboard.Torpedoes
3 and 4 reload. Ready one for fire.
Chief, we can't take
much more of this.
We have to fight back.
No! We can do this.
We can do this!
I need damage reports!
Fire!
- Incoming.
- Incoming!
- Shit! What?
Right rudder!
Goddamn, seems all hell's
broken lose out there.
I'd like to know what the hell
is going on, is that too much to ask?
Give it to me.
No, there.
Cease fire! Cease fire! There's Germans
onboard and we're in control.
- Cease fire!
- Prepare for combat.
- Next time we're dead.
- It's our countrymen.
They're going to kill us!
I can't fire my own!
They don't seem to have
a problem firing on you.
I can't make this decision.
You have to.
You're the Captain now.
We've one shot to do this.
How's that?
We have only one torpedo left.
Ready three and four.
Chief, U-boat 220 meters.
She's turning around.
She's right in front of us.
She's getting into firing position.
Destroyer 1,800 meters.
You let me worry about the destroyer,
just stay on that sub!
Our lone torpedo is in the stern...
Ok, on my mark, all ahead, full.
On my command, all ahead, full.
Load rear torpedo tube, uh...
- Six.
Ready when you are, Chief.
Ready? Hold on everybody.
Now!
Dive!
We're right on top of her.
35 meters.
- We need more speed.
- Come on, you piece of junk.
50 meters.
75 meters.
Hold on, Coop. We only got one shot,
let's make it a good one.
I will not disappoint you.
- 90 meters.
- Wait.
Hold on.
- 120 meters!
- Fire!
Fire!
It's a dud, Chief.
Hit but didn't detonate.
Fire!
Incoming!
Crash-dive!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I can't hear.
Hey! Hey! Chief, we're open!
We're open!
Put him on the speaker.
You're on.
This is Chief of Boat, Nathan Travers,
of the U.S.S. Swordfish.
Hold your fire. I repeat,
hold your goddamned fire.
Chief Travers, this is the U.S.S. Logan,
we read you loud and clear.
Chief Travers, glad to hear
you and your men are alive.
This is Captain Samuel Littleton.
You are to secure the enigma decoding
device, and any and all documents.
I'm sending an armed boarding
party over. Do you copy?
We're taking on water fast, Sir.
There's a... there's
a crack in the hull.
We're going down fast,
abandoning ship.
Chief! Chief!
Listen to me, you are to secure
those items.
- That's an order!
- Chief?
We're not sinking.
Yeah, we are. Yeah.
It's a big damn crack.
Runs the length of this hull.
Don't you see it?
Guys, don't you see the crack
going through the hull?
Abers?
Yes, Chief.
- Big crack.
- That's right, a big one.
So let's open all the vents
and scuddle this boat.
Open them, now!
A promise is a promise.
U.S.S. Logan, did not copy last
transmission, you're breaking up.
Did not copy last transmission.
Chief!
Dammit.
- All clear, Chief.
- Up you go.
Ho-hoo, we're going home!
After you.
I'm still the highest ranking
officer on this boat.
After you.
- But, Sir, you don't--
- No, Nate, I do.
- I understand entirely what you're saying.
- But, Sir--
I just hope that you can appreciate
that, as prisoners of war...
it makes the situation
somewhat delicate.
Sir, had it not been for their
actions, six American lives...
including my own,
would have been lost.
But they're Germans.
And we're still at war here.
I'm sorry, Nate.
My hands are tied.
It is impossible.
I hope you understand that.
Nate.
I realize what these
men did for you.
And I'm gonna do anything
in my power to see to it...
that they're as well taken
care of as possible.
Thank you, Sir.
I was dead, several times.
I...
I gave up all hope
of ever coming home.
I wish I could have
been there for you.
You were. In more ways than one.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
What?
You think you can get
rid of me that easily?
Camp Cooke, California
German P.O.W. Compound
Thank you.
Hello.
This is my wife, Rachel.
She wanted to meet you.
It's my pleasure.
None of us would have made it
had it not been for your husband.
You've a brave man there.
He says the same about you.
A telegram...
was sent to my house...
it said that my husband's
boat was missing.
They had lost contact...
and the crew was presumed dead.
Thank you.
I'll let you two talk.
I'll be right there.
She's beautiful.
I can't take credit for that,
but... thanks.
Here.
My cigarettes!
How did you get these?
You don't wanna know.
Thank you.
How are the men?
The food is good, clean rooms...
The Captain was unrealistic
in his demands.
I suspect he even knew
this'd be our fate.
He didn't want you
to end up here.
He wanted us to live.
He succeeded.
We succeeded.
- The war will be over soon.
- Yeah.
We will return home.
If that torpedo had detonated...
I... I don't know.
I know.
Good to see you, my friend.