Sorry, uh...
- Did you want your kite?
- Yes.
- Come and get it.
- Thank you.
Is there anything else you want?
INNOCENTS WITH DIRTY HANDS
Louis, I want you to meet Jeff Marlo.
He's a writer
...he rents the little blue house
and flies a kite.
Yes, I saw you swimming this morning.
I swim a lot.
Ah, I'm sure you do.
Would you like a drink?
- I've got one, thanks
- OK
So, I'll take care of myself.
I suppose that my...
...charming wife told you I drink a lot!
To your health.
How horrible.
Why are you laughing?
Why not?
You can't imagine... what it feels like...
...suddenly, it's like your heart explodes...
...and then, everything is black...
...and you die.
So, why drink, it's not very clever
No, no, it's got nothing to do
with being clever...
...or intelligent...
But it has everything to do with:
Pain!
Anyway...
Soon I'll take my...
...marvelous wife,
...somewhere, anywhere...
to America or Martinique, we'll see...
Come here, come on,
come, come, come...
...come come, closer...
...come here, please...
Listen, I have a few questions
to ask you, Julie...
...first: Why can't we make love any more...
...next, why don't you ever kiss me?
...next, why do you refuse to
let me touch you?
...and, do you hate me?
Stop drinking...
...It's too stupid.
Louis, I beg you.
Why do you put yourself in such a state?
That's a good question...
...That's what I call a very good question!
- Does he do this often?
- Yes
Help me, I'm going to put him to bed.
He's crazy.
NO. Don't touch it.
Don't touch the belt, help me.
What's going on?
It's nothing Louis.
Go to bed.
- How can you stand it?
- I can't.
I've had enough.
He hasn't touched me since his heart attack.
He sold his business and we settled here.
Now he wants us to go to Martinique.
He probably wants to replace
his whiskey with rum.
He'll never get there alive.
He won't hold up very long at this pace.
Why did you marry him?
He's at least 15 years older than you.
Eighteen.
He was very kind to me...
...I was supposed to do a film
and he financed it.
You were an actress?
I was starting out,
I didn't really want much. Anyway...
...he was really very nice...
...not great in bed, but nice...
So, let's talk about you,
what do you do besides fly kites?
- I write stupid shit.
- What?
I'm a writer.
I type because I can't read my handwriting...
...but I have no talent, I'm lazy...
...and I'm easily bored.
Bastard!
...I'm easily bored but you excite me...
Bastard.
He won't be around much longer,
take my word for it.
He won't last long.
THREE WEEKS LATER
- Are you Madam Wormser?
- Yes, I am.
- Your car is here.
- Don't you want to see it?
But are you sure you're not mistaken?
Mr. Wormser came by the garage...
- I'm a little late. Hope you like the car.
- Goodbye, thank you.
- You're crazy. This car!!
- Do you like it?
Of course I like it, it's my dream.
- Thank you.
- No no no!
Thank you...
Thank you for putting up with me.
It's to compensate...
Go on, go try it out.
No not today. Too much traffic.
I'm just going to look at it.
You've deserve it.
Me, I think I deserve a drink.
Don't move. I'll get it for you.
I love you!
Thank you.
I've been restless lately...
and I want to move, to go...
...do you understand?
- Yes.
It's true, I drink too much.
And afterward I feel...
...so tired...
too tired.
Sorry...
I talk too much.
I better go to bed, good night.
Good night.
Good night, Louis.
Good night, Julie.
This old guy is off to bed.
Jeff, please, Jeff, stay with me.
Don't go, I beg you...
...I beg you, please, Jeff,
don't leave me alone.
- No. We're already behind schedule.
- Jeff!
No, we can't see each other for 3 or 4 days.
Not even phone each other.
Maybe I'll just leave a few days, until...
the accident becomes official huh?
I'll let you know one way or the other.
You must really...
Yes, yes. He could wake up.
Think about what I'll have to do.
I'll have to stay alone with him all night.
Can't you come back sooner?
God, you know we can't.
We have to have
Mother Chauvinet as an alibi.
No one can even suspect
that were in this together.
It's 11:30.
In 2 hours, in 2 hours...
The thing is on the corner of his desk...
...anyhow, I'm leaving.
See you later.
I killed him.
The car!
Darling, I took the Datsun.
After this Interminable night...
...I don't have the courage
to go see the cops right away.
I'll bring the car back In 2 or 3 days.
You'll just need to explain...
...that I had to go to Italy
to do research for my novel...
...and since I had no money,
Louis Insisted...
...I borrow the car...
Everything went as planned.
I'm certain that
Mother Chauvinet Is ready to swear...
...that I didn’t leave the house
and worked all night...
If you want to join me,
write me at my P.O. Box In Menton.
I'll check It tomorrow and the day after.
I'll be back before the beginning of the
Investigation, If there Is one.
But afterwards,
It'll be just the two of us.
- The maritime police?
- Ah yes!
We've decided to investigate, Mrs. Wormser.
Oh! What's going on?
We were just going to
take the helicopter out.
I'm probably worrying for nothing.
But he's always so punctual...
Thank you
Must be the salt air, my underwear is itching.
Yes
- Madam.
- Gentlemen.
Madam Wormser?
I'm Inspector Villon, from Draguignan.
- Please come in.
- Excuse me, Madam.
Didn't we meet at the Mayor's Reception?
That's it, yes, let me introduce
you to Inspector Lamy, from Paris.
I took the liberty
of asking him to come along.
Hope you don't mind, Madam.
I'm on vacation here
and Villon, my colleague, has requested...
- Please gentlemen, sit down.
- Thank you Madam
Well, Mrs. Wormser
We received a phone call
from the Maritime Police.
Yes?
They have, uh,
they have found Mr. Wormser's boat
But no one was on board.
What's that?
Oh no!!
The divers searched
for over an hour with no results.
And you think that...
Excuse me,
would you like to drink something?
- No.
- Thank you Madam.
Please.
We understand
what you're going through, Madam.
I'm terribly frightened.
Mr. Wormser perhaps went
aboard another boat...
...to say hello to friends.
Oh, that's very unlikely madam.
We are going to inspect the boat.
We wondered if...
...you'd like to go with us.
Ah, well, I don't know... I...
Ah, you'd rather wait here
for your husband to call...
...to tell you where he is?
You know, I'm beginning...
I'm beginning to fear
that he won't be able to.
Ah, we realize how you feel, Madam.
There is perhaps a very simple explanation
for this disappearance.
But, my colleague is forced
to ask you a few questions...
...that you might find indiscreet.
I don't know how I can help you gentlemen,
but I will tell you everything
you wish to know.
Yes well, do you know
if your husband has enemies, madam?
Enemies?
No, certainly not.
He's a very kind man, very peaceful.
He retired.
He wanted to live here.
And where did you dock your boat Madam?
In the harbor?
No...
We had a dock at the foot of the cliff.
- Could I trouble you for a glass of water
- Of course
- No don't get up.
- It's this way
excuse me
- You'll find glasses by the sink.
- Ah thank you
Tell me, it's quite a climb
up from the dock, isn't it?
Yes it's why we were thinking of moving.
Ah, but you would stay in St. Tropez?
I didn't know my husband
was considering the Antilles.
I've heard it's a marvelous place.
You know, nothing was really decided.
Tell me, do you see your neighbors much?
No... but last night we had a visitor,
Jeff Marlo.
He often comes to see Louis.
He came to dinner.
Ah and is he a neighbor?
Yes he lives just two houses below us.
He's a writer.
- Yes, they developed a friendship
- Ah... Yes, yes, yes.
Perhaps, he could see your husband's boat?
Well, we'll go pay him a visit.
Oh, I don't believe it will be worthwhile.
He told us last night
he was going to Italy.
He was leaving very early this morning.
Well, anyhow, we'll go and make sure.
No I'm quite sure he left.
He took one of our cars, the Datsun.
Oh, he did?
Did you lend it to him?
Yes, well...
My husband did.
Mr. Marlo has no car and we knew
that he has very limited means...
He was planning on going
for 2 or 3 days to... huh...
...ah yes, he wanted to gather material
for the book he's writing.
So, my husband lent him the car
to save him money.
And he accepted?
Well, yes, Louis insisted.
You say Mr. Marlo
lives two houses from here?
Who owns the other?
Mrs. Chauvinet, an elderly lady.
Has she visited you lately?
No, I rarely see her.
I'm afraid.
Of what madam?
I think that Louis had another heart attack.
...and he must have fallen overboard...
He had a heart attack last year.
Yes, it is plausible.
Ah yes, effectively, yes.
One last question Madam,
if you'll allow me.
Did your husband often keep
large sums of money on him...
...or on the boat?
Ah yes, I see that's interesting.
Did he have a lot of money on him?
No, I don't believe so, no.
...I'm sure he didn't.
- So?
- Well, let's see...
...according to this Madam Chauvinot...
...it seems he was home all night, typing.
Although, she did sleep a little
so it's not a perfect alibi.
And also she saw Mr. Wormser
go out with a big bag of some sort.
...Around five in the morning.
This woman must spend
her whole life at the window.
She has insomnia.
I think she's a bit of a drinker.
She's rather funny.
Can't smoke on board, Inspector.
Say, on the subject of drinking...
...I don't think that
the Wormsers were teetotalers.
The trash can is full of whiskey bottles.
How'd you find out?
By getting thirsty at the right time.
We've checked everything,
there is nothing suspicious.
Well, let's see about that.
What's in here?
The head.
One could say this is a well kept boat,
it looks like it's never been used.
Yes, a little too much so. It looks like
Wormser didn't do a lot of fishing.
- There's no bait.
- Maybe on the deck.
Hey, officer, wasn't there any bait?
Bait?
No, say that's true, there was no bait.
- Alexander, can you come see?
- What is it?
- A spot of blood, look here.
- Ah yes.
Let's have it analyzed and dusted for prints.
Well, I don't think we'll find anything else.
Say, I wouldn't mind a drink.
Say, I suppose that confirms
the story of the heart attack.
What?
The blood stain?
Yes.
He headed out to do some fishing...
...dropped anchor, heart attack.
He collapsed, hit his head
and passed overboard.
Not too complicated.
Yes, but several things bother me.
The lack of bait, the whiskey bottles.
The wife is young and pretty.
Seems hot to trot.
The neighbor borrowed the car.
You know,
I think you've got something there.
Still, I like your idea there.
Wormser was an alcoholic.
His wife and that guy kept him drunk...
Then, knock him off
to live happily ever after with his money.
Yes, but if the writer is involved...
why did he borrow the car?
That wasn't smart!
Maybe he just got scared.
We've got to find this Marlo,
interrogate him.
I'm going to call the police station.
Then we'll have that drink.
Julie darling, It's so stupid,
forgot to warn you about the money belt.
It was full of bills and jewels.
I'll put It In a safe place
until I get back In a day or two.
Everything went well, just like I said.
He came on board
and gave me a bloody nose.
That's all he was able to do.
Write me as soon as you can
and tell me everything.
P.O. Box Menton. I love you.
Jeff, my love, my darling...
Everything Is going well.
The police came to see me...
...but they don't suspect a thing.
Hurry back, please.
I'm going crazy without you.
I love you, I love you, Julie.
Hello sir.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
I would like the balance
in my husband's account, Mr. Wormser
Certainly, Mrs. Wormser.
I assume it's a joint account?
No, it's in his name.
Ah, we can only give
this information to the titled owner.
Of course, I understand.
But... something terrible has happened.
Yes I know.
News travels very fast, you know.
I think we could
bend the rule just a little...
I believe your husband made
a recent withdrawal. Excuse me.
Yes, it was yesterday actually.
How much did he withdraw?
A rather large sum; a million and a half.
150 million old francs.
But, that's impossible.
Well, we were surprised but it's a fact.
And... what is left in the account?
Oh, 92 francs.
We had to notify him
this is below the minimum.
Aren't you feeling well, madam?
- Yes, please excuse me.
- Good day Mrs. Wormser.
Mrs. Wormser...
- Hello Mrs. Wormser.
- Gentlemen.
This is a happy coincidence Madam.
Yes, we received permission
to open your husband's safety deposit box.
You're welcome to join us.
I'm at your disposal.
You are very cooperative,
Madam. We appreciate it
Mr. Wormser was here recently.
He apparently took everything.
I'm happy you're here, Julie.
You see I am so distraught.
Since yesterday,
I feel like I'm in a waking nightmare.
Poor Julie.
Ah, it really is incomprehensible.
Georges, I had thought
maybe Louis told you his plans.
You were much more than
a financial advisor to him.
Don't speak about him in the past, Julie...
In the past?
I'm sorry to see you in this state.
You know I'm very fond of you both.
There, there, I'm sure everything
will be explained, go on and eat.
- I'm really not very hungry.
- Eat anyway.
Shall we have a soufflé for dessert?
The police came to my office this morning.
They asked me the same questions you did.
I told them I didn't know anything.
I won't tell you exactly the same thing.
In fact, he intends to leave
for the Antilles as soon as possible.
He'd already made all the arrangements.
And you think he's left for there?
Now now Julie, not without you.
He adores you.
No but I do believe
he's put the house up for sale.
Put the house up for sale?
He found something in Martinique, I believe.
He wanted to surprise you.
Now you're talking about him in past tense.
I'm concerned about leaving you alone, Julie.
You're very nice George, thank you.
I've got so much work right now.
Anyway, if you need anything, call me.
You can count on me.
Thank you.
I know I can count on you.
You're very pretty, Julie.
Dear Mrs. Wormser...
- Please excuse our intrusion.
- Madam
Gentlemen
- Mr. Thorent brought you back?
- Yes.
We saw his car.
I suppose he told you
about our visit this morning?
Yes, he did.
Yes well,
we have some important news Madam.
We saw Mr. Wormser's doctor and...
...he made some rather surprising revelations.
Dr. Favart? What could he have told you?
Well, he told us that
your husband never suffered a heart attack.
What do you mean? But...
That's right, it was an act.
Mr. Wormser suffered another illness
he found terribly humiliating.
According to Dr. Favart,
he had become impotent.
And so, it was to justify
his lack of passion towards you...
that he invented...
...that he invented this story
about the heart attack.
That makes no sense.
I don't believe a word.
Ah, you mean to say that
you had normal relations with him?
Sexual relations, that is.
No.
So the good doctor's statement was correct.
We have several rather difficult revelations
...in any case, surprising ones to tell you.
Please sit down.
Thank you, but I'm fine standing.
Oh no, Inspector Villon is right.
You'd better to sit down, believe me.
We found the Datsun, Madam.
It crashed into some rocks near Menton.
There was neither corpse
nor wounded in the car.
We think the driver was thrown. Then...
...washed out to sea.
We found a sports coat in the back...
...in it were I.D. Papers
with the name Joseph Marlo...
...writer, living in St. Tropez.
My God, what's going on?
Ah nothing very rare, I'm afraid.
We checked Mr. Marlo's house,
and found...
...this,
in the living room, under a cushion.
This is yours, is it not?
But I've never been in
Mr. Marlo's house, never.
A formal inquest has been started
for your husband's disappearance...
...Mrs. Wormser,
...the judge is very anxious...
...to interview you as chief witness.
Your lawyer sends his apologies,
he will be a little late.
That's not unusual for him.
I don't know him.
He hasn't seen you yet?
A friend of my husband's
asked him to defend me.
From what I've seen so far
he'll have to be very talented.
Don't worry, he doesn't lack talent.
I'm not worried sir.
- Maybe you should be.
- Anyway we'll see.
You're very close to being indicted, Madam.
I'd rather not discuss this
without my lawyer.
You have every right, Madam.
Smoke, your Honor?
No, thank you, I prefer my own.
You've got nerves of steel, bravo.
I hope you can keep it up.
Your honor.
- Counselor.
- Please excuse the delay.
Ah, Mrs. Wormser...
They're giving you trouble, eh?
Don't worry, I'm here to defend you.
My name is Albert Legal.
Perfect name for a lawyer, no?
You know, you are ravishing.
So, your honor,
I know you adore torturing pretty women
...but I need to ask you
to wait a few more minutes.
...because I have not yet had a chance
to talk with my client alone.
Is there a corner we could be alone,
I promise we won't be 10 minutes.
Your little scene doesn't impress me,
but I will grant you the time.
Please take Mr. Legal
and his client to the back room.
Thank you, your honor, I'm very grateful.
You are a superb woman
Yes, it'll do.
And no listening at the door huh!
Please sit down.
You're much younger than your husband.
I can't help it.
Relax. I'm a little late
because I went to see everyone:
...your husband's banker,
your neighbor, and also...
...the real estate agent handling the house,
and of course the garage.
So now the police are sure
you've killed your husband...
...with the help of that guy...
what's his name?
Jeff Marlo.
Yes, that's it.
Like they say in novels,
was he more than a friend?
No, nothing more.
You don't say his name
like that of a simple friend.
Be careful.
Now, did he visit you often?
They liked to chat together.
They got along very well.
They'd have a couple of drinks.
Oh, don't make me laugh.
Louis drank like a fish...
...maybe he cut down a little
when his heart kicked up.
As soon as he felt well
he began drinking again...
...but not a great deal.
Did you lead normal lives,
I mean like a husband and wife?
- We had separate bedrooms
- Yes that's it.
Now tell me about this earring, was it yours?
Yes.
You've never gone to his house?
Yes, just once.
It wasn't very smart to have lied.
Tell me the whole story.
Oh it was a couple of weeks ago.
We hadn't seen him in some time.
...and Louis asked me
to drop in and see him...
...the door was open, I went in.
No one was home...
...I smoked a cigarette, waited,
he never showed up.
The next day, we found
he was spending a few days in Italy.
I see! No doubt to be seen...
and he came back this week!
We can't keep the judge waiting...
Let me take care of everything.
Just repeat in your head
"I keep my trap shut"
Do you dig, Julie?
I dig, Mr. Legal.
You're lucky to be so good looking...
...or I'd have dropped
you like a hot potato.
We weren't too long, your Honor?
Please Counselor,
don't start your little song and dance again.
It's eventually going to get on my nerves
and it won't do you any good.
You don't feel you have a solid case.
My only intention is justice.
Oh sit down, you are making me dizzy!
Please Mrs. Wormser, sit down.
- I have a few questions to ask you.
- Yes
About what?
But about Mr. Wormser's
disappearance of course!
Just a second Your Honor,
the police report goes quite a bit further.
Yes, the police report you saw...
...concluded that Mr. Wormser
was robbed and killed, Counselor.
Madam Wormser has a right to know
what she is suspected of.
The report alleges the crime was committed
by a Mr. Joseph Marlo...
...and Mrs. Julie Wormser, born Schumann,
was his accomplice.
Well, now we know were we stand.
The police report explained
the following theory:
Louis Wormser was dead or unconscious
on his boat Monday morning.
That morning the neighbor,
Mrs. Marie Chauvinet, saw...
...a man pulling a big seaman's kit bag
along the beach, so she says.
The police report suggests it was in fact...
...the body of Louis Wormser,
and Joseph Marlo was carrying it.
Marlo threw the cadaver out to sea. Then...
...he swam back to shore.
He then continued to type
as if he had not stopped for the whole night.
Pardon me, your Honor,
Mrs. Wormser needs a glass of water.
- Over here?
- Right.
- Are you feeling better?
- Yes.
You're o. K?
Yes, I'm fine thanks.
Please continue Your Honor.
You're very gracious.
Marlo took the money
and whatever else he found on the boat...
maybe even on the victim's body,
a total of about 2 million francs,
...200 million old francs,
...and taking Mrs. Wormser's
new Datsun 260...
...he fled and Mrs. Wormser was
to join him later.
The police report states that
they were lovers.
But they never met up
because he was killed in a auto accident.
Well...
I can only compliment the police's reasoning.
It is barely certain
J. Marlo killed Louis Wormser.
Well, I'm delighted we're in agreement.
Yes certainly, from what I've learned.
Jeff Marlo went out of his way
to befriend Mr. Wormser.
He was almost broke,
at the end of his rope...
I suppose there is
a great deal of proof of his guilt.
Obviously the stolen car is one.
Well, Mrs. Wormser stated,
her husband loaned the car to Marlo...
...even insisting he take it.
Between us that is highly unlikely.
All right, fine fine. What else?
Well go back to that...
The blood on board the boat.
The blood?
What is this story?
Additional evidence.
We were sure when the report became final.
- This isn't a trap, is it?
- Please.
We're talking about
a little blood on the railing.
Before being killed Mr. Wormser must
have fought with his assassin...
...the "little blood" in question is
the same type as Mr. Marlo's.
...which proves Marlo was on board.
What blood type is it?
Type O. Not Mr. Wormser's.
OK, fine,
What else?
We have proof Marlo mailed...
...a letter to Mrs. Wormser from Menton.
Do you have the letter?
No, but we know
Mrs. Wormser received it...
...the day of J. Marlo's death...
The Inspector is certain.
The mailman saw the letter stamped Menton!
What is this! A mailman
who remembers the stamp of Menton!!
Not Madagascar, nor Tahiti,
but Menton. Oh no.
You're not well, counselor?
It's obvious the mailman heard of
Mr. Wormser's disappearance...
It's normal he was curious
about his wife's mail.
Fine, but nothing proves
it was from J. Marlo.
Do you have another idea?
No, the letter was definitely from Mr. Marlo.
Mrs. Wormser spoke to me of the letter...
Marlo said he had seen
the papers and was returning...
...because the police wanted to discuss
the disappearance of the car.
You're not lucky, counselor.
The car was headed the opposite direction
at the time of the accident.
Of course, Marlo lied in the letter.
He simply wanted
to appease Mrs. Wormser...
...to buy a little time.
He was running.
You're saying his only goal
was to appease her.
How do you explain this?
It was found in Marlo's suit
while checking the wrecked Datsun.
The handwriting is Mrs. Wormser's.
We checked.
Bravo.
Fine work.
I suppose you have the letter.
This is your handwriting, is it not, Madam?
I suppose you have the letter Your Honor?
No, but it seems logical to me
he had put it in his pants pocket...
It's logical.
Ah yes, logical but it's too bad.
That letter would have proven
Mrs. Wormser innocent.
How would you know?
Very simple, Mrs. Wormser told me
what she had written the letter.
She is ready to repeat it.
Very simply, she was imploring
Joseph Marlo to return immediately.
A man who pretended
to be his friend could not have betray him.
Good God, of course she suspected.
The Police saw to that.
That is why she checked
her husband's financial status.
Counselor, Mrs. Wormser is capable
of telling me all this herself.
Yes of course, I understand, but...
...she wrote him, begging he clears himself.
She was convinced of his guilt
but still wrote him.
Please Madam, tell us.
That's it exactly, your Honor.
Inspector Villon went to
Mr. Marlo's residence...
...and found this by the couch...
...and he found the second earring
in a dresser drawer.
Please, madam.
...please repeat exactly
what you told me for his honor.
Yes, I don't quite know
why but in my sort of panic...
...I told the Inspector
I had never been to Mr. Marlo's.
I did go there with my husband one time.
He wasn't home, I waited a few moments...
I think that's when
I must have lost the earring.
So, I add, if the police intend to use
this earring as proof of complicity...
...I warn you that
I am quite capable of proving...
...the police attempted a set up...
..."planting" the earring
due to insufficient evidence!
I won't do it, of course, but...
...but I could if forced.
No threats, counselor.
I'm not threatening, I'm simply stating...
When Inspector Villon,
accompanied by Inspector Lamy of Paris...
...and you, the judge of their undertaking...
...interrogated my client,
the hypothesis was a heart attack. Why?
Mrs. Wormser mentioned a heart attack
less than a year earlier!
Yes.
So why did the police change their minds?
Because they learned
Mr. Wormser never had a heart attack
The truth is he was impotent.
Enough to convince them
Joseph Marlo was Mrs. Wormser's lover...
...add to that,
she is 15 yrs younger than her husband.
Preconceptions are so convenient.
Except there is one little catch...
The little catch is Mrs. Wormser
didn't know her husband was impotent.
You can check the police report;
it's clearly between the lines.
So, I ask the question:
What remains of their fantastic accusations?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Nothing proves that
Mr. Wormser was killed...
You can't even prove anything was stolen,
since the prime witness...
...the number one suspect,
and rightly so, Joseph Marlo, is dead.
So, legally speaking, what we have is:
A victim that doesn't exist,
...a fortune that doesn't exist,
and a suspect that no longer exists.
Your Honor: Allow me
to leave these chambers with Mrs. Wormser.
This has been a terrible trial for her.
Let's face it, this is a ridiculous affair.
Nobody's going to gain anything from it.
Yes, I see,
they might as well go back to square one.
It'll never stand up in court.
Good day, Madam.
Goodbye and thank you, your Honor.
Are you surprised?
How can you be alive?
It's a long story!
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
I should, but I won't.
No one would suspect me.
...since I'm already dead, amusing, isn't it?
What happened?
You're a pretty cool girl aren't you.
Come here...
Closer.
You should see your eyes.
It's extraordinary...
You're not even afraid.
Of course, I'm afraid.
Tell me what happened.
It's very simple.
Your plan went to shit!
I knew everything from the very beginning.
I woke up not feeling well one night,
I needed a breath of air.
I saw you and Jeff that night.
The following night,
I decided to not drink, I listened to you.
And the following night,
and every other night...
I listened, listened, listened...
...until one night,
I heard Jeff talk of murdering me.
And it became a sort of game.
But it was much more than a game for me.
What have you done to Jeff?
Did you kill him?
Would you like me tell you
about the night you killed me?
I went up to bed.
You thought I was sleeping.
But I wasn't.
I waited 'till Jeff went home.
Then I hit him.
You want to know what I hit him with?
With the same cudgel you used later
And I too carried him to the room
by the back door...
...and put him In my bed.
After that it was simple.
I just had to carry out your plans.
I went to Jeff's, tapped the typewriter...
...'till 5 in the morning.
I came home, through the backdoor.
What if I'd gone upstairs to your room?
Well, I would have killed Jeff.
And I would have convinced you
that you had.
We would have been in it together.
You probably would have
begged me to help you...
...I would have said
"Yes, of course my darling."
But to return to that marvelous night...
Once out to sea, when he came to.
I had him drink whiskey
to bring him around completely.
You woke him up?
Why?
For the pleasure of it.
I wanted to see his expression.
And I had him write out
a full confession...
...stating that you were his accomplice.
Did he write it?
Of course. He had no choice.
He ether wrote or died!
He wrote It then he signed it.
And what did you do after?
I knocked him out.
I dragged him to the side of the boat...
...and held his head under water
'till he drowned.
I let go of him
and the sea carried him away.
You didn't think I was capable did you?
It's very easy to understand.
It was the first time that
my wife wanted to kill me.
When a man finds his wife
plans his death, he is capable of anything.
You are sick Louis, you're crazy!
No, I'm not sick, I'm very lucid...
...and I'm not finished, my dear.
I wrote the letters you received from Jeff.
I crashed the car,
placed your envelope in his coat pocket...
...your earring in his house...
I put the jewels in a safe place.
I did all of it, me alone.
And what do you have left now?
Nothing...
You have no lover, no jewels...
...you've got nothing!
And that's what I call justice.
You think so?
It's rather funny,
you made love to Jeff here...
...now you're going to do it with me.
You see, I'm not afraid
I'm not man enough for you.
What do you want?
What do you want to prove?
I don't want to prove anything.
From now on, we'll have a new,
"complete" relationship.
Oh yes.
A new and complete relationship,
that's impossible for you.
Even if you wanted to.
We'll see.
Louis, you're kidding!
No, I'm not kidding.
You'll do exactly what I want
or I'll go to the police.
All right, let's go to the bedroom.
No, we'll do it right there.
Where you made love with him.
Yes, now.
You son of a bitch.
You're a son of a bitch.
Do you want a drink, Louis?
No, thank you. I've stopped drinking.
- Your sun
- Thank you.
I found it with the money you left.
Does this signify our new relationship?
Yes, that's it.
500 francs, that's not bad money
to be my husband's whore. Thank you.
Don't forget your husband is dead.
How long do you think
this can last, Louis?
Who knows!
That's disgust isn't it...
...hatred or what?
Accepting hatred.
Maybe we'll find happiness later.
Hum. Happiness!
How could you live with a woman
who tried to kill you? How?
Oh, there are millions of women
who dream of killing their husbands,
...and millions of husbands
who dream of killing their wives.
The only difference is you tried.
No that's not it.
I actually wanted to kill you, Louis.
Yes, I understand very well, and right now...
...I'm actually trying to forgive you.
Do you think I could ever have anything
but hate towards you?
Even after last night?
Last night was different.
What... healed you?
Watching you and Jeff together.
Each time I watched you,
I thought I couldn't take it.
I would leave...
...but I would come back
and start watching again...
I did that night after night...
...watching, and eventually...
...one day, my feelings began to change.
...almost like I became him.
Then I was a man again.
And after that
all my anxiety's disappeared...
...my nightmares disappeared.
It's funny; thanks to you,
I feel alive again...
...and I love life.
Are you sure, Louis?
Am I wrong?
You really have no money whatsoever?
Really.
I hardly have enough to feed myself.
Louis took everything we owned...
...our savings, our stocks. Everything.
Yes and you...
Oh, no, no, no, nothing.
Listen, I'm very sorry, I didn't know.
Naturally,
I can lend you money in the meantime.
In the meantime, what?
I don't know how to ever repay you.
Don't worry. We'll find a way.
No. It's impossible.
I've been thinking,
didn't Louis have a life insurance policy?
Yes of course.
50 million old francs, I believe.
Couldn't I get a loan
with that as collateral?
Possibly, around 10 million.
No more?
How much would you want?
I need at least 30 or 40.
Want do you want to do
with that much money, Julie?
But George, I have absolutely nothing!
Louis sold the house.
I'm going to need to find a place to live.
And I want to leave here.
I want to forget everything.
Well, obviously there is
no longer anything here for you.
But please understand the process of
inheriting could be a long one!
Louis' death needs to become official,
his will needs to be validated.
It could take over a year.
With luck, maybe I could get you
a small monthly income to get you by...
...but not the money you're asking for.
I'm willing to help you
as much as I can Julie, you know that.
If you don't know where to go,
I can put you up.
If you have nothing to eat,
you could share my meals.
But it's not possible to get you
the kind of money you're asking for.
You must not leave, Julie.
Not bad, huh?
Especially with the wind.
Too bad you're leaving so soon.
You could turn pro.
- Say, I've thought about the Wormser case.
- Yes?
I wonder if that cretin
isn't right after all?
How's that?
Maybe we blew it.
Maybe we didn't observe the person
who holds the key to the case.
Who is that?
- Louis Wormser.
- Your turn, Fernand.
But you're speaking
about him as if he's alive!!
And why wouldn't he be?
We have to think about
what Louis Wormser did before the crime.
Just doesn't fit.
He got out all his money...
...put his house up for sale,
didn't say a word to his wife.
All this after 10 years of marriage.
So that the beautiful Julie found
herself alone and ruined...
...when he disappeared,
and of course, under suspicion.
As if she was being punished.
She damn well deserved it...
...believe me she's a real slut.
Hum, that's just the point.
Was this a coincidence or planned?
You think Wormser arranged
it all before he disappeared?
Yes. That's what I'm thinking.
He knew his wife was sleeping with Marlo.
Or he'd have no reason to punish her.
Maybe he knew
our two love birds planned to kill him.
Yes, but they still had time act, no?
No, I don't think so.
Do you want dessert?
No, thanks, just coffee.
Do you have an aged liquor?
Cognac or something?
We have a local brandy.
Perfect!
Two provincial brandies and cigars please.
This thing with the earring
has always bothered me.
You don't lose them just like that.
Or else you notice it.
In my opinion, the earring was
planted to get little Julie under suspicion.
And Marlo had no motivation.
But Wormser certainly did.
That's true.
Here's what I think.
Wormser acted first.
At some point he took Marlo's place.
He killed him on the boat.
After all, it is Marlo's blood, right?
Not Wormser's.
He's the one who stole his own car...
...and who wrote the letter.
What about the car accident?
- A little more Brandy?
- Gladly.
So the car accident?
That's easy...
Wormser stole Marlo's papers
before throwing him overboard...
...he steals his jacket
...and the envelope to the letter
that Julie sent to Menton.
Now there, Wormser that's a brilliant idea.
First of all the letter itself
probably contains the proof...
...to Julie's guilt in
her husband's murder attempt.
Finally, the envelope's disappearance
scared the shit out of the chick.
Especially, it seems to prove
Marlo was killed running from the cops.
There, he got us, the bastard.
Marlo wouldn't have left the envelope
if he had faked the accident.
Wormser is definitely very good;
he got what he wanted.
He threw his chick into the street,
killed her lover...
...split with all the dough.
Say, you know it's very clever
what you've figured out.
Not clever but it stands up.
Say, you have any idea
where Wormser might be hiding?
Oh there, you're asking too much.
But if I was you...
Wormser's financial counselor.
Who?
Georges Thorent?
Yes, Thorent.
He's one of his best friends.
And he'll surely need
to contact him sooner or later.
If I were you, I would watch him.
Why are you so strange, Louis?
Because I'm getting sick
of going in and out like a thief.
- But nothing forces you to.
- No.
- No, it's simple just go to the police.
- Well.
- I'll tell the police I have amnesia
- Yes.
They'll never swallow that.
- Louis.
- Wait.
Suppose I go to the police to explain...
I'm kidding of course...
What would you do?
I would stay near you.
They won't question it.
If I live with you,
they couldn't say anything.
We'd go back to living together?
I'd want to try, anyway.
You've changed Louis,
and I've changed also.
I can't believe you.
Louis please...
...Please, let's try.
Try, but how,
even if we lived together 20 years...
...I would always think
it was because of the confession.
Just burn it and we can forget everything.
Very nice!!
Congratulations.
What are you saying?
It's becoming so clear.
I'll tell you exactly what I think...
You want me to destroy the confession.
You'll have your Jeff back...
...get your jewels, the house,
everything back. You don't love me.
- I'm not crazy. I'm not an idiot.
- Louis.
- Good evening, Mrs. Wormser.
- Good evening gentlemen.
Good evening Madam.
I'm happy to find you here.
No thanks to you.
Ah Madam, police work is thankless work.
We sometimes have to pry.
Don't hold it against the Inspector.
Could we have a word?
At this hour?
Well, gentlemen
you're lucky to find me still up.
Yes, I know.
Please forgive us...
...but we have some interesting conclusions
to present you.
Yes and I'd like to ask you a minor question.
Have you had any news from your husband?
Of course not, I would have called you.
I don't doubt it at all.
So why this idiotic question?
Oh, it's not idiotic, Madam.
It's possible that
your husband is still alive.
Oh please, you have no right
to play with people's minds.
And you're mocking my husband's death...
We're not playing.
This is not a game!
We're not fooling around.
We're seeking the truth.
The truth?
Your truth has many faces!
I haven't forgotten
your report to the police, Inspector.
Three days ago you were sure
my husband had been killed...
...and that I was an accomplice
to the murder.
Well, we think the facts
can be interpreted another way.
You think? I wouldn't have thought
you capable of thinking Inspector!
Is that a threat?
Listen Madam,
it's entirely possible your husband is alive.
If he was alive, he would have come home.
No, maybe not.
He could have suffered a blow to the head.
And suffering a temporary loss of memory.
That's why the Inspector
asked you if you had news.
No, I don't have news from him.
We don't want to take up
any more of your time Mrs. Wormser.
I'm sure you'll contact us
if you see your husband, right?
Inspector, if I see him
I'll throw myself into his arms.
May I go to bed now?
You were great and I was stupid.
Please forgive me.
That was a little close for comfort.
Yes, but we'll have to leave.
We can't hide here our whole lives.
What do you mean?
Don't you want to keep paying me
to make love to you?
Sure, I'll keep paying you.
Here's what were going to do...
I'll trust you if you'll trust me.
I'll forgive you the same way
you'll forgive me.
O. K?
O.k.
They're gone.
Do you have a car?
- But this is...
- Get in.
Does George know about Jeff and me?
George knows everything.
What's come over you, bringing her here?
You're crazy.
No, no, not at all!
The police came to the house.
They thought I was alive.
Julie held them off all alone.
She was Magnificent.
All she wants is
to get her confession back.
You'll see how fast
she'll turn you in after that.
That's disgusting!
You don't get it.
She's trying to get her dough back
any way she can.
She hit me up this morning.
Almost showed her ass to get her bread.
Why do you hate me?
It's just that I don't like women,
dear friend.
She tried to kill you to get your dough...
...and to split with that asshole
with the big dick.
She would steal your gold fillings
if she could. And you trust her?
Are you going to keep her with you?
Yes, that's right.
You're really a child.
No I'm not a child.
I love her...
...and I want to stay with her.
All you need is to take
that fool's confession to the police...
You can have a new life.
You deserve it, you've got the mean.
No, I would never do that to her.
- O.k., so you're an idiot
- Georges
Excuse me but Julie is my wife.
And you'll speak to her with respect.
I'm tired, very tired...
...that's enough.
This comedy has gone on
long enough. It's finished.
Leave me alone.
You already know I have nothing left.
You shut up you stupid female!
No, I won't shut up.
You can't make me shut up.
You have no right.
Louis forgave me.
We're starting over
and you can't make me shut up.
Jeff's confession and Louis' money
are in a safe at my place.
George, please stop.
- Good. All this is good to know.
- Jeff!
Yes...
and now all the dead are resuscitated.
I'm sure she's cooking up something.
In any case the bitch knows
more than she's telling us.
You're a misogynist, old man!
I don't know, but women like her
frighten the pants off me.
She wouldn't need
to frighten my pants off.
Do you think she's seen her husband?
I'm sure of it!
It's funny, but when I propose
a theory you jump on it with both feet.
In any case, nothing proves
Wormser is still alive.
You've proved it to me.
If she's seen him
she knows he killed her lover.
Why hasn't she turned him in?
She can't. He's got to have proof
she and Marlo tried to kill him.
Ah. One for you!
You're right!
Mmm, your sandwich is very good.
You have to put butter and ham.
God I was stupid. I should have had
the villa watched day and night.
...rather than watching
the financial advisor.
Does your T.V. Work?
It works but there's a strike
and in any case...
Even if there wasn't, it's 11:30 so...
Did you know he was alive?
Of course he knew.
All the time he fucked you, he knew.
Listen Julie,
you're going to appreciate this.
Go on, Louis.
Tell your clever little scheme.
What do you want?
I'll tell you what I want.
I want the girl,
the dough, and the jewels...
...And I'll get it all.
He told you I was dead, huh?
Yes... that's what he said.
I could never kill anyone.
Tell her, tell her what happened!
When he came to,
we were on the boat.
I held my gun on him...
...told him I wanted to kill him.
Told him that I knew everything.
He begged me to spare him...
...he started crying.
Watch out, I'm the one with the gun now.
A gun can't change anything now.
After that, I forced him to write
and sign the confession.
I offered him 50,000 new francs...
...and he took it.
I would have given him much more.
Poor loser, it's all his money.
When did you get back?
Same time as him.
I saw you two making love.
You got off on it huh?
Yes, she did.
You shut up, I'm talking to her now.
I thought about you all the time Jeff.
Julie!
You're coming with me.
We're going to get back the dough,
the jewels and my confession.
You watch him, I'll be back in half hour.
Jeff! Let me come with you.
Please!
Watch him carefully.
I won't be long.
You lied to me!
Be quiet!
They're gone.
Louis, Louis...
What's the matter?
Talk to me, Louis.
You know very well
it was a just a put on, nothing more.
"Put on" sometimes kill...
We don't think about it,
and one day it happens.
Hold on, hold on, don't move.
Hold on tight, I'll be back soon.
Good, stay here.
Shit
About time.
Hello yes. It's me.
- Is that him?
- Yes, hold on.
Tell him Thorent came in
with a man who could be Jeff Marlo.
Thorent just came in with a man
who could be Jeff Marlo.
Are you sure?
Thorent just went in to his place
with a man who could be Jeff Marlo
What?
- What do we do?
- Wait a second.
Hello, just one second.
Let me think.
Tell them to stay put.
If someone comes out, follow him discreetly.
Be ready to tail if one of them comes out?
He says stay put
and get ready for "tailing".
Tell him we're coming.
- Hello, I'll be right there.
- Very good, Inspector.
What a mess!
What are you doing here?
Louis is dying, quick, quick
Julie.
What happened?
You shot him?
He's dying.
His heart is giving out.
- We've got to save him,
Jeff. Hurry, help me!
Hurry...
No, no! Don't stop!
Why?
Everything is fine.
Don't stop, he's dying,
I've got 200 G's back there.
And I burned my confession.
Where is George?
Don't worry about it.
Did you kill him?
Never mind. If your husband dies
we have what we wanted.
Everything worked out for the best, no?
But I can't leave him like this.
He's suffering.
You're going to make me cry.
Let's get the fuck out of here,
let's disappear.
We're free and rich Julie, rich.
I don't want to go with you.
Oh, So you're only
interested in the money.
You want to dump me like
a piece of shit? You whore.
You're mine,
you hear me, you're mine.
You're mine.
I'm going to make you come, you slut.
- You're going to scream like you never have.
- You're mine.
- No Jeff, stop!
- Tell me you want some, tell me again.
- No, say it again.
- No!
- Say it again.
- No.
- Cuff him.
- Julie, Julie!
We've got to save my husband.
Your husband is dead Madam.
Your client is waiting in the green office.
- Where is it?
- Follow me.
Thank you, officer.
You don't look like you're well.
Hello?
You don't want to talk to me?
Admit that I've done you nothing but good!
No, you don't want to.
I was told you were traumatized
by this whole affair. Understandable...
...your position could be a lot worse
We're going to pin everything
on your boyfriend, he asked for it.
I'll bet he gets a solid ten to fifteen.
As for you my beauty, it's cake...
I'll have you freed on your word...
...and you'll get a year, a year
and a half probation.
This is unbearable.
What do you want me to say?
I don't know, you could say thank you.
Thank you.
In a way, you got everything you wanted.
You're rich, and your husband is dead.
Please, be quiet.
A lawyer never stops talking,
you should know that.
I would give everything to have Louis alive.
Oh the fickleness of women!
I get the feeling you hate me.
No, not especially.
What is it?
It's odd. When I tried killing my husband
nothing happened to me...
...now I'm trying to save him
and I'm being punished.
That, my beauty,
is the puzzle of justice.
The truth is whatever
people want to believe.
And don't forget
that it's a man's world.
With laws made by men, for men.
It's men's justice.
You're not even trying
to understand me.
The law doesn't give a damn
about understanding.
Come on, the Judge is waiting.
Julie!!!
Julie!!
Julie!!!!
Julie!!!!!
Ripped by:
SkyFury