Jesus..., oh!
God!!
No Metal in the microwave.
No metal!
Martha, it's Robert.
Just to let you know to
keep an eye peeled
for the first reviews of
your breathlessly awaited first novel.
Word is, the Times is going to rave,
rave, rave.
Talk to you soon.
Thank you.
You look like shit.
Where's Grandpa?
He's so cute with the headphones on.
Hi Grandpa!
Hi
Do you think he remembers me?
Come on, it's a steal.
You've got to see it.
You'll have your own room to
write in.
Grandpa could be out in
the back chopping bricks
or whatever he does out there.
You'd never even know he existed.
I wish he didn't.
God, he's really getting you down.
From the way Alex has acted for
the last seven years,
you would have
thought he didn't have a father.
And then boom,
a month ago this shows up on
the doorstep.
I haven't written a word since.
Well, Alex has got to get him out
of here.
It's not that simple with Alex
and frankly we can't afford to
buy another place
let it alone to buy a mansion.
Of course you can
especially if your mother's offer is
still good.
Alex will never accept money
from her, you know that.
Work on Him!
For God sakes, Martha,
you have alot to learn about men.
And you have a lot to
learn about husbands.
Sorry.
It's OK.
I am getting a dog.
Hi Alex!
Smells good.
Good Jeremy.
Grandpa, I'm home.
How's my boy!
What's that?
It's a book that I made for you.
Animals that change.
One day
I saw the most weird thing.
It was a turtle and a fish, and a rat.
They lived in a puddle of potion.
They grew.
They destroied the universe.
The end.
Jeremy gets some ideas.
Come on,
let's clean up for the dinner.
Dad
you shouldn't eat so
much fat at your age.
How are you today?
Did you watch
those tapes I rented for you?
Terrible!
Then I'll get you some
Taiwanese Shows.
They'll be just as bad.
Well, what about some
Hong Kong Kung Fu movies?
The worst!
Their Kung Fu's a joke.
Dad! They're only acting,
but you are a Tai Chi master.
To learn English is boring to me.
To go back?
Even more boring.
My life is going to nowhere.
Dad.
It hasn't even been a month
since you retired and came to
the States.
Give yourself some time.
Jeremy
Come here
Come here! You little rascal.
Come here.
Come here, Jeremy.
Get off the couch.
I don't have time for this, come here.
Whoa!
My precious young man
running barely naked!
The future of our Chu family
depends on your little treasure.
What does he think he's doing?
That's all right
Chinese elders must
always reassure themselves
that their family name will go on.
Come on Jeremy, upstairs with you!
Eh? She's afraid he'll catch coId.
Kids aren't made out of paper.
Thanks.
No, thanks.
Why this American woman only
eats vegetables?
She's afraid of getting fat.
Why am I not fat?
On this Earth there are
two kinds of food.
Vegetables are "yin".
Meat is "yang".
You must eat both to be balanced.
Then the man can be completed.
Alex, Linda came over today.
Great.
What's that supposed to mean?
Just great.
What exactly do you have to
against her anyway?
So what if was a Maoist in coIlege.
From Maoist revolutionary to
real estate baron.
If there's one thing worse than
a communist,
it's an ex-communist who has
become a capitalist.
Well, she's ready to
do us quite a big favor.
Oh no, she's trying to
sell us a house again.
What's she mumbling about?
Nothing.
Something about cigarette butts?
What?
Mom said she wants to move out.
Quiet!
Alex, I'm talking to you.
Mom, can I watch cartoons?
Here.
Put some meat on your bones!
I don't want it, thank you.
Jeremy, finish your milk and
you can watch TV.
What did she say?
If he finish his milk,
he can watch TV.
American people teach children
like they're doing business.
Everything's a deal.
You should at least take
a look at the photos.
It's apparently a real steal.
If children can't concentrate
on eating,
what else can they concentrate on?
Yes, father.
And these American cartoons
are only adding weirdness and
violence
to mess up the world,
For children?
It's just a mess.
Our sages said...
Dad...
Just eat!
Please don't get upset.
I'm just afraid
your dinner's getting coId.
What has he been babbling about?
The violence in cartoons.
How could he complain?
He's a martial arts expert himself.
Isn't that violent enough?
Would you cut it off?
Both of you!
Just eat.
You finish up.
I'm going out for a smoke.
In America, you're so polite to kids.
You think so?
You don't treat kids as kids
It's interesting.
It's very interesting.
It's called democracy.
Democracy means no big and
no little.
Ok,
you understand America better than
I do.
Chinese Time.
Jeremy, stop playing.
Come on, time for homework.
Alex.
The teachers here can't
speak Chinese fluently,
how can kids learn in the good way?
They are fine,
don't be too picky!
We only have
one Chinese schooI around here.
Every weekend,
Jeremy learns some Chinese,
I can play basketball,
and you get to teach Tai Chi.
Thanks God for it!
No matter how they teach it,
We learn it by their ways.
Eh! Not like that!
Dad, I've got some things to
take care of.
Jeremy,
look!
Grandpa will teach you an
oId Chinese rhyme.
On East West Street.
North South Go.
Outside the gate, a man bites a dog!
Grab the dog to hit a brick.
Watch out!
That brick might bite the hand.
FoIlow Grandpa.
On East West Street.
North South Go.
Outside the gate a dog bites a man.
A dog bites a man!
A man bites a dog!
Shit!
Just one more sentence.
Okay.
How's your computer virus?
Almost killed.
When can
I start reading your new book?
There is no new book, can't you tell
Shit Alex,
are as out of it as your father
You don't know my father.
I have spent every single day
in the same room with that man
since he showed up here
a month ago.
Alex, it's impossible.
He has taken over my work room,
I just don't have the space to think.
Not enough space?
In China,
this house is big enough for
four families.
Sure, but they'd speak the
same language
so they could talk to each other.
Alex he hasn't learned one word
of English.
And what about you?
What have you done
but making fun of him,
treating him with disrespect?
Alex, I've tried.
I'm his only son.
What do you want me to do?
You could consider moving into
a bigger place.
We can afford it.
No.
I don't see why we have to
pay for his insurance,
letting him eat us out of
house and home
when we can't accept a little loan
from my mother.
It's not a little loan,
it's a bride,
a big bride,
and you know it.
You look a little freaked out here.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Good night, Alex.
Honestly, Linda,
I don't know why we're here.
Come on, let's explore.
Father and the son.
Father.
Mom.
M for mom...
Mother.
Son.
Punch.
Sweep.
Step back.
CoIlect a cloud.
Hook.
Step out.
Single whip.
Raise hands and step up.
Lean.
White crane spreads its wing.
Left hand ward off,
and right hand attack.
Excuse me,
are you the instructor here?
My name is Chen.
I teach the cooking class.
Could you please do me a favor?
What is your name?
Chu.
Master Chu.
Please, we're all friends here.
Don't call me master.
Mr. Chu.
I don't know what our principal
is thinking,
my class is making dumplings,
half-done.
Some workmen just came
in to do some repairs,
and we have to leave.
I see you have plenty of space here,
Could we move in?
Just this once?
Dumplings can be moved in,
but they can't be moved out.
We've also got scallion pancakes
and spring roIIs!
Come on, let's help!
Thank you.
Sink your chest.
Stretch your back.
Imagine a string pulling up
your head.
Sink lower your body.
Lower.
Master Chu,
don't torture the child!
Look at all his weight.
How can he "sink his chest"?
Let him help me knead the dough.
Oh, it's so difficult.
Mrs Chen,
next week I'll help you to make dumplings.
Can I be enroIled?
There will be
no dumplings next week,
but General's Tso's Special Chicken.
Master Chu,
would you please demonstrate
how to emit force with
Pushing Hands?
Okay,
let's try.
Thank you.
Ouch, would that hurt?
Master Chu, try me!
I cannot move you.
So your Kung Fu can only go so far!
Okay.
Hey!
Mr. Chu right there!
Can you take the fighting away?
Don't you see these burners
and the boiling water!
It's alright if the
heavyweight gets burned,
but if you smash the dumplings,
what should we eat then?
We'll eat roast pigling!
OK, OK!
Far enough?
I'm ready Master!
What! Haven't you any eyes to see!
Sorry, sorry!
I don't mean you!
It's your Master who wasn't looking!
Hey,
of all the directions,
why did you throw the
heavyweight on my dumplings!
Excellent aim!
Okay! No dumplings today!
Instead, we'll have sandy
crab scalded noodle lump soup!
I'm sorry, it was a mistake.
It wasn't on purpose!
It was on purpose!
Are you OK?
In front of all these people sooner
or later,
I knew you'd show off!
All the skills you have learned,
will be shown to all the audiences.
Sorry, sorry!
Okay! Don't stand there with
a red face!
Let's clean up!
Sure.
Everyone helps!
No more Tai Chi Chuan!
We'll make dumplings!
Come..., did you hear that!
Master says no more Tai Chi!
Hurry up!
Heavyweight, wipe your face!
Oh my goodness,
what's this shape?
HoId on, let me see your hands.
Filthy!
Men, all of you wash your hands.
Use soap!
No dirty hands on my dumplings.
Is that clear?
Hurry up!
Mr Chu,
please have a seat.
Let the young people stand.
Come and have a seat.
Not bad.
Thin skin, plump stuffing, nice twist.
It's nothing.
Northerners like making things
from dough.
Where did you come from?
Are you from Beijing?
Yes.
How long have you been here?
Just over a month.
Are you used to it here?
If I was,
would I be here messing around.
Watch what you're saying,
I'm here too.
I didn't mean it.
America is a world for young people.
Are you also from Beijing?
Do I seem like I am?
By your accent, yes;
by the way you look, no.
That's right.
I went to Taiwan
with my husband in 1949.
And Mr Chen is?
He is dead.
His name wasn't Chen.
Not long after we arrived in Taiwan,
he got liver cancer and passed away.
I'm called Mrs Chen
because of my second husband.
Oh..., and Mr. Chen?
He's dead too,
just in last year.
Life and death, it's fate.
Riches and rags are
given by the gods.
You just accept it.
Everything is destiny.
Sure, sure.
Earlier this year,
I left Taiwan for here with
my daughter.
Every Saturday,
I bring my granddaughter here to
study Chinese.
Are you used to it here?
How did you put it just now?
If I wasn't so bored at home,
how could your Heavyweight have
smashed that.
A computer couldn't have
aimed more accurately.
Destiny, it's all destiny.
That's right!
What a great Kung Fu!
What's the matter?
Since last year,
Sometimes my right
arm just gives out.
When I pick up
something a little heavy,
it's out of control...,
it's useless.
Have you seen a doctor?
Yes.
Chinese doctors, western doctors,
accupressure, acupuncture,
herbal remedies, shots, medicine.
I've tried everything
but getting a spell cast on me.
I'm just oId.
Mrs Chen,
I don't want to sound like a self-promoter
but practicing Tai Chi will
heal your arm.
Okay, give me a break!
Haven't I suffered enough in this life.
Practice!
I am not that stupid.
When you practice Tai Chi,
your circulation and energy will flow.
I've let go, I'm not hoIding on.
Energy must be released,
cannot be practiced.
When its released there's no tension,
and one feels at ease.
What's up?
The review, I can't find it.
When you arrive at oId age,
everything is quiet.
There the gentle wind
passes through the pine forest.
Fifteen minutes to practice.
Okay.
When the moon is rising and
shining on the mountain.
I only want to go to
the familiar forest.
I reply with
a simple fisherman's song.
Alex?
Yes?
Where can we mount
Chinese calligraphy in NY?
Who's the present for?
You know, last week,
I smashed Mrs Chen's dumplings.
I was so embarrassed,
and I want to give her this.
I'm just afraid she'll laugh at
my calligraphy.
C come on, Dad,
we know you're good.
What's the matter?
They've ignored the book.
Just pretended that it doesn't exist.
It will be in the next week.
What's the matter with her?
There is no review of her book.
Just tell her,
years from now,
we'll all be lying peacefully underground.
What's the big deal?
Dad, when're we going?
OK!
What is it?
A stomach cramp or something.
Nothing important.
Do you want to
lie down on the couch?
What's wrong with her?
A stomach cramp.
Let me take a look,
make her lie down.
Dad said he wants to take a look at it.
He knows this kind of thing.
He does?
Yes, he is an expert.
She's too nervous,
something's wrong with her stomach.
You are too tight.
Thanks for letting me know.
Tell her to relax.
Just relax.
What happened!
Mom!
Relax!
Oh my God! Get away from me!
What did you do to her!
Her stomach's bleeding!
Quick get her to the hospital!
I want to go too.
Jeremy, be good.
You broke Mama.
Jeremy wants a goIdfish, right?
Here's a big tail,
big eyes,
thick lips.
And wings.
What's Martha's condition?
She has to stay in the hospital for
her bleeding stomach.
How's Mommy?
Yes?
Mommy is all right,
and she just needs a little rest.
I didn't do anything to her,
but she did it to herself.
I know that.
Can I go to the hospital with you?
Dad.
Is this the calligraphy you
want matted?
Go and take care of Martha,
and just leave alone.
Can I have some macaroni and
cheese please?
Wait until Sunday when
your mother comes home, all right?
Hi, Master Chu.
Hello everyone.
Master Chu, they toId me that
your kung-fu is great.
Last week, you sent Mr.
Sung flying by barely touching him.
And threw the fatty Zhao on
the dumplings, too.
I am flattered.
Where is Mrs Chen?
I don't know.
She is not teaching anymore.
Now I am the teacher.
Not teaching anymore? Yes.
Why? I don't know.
Maybe you can ask them.
Their family changes to
the school in north.
If you want to find her,
you can ask the principal about
her telephone number
OK, I will go for my class.
No General Tso's Special Chicken
today?
There is no left cock or right hen,
but the "Stoky Rice" today.
"Stoky Rice"?
Yes,
"Stoky Rice".
Oh yes, STICKY RICE.
Hey, will you throw the fatty Zhao
on our sticky rice?
Alex, will you make a call for me?
What's that?
Mrs Chen's family doesn't come
here any more.
And calligraphy is mounted,
we should contact and
send it to them.
It's their answer machine.
Yici Chen, this is Alex Chu.
My Dad has a present to
give your mother.
Give us a call when you are back
at 287-0425.
Thanks.
How can you talk like that?
Like what?
Enough! I won't go to
the hospital with you to see Martha.
Take me home to wait for the call.
Relax, they're not going anywhere.
I can't communicate with Martha.
You'll be there for hours,
and all I can do is stare at ceiling.
Okay.
Hey mister, don't make fun of me!
I never make fun of any one.
What's that?
A grenade!!
Hello, yes, it is Mr. Chu speaking.
Yes? Mrs Chen?
Why weren't you at school?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no, please don't listen to my kid.
What a nonsense!
It's not a present.
I'm still embarrassed about last week
that I just messed your class up.
Ok. How about this?
Tomorrow at 11:00 am,
my son will pick his wife up
from the hospital.
We'll come by at 10:30 am,
does that work?
Yes?
Its' nothing serious,
she has a small stomach problem.
Then we make the appointment.
Fine,
see you tomorrow.
Hello, Uncle Chu!
Sorry for bothering.
Not at all, welcome!
Mom, they are here.
How are you, Yici?
Hi Jeremy.
Hi Yi-yi.
Why are you all guarding the door?
Come in.
Maybe next time,
we've got to get to
the hospital to pick up my wife.
Oh, you can't be late then.
Is your wife all right?
What am I talking about!
She is getting out of the hospital.
Mr Chu, how are you?
Good. Mrs Chen,
is there a cooking class at
your new school?
Not until I showed up.
There's a Kung Fu class too.
But it's only Karate.
Their Momentum is stronger than
Tai Chi Chuan.
But they can't throw people
as far as you can.
And they don't perform
as handsome as you do.
Much worse.
Dad, we better get going.
We planned for you to
stay for dinner,
and we even went food shopping
for that,
but you've got to get to the hospital,
So maybe next time.
Thanks and bye.
Uh, you stopped by today to?
Ah! I forget.
You shouldn't have. Thank you.
I'm going to hang it up right away.
It's nothing.
Drive carefully!
Bye. Good bye!
What's the rush!
We didn't even get the scroII open!
Thanks!
Toothache?
I thought there is
not much you can do,
a lot of problems for sure you have.
Mr Philips called.
Jeremy received the
lowest reading scores
in the gifted class again.
That schooI is
too distracting for him.
No Alex,
we're too distracting for him.
He's only responding to
the atmosphere at home.
Then change it!
What's your problem?
I ain't got any problem.
Get back in the car, Alex!
You get back in the car lady!
Shut up!
Great!
Martha?
What do you want?
I wanna go for a walk.
A walk?
I don't know.
I don't want to see if you get lost.
Smoking.
You know,
in a way I'm kind of baby sitting you.
I'll just hang around, won't go too far.
I'll just hang around,
won't go too far.
All right. Go ahead.
What do I care.
Oh Jeremy. Where'd you get those.
Teddy gave them to me.
That's disgusting!
Wel, I go put them away.
Go on. Go get yourself cleaned up.
Dad.
What're you looking for?
Dad. Where is he?
Oh no.
Where is he?
Is he back?
No.
Did you check with the police?
Alex, I'm sorry.
I should've been more careful.
But I'm...,
with the book...
In some ways,
your father is more and more like
a child cooped up here with me.
And I can't talk to him.
I was trying to write.
I had a feeling that
he was gonna get himself lost
just like a kid rying to
get some attention.
I grew up in believing
you should care for your parents
the way they care for you.
My father is a part of me.
Why can't you accept that.
I know.
I tried.
Just leave me alone.
Oh my god. You've found him.
Thanks God, he's safe and sound.
We're looking for Mr chu.
Alex is still out looking for his father.
I'm his wife.
Okay. Mr Chu,
you take care of yourself. All right?
Thank you very much officers.
Alex is still out looking for you.
Are you hungry?
Thirsty?
You really should eat something.
I'm sorry too.
Alex is furious.
Jesus.
How did you get so drunk?
Dad, where did you go?
I was just walking around
and I lost sight of the church steeple,
my landmark.
Policemen brought him back
two hours ago.
You're back, that's good.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I won't bump this wall,
if I know this wall isn't thick.
What're you doing? Stop it!
Mom?
Calm down.
Jeremy, Dad isn't feeling well,
he'll be all right.
Let me talk him.
Jeremy,
Dad banged his head by accident.
Do you need a band aid!
Okay.
Jeremy.
Only Jeremy is good.
Jeremy cares for me better than
Mommy and Grandpa do.
I haven't seen you that drunk since
the night we've got married.
That drunk?
Yeah.
Well, my head is clear now.
What're you mumbling about?
I've made up my mind already.
About what?
The oId man has got to go.
I'll send him to
an oId people's apartment.
Are you sure?
I really don't have too much choice,
do l?
I'll go tell him right now.
Come in.
Dad, why didn't you get up and
exercise today?
Aren't you feeling well?
What's wrong?
I was being outside
too long last night,
so maybe I catch a coId for that.
I'm going to call a doctor.
You've got
important business at work,
don't waste your time on me.
Come on, dad,
cut it out!
You're never sick,
if you don't feel well,
it must be serious.
I'm going to call a doctor.
Why get sick now?
The vital organs are not in harmony.
The circulation's blocked.
That's why one is sick.
Dad, Ma's been gone for
so many years,
and you've never wanted to
look at her picture.
I couldn't face her.
Do you remember this scar!?
When the red guards came to
our house,
they knew that they couldn't hurt me,
so they took it out on you and
your mother.
I only had this one body!
In protecting you,
I couldn't protect your mother.
When they finally stopped
their beating,
she was too gravely injured to
survive.
In this one life,
I can never face your mother again,
but I can face you!
Dad,
It's been so many years,
why talk about it now?
I feel stifled.
Let me tell you something,
comparing to loneliness,
persecution is easy.
Look at how much hardship and
injustice
I've endured in the last 40 years,
their tortures only inspired me
to perfect my Kung Fu.
To study the
"Soft Internal Style of Strength",
we pursue the state with the loss of
tension,
so we can attain concentration.
And from that one,
we achieve carefree,
then this is nearly impossible to
be upgraded.
Sure, the surface is always easier.
Go on,
don't bullshit me!
I'll go call a doctor.
Do me a favor and call the
Chinese schooI principal
tell him that I can't teach the class
on Saturday.
Okay. You'll go when you're better.
I'm not going anymore.
Why?
The students always want me to
show off. I hate that.
Then what will you do on
the weekends?
Why don't we change to
that schooI north of here?
You mean with Mrs Chen?
No!
They say it'll be good for
Jeremy's studies.
I heard they're much stricter.
How about it?
So did you tell him?
He's sick. Caught a coId from
last night.
I couldn't tell him.
I hope it's not serious.
No, I don't think so.
But I'd better take him to the doctor.
I've got a great idea
about what to do with him
without hurting anyone's feelings.
What's that?
Just be patient.
Promise me,
you'll be nice to him for the time being.
Okay?
Go on.
You have something to do?
Nothing.
Then why do you keep looking
at your watch?
Nothing.
Hello?
Oh... yes... Yici.
How's the picnic?
Sorry for bothering you.
...yes,
it's great weather,
and it is a pity if you don't go picnic.
Unfortunately, he doesn't have
much energy now.
If he got sick again,
it'll be trouble.
Maybe we should let him to
have some rest.
Okay.
Say thank you to Chen Mama for me.
Okay? That's it.
Don't hang up,
Don't hang up, hoId on.
Who said that I'm sick?
I didn't say sick, I said energy.
"No energy" means that
you need to get out!
Yici,
my father says he's fine,
he'd like to get some exercise.
Let's do it by the same plan.
Yes.
Okay.
That's settled then.
Bye.
Right.
How can it be healthy to
stay home all the time!
That's how you get sick!
Ma, I've already had two.
Have more!
Here YiYi.
Thank you.
Kids should eat more.
Jeremy?
No, thank you.
Have more!
Help yourself, don't worry about him.
Have another piece.
No..., thank you.
Listen to me, there's lots of meat,
and there's no point in saving it.
I have to
leave some room for tonight.
It's only the middle of the day,
and a man shouldn't worry for this.
Come on!
I haven't eaten since
yesterday morning.
I'm preparing for
the dinner you're cooking tonight.
He is a stupid one.
Nonsense!
Here.
Please let me have it.
He's reaching middle age,
he's afraid of fat,
cholesteroI, and high blood pressure.
Ma, again?
Yes, damn it.
Can you give me a little massage.
Let me take a look.
How can I let you do that?
It's okay.
Did you find the spot?
This is troublesome.
If it's trouble, leave it alone.
Noop,
The Chi in your Bladder Meridian
is too strong,
but the blood is too weak.
This kind of problem is called
"Mid-Spring Paralysis".
Now try to move the pinky toe on
your left foot.
Did you feel that subtle pain?
So, I was right.
When this illness gets serious,
you'll get a spasm under your knee,
sore waist,
your back will give out,
your neck will tense up,
you won't be able to lift your arm,
and your muscles will be stretched
between your armpits in
one tight knot.
Enough!
Stop! Once you keep diagnosing,
all my internal organs will be shown!
Let me see.
It's her right shoulder that's stiff.
He knows!
He was rubbing your left hand.
Shush!
It's burning.
Burning?
Your meat, on the barbeque.
Why don't you pay attention to
your own business?
Mr Chu, thank you.
I've just begun.
You've got a complicated problem.
It would take over a year of
treatment to get results.
What a bother! Okay,
don't break me apart.
Jeremy, let's go play frisbee.
Oh goody, goody
I want to look too.
Don't got too far,
you hear me?
Okay.
Mr. Chu,
your Kung Fu is so powerful,
how do you manage to
have such elegant calligraphy?
I'm ashamed to talk about it.
My grandfather was
a Ching Dynasty Scholar,
my father was one of
the Nation Founders
who's in charge of
the Nationalist government.
My son is a PhD in computer science.
In the middle of this line,
there's worthless me.
Fate and circumstances
pushed me to spend my life
on practicing martial arts.
You shouldn't say that.
I had poor health when I was a kid.
I'm an only son.
My family was worried.
They took one of the doctor's advice
and made me practicing Kung Fu.
I couldn't take the rough styles,
I could only take the
gentle styles like Tai Chi Chuan.
Who would have thought that
a couple years later,
I was completely vigorous and healthy.
At 30,
I won a national Tai Chi Pushing
Hands Championship.
Exercising the body and
teaching students,
that's a relatively simple,
trouble-free life.
Trouble-free?
Since the communist liberation,
I've suffered all the pains.
Let's not talk about it.
When it comes to eaching students,
it has also hurt me so much.
Oh..., yes,
have you gone back to see
your oId home and
relatives since Taiwan loosened up?
Two years ago,
I went back but
I don't have any close relative
but just some nieces and nephews.
Still, a reunion with your family,
it must have been a happy time.
Not really.
When I left,
they were not born yet.
I felt like Santa Claus,
giving so many gifts.
There's no fun at all.
Beijing seemed to have
lost its flavor,
The oId warmth was gone.
But I was very young when
I left 40 years ago,
maybe my memories are mistaken,
anyways,
I don't know what to
say but everything seemed unreal,
I couldn't put my oId and
new impression together.
Mr. Chen,
Your impressions are not mistaken.
Beijing has changed a lot.
Is that so?
I feel closer when talking with you
than talking with
my neighbors in Beijing.
Really?
Relax, don't move.
Mom, you're still in one piece.
Child!
Dad, we're going to
take the kids up the hill.
Don't go too far, you hear me?
Okay.
Don't leave us here!
I'm going with you.
It's a steep climb.
You won't make it.
I'll take it slow.
Let's get everything cleaned up
and put in the car.
Mrs Chen,
let the young foIks go ahead.
You take it slow.
No, I'm fine.
How come your son-in-law
didn't come today?
Gone... gone... a... way
on bus... business.
If he weren't away...,
we wouldn't have you over for dinner.
Don't mention him!
He makes me angry.
What about your daughter-in-law?
We have almost the same story here.
Chen Mama,
it's too much for you, let's go down.
Ah, Ah..., shut up, just keep going.
Grandma!
Grandpa!
Don't run so fast, wait for me.
Hey!
The young people are so energetic.
They can't slow down,
just let them go ahead.
I'll climb slowly with you.
Why not sit down and rest a bit?
I'm old and useless.
No one wants me.
We're out for fun,
why get mad at the kids?
How can you be so
developed in Kung Fu
but have no insight?
They set us up,
can't you tell this?
Set us up?
Your precious son
came to our house last week
and arranged for my daughter.
He asked my daughter to
call and invit you.
They thought that I was taking a nap,
but actually I heard everything.
Can't it be?
It cen't be?
At our age,
why don't we have any self-respect,
but letting those
two children manipulate us?
What's this for?
Devalue me for my oId and useless.
Son, thank you for your kindness
trying to fix me up with Mrs Chen.
But we still have our pride.
No need to drive oId persons out.
I have the sense to leave on my own.
You know the oId saying that
"It's easier to struggle together
than to pass happy days together."
I've never imagined that
this would apply to
us father and the son.
How many difficult times in China,
we could overcome challenges
happily together.
But here in US with so
many fine-material things,
it seems there's no place in
your home for me.
Comparing the two,
I can't help but recall the days
when you were a small lovely boy.
Don't look for me.
Enjoy your life with your family.
I wish you all the best.
If you have time,
send my regards to Mrs.
Chen and her daughter.
The world is so big,
how can't one find
a little corner for him?
I'll rent a little room,
so I can spend my worthless oId age.
Life passes before
one's eyes like smoke,
so one shouldn't set his heart
on anything.
Father.
Hurry up!
Thank you, come again.
Bye-bye.
Please wash the bowls faster.
If I can't put out the soup,
my other dishes can't go out.
I'll wash you a bowl first,
then the dishes.
Sorry.
Thanks.
Old Chu, I beg you, please do it faster.
Coming, coming.
Why do you keep sending out
the take-away orders?
There's guests at the tables with
nothing to eat!
And a line around the block!
Boss, we can't put out the
food without dishes!
Yesterday at the employment agency,
you said you had experience!
More or less, I am getting used to it.
I'm running a business to make money,
not to invite you for the free lunch!
What do you mean more or less?
This is less!
Yeah, yeah, don't get mad,
I'm hurrying.
Soak the plates with
solid-honey in hot water.
Don't just scrape them!
You break the plate,
you pay for it!
Yes.
Boss,
can you please do us a favor?
How about not selling those
stupid honey banana balls?
It's hard for us to make and
hard for him to wash.
Not worth it.
I'll decide if it's worthy or not!
If you don't do it,
others will!
Come on,
it's just a good hearted suggestion.
Thanks!
What are
you three guys stuck here for?
Waiting for bowls.
Can't you do
something else while you are waiting?
Are you brain dead.
There's nothing else to do!
Are the
Mu Shu Pork pancakes steamed?
In the steamer.
Sauteed Minced Pigeon with
Sliced Vegetables?
Vegetables are soaked.
The wontons are boiling,
the orders are taken,
the tables are cleared,
the checks are paid.
Chu,
here's today's pay.
Thank you.
It doesn't work.
Don't come tomorrow,
I'll find someone else.
Boss he's going okay now.
There were enough dishes.
And there is no problem when
taking orders.
What do you mean "enough dishes",
"no problem"?
It was only after the dinner rush hour
that things returned to normal.
Don't be pleading for
him because he's oId.
Lots of young guys would fight for
the chance
to make 700 doIlars a
month washing dishes.
Why should I have an oId man?
I'm not running an nursing home.
Are you kidding?
Boss, please give me one more chance.
We all have to start, right?
Okay, okay. One more chance.
Thank you.
Is Sargeant Warren there?
It's Alex Chu...
Yes.
No?
Thanks Sargeant.
Bye bye.
Linda?
It's Alex.
Let's have a talk...
...about the house.
Hey, congratulations on your review:
"A boId new voice in women's fiction"
Better late then never.
I'm proud of you,
although,
it makes me feel like I should quit my job
and become a painter.
In the meantime, all I do is eat.
Maybe you're pregnant.
Sure, if you believe in
immaculate conception.
You know,
I'm even thinking of going to
my high schooI reunion
to see if there are
any aging jocks sill available.
Oh, Linda!
Well, at least I have my work.
How's yours coming?
Two chapters this week.
Oh, more travails of
study pioneer women.
Actually,
I've written in a Chinese family.
The father brought over
to work on the railroads.
Don't tell me you miss the oId geezer?
Of course not.
Runaway Grandpa.
I'm gonna have nightmares for
the rest of my life
imagining his face every morning
on the side of my milk cartons.
It's sad.
And Alex...
He blames you, does he?
No, he's just anxious...,
and I blame myself.
Ah! Li, how can I let you do this?
You'd better do your own work,
Don't worry about me.
Hurry up, once I get busy,
I won't be able to help you anyway.
Wu, everyone's got work to do.
Don't treat me special.
I can take care of myself,
you also have works to do.
Chu, this is for you,
I've got someone.
Boss, I've been doing all right.
Eight bowls,
five plates,
now it's only 6:30 pm,
and you even need those two to
help you.
What will happen at 7:30?
My guests will be
lined up outside the door?
He didn't ask for help,
we volunteered.
You volunteered? Fine!
He asked for help, fine!
I don't care.
I can't take any risks tonight.
Liu
go downstairs and
get yourself an apron.
Here's ten doIlars,
take it or leave it.
Boss, do you have to
treat an oId man this way?
I'll wash faster.
Not just faster, but cleaner too!
Come on, cut the crap, go!
Time is money.
Have you heard that before?
Probably not,
you came from Mainland China.
I know everything's shared there,
working more but gets you nothing.
Four decades of
such thinking has produced
all you lazy bums.
Useless trash.
Who are you calling a useless trash?
Eh? What's wrong?
You don't accept that?
Then go back to China and
live off others. Go on!
No one's stopping you.
I'm telling you,
this is America.
There's no communal property.
You have to earn everything
by yourself!
You wanna be an American?
Go all the way!
Buy a dishwasher to
wash faster and cleaner.
Yeh! I'm offering you ten doIlars
because I respect your age.
I'm saving face for you,
if you don't want that,
then I'll throw you out!
See if you can.
Don't think I won't touch you
because you're oId.
Come try me!
If you can move me half a step,
I won't say another word,
but turn and leave.
Don't...
So the oId geezer knows Kung Fu.
No wonder you dared be
so arrogant with me!
Li, Wu,
help me!
I'm not getting involved in this.
Chang, Chien,
get over here!
Boss, this is none of our business.
Do you want to keep working here?
Quick!
Old Chu,
don't get angry, but we've all got
families to take care of.
We'll just move you half a step, okay?
Then the business will keep going,
and everyone will thank you.
Come on, careful now.
Come on.
Get him!
Liu, help out!
Do something!
Chu, you're a hero.
We can't move you.
We brothers apologize.
Boss Huang,
we quit!
Go find yourself some
shameless big muscles rogues.
I can't take this!
Hey, you can't all leave!
Okay!
I'm calling every employment agency!
Don't think you'll work in
New York again!
All right tough guy!
The business is closed tonight.
Think you are good?
But I'm calling the cops on you!
I don't have a green card.
You hired me illegally.
They'll fine
you three thousand doIlars first.
I'm telling you,
I'll move you without the cops!
Thank you, come again.
The oId bum is in the kitchen.
Go and smash him!
Show no mercy!
Yeah, I've seen this kind before.
Ten police officers from
the Fifth Precinct
were injured earlier this evening
in a brawl inside
a Chinatown restaurant.
Helen Wong reports.
Shirley, I'm standing in
front of the Lai Fu restaurant.
The owner Frankie Huang tried to fire
his seventy year oId dishwasher here
earlier this evening.
But Huang get more than
he bargained for
because the man he tried to fire Mr Chu
refused to leave the restaurant.
Alex.
Police said that Mr.
Chu is a Tai Chi master.
And he let lose a hundred
thirty pounds of martial arts fury.
And hurt over a dozen of
New York's finest.
Now it appears that
Mr Chu's being lead out of
the restaurant by the police
and is being put into a squad car
and taken to the precinct and
be arrested.
Peporting live, Helen Wong,
now back to you at the studio.
He's been like this ever since
he came in.
The entire time he has been here,
he hasn't said anything
nor has he eaten anything either
to drink.
I tell you,
I don't know if he's meditating or
sleeping.
If you don't mind me saying so,
Mr Chu,
it's kind of depressing.
I'll let you go in and talk to him.
Thank you, officer.
Any time.
Dad.
Ah, attaining nothingness isn't easy.
Dad, we've bought a new house,
it's much bigger than the oId one.
What for?
I'm here to take you home.
Home? Who's home?
Mine is yours.
Forget it. I see clearly now,
the only thing that matters
is that you have a happy life.
If you want to
show me some filial respect,
rent me an apartment in Chinatown.
Let me peacefully pass my days
and discipline my spirit.
In your free time,
bring the boy to see me.
By this way, when we get together,
there'll still be some good feelings.
Dad,
all these years,
I've studied and worked so hard
to build a family
in order that one day
I could bring you to the States,
so you could have some good days
in your life.
Dad!
Alex, can you give a hand up here?
Okay. Coming up
Is this straight?
Lower on the left,
yes.
It's fine.
Do you think he'll ever spend
a night here?
Oh, yes.
As long as Jeremy is here,
Grandpa will visit.
Jeremy wants to be a Tai Chi master.
Why didn't you ever learn any
Tai Chi from your father?
You know, for Dad,
Tai Chi was a way to
escape from reality.
Even when he did pushing hands,
for him, it was a way to
avoid other people.
Pushing hands?
Yeah, it's like Tai Chi for two.
A way of keeping your balance
while unbalancing your opponent.
Like marriage, only kidding.
Okay, you stand like this.
Balanced?
Yup.
If you try to unbalance me,
I simply avoid your energy
and turn it back on you.
Relax.
Don't resist and don't break contact.
Feel it?
Good.
Relax.
Relax little, relax, squat down.
Relax little,
lower.
Relax.
Raise your right arm, too much,
and look at far distance.
Mrs Chen, such a long time!
You've come a long way to
buy groceries.
No, not far. I live in the area.
Your daughter have moved?
No, but I have.
That's great! Living on your own,
you're free.
You can do whatever you want.
I just finished food shopping
saw it was early,
so I decided to stop by your class.
How did you know I was
teaching here?
Wow! Who doesn't know about
the hero oId Mr Chu,
is famous all over Chinatown.
The TV news showed that
a gang of American police and
Chinese hoodlums
were all smashed by you.
From what I can see,
if Tai Chi Chuan could be
practiced upside down,
the ceiling of this oId age centre
would be packed with your students.
You're making fun of me!
I'm speaking the truth.
Did you make a fortune?
No way.
Every morning,
I come here and pass the time with
the students.
Anyways,
we oId foIks have nothing
but time to kill.
That's fine.
I earn my own money and
don't take anybody's flack.
That's why I always say,
you can't hoId everything inside.
Sometimes you've got to
lose your temper
to straighten things out.
The kids are grown up.
If we oId foIks don't take care of
ourselves,
who will?
You're right.
Is your shoulder better?
Better?
At my age, if it doesn't get worse,
I should thank the heavens.
I don't know Kung Fu like you.
But is it convenient living alone?
It's all right.
My daughter comes to visit me
every two or three weeks.
And we will go to movies,
restaurants, or go food shoping.
Uhhhh. That's good.
Alex and his family do the same.
You'd better take care of
your students, I'm leaving.
When you're free, stop by.
Sure, we're neighbors now.
Well, please take care.
You too.
Mrs Chen!
Why did you come out?
To see if you had left.
The sun is so pleasant today.
I was thinking that live by myself,
I could go home or stay out,
both would be good,
anyways, standing here,
I got lost in thoughts.
Where do you live?
I live in that building, room 1168.
I live in that building, room 2101.
Stop by for a visit sometime.
Do you have anything to
do this afternoon?
Uh... Nothing.
Nothing? Nothing.