Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 12
Repeat what I heard just now,
without leaving anything out.
Tell me the truth.
President.
I love Ah Ran.
Now, let go of your daughter-in-law.
Kid, are you crazy?
Is what you're saying human?!
I started liking Ah Ran a long time ago.
Now I can't separate myself from her.
Please...
- Allow us to get married.
- Get out immediately!
I don't want to hear a single word of this.
Never appear in front of us again!
Joo Seung, how could you do something like that?
I...
Loved you like a son!
Why can't I...
- love your daughter-in-law?
- Won't you stop?!
Do you want to Mom and Dad to faint out of anger?!
Mother.
Don't believe what he's saying.
I have no feelings for Dr. Nam at all.
I'll never leave this house.
I want to live my life as Shin Hyun Woo's wife.
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Hyun Woo!
Episode 12
What should Mom do?
Tell me something.
I called, pretending to ask about her,
but she's not back yet.
Everybody seems worried.
Mom has nowhere to go.
Maybe...
Could she have gone to the Yang Pyeong villa?
Maybe she missed you so much that she went to the villa.
That's right.
The villa.
A few days ago, I saw Mom at the Yang Pyeong villa.
Jae Hee, I'll be back.
It's me.
Did Mother go to you?
She didn't come here.
Did something happen to her?
We haven't been able to contact her since she ran out.
Have you filed a missing persons report?
Brother-in-law called the police,
but there's no news.
- So you're not doing anything and just letting it be?
- This was all because of you!
Why did you act on your own accord and complicate things?
If something happens to Mom,
we can't escape.
Don't you know that?
Is there someone named Jo Kyung Hee?
I'm sorry.
Could you help me check,
among the 119 calls,
is there someone named Jo Kyung Hee?
Mom!
Hurry, wake up!
You can't die.
You can't just leave like this.
Mom,
I was wrong,
I was wrong.
So,
hurry and open your eyes.
Mom,
please.
Hyun Woo.
If you find her, please contact me.
Just now, you were looking for someone called Jo Kyung Hee?
Yes.
Did you find her?
Yes, my teammate just contacted me.
She's already been sent to the emergency
room at Yang Pyeong Han Ahb Hospital.
- Yang Pyeong?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Jo Kyung Hee... Where is she?
Madam.
Madam!
I'm the guardian for this patient.
What happened to her?
We're still checking.
Because she suffered a mental breakdown,
she lost consciousness temporarily.
We put an IV drip in her. She should be awake soon.
Ah, this is the paramedic that sent her here.
Where did you find her?
How did you get her here?
We got the call really late.
They said someone had fainted at the Yang Pyeong Villa.
Who was the one who filed the report?
It was a young man.
He was crying really hard in the ambulance,
and I think he kept calling her Mom.
Mom?
He was just here. Where did he go?
He called her Mom.
It can't be...
Mom!
Is that Hyun Woo?
Hyun Woo!
Why are you here?
Aren't you cold?
It's really Hyun Woo.
It's my son, Hyun Woo.
How could you be cold?
I'm not cold at all.
Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo. Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo!
Madam.
Are you awake?
Where did our Hyun Woo go?
He was clearly here just now.
Hyun Woo?
That's right.
Our Hyun Woo definitely came.
Mother.
You must be strong.
So I may return honorably,
I must pretend I don't know you right now.
Are you all right?
If you're tired, take a rest.
I'm fine.
If you had been discovered a little later,
it would have been dangerous.
Everyone is worried.
I have Hyun Woo and Hyun Min.
I have two sons.
You don't have to worry about me.
Hyun Woo is dead.
Even if I'm not your son,
I've known you for 20 years and I've been to your house often.
Can't we be a little closer?
Do you have the right to say that to me?
Does it make sense to fall in love with the woman Hyun Woo loved?
Even though he's not in this world,
I can't tolerate,
any humiliation my son will suffer.
That's right.
Let's wait and see.
I'm curious to see
how long you can deny me.
Joo Seung is bringing Mom from Yang Pyeong.
She must have gone to Yang Pyeong Villa because she missed Oppa.
Now that I think about it,
since you've come in, our house has never been peaceful.
And,
you even dared to fool around with Joo Seung,
who is about the same age as your brother-in-law.
You're so casual.
Did our Hyun Woo die knowing this?
That's right.
Thinking about the day Oppa died,
why did he go to Chang Won on a stormy night?
No matter what, it's strange.
Something must have upset him.
I swear I never liked Doctor Nam, Father.
Father, it's not fair to make me responsible for his one sided love.
Don't call me Father.
I don't want you to be part of our family.
Pack up all of your things and leave.
Looks like Madam suffered a huge blow.
It's good that nothing happened to her.
Since Nam Joo Seung came to the hospital,
he should have contacted my family.
But,
Your mother didn't see your face?
If you sent her to the Yang Pyeong Hospital,
then Joo Ah Ran and Nam Joo Seung will be suspicious.
That's true.
Because she lost consciousness,
she shouldn't have seen it.
But she should have felt it in her heart.
Mom!
Are you okay?
Your health is not good. Why did you go to Yang Pyeong?
You should have asked me to come along.
I'm sorry
to have made you worry.
Who was worrying?
I don't want to see you.
Go in and lie down, or do whatever you want.
Mom.
But what is this?
Why are you wearing a men's scarf?
It seems like it belongs to the person
who sent her to the hospital.
She keeps saying it belongs to Hyun Woo.
What?
Are you insane?
Why do you keep talking about your dead son?
- Take it off immediately!
- Please, please don't do this.
This was given to me by our Hyun Woo.
I clearly heard him crying out for me.
Any mother...
How could she not know the smell of her child?
I know, Mom.
Maybe Hyung misses you too much,
so he came to look for you.
Go in and lie down.
Please make a cup of hot tea for Madam.
What right do you have to be here?
What if something happened to Mother because of you?
I clearly told you.
I never liked you, not even in my dreams.
Being misunderstood like that by my in-laws,
I'd rather go stand in front of Hyun Woo in death.
If you want to die, go out and die.
I don't want to know if you die or not.
Why should your ugly body die in my house?
Just pretend you don't know.
Someone who's intent on dying...
There's no reason to stop them.
Evil people.
Where in the world would you play some evil tricks?
Were you going to eat this and die?
This is given to me by our Hyun Woo!
I clearly heard him crying out for me.
That scarf
was definitely a present I gave to President Ahn.
No, how can it be?
What am I thinking?
President Ahn couldn't have gone to the Yang Pyeong Villa,
let alone meet Mom.
That's right,
Shin Hyun Woo is dead.
They've even found his teeth.
What's there to be suspicious about?
[Jo Kyung Hee.
Seoul, Jongro-gu, Peongchang-dong, 46P-2]
This,
was written by the person who brought the patient in?
Yes.
Of course that person wrote it. The patient was unconscious.
Maybe...
Do you remember anything about that person?
Even what he was wearing?
That...
I only remember he was quite tall and quite good-looking.
There weren't only one or two people that came.
Ah, that person said he didn't bring his phone,
and he borrowed mine.
Is that so?
I'm sorry,
but may I take a look at your handphone?
It seems to be this number.
010-9329...
Isn't that Nurse Yoon's handphone?
The people at Yang Pyeong Villa know Nurse Yoon.
Then, there's only one person who's suspicious.
Father.
Father, I'll do whatever you want me to do.
I'll settle the mortgage on the house as soon as possible.
I'll also find a way to settle the Julie Jung problem.
Please give me some time.
- I'll prove my innocence to Dad.
- These are divorce papers.
You don't have to waste time.
Settle it within this week.
Niece.
Did you sleep well?
You're going to work early today.
What are you doing here?
How did you find out where I stay?
We're people who cheat for a living.
These are the basics.
So,
I thought about it.
If we told your father-in-law who your parents were,
we might be able to get a big amount of money.
It would be good for both of us.
Let's just live with each other.
Exactly.
So,
If they give us a lovely apartment that's 100 square feet
and a storefront to do a little business,
I'll just pretend I don't know about you.
That's right.
What's wrong with sharing the property of our enemy?
Get lost immediately.
Even if you wring my neck, not a bit of money would come out.
I don't even know when I'll be chased out,
and I still have to worry about you?
Ah Ran!
Listen to me, it's not that.
What is this?
She said she was getting chased out?
Could it be that everything's out?
What?
Then won't they become the dogs that chase after the chickens?
What should we do?
Director.
Tell me honestly.
Who's Ahn Jae Sung?
W-what are you saying?
You know, right?
Is Shin Hyun Woo alive?
He's using another name
and is around us, right?
I don't understand what you're saying right now.
Ahn Jae Sung went to Pyeong Yang Villa yesterday,
and when he got there, he found Hyun Woo mother,
who had fainted.
He called 119 and sent her to the emergency room.
- Am I wrong?
- Does that make sense?
How would President Ahn know Madam from Pyeong Chang Dong?
And how would he know about Yang Pyeong Villa?
Then,
in the nurse's handphone...
Why was your number in there?
Obviously the person who sent
Madam to the emergency room
knew you.
How do you explain that?
At Yang Pyeong Villa, there are people who know my number.
I met them while I was out for a walk.
Maybe they were too anxious, so they called me.
I didn't get it because my handphone was turned off last night.
Don't lie!
You think I'll be fooled by those lies that don't make sense?
Shin Hyun Woo is alive, right?
The person who sent Madam to the hospital is Ahn Jae Sung, right?
What are you doing?!
Are you always this rough towards girls?
What is your real face?
What is the reason you're appearing in front of us?
Hurry and take off your mask!
Why are you so anxious?
What is my real face?
Then what is your real face?!
Joo Ah Ran, Yoon Jae Hee...
Which one do you care for?
You...
You think you can fool me?
I will...
I definitely will find out who you are.
Go ahead.
What should we do?
Director must have found something out.
Looks like he believed that the person at
the Yang Pyeong Hospital was you.
Don't worry.
Things will be over before Nam Joo Seung discovers my true face.
That aside, I would like to ask you for a favor.
How is your health?
Director wanted me to come and see how you are.
There's no need.
Anyway, take a seat.
You still don't look well.
Let me give you a nutrition jab.
Oh, right.
I saw this in the mailbox, so I brought it in.
This...
looks like a traffic violation.
Were you speeding on Yang Pyeong Bridge?
Nov 27, 7:00 in the evening.
When was that..? To only come now...
Nov 27?
Wasn't that the day the villa caught fire?
That's the day I quit my job at the villa.
I remember it very clearly.
That's right.
That's the day our Hyun Woo met with his mishap.
But...
Why was Ah Ran at Yang Pyeong at 7:00?
She definitely left me at 5:00 in the evening.
Then you go to the market, Mother.
I have to make a trip to the factory,
so I'll make a move first.
I'll leave Hyun Woo to you.
It can't be.
She clearly told me she was leaving for Seoul.
Madam,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry, but can you leave?
I have to think about some things alone.
Why are you waiting here? Why didn't you go in first?
I wanted to see if the scarf I gave you was good.
You didn't wear it?
Ah, that...
I don't really like scarves.
Could it be that you lost it?
Or that you gave it to someone else?
Are you in the habit of always checking up
on the gifts you give to people?
The scarf is all right. Don't worry.
Go and have a cup of tea.
Are you hiding something from me?
Tell me honestly...
Who did you give that scarf to?
Last night, who were you with?
I'm not so impolite that I would give someone else
a gift that I had received.
Here.
Is that all right?
How?
I thought I could communicate with you.
Maybe I was mistaken.
How disappointing.
Real trust is not trusting in what you see,
but trusting in what you can't see.
I'll treat it like I've never received this present.
Welcome!
Why are the two of you here?
Welcome.
What furniture are you looking for?
That...
I would like to see the most expensive bed in this shop.
A bed?
All right, we'll take care of you.
Please go around and have a look.
Yes.
This standard... should be quite expensive.
For a showroom like this, how much do you earn a month?
What?
No, if you came to look at furniture,
you should just look at furniture.
Why are you asking about their sales volume?
- Is this the most comfortable bed?
- Then, you'll have to lie down and try it out.
That's right.
Aigoo.
I'm getting sleepy and comfortable.
Then, let's try it out by sleeping.
- Don't worry about us, just go about your business.
- That... Customers...
Hurry and get up.
Go wait at the coffee shop in front.
I'll get Ah Ran here.
Hurry.
What is this?
It's an investment flow report.
It shows how much money is needed to settle Soul.
That might be a little difficult.
Although I did agree to invest,
I can't just give money without principle.
If we just make it through this difficult period,
everything will be smooth sailing from then on.
Soul is about to provide furniture to the largest vacation resort in the country,
and we're also in contact with buyers from China.
Is that so?
All right.
I've already introduced myself to President Shin Woo Sub.
Could there be any mistakes?
I'll deposit the money you need today.
Thank you.
I'll definitely not let you regret it.
[Yeon Jae ]
I've just sent them to the coffee shop in front.
You have to come and take care of this.
I was so afraid Manager would find out
that my heart jumped into my mouth.
It's 10 million won.
Take this money, hurry and leave.
If you appear one more time,
I'll call the police.
Ah Ran,
did you think we came here just for the 10 million?
It was because we were worried how you were going to weather the difficulties.
It's because your family is here.
I didn't ask you to worry about me.
Please live like you're dead.
People who sold their 18 year-old niece to a forty year-old man...
Why are you talking about family now?
All right,
You don't seem to want to accept us as family.
Then, we can't do anything.
Then, forget about finding out about where
your sister went your entire life.
What?
You know where our Kyeong Ran is?
Our Kyeong Ran is alive?
Where is she?
Where is our Kyeong Ran?!
Why did you talk about Kyeong Ran?
We can't just pull her out of thin air.
You don't treat us like people.
Why should we waste effort looking for Kyeong Ran?
What did you do to my sister?
It wasn't enough to do it to me.
What else did you do to that poor child?!
If you want to put it bluntly,
even if we did abandon the two of you,
you shouldn't be getting angry at us right now.
When your parents died, it wasn't as if they
died in a building in Myeong Dong.
Why should we waste so much effort?
Help me find Kyeong Ran.
If you help me find Kyeong Ran,
if you want,
I'll risk my life for you and give everything to you.
I promised Mom and Dad I'd take care of Kyeong Ran.
Really?
You'll give us whatever we want?
Then,
give us your brother-in-law's showroom.
Oh?
What courage have you grown?
We don't want anything else.
We just want that.
You pay for the coffee.
Let's go.
Kyeong Ran.
Kyeong Ran is still alive.
Our Kyeong Ran...
All right.
No matter what, I have to stay strong.
Once I find our Kyeong Ran,
I must show her my success.
We won't go back to our poor and pathetic times.
Never.
President,
someone sent you flowers.
Who sent them?
There's no name written, just the initials NNJ.
NNJ?
Never accept these flowers again.
Throw them away.
Also, if Nam Joo Seung ever comes looking for me,
just say that I'm not here.
Understand?
Yes.
Mother.
I came here to ask you about something.
Before Hyun Woo met with his accident,
were you dating Doctor Nam?
No.
You saw what just happened.
It's Doctor Nam who has the one-sided feelings.
As Hyun Woo's wife, I am not ashamed at all.
Please believe me.
Then I'll ask you something else.
The day the villa caught fire,
why did you, who parted from me at 5:00,
leave Yang Pyeong at 7:00 in the evening?
Where were you and what did you do during those two hours?
Mother,
what is this?
What are you thinking right now?
Doctor Nam clearly did this.
He's using these methods to threaten me because I didn't accept him.
That's right.
Even if we dig up the past, Hyun Woo is not here
anymore. What difference would it make?
But promise me something.
If you really loved Hyun Woo,
Doctor Nam won't do.
To your father-in-law, Doctor Nam is a special person,
and the only person who got hurt because of this was you.
I will remember that.
What you're worried about will never happen.
Joo Seung, are you such a clingy person?
Love involves two people.
One-sided love is just obsession and violence.
What's wrong now?
Did something happen?
You're even so childish as to send flowers.
Do you think anything will change between us?
Don't turn the beautiful memories from
the past three years into evil.
Please just end it here coolly.
Flowers?
I didn't send them.
Liar.
You used the initials on our couple ring,
and you're still denying it?
You were the one who sent Mother
the traffic violation too, right?
Tell me what you get out of telling her who set the fire.
It wasn't me.
If anyone intentionally sent anything, it must be Hyun Woo.
- Shin Hyun Woo is dead.
- He's not dead.
The person who sent Madam from the
Yang Pyeong Villa to the hospital must be Hyun Woo.
Madam didn't see wrongly.
The only person who knows the initials on our couple ring
is Hyun Woo.
Even if Shin Hyun Woo is alive,
do you think I'll abandon everything in that family and leave?
Please wake up.
Before it gets more dangerous, leave that family.
This is your last chance.
You can't let go of my hand.
As long as you shut your mouth, I'll be fine.
I really didn't want to say this,
but your wounded look is tiring.
My wounds are already deep enough.
I can't breathe or think when I look at you.
Yes!
I had a rough life in this world.
I grew up alone without my mother.
My father worked his whole life under President as a secretary
and eventually died of illness.
Someone who's never had parental love...
Isn't it normal to be dissatisfied with society?
But...
they say that the flowers that grow deep
in the mines are beautiful too.
Even if your love has changed,
don't insult my love.
How can I trust you?
If we meet danger, you'd step on me to get to safety.
Before you hurt me,
I have to make the first move.
Tomorrow, I'll leave President's medicine to you.
[Madam]
Madam.
I have Hyun Woo, Hyun Min... two sons.
You have no need to be worried about me.
Nurse Yoon,
I'm sorry,
but after you come to work tomorrow,
please deliver the President's medicine to Pyeong Chang Dong.
I'll leave the prescription on the table.
[Shin Woo Sub]
Nam Joo Seung.
The person who's helping me now,
is not you, it's Ahn Jae Sung.
Nurse Yoon, what are you doing here so early?
Director wanted me to bring the President's medicine.
We still have a lot of medicine.
Maybe the medicine changed.
We're going to change hospitals.
You don't have to work so hard in the future.
Nurse Yoon,
because you came so early,
have some breakfast before you leave.
No, it's fine.
It's all right. Have some before you leave.
It's just adding a pair of chopsticks.
I'll eat well.
Dad!
What's wrong? Dad!
- Dad!
- Hyun Woo's dad! Hyun Woo's dad!
- Hyun Woo's dad!
- Dad!
Hurry and call an ambulance, hurry!
Hyun Woo's dad!
Hyung, what are you trying to do?
Are you trying to kill my father?
Why...
Why did you do it, why?!
What are you saying?
What?
Father.
Ahjussi, something big happened.
What?
Father fainted?
Ah, I know.
I'll call Joo Ah Ran and find out what happened.
Jae Hee, you go to the hospital.
I'm leaving Mom and Dad to you.
After doing the tests,
it should be due to the side effects of the medicine.
I looked at the prescription,
and there are fatal drugs that will cause patients
with high blood pressure to have breathing difficulties.
The doctor in charge probably made a mistake.
What mistake?
He has a current license.
How could the person who gave me medicine have made a mistake?
How could Joo Seung do something like that?
President,
Are you all right? Are you awake?
You bastard.
Because you want Hyun Woo's wife,
you want to go as far as to kill me?
You evil fellow.
What are you saying?
After seeing this prescription,
you still want to make excuses?
No.
What?
I used the same prescription that I always use.
I got the medicine with the prescription on the table.
You're playing around with your elders' health.
We'll change our doctor immediately. Please leave.
Nam Joo Seung,
how does it feel?
Now you're an enemy to this family too.
No one will believe anything you say.
Yes President Ahn, I'll come see you as soon as possible.
Tell me,
what were you thinking coming up with a plan like this?
It was you who used Madam's name to send me a message.
- I know.
- What did I do?
If it was as you said,
it should be the dead Shin Hyun Woo who did it.
It's not. Hyun Woo wouldn't do this to his father.
Move aside.
I don't want people in the family to misunderstand needlessly.
Get out!
Hurry and get out!
Hospital?
Doctor Nam broke up with me hatefully.
It seems he played around with Father-in-law's medicine.
He's in the hospital because of the side effects.
As a doctor, he doesn't even have a basic conscience.
Clearly, it shows his love is deep.
But
you get sick of flowers too.
Now his love is suffocating too.
Don't ever mention Doctor Nam in front of me again.
We don't have enough time just talking about the two of us.
Is it important who looks at me?
What's the most important is that I'm looking at you now.
This is the first time
I feel like a business partner can also be my life partner.
Then, are we in a partnership?
The reward for a career
is sweet red wine and a world for two people.
The aim of a career
is to snatch the heart of each other.
What do you think?
From now on,
you are the Romeo of my heart.
The Romeo of your heart?
- Then what about you?
- The Juliet that's got her heart stolen?
Stealing hearts...
Those words are charming, but a little scary.
If you don't want to have your heart stolen,
you have to steal someone else's heart.
If you want to steal hearts,
it's too bright here.
I'll prepare appropriate wine and set a date
before calling you.
Your hospital is a little bigger than I thought it would be.
What are you doing at our hospital?
Your hospital deed is in my hands.
President Joo said she needed money urgently,
and she gave it to me to help her handle it.
But, I should listen to the hospital Director.
President Joo gave you the hospital?
She provided the money.
Of course, we should proceed according to her wishes.
Just handle it.
It's not like I'm lusting after the hospital.
Is that so?
Then, I'll do as you wish.
A paid doctor is more comfortable.
Then.
His blood pressure is normal too.
I watched him eat before I came.
Is that so?
That's good.
Everyone had a bad scare, right?
Looking at your family,
I feel like having a family is really a good thing.
You worry about each other, are anxious,
and grateful.
You have no family?
I heard my parents passed away,
and that I have an older sister.
An older sister?
Why didn't you tell me about your older sister?
No matter where she is, you should look for her.
Let me meet the Director.
President, just now, SM Company called.
Is that so?
Have you set up a meeting time with them?
They say they don't want to meet and turned it down,
but they sent this over.
[Merger Proposal]
What?
Merger?
Who's the boss there?
Who in the world is it? To say crazy things like that...
I asked around, I heard the boss is a woman named Jung Sang Hwa.
Jung Sang Hwa?
She came back from America not long ago
and started her business using her brother's designs.
Her brother's name is Jung Sang Mo.
What?
Jung Sang Mo?
That SM representative
is Jung Sang Mo's sister?
From the beginning, she watched me and planned how to act?
This won't do.
No.
You gave me so much help at my hardest moment,
yet I didn't come and visit you. I'm really sorry.
It's all right.
Compared to the help that Mr. Shin has given to our orphanage,
I'm really ashamed.
Actually...
I came because I'm helping Jae Hee look for her family.
I heard she has an older sister.
Do you know about this?
What to do?
I don't know anything.
Actually,
the person who brought Jae Hee here,
was Mr. Shin's mother.
What?
My mother?
But your mother didn't seem to know where she grew up either.
When Jae Hee came to our orphanage,
she was only three years old.
How about looking in the child protection agencies in Seoul?
Yes.
Why did Mother bring Jae Hee...
What reason...
Are you sure it's here?
That's right.
This is the biggest place in Seoul.
We brought her here because we were looking out for her.
That's right, that's right.
Joo, Kyeong Ran, right?
Yes.
We abandoned her at the doorstep 25 years ago.
This...
Not abandoned.
We had to leave here temporarily because our lives were too hard.
Now we're here to look for her and seek forgiveness.
Yes, here.
Joo Kyeong Ran,
a girl of 21 months.
Right?
Right, right.
That's right!
Is that child still here?
According to the records here,
it only says that a welfare home took her.
What?
Which welfare house was it?
It doesn't say.
Oh, my... What does that mean?
Was she adopted or sent overseas?
There should be a record.
How could people do things so unclearly?
Back then,
a lot of people didn't like others to find out about their adoption.
So they probably didn't leave anything on purpose.
Here, it says that she kept looking for her sister,
and that she liked red leather shoes a lot.
This thing concerns life or death.
Please ask around a little more, and you must inform me.
These are really strange people.
They should have just raised her honestly.
Why did they give her to someone else?
We could have just found her.
Who decides?
They didn't even record the phone number of the person who adopted her.
Oh, that scared me.
- It's like he's never driven before.
- Exactly.
I'm really sorry. Are you all right?
Drive properly!
Let's go.
Where should we to find Kyeong Ran?
There are no records of a child called Yoon Jae Hee.
Maybe, she was left at a different agency.
Yes, I understand.
Is that true?
If you don't believe me,
you can go to the police station to verify it.
Because my brother killed himself,
the police investigated it too.
Then,
during that period of time, all the furniture that
Soul used based on Sister-in-law's designs...
They were copies of your brother's designs?
I'm uncovering your sister-in-law's crimes for my brother.
How you're going to compensate SM Furniture...
Discuss it with Joo Ah Ran before letting me know.
Then, I'm leaving.
Look at this.
The child kept looking for you.
The agency had a photograph, so I photocopied it for you.
She kept looking for her sister.
She especially liked red leather shoes.
Kyeong Ran.
No matter where you are, just stay alive.
I will definitely look for you.
Who is Jung Sang Mo?
Brother-in-law.
I just met Jung Sang Hwa,
so I heard everything.
What relationship did you have with Jung Sang Mo?
How did you steal all of Jung Sang Mo's designs?
It's not true.
That woman is lying.
It's that side who is lusting after Soul's designs.
That's why they're getting close to you.
You can't get involved.
At this point,
I really hate Hyung.
How could I love someone like you?
If he was here, I would really beat him up.
Because of all your lies,
I'm resenting my brother who passed away.
This is all because of you!
Snap out of it, Joo Ah Ran.
You can't fall like this.
You have to find Kyeong Ran
and bring her in front of Dad and Mom.
Before that, you have no right to die.
You have to overcome the hurdles of Shin Woo Sub and Jung Sang Hwa.
If you don't want to get chased out by Shin Woo Sub,
you have to find his fatal flaw.
President Hwang is someone who knows Joo Ah Ran's past.
Through that person,
unveiling Joo Ah Ran's mask should be interesting.
Can you help me, Julie Jung?
Go ahead and do it.
I have a classmate who is close to President Hwang.
I'll arrange the situation.
Soon, there will be a merger of SM
Furniture and Soul Furniture.
I've sent over the merger proposal,
but there's been no response from Joo Ah Ran.
Soul will eventually leave the hands of Joo Ah Ran and will be mine.
Thanks for the investment funds that you sent over.
But what is the matter?
After I made the investment, I was worried.
I compared the news about SM Furniture and Soul Furniture.
The designs are very similar,
but the prices are ridiculously expensive.
[Soul Furniture and SM Furniture with similar designs,
but Soul Furniture is double the price.]
They're criticizing Soul.
Don't worry.
This SM Furniture is not a competitor.
If there's a chance,
we're planning on suing them for stealing our designs.
But, you can't neglect the power of media.
In the report,
it says Soul is stealing the designs.
I don't know if consumers will trust the words of President Joo.
I will immediately go see the President of SM and issue her a warning.
I heard the rumors that her dead brother is a furniture designer
and their president is a rookie in the furniture business.
We'll see how long they can hold out.
At least you have your confidence.
As long as I gain back my investment funds,
I can leave confidently.
[Myungsung Electronics: Believe its fraud]
President Hwang?
Find out what's happening with Hyun Woo's wife.
If you don't find a decisive weakness,
she won't back down quietly.
Yes, President.
That's right,
the young brother of the manager of Joo Jang Chun factory
and his wife were released from prison not long ago.
Is that so?
Find out where they live.
Hello.
I heard you were sick, and got a shock.
It's fortunate that you're all right.
Aigoo, a busy person came to see me.
I'm really grateful.
I didn't even know you were sick.
I just found out.
I'm good friends with President Hwang of Myeong Sung Electronics.
He heard it was a company I was investing in,
and said he had to meet you.
President Hwang?
I heard he's a friend of Shin Woo's wife's father.
That...
I'm getting discharged tomorrow. Arrange a meeting with him.
Can I do that?
Tomorrow, at 6:00 in the evening, please come to the Seoul Hotel.
It's been a long time since we've eaten together.
I have important business to talk about.
You can look forward to it.
Tomorrow, at 6:00 in the evening,
please come to the ChungDamDong Hotel
that Joo Ah Ran used to work at.
I'll arrange everything else and will be waiting.
Yes. This is Beautiful Hospital.
Have you checked the security records?
Yes.
The first security alarm was set at 7:30 pm.
and then disabled two minutes later.
It was disabled using a password. That's why we didn't take action.
All right, I understand.
Joo Ah Ran, it was really you.
The only person that can deactivate the code
is you.
Welcome.
I'm Julie Jung.
Where is the President?
There is an important guest that is coming from
overseas for the President, so he didn't come.
I came by myself. Are you disappointed?
No, how can that be?
It's an honor to meet you.
What's the reason you called the two of us here?
Wait and see.
Madam
has to take revenge at least once.
Revenge?
President Shin really wanted to meet President Hwang,
so it was such a pity.
Since Madam is here,
you should ask her anything you want to.
Actually,
I wanted to meet you because I had something
I wanted to ask about my daughter-in-law.
President Hwang said he knows her very well.
Not just well.
I heard she married into a furniture
company, so it's Soul Furniture.
Taking that kind of woman as your daughter-in-law...
President Shin is really great.
That kind of woman?
Looks like President Shin isn't a man.
Is there a man in Seoul that doesn't know Rosemary?
The fox among all foxes that seduced our family's President,
despite his love for his wife.
Rosemary?
Who's Rosemary?
That...
How could that happen?!
Welcome, President.
You've been well, right?
You still have the guts to meet me?
That day, you were the one who took my passport and my ticket, right?
I also knew you didn't get on the plane that day.
Are you still angry about that?
Stop being angry.
You evil fellow.
Today, I won't let you just leave obediently.
I have to get rid this anger.
You'd better be prepared.
I have guests coming. Will you be all right?
Guests?
To expose the special relationship between President and I,
I called a few reporters.
The information that you asked me to steal
about Sae May Electronics' new products... Here is the evidence.
In this memory card, there are the emails
that the President and I exchanged.
And this
is the investment contract that Myeong Sung
Electronics has with Soul Furniture.
How about you take this opportunity to invest in Soul Furniture
and become business partners with me?
The choice is in the hands of President.
Come clean that you're an immoral
businessman in front of the reporters, or
appear as Soul's investor.
No matter what decision you make,
I'll listen to the President.
I've been...
so nice to you, that I didn't know this was an evil road.
You think you can play me with this game?
Oh,
we heard that President Hwang and President Joo have a special deal.
Is that true?
What are the contents of the deal. Could you tell us in detail?
Are you crazy?
If you don't want to die, get rid of the reporters!
If you don't want to invest,
then just come clean with the memory disk.
We should also reveal that the President is my sponsor.
I have nothing to lose anymore.
Do you think I'll agree to that?
Business is not child's play!
Soul Furniture
is a company with huge potential.
Compared to the investments you made on my body,
this should be a better deal for you.
Because of Myeong Sung Electronics' large investment,
in the future, our Soul Furniture,
will develop to become the best furniture company.
With Myeong Sung Electronics backing me,
no one can do anything to me.
Father and Ahn Jae Sung
all have to do as I say.
- Hurry and get in the car.
- Let go.
We're done.
There's nothing more I have to say to you.
You and I!
It's not over unless one of us dies!
No matter how you step on me, lie to me...
I can't let you go.
No, I'll love you more.
Listen to me!
I like Ahn Jae Sung.
If you're helping me take revenge,
then Ahn Jae Sung's the one who will help me succeed.
The time spent with you was torture.
I want to be happy.
I'm living by using my strength to snatch Soul away
as compensation for the days my sister and I spent.
So you
and the misfortune should vanish from before my eyes.
I'm back.
I'm a little late.
Dirty person!
Father!
Who is Rosemary?
All the men in Seoul know
who Rosemary is.
I don't admit that you're my daughter-in-law!
Even if he leaps over with a knife,
I'm not in the least bit frightened.
- What ring is this?
- It's a couple ring!
The woman who was sitting in Hyun Woo's car was you, right?
- Wait and see.
- Mother, you should leave.
You take over Soul and develop it.
I want to live as your woman.
Taking over someone else's woman,
do you think you'll be happy?
A child that was abandoned by his mother...
What can he grow up to be?
Should I take this opportunity to say
how Hyun Woo met with his accident?
Shall I also reveal that the manager
of Joo Jung Chun Factory was your father?
Joo Seung's birth parents!
He wanted to use my parents' death to crush that family.
In the end, Joo Ah Ran and Nam Joo Seung's
battle will only get more heated.
The war starts now.