Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 18
Jae Sung, we've fallen into a trap.
Everybody is maligning me!
I told you clearly.
Shin Hyun Woo died
in a gas explosion.
I wasn't there then!
I had nothing to do with
the traffic accident either.
What...
if I don't believe you?
You have to believe me.
We don't need the wedding ceremony.
Let's leave!
Let's go.
You took someone's life!
Do you want to just run away like that?
You actually thought
you can stand here, blissful.
How shameless and hateful.
I must...
make the crimes that you committed,
crawl out of your mouth like worms.
Till the day you die.
You have to pay for
your crimes till you die.
Who are you?
Do you still not know?
The Romeo who lost his heart,
the person you killed,
your husband,
Shin Hyun Woo.
That's right.
This person here, is Shin Hyun Woo.
He underwent plastic surgery
because of serious burn injuries.
But, he is definitely Shin Hyun Woo.
I'm the witness.
Now, you know?
The Ahn Jae Sung you loved,
is the Shin Hyun Woo you killed.
The Ahn Jae Sung who was going to save you,
didn't exist right from the beginning,
only the Shin Hyun Woo
who was stabbing you in the back.
No.
You're not Shin Hyun Woo.
You're Ahn Jae Sung.
Tell me.
You're the Ahn Jae Sung I loved, tell me!
Wake up and face reality!
I wanted you to feel it in your bones,
the feeling that living
is more painful than dying.
If the law can't do it...
I'll do it.
Is that so?
To take revenge on me,
with your body full of stab wounds,
you became another person.
You hated me to the point where your face,
your blood and heart
had to be replaced.
Or,
did you love me that much?
Shut your mouth!
The moment when I return to Shin Hyun Woo,
it's over.
There are a lot of reporters
outside the house.
Outside this hotel,
there are police officers
waiting to shoot you.
Just as long as I say one word,
tomorrow,
it'll be all over the news.
Your life,
will be unsalvageable.
I'll give you one last chance to repent.
Now, you walk out by yourself,
spill out everything,
and confess to the police.
Confess your own crimes with your own mouth.
That would reduce half of your sins.
Make your own choice.
You're really cruel.
Will you only be happy and give up, after
you've pushed me into a bottomless pit?
All right.
If that's what you want,
I'll do as you wish.
Then, how content you'll become,
I want to see it with my own eyes.
What big news could there be?
Making us wait like that?
All right, let's just wait it out.
It seems like something
interesting is happening in there.
Father.
Mother.
You...
No, you...
Really are Hyun Woo?
My son, Hyun Woo, am I right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
This time, I've been pretending not to know.
Please forgive me,
I could only do this.
You horrible fellow.
Are you an orphan?
When were you going to leave your
dad out of the loop, before you told me?
Was I that untrustworthy?
Hyun Woo.
It's our Hyun Woo.
This gaze,
this smell,
it's our Hyun Woo, that's right.
My son!
Mother.
I'm sorry.
I came back in this manner.
I missed you this much,
I thought about coming
back a few times a day,
but I couldn't return weakly,
without having done anything.
Then, you should also
tell Mother that you're alive.
Did you know that Mom's heart
was on fire, why did you do that?
Why did you have to bear it
by yourself, like a fool?
What should we do?
Are you really going to turn yourself in?
No, I can't.
The guilty person isn't me,
it's Shin Woo Sub.
That person is still alive and free.
He can't pin all the crimes on me.
That Shin Hyun Woo that looks so righteous,
that dirty blood is also
flowing through his body.
But we can't get away now.
From the front, and the back,
they're all watching us.
Leave it to me.
All right, brother-in-law,
since this is the case,
I'll go see the police
and tell them everything.
But, let me change before that.
I can't let the police interrogate
me when I'm in this state.
You should accede to that request, right?
You can see the police
are oustide everywhere, right?
Don't even dream about playing tricks.
You can't run anywhere.
No matter what, we have to escape from here.
As long as we get on a plane to America,
Shin Hyun Woo can't do anything about it.
What time is the plane?
7.
We can handle all the procedures
as long as we leave right now.
All right.
Looking at the situation,
I'll leave with you.
Change your clothes first, I'll go see
if there's a door that leads out from here.
That's right.
I'll avoid this storm first.
Now, if the police looks into everything,
things will look bad for me.
To look for the sister I
haven't seen in 25 years,
I can't go to jail.
- Who are you?
- Get my handbag here now.
- What?
- Now!
Ah, yes.
It's me.
Have you found a way out?
All right. I'll go there right now.
Is Joo Ah Ran still in there?
She just left.
What?
Stand there!
Joo Ah Ran!
If you take this, you will see an exit.
Get out from there, and take
the car to Angel Orphanage.
And go straight to the airport.
What about you, Joo Seung?
I don't think I can leave with you.
You leave first.
No matter what,
you can never get caught.
Understand?
Joo Ah Ran! Stay there,
hurry and come out!
I'm going to grit my teeth.
Today, no matter if you're my Hyung,
because of my brother,
I'm not going to let you off!
You can't go.
You can't go!
What's going on?
My passport, my air ticket!
I clearly left it here.
Are you looking for this?
What are you doing?
Give it to me.
Where are you running away to like a coward?
Your crimes cannot even be counted,
you don't even have a sense of shame,
and you want to run away to
a different country to live freely?
That,
even I, who was beside Shin Hyun Woo
watching him suffer, cannot forgive.
Stay out of it.
Are you Shin Hyun Woo's wife?
This is something that Shin Hyun Woo,
his family and I have to settle.
Third parties should stay out of it!
Then you should settle
everything before you leave.
Stop pretending to be someone
else so cheaply and running away,
it doesn't seem like Joo Ah Ran.
No! No!
What are you to, involve yourself
in someone else's business?!
Don't touch my woman!
What?
Your woman?
Listen clearly.
Yoon Jae Hee,
is a woman I love.
As much as you toy with my life,
I won't allow you to touch my woman.
Don't use those cruel hands
of yours to touch a hair of my woman's.
I'm not that Shin Hyun Woo
you played around with.
Joo Ah Ran!
Let's take a trip to the police station.
We'll have a joint interrogation
with Shin Hyun Woo.
No.
If you turned yourself in,
I was going to leave you a way out.
But you kept walking
towards the gates of hell.
I had no other choice.
If you wish, I'll walk with you.
Take her away please.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Ahjusshi, I have to go back to the hotel.
I've made an appointment with my Unnie,
and the time has passed.
All right. Go.
After you meet your Unnie, give me a call.
All right.
Hyung, turn him over to the police too.
He's the same person.
There's no reason to think about it anymore.
Do you really have to do this?
She was the one who abandoned
me and put on a wedding dress.
But,
do you really have to get
the police to waste her like that?
Even though you and
Joo Ah Ran failed at killing me,
I have no intention of
giving in to you at all.
Although you wanted to
leave the country and hide,
there is no place for you to
run and hide anymore!
All right.
We will be punished.
But, give us some time to cool down,
And, for this woman who loved you,
and had your baby,
is that too much to ask?
No!
Now, drag them away right
now and convict them!
There's no reason to
drag it out any further.
Get in the car.
Hold on.
The other party wants to
savor her pain slowly.
Then, letting them get what they want,
is not a big deal.
I'll see them tomorrow
at the police station.
Ah.
What is this?
Today is our Ah Ran's wedding.
Aigoo, she didn't call us,
what wedding could it be?
Isn't it written here?
Groom, Ahn Jae Sung,
Bride Joo Ah Ran.
Oh my.
Looks like the important thing she
was talking about was her wedding.
What a shameless creature.
Then she should at least have
called us over for some pork rib soup.
Just, letting us wait
blindly for Kyeong Ran.
Oh, what is going on?
Is it all right for her to marry
another guy while living at her in-laws?
Then,
wouldn't she be chased out of
her Director position at Soul Furniture?
Oh, that's right.
Where are the guests looking for Kyeong Ran?
Kyeong Ran?
They were just here, maybe they left?
What?
I left a message asking them to wait.
Could she have left a message when she left?
There isn't anything.
Yes.
You have to wipe your face.
I'll go get you something.
What are you doing right now?
Let me go!
I don't want to live!
Stop now, do you hear me?!
Just let me go!
This world was never on my side!
Even if I struggled so hard to live,
the result was the same.
Since it's a life where I'll never be happy,
I should just die.
Who continues living for a reason?
Does anyone just sit there
silently if they have something to say?
Why are you so irresponsible?
Even for your parents,
where is the Joo Ah Ran
that would live on courageously?
Even if you crush the whole
world, it'll become yours,
where did that courage go?
Dad and Mom will understand too.
If I go,
they should welcome me happily.
Don't hold onto me.
Why will you die?!
Without my permission,
you don't have the right to die.
You have to stay by
my side your entire life,
to repent for your sin of betrayal.
What?
Isn't that better.
At least you didn't kill Hyun Woo Hyung,
you're not a murderer,
I thought you would be happy.
Shin Hyun Woo is back!
Everything has returned to Shin Hyun Woo.
Shin Woo Sub has not lost anything either,
what good is that?
I can only think about what I can get now.
Ah Ran, you're not Shin Hyun Woo's,
or Ahn Jae Sung's.
You'll stay by my side.
You're crazy.
You're mentally ill.
Why can't you let go of me?
I'm a woman that ran off after loving me,
why can't you let me go?!
Why?!
One-sided love, could be my
destiny right from my birth.
It's fine if you don't love me,
as long as you're by my side.
If even you leave me,
I might not be able to live in this world.
Then, it was Nurse Yoon that saved Oppa.
That Agasshi looks really intelligent,
she has really become
the savior of our family.
It's because of all the fortune
Mom accumulated through her charity,
that I managed to get some help.
Without Jae Hee,
I wouldn't have been able
to wake up from my vegetative state,
and dream about living like a human.
What a strange world.
Mom supported Nurse Yoon
throughout university,
and Nurse Yoon saved Hyung's life,
which is why people
have to live with kindness.
What a great piece of news after so long.
Then, what is with the company?
In name, it is all under Ahn Jae Sung.
I've discussed it with the lawyer,
to change it to Shin Hyun Woo.
Then, Sister...
Then, what about that woman Joo Ah Ran?
Of course she has to be judged by the law.
She created two incidents that were
so horrific, and split our family apart.
No matter what she can't be forgiven.
Since you were going to use the law,
why did you wait so long?
When you first woke up, if you
had gone to the police straight away,
at least she wouldn't
have set the villa on fire.
I wanted to take all the betrayal
I felt, and give it to her.
I also wanted to know, why Joo Ah Ran
wanted to do such things.
You won't be uncomfortable, right?
How about sharing a room
with Hyun Min first?
No.
I have a house that I looked for,
I'll just stay there.
You want to live apart from us?
Why?
We haven't seen each other for such a long time,
why do you want to live separately?
I will come often, don't worry.
After going through such
a difficult surgery,
you must have suffered so much pain.
How lonely you were, how tired,
Mom couldn't do anything either.
Why is Mom sorry?
That's the payback I get
for loving the wrong person.
That's right.
It was you who brought Jae Hee to the
orphanage. How did you know Jae Hee?
What do you mean know?
It was a coincidence that
a friend asked me for a favor.
I was just helping a friend.
Is that so?
She said she was going to see her
Unnie, I don't know if she saw her.
Did you meet Ah Ran?
Her dead husband actually came
back alive, how embarrassing.
What?
Who came back alive?
You don't know?
Ah Ran's husband came back alive.
Our Manager's Hyung didn't die,
he just hid using someone else's name.
Oh my, oh my,
what is this?
Then, the fact that our Ah Ran is
marrying someone else is out?
It's not that, the groom was that person,
that person was the groom.
What is this girl talking about?
Then, you're saying that
after she got married,
two husbands appeared, and her being
chased out, is just a matter of time.
Oh my, oh my,
I'm so frustrated.
Oh my, I'm so frustrated.
It's locked.
Jae Hee, if you kiss it, it could open.
I would never love anyone again,
because my heart froze into a block of ice.
But, you just opened my heart.
Ahjusshi.
Do you... want to marry me?
Kyeong Ran.
Unnie is really tired.
That man, was just the son of our enemy.
But, why is my heart being
torn apart because of that man?
Since we can't be in love,
we might as well, hate each other,
and step all over each other.
The interrogation is going to begin.
July 13,
In Seoul, north Changwon,
in Hyun Woo's car,
was involved in a car
accident due to bad driving.
Who was driving?
Then, my wife, Joo Ah Ran was driving.
That was my husband's, Shin Hyun Woo's car.
When the incident happened, the person sitting
in the driver's seat, was also Shin Hyun Woo.
Now, I'm in front of you.
Are you going to lie?
I can take out the black box that
has been kept, as evidence.
Officer.
I'm prepared to accept
the punishments for my crimes.
But before that, I have a request.
A request?
A long time ago,
in the furniture company
that Shin Woo Sub ran,
there was a couple who died
because of hidden reasons.
I hope you can investigate that incident.
What are you saying?
Who killed who in that furniture company?
Do you still not know, even now?
Your father,
killed my parents,
in front of my eyes.
And he even cruelly,
crushed them under wood.
Don't lie anymore.
I won't be cheated by your
cheap tricks anymore.
It's true.
I know Ah Ran.
And it was also because my dad asked
me to take care of Ah Ran when he died.
Because of President,
she grew up as a lonely orphan.
If you don't believe me,
ask your Dad here and ask him.
Letting my poor parents die,
and my poor sister run away,
ask him here immediately!
Why I had to live,
selling drinks and smiles,
was all because of your father.
What is all this in the
middle of our interrogation?
Shin Hyun Woo.
Now, is what Joo Ah Ran is saying, true?
No.
This is the first time I'm hearing this.
How about meeting again
after you've found out the truth?
We were also thinking about looking
for a lawyer, to start a true investigation.
You're still alive.
But my parents are already dead.
Whose crime is bigger,
is clear without even comparing.
Because of your family,
do you know how I lived?
My parents, and my sister!
Getting married, to my pathetic
life, is a strand of straw.
And a shame to my parents who died wrongly.
They worked hard their
entire life in a factory.
But died wrongly because
of a truth they spoke.
It was a cover up, for the
murder that they suffered.
Even though we've let it out,
but the matter with Shin Woo Sub was
something that happened 20 years ago.
It's also past the investigation period.
Even if they find the truth out now,
there can't be any punishment.
I know.
We came all this way because
the law can't serve us.
But, it can't be because time has passed,
that the crime of breaking
up a family is let go.
For a man like Shin Hyun Woo,
he won't be able to neglect his
father's crime and send me to jail.
Let's go, I'm tired.
That's right. We have to say that
Nurse Yoon is Ah Ran's sister.
No matter how Hyun Woo
Hyung wants to take revenge,
he can't leave the sister
of the woman he loves alone.
For Nurse Yoon, he'll have
to destroy all the charges.
Nurse Yoon.
You said you were looking for your Unnie.
I'll let you meet her.
I know. I'll go when the time comes.
Was it Nam Joo Seung?
How could Nam Joo Seung
know where your Unnie is?
But, it doesn't seem like he's lying.
He told me to meet him at
6 at Seoul Hotel's coffee shop.
Nam Joo Seung has no
reason to find your Unnie.
All the crimes have been revealed,
there's nowhere to go.
He might do something to you,
you have to be careful.
It'll be fine if Ahjusshi comes along.
They're under police
investigation right now,
they wouldn't cause any trouble.
Hurry and go in.
Thank you. We were just about
to call you, it's good you came.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
It's not like we can repay what
you've done for us with a meal,
but at least we can express our gratitude.
No, it's not like I've done anything.
Actually, you've sent me to school,
I've been the one who has been getting help.
Go wash your hands. On the way here,
didn't you keep saying you were hungry?
Sit.
That's right, what happened
at the police station?
Don't feel like you should sympathize
with Joo Ah Ran, don't dream about it.
Other than that, Father,
when you were running Geum Ok Furniture,
were there any employees that died while working?
A couple that died on the same day,
did that death happen when Dad was in charge?
What? Who told you that?
Hurry and drag that person
over by his collar!
Please tell me,
I have to know.
Those are all things in the past.
They died because of a mistake they made,
why do you have to blame it on me?
Looks like they want to find
someone to take revenge on,
do they think I'll blink because of that?
You remember it too, don't you?
That brother-in-law and his wife,
barged into the office,
and made a nuisance of themselves.
Do you not remember?
Yes, I remember.
Then, did you compensate them?
Is there any evidence of compensation?
These are the secret accounts
for Geum Ok Furniture.
Secretary Nam was in charge of it.
Not long ago, Joo Seung said it was part
of Secretary Nam's things, and brought it here.
Then, the company wasn't doing well,
so we couldn't give much compensation.
But giving that amount was already enough.
But,
did they really die because of an accident?
I said it was so, why won't you believe me?
But,
who told you all of this?
Did that brother and his wife,
come look for you?
Actually,
Joo Ah Ran, is the daughter
of the couple that died.
What?
Joo Ah Ran is the daughter
of Factory Manager Joo Chul Min?
How can something like
that happen in this world?
That means, she had bad intentions
when she married into our family?
She thought I killed her
father, or something?
No matter what methods Joo Ah Ran uses,
she'll use that incident to force my hand.
I can't handle the situation
without knowing the truth.
That factory manager was frustrating
me because of his bad behavior,
it was true that his relationship
with me was bad.
But, am I the kind of person
that will kill a person so he'll shut up?
Don't be influenced by her.
You have to get Joo Ah Ran to repent
for every single one of her crimes.
Yes, I believe Father.
I'll take care of this account book.
I heard Hyun Woo say you
we’re going to meet your sister.
Did you meet her?
I haven't met her yet,
there were too many things
going on yesterday.
Maybe I'll meet her tonight.
Ah, is that so?
Being able to meet my family,
is something that I never even dreamt about.
I'm especially excited and happy.
Tonight, I'm meeting Unnie,
Ahjusshi also promised to come with me.
Ah, sit.
There's nothing much, just eat up.
It looks delicious,
I'll eat well.
Nurse Yoon looks like she
hasn't gotten married.
Is there a person you have in mind?
I was going to tell you after dinner,
but after the police investigations
and all the complications are settled,
I was thinking of marrying Jae Hee.
Marrying? It isn't anything bad too.
When you were in trouble, you spent it together,
looking at each other and relying on each other.
Although it's a shame
you don't have parents,
as long as you're not the
daughter of Joo Chul Min.
What do you think?
They're quite compatible, right?
Yes?
Until now...
Ah, let me go.
I said, I don't like it!
Why don't you like it?
I said I want to introduce you formally
to my family, does that make you so angry?
You said we were going somewhere else,
and asked me to dress up,
so we're going to your house?
When did I say I would marry you, Manager?
Then, Yeon Jae, you don't like me?
You haven't had any feelings
for me all this time?
Even though it's not the case,
but it's not marriage either.
I don't want to be the daughter-in-law
of such a powerful family,
and then go around being bullied
like I have a needle stuck in my heart.
Is that the reason you don't want to?
It looks like Hyung is telling them he
wants to marry Nurse Yoon today.
Nurse Yoon and Yeon Jae
are not very different.
She grew up alone in an orphanage,
and had a hard time going to school too.
Even so, she's a lady.
Your brother has been divorced before,
and now he's marrying a lady...
What conditions could he ask for?
Then, are we married,
or someone insignificant?
What's the difference?
I'm not a lady!
Actually, he already died.
What... What?
Although he died before
we could register it,
but I've also had a wedding ceremony
where everybody came together,
I clearly had a husband.
Although that idiot left a huge debt,
but, he was my husband for a day.
So, Manager, you wake up too.
It... It can't be.
Yeon Jae... How could she...?
Hyun Woo, are you really,
going to marry Nurse Yoon?
Yes.
Once the divorce is settled,
I'm going to marry her.
That won't do.
You can't marry her, I don't agree.
Why? Because she's an orphan?
Mom, you know too, what kind
of person Jae Hee is to me.
Without Jae Hee, I wouldn't
be the person I am today.
You can repay that gratitude
in a different way,
you don't have to get married
because you're thankful.
If she needs money, help her with money.
Mother, this sort of groundless
refusal doesn't seem like my mother at all.
You have to at least give me a reason.
Hyun Woo,
although you loved Ah Ran,
you didn't know everything about Ah Ran.
Jae Hee is the same too.
What parents gave birth to her,
what her past was like,
you don't have any idea.
Why, do you want to marry someone like that?
- Ah Ran and Jae Hee are different.
- There's no difference!
Actually...
Actually... Jae Hee...
Hyung,
what are you doing here?
Marry me.
Don't touch my woman!
What?
Yoon Jae Hee,
is the woman I love.
Don't use your cruel hands,
to touch a single hair of the woman I love.
No,
I can't give up.
Whether that man is Shin Hyun Woo,
or Ahn Jae Sung, I can't give up.
He was clearly in front of me.
My heart is clearly still beating.
It doesn't matter if I love him or hate him.
I can never give that man to Yoon Jae Hee.
Ah Ran came here, right?
Where is she?
Why would she come here?
Did you forget?
Our Hyun Woo came back alive.
Is that so?
Your tone makes you sound really grateful.
But, Hyun Woo coming back alive,
for Madam, you aren't just happy, right?
Hyun Woo, will continue
hanging out to Ah Ran.
Then, the only people that will be hurt,
will be your family, Madam.
Hyun Woo clings on to Ah Ran,
Ah Ran clings on to your family.
What an interesting cycle.
Oh right,
I'll take this opportunity, maybe the secret
between Madam and I will be exposed.
Why in the world are you doing this?
If you want to take revenge against me,
and linked hands with Ah Ran,
please stop.
For Ah Ran, how much of
your life do you want to ruin?
Your doctor's license has already been
suspended, how are you going to live?
Half a son is still a son,
are you worrying about me now?
But, no matter what happens,
I won't abandon Ah Ran.
I'll stand by... my father's
words to watch over Ah Ran.
Joo Seung.
Madam, you know too, right?
Ah Ran's sister, is Nurse Yoon.
How did you know?
The person who handed Nurse Yoon
to the orphanage and kept supporting her...
was you, Madam, right?
You wanted to redeem your crime
of killing Ah Ran's parents, right?
But, by your hand,
Hyun Woo and Nurse Yoon,
me and Ah Ran,
two brothers and two sisters,
have an inseparable relationship.
This life is interesting, right?
Hold on.
I have to talk to you,
about why I wanted to marry
you and created all this.
You want to say that my
parents killed your parents,
stop creating trouble.
Your parents died because of an accident.
Here is evidence that your uncle signed,
and we also paid you compensation.
How can you believe that account book?
Have you thought that it
could have been faked?
Stop trying those cheap threats!
It looks like you want
to use those baseless excuses,
to get yourself off.
I'll never let you off that easily.
Jae Hee, it's me.
I'll be late.
You go to the wedding dress shop first.
I'll be there.
Wedding shop?
You've made me so pathetic,
and you want to marry Yoon Jae Hee?
Then, the ring, necklace, and the earrings
you gave me, what are these?
Was it all efforts to trick me?!
All right.
You and I,
will die here today.
Stop the car immediately!
I'm not stopping!
Even if you can't be with me forever,
I can't watch you go back
to Yoon Jae Hee's side.
All right.
I won't die in your hands,
much less die with you!
Jae Sung.
Look at me.
Besides your parents,
and my parents,
let the two of us talk.
Wake up.
I'm not Ahn Jae Sung,
I'm Shin Hyun Woo.
Did you forget?
My heart still remembers Ahn Jae Sung,
what do you want me to do?
Please take away the memories
of Ahn Jae Sung in my heart too, please.
Such a woman like you is really disgusting.
You just explained that it was because
of your parents that you sought revenge.
Now, you're saying it's for love?
But what can I do?
I didn't want to spend a single
cent of my money buying your love.
If you want love so much,
how about going back to being Rosemary?
Ahn Jae Sung.
You underestimate me.
I won't die that easily.
Are you Yoon Jae Hee?
Yes.
President Ahn Jae Sun
asked me to pick you up.
Ahjusshi?
He asked me to wait here.
He said he would take a long time.
Please get in the car.
Who are you?
Where's my guest?
She's not here yet.
What? Not here yet?
The time has already passed.
Your call cannot be connected right now...
Jae Hee.
Jae Hee, where are you?
Nothing happened, right?
Everything is fine, right?
Tonight, at 6, he asked me to go
to Seoul Hotel's Coffee shop.
Where did you go?
In the future, no matter
what you do, tell me.
Joo Seung.
Do you still have anything you need me for?
You clearly know that being
with me will be dangerous for you.
Why aren't you leaving?
I still have things to do for you.
I contacted Kyeong Ran.
We made an appointment to meet
at Seoul Hotel's coffee shop at 6.
Is that true?
How do you know Kyeong Ran?
How I know her, you'll
understand when we meet.
Hurry and get ready. It's almost time.
Ah Ran. Don't hate me.
This is the best choice I can make for you.
If you don't hurry and capture Yoon Jae Hee,
you won't escape the palm of Shin Hyun Woo.
What are you doing here?
Where's Jae Hee?
What have you done to Jae Hee?
From the afternoon,
Jae Hee has been missing.
Nurse Yoon is missing?
She's not at home, she's not picking up her
phone, her person has gone missing.
If the two of you have messed with Jae Hee,
I'll risk my life, and
not let the two of you go.
Those leather shoes,
whose are those?
It has nothing to do with you.
I've made an appointment
with someone really important.
Please don't pretend you're interested,
and leave.
No.
This has something to do with Hyung.
Take a seat.
Since you're here, I want to
tell you about Ah Ran's sister.
What does that mean?
Why do we have to tell him about Kyeong Ran?
Kyeong Ran?
My real name isn't Jae Hee, it's Kyeong Ran.
- Kyeong Ran?
- That's right, Kyeong Ran.
Hyung, you know her too.
How does he know our Kyeong Ran?
Because Kyeong Ran...
is Nurse Yoon.
What?
Nurse Yoon's real name is Joo Kyeong Ran.
When your parents died,
Madam handed Kyeong Ran
over to Angel Orphanage.
That can't be.
Yoon Jae Hee is Kyeong Ran.
Our Kyeong Ran...
how could she be Yoon Jae Hee?
Jae Hee...
is Joo Ah Ran's sister.
That can't be.
Open the door!
Please open the door!
Someone!
When did you know?
Why didn't you tell me, why?
I only found out not long ago.
I was afraid you would be affected,
so I didn't tell you.
Why does it have to be Yoon Jae Hee?
The sister I was looking so desperately for,
why did it have to be Yoon Jae Hee?
How does it feel?
Hyung, the woman you hate the most and
the woman you love the most are actually sisters.
Their blood is connected.
Sisters who have met only after 25 years,
are they going to go against
that because of you, Hyung?
No, it can't be!
Jae Hee can't be sisters with Joo Ah Ran!
If you don't believe me, go
ask Madam personally.
Madam knows everything.
What?
It's all a lie.
I don't believe it.
I can't not recognize my sister.
Something must have gone wrong.
Yoon Jae Hee is not my sister!
Nurse Yoon...
is our Kyeong Ran?
She's my sister?
That's really strange.
Sisters born by the same parents.
One wants to give someone love,
one wants to give someone hate.
Nurse Yoon, even if she's Joo Ah Ran's
sister, you haven't been moved, right?
I don't know either.
Why is everything so complicated?
Because of me, what if
something happens to her?
My heart is so restless
it's about to explode.
I can't let Jae Hee get
hurt because of my revenge.
Don't worry too much.
It'll definitely be all right.
When you can't do anything,
just don't do anything.
We can only wait for time to pass,
and let the storm settle.
Love is really difficult.
You really don't know where Nurse Yoon is?
I don't know.
What are your plans for the future?
Even if I'm Yoon Jae Hee's sister,
what difference does it make?
I'm still Joo Ah Ran.
What a really cheap and unsalvageable woman.
I've always especially despised you,
but I think you're pathetic today.
In order to live such a terrible life, your mother
suffered so much pain to give birth to you?
How pathetic.
Mom.
Dad.
What should I do?
Tell me.
I shouldn't have looked for Kyeong Ran.
I should have just thought she was dead.
Then, I wouldn't be in so much pain now.
Jae Hee is Joo Ah Ran's sister,
is this true?
How do you know?
So it's true.
Till the end, I hoped it wouldn't be true.
That's why I objected to your marriage.
Does Jae Hee know too?
She still doesn't know.
From yesterday afternoon,
she's been missing.
Missing? What does that mean?
No matter what, I think Ah Ran
has done something to Jae Hee.
I have a bad feeling.
If nothing happened, she wouldn't
be uncontactable like this.
My guess was too shallow.
I shouldn't have helped that child.
If I hadn't helped that child,
you wouldn't have met like that,
and Ah Ran and Jae Hee, wouldn't
meet under these consequences.
Even if it wasn't for Mother, people who
were meant to meet, will still meet.
Jae Hee is Ah Ran's sister,
but my heart won't change either.
I want to marry Jae Hee.
That won't do.
Ah Ran is your wife,
your legally married wife.
But, how could you marry Ah Ran's sister?
That's incest.
Even so, I have to take
responsibility for Jae Hee.
No matter what, I can't let her get hurt.
If something happens to her because of me,
I'll never forgive myself.
Hyun Woo.
Even though I'm sorry to say this,
can you not press charges against Joo Seung?
No matter what, to you,
he was a child that was
like a younger brother.
This time,
there are burdens that
he has to bear as well.
Mom should harden her heart,
and just watch.
Shin Hyun Woo.
Do we have to go all the way?
This cannot continue.
No matter what card Shin Hyun Woo plays,
we have to make preparations.
There's a lawyer we know, you go meet him.
I have to go around and
make preparations too.
She's all right, right?
Don't do anything to her, just monitor her.
I'm leaving right now.
All right, Joo Ah Ran,
you make your move.
Now that you know that
Jae Hee is your sister,
you can't be completely unmoved either.
All right.
Since this is the case,
I have no choice either.
I can only tell the truth now.
This is Maria Nunnery, right?
No!
Come down. No.
So it was you,
who shut me here.
Not only are you not repenting,
are you going to continue doing evil?
I won't be controlled by you anymore,
rather than that,
I might as well jump down
from here and break both my legs.
No! It's dangerous!
Jae Hee!
No, don't move.
Ahjussi.
No! Kyeong Ran!
No.
I promised Mom.
I would take care of you.
No.
It can't be.
It can't be!
Jae Hee!
No! Kyeong Ran!
Joo Ah Ran is really my sister?
She isn't right?
How can such a frightening
person be my Unnie?
We're not sisters anymore.
There's only Shin Hyun Woo's
woman, Yoon Jae Hee.
Joo Ah Ran is Joo Ah Ran,
Yoon Jae Hee is Yoon Jae Hee.
I'm going to kill them all.
The President...
Your Mother and Hyun Woo.
You found the real Ahn Jae Sung?
If only the real Ahn Jae Sung is alive, every
contract that Shin Hyun Woo made would be a fraud.
The person who spoilt the wheel,
was you, Shin Woo Sub, right?
You left out an important detail.
My dad has two daughters,
the elder daughter is me, the
younger daughter is Yoon Jae Hee,
Father's prospective daughter-in-law.