Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 14
Shin Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo hyung.
It's been a long time.
So I see you're alive.
- What are you talking about now?
- Keep those childish acting skills!
With another face, another voice,
you think I wouldn't know?
What plans do you have?
If you're alive like this, and not going
home, what plans do you have?
Are you following me?
The hospital is about to be transferred, you
actually have time to waste time like this?
How did you survive the fire?
In order to hide your burns,
you underwent plastic surgery?
Joo Seung.
I'm a doctor.
No matter what Hyung changes into,
as long as I have a drop of blood,
a strand of hair,
I'll be able to tell who you are.
Aren't you going to let him go?
Episode 14
Why are you so clingy and pathetic?
Didn't I ask you to let it
go cleanly like a man?
Why are you so persistent and tiring?
This man here, is not Ahn Jae Sung,
but Shin Hyun Woo.
What?
He had surgery to get another person's face,
and purposely got closer
to you in order to take revenge.
Finding evidence to show
that you killed Hyun Woo Hyung,
and then pushing you into
desperation, how could I not know?
Joo Seung.
If you don't believe it, take a look at this.
Can't you see the words, "Shin Hyun Woo"?
If it wasn't really Hyun Woo Hyung,
how could he use Hyun Woo Hyung's
name and do business with the bank?
With such clear evidence,
why don't you believe what I'm saying?
It's because of this?
That bank book, I gave it to Jae Sung.
What?
The code to Shin Hyun Woo's
bank account changed,
that's why I asked
Jae Sung to do me a favor.
How did things go, are they settled?
After I showed them your ID,
they told me just like
I was Shin Hyun Woo himself.
The money in the account
has all been taken out.
I was so worried,
it's such a relief.
Thank you so much.
Lies, nonsense!
Then what about the plastic surgery,
what about the painkillers?!
Because I have a slipped disc,
I had a prescription for painkillers filled at a
hospital owned by one of my closest Hyung's.
Do I have to explain something like that?
Other than that,
what evidence is there concerning
Shin Hyun Woo's death?
Could it be,
that Ah Ran has something to do
with Shin Hyun Woo's death?
What are you saying?
That's ridiculous.
Don't you understand that
Doctor Nam is trying to trick us?
You have to rush back to
the office, don't you.
You should head back first.
All right.
I'll call you.
What are you doing?
Are you going around
saying I killed Shin Hyun Woo?
What if Ahn Jae Sung's
suspicions are aroused?
You killed Shin Hyun Woo,
could Ahn Jae Sung not know about it?
That's because Ahn Jae Sung
is Shin Hyun Woo.
I really don't understand
why you're so persistent.
Mother's favorite son is dead,
and her other son was in love with his wife,
shouldn't your revenge be over by now?
We're not talking about me right now.
Are you really that angry that
Mother doesn't want to accept you?
But you have your mother,
your profession as a doctor,
and your siblings.
For someone who has 99 houses,
do you want to use me as a shield,
and get your hundredth?
It is a fact that I hate
the mother that birthed me,
but I don't want to ruin
you in order to fulfill my desire.
Now, I have no interest in revenge,
and I have no other thoughts but
protecting you from Shin Hyun Woo.
If you ever loved me at all,
you would give me freedom now.
The investor that helped
me was Jo Sung Mo's sister,
and after the family found out about my past,
they leapt at me like they wanted to kill me.
Even President Hwang is strangling my neck.
If you force me as well,
there is only death for me.
The aftereffects of the plastic surgery
on your entire body is very severe.
The site of the skin
grafts keep getting infected,
and your heart is getting weaker,
unreasonably working out is also very dangerous.
You're here.
What medicine is that?
Are you feeling unwell?
It's a medicine that I have
to take for the rest of my life.
Because of the traffic accident and
the aftereffects of the plastic surgery,
my entire body is plagued
with strange symptoms.
It's a pain that will accompany
me for the rest of my life,
I'm used to it.
I always thought
only gods could punish human beings.
But, my thoughts have changed.
I won't blame it on the gods anymore.
The price of my brother's life,
the price of your pain,
I will personally reap it back.
The real revenge,
is to wait for the other party to get more,
before you see them fall,
even more tragically.
The child that Mom abandoned,
how great could he grow up to be?
Even the mother that gave birth to
him pretends not to know him,
there's nothing to hope for either.
To understand the hate
accompanying the death of your son,
you want to kill that son you've
pretended not to know for 30 years?
That's right.
Ah Ran and Joo Seung must know something.
If Hyun Woo's father knows too...
Could you know,
a way to contact the Father?
I don't know.
He either calls me directly,
or he contacts the people
who brought me here.
What?
The people who brought me here?
Wasn't I abandoned in the orphanage?
Director, that's what you said.
Is there really a ghost?
Do you remember the factory
manager that died 25 years ago?
My hands are too slippery.
I've forgotten it after
living for so many years,
but this has been pressing
on my chest recently.
Hyun Woo's death,
the instability of the company too,
it feels like a ghost is toying with us.
Keep your voice down,
the children can hear you.
So what if they hear?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Someone who moves lumber,
he brought his family during working hours,
and died because of his own mistake.
It's not that I killed him,
what do I have to feel bad about.
Please tell me,
who was the person who brought me here.
All right,
it shouldn't be a secret anymore.
Actually, the person who's always supported
you, President Shin, his mother,
was the person who brought you here.
What?
Madam?
She always took care of
you like you were family.
Maybe she had some difficulties,
she never explained the details.
Madam...
Why would she leave me here?
How did she know me?
About that...
Maybe you're distant relatives.
At first, it was the chauffeur that came,
after that it was her son.
Just now, I heard my
Uncle called them.
Then, Madam should know
my Uncle's contact details.
Mom.
Dad.
It's almost coming.
God might pity me too,
and sent me someone who could help me.
Just wait a while,
I'll personally close your eyes.
Here, a birthday present for our Ah Ran.
Here's another pair of Kyeong Ran.
Wow, it's too pretty.
Kyeong Ran, Unni's is pretty too, right?
Don't keep them, wear them all you like.
If they're too small you
won't be able to wear them.
I might lose them, so I should
write my name on them.
What are you doing on the new shoes?
Kyeong Ran's too.
In any case, our Ah Ran is the brightest.
Here.
Kyeong Ran.
Where are you?
How hungry you must be,
and how hard your life must be.
Director.
Nurse Yoon.
I would like to know something.
What relationship do you
have with Ahn Jae Sung?
I... love President Ahn.
But because of that, I'm always
being threatened by Joo Ah Ran.
Please help me.
Doesn't Director love Joo Ah Ran?
Let me love President Ahn freely,
please, Director, catch hold of
Joo Ah Ran. I'm begging you.
Tell me honestly.
The person that Nurse Yoon loves,
is it Ahn Jae Sung, or Shin Hyun Woo?
As long as you answer this,
I'll help Nurse Yoon.
What are you suspicious about?
The last time I saw Patient
Shin was that day at the villa.
His death in that fire,
I only heard about it later.
When the fire broke out
at the Yang Pyeong villa,
the person that helped
Shin Woo Hyung was Nurse Yoon.
Is there a reason to help Hyun Woo Hyung?
Could you have known each other from before?
Wasn't the person who introduced
Patient Shin Hyun Woo to me, you, Director?
And the person that made me meet
President Ahn, was also, you Director.
No!
President Ahn Jae Sung and Nurse Yoon,
you knew each other from before.
I've seen the two of you together.
If the Director and Joo Ah Ran,
keeps torturing me like that,
I might as well tell the truth
to Patient Shin Hyun Woo's family,
just to shake off the two of you.
Are you threatening me right now?
That's not a threat,
that's asking for a favor.
Then, goodbye.
Who is it?
Where did you go?
I waited a long time.
Is that so?
I went to the orphanage
after I got off work.
Actually, my Uncle came over,
and said he wanted to see me.
Is that so?
That's good, are there any contact details?
Not yet,
What I want to find out,
I'm not sure, if Madam has any
information that could help me.
Well...
She did say that a pretty
girl wanted some help,
but didn't say anything else.
Today, I heard from the Director,
that Madam was the one
who brought me to the orphanage.
Was I... someone's child
that Madam knew?
I heard about it a while ago,
but it's not like I could go ask Mom
about it, what a headache.
Or not, Jae Hee, why don't you ask Mother directly?
Take the opportunity to tell her you
were the little lantern that received help.
Can I... really do that?
I'm sorry.
Even with this,
I can't help you at all.
As a compensation,
tell me another wish,
I'll try and fulfill it.
Another... wish?
I want to see the sea in the winter.
Do you want to come with me?
Jae Hee.
There's no one here.
Let's yell out the stories in our heart.
Of course,
in front of the sea,
everyone wants to spill their hearts.
It's just like an explosion in
your heart that clears everything away.
Why? Just shout out loud.
I am...
Shin Hyun Woo!
My name is...
Shin Hyun Woo,
wait a while more.
I'll immediately use your name to return.
Grit your teeth and hold on, you punk.
Ahjussi.
It's my turn.
'Till now,
I've never called out for Dad and Mom.
I have to gather up some
courage and shout for them.
It has to be really loud
to travel to the heavens,
you can't mock me.
Dad!
Mom!
Can they hear you like that?
In order to get rid of all
the grievances you've faced so far,
it has to be louder!
Dad!
Mom!
Unni!
Where are you?
You haven't forgotten me, right?
Why aren't you coming to look for me?
Waiting like this,
I think I'm going to go crazy.
Jae Hee,
I will definitely look for
your family for you.
Don't cry.
Once you cry, I feel like
my heart is going to explode.
I love you,
I love you, Jae Hee.
What happened with the
matter I asked you to look into?
Factory Manager Joo Chul Ming, we've already gotten
a hold of the address for his brother and his wife.
Is that so?
Call the office immediately.
What that family is planning on doing,
we have to take a thorough look.
Who is the person that is disturbing
someone who has been dead for 25 years?
Are they doing evil to our family?
I have to find that all out.
Did you have a good sleep, Father?
Did something bad happen?
Don't get involved in our family matters.
Double check again, when the money
from Myeong Sung Electronics is coming in.
That...
President Hwang might need more time,
because of the mistake at the meeting.
That's why,
why don't we go meet SM Furniture,
in order to expedite the merger deal?
SM Furniture?
Such a strong company is investing in us,
what reason is there to merge
with such a small company?
SM Furniture is not a
company to be taken lightly.
They've just expanded their business online,
and there will be less problems in the future,
because their designs are similar to Soul's.
President Hwang hopes for the merger too.
President Hwang too?
He wants you to keep your
position as representative.
To Soul it's not a bad deal.
Although I don't have
the right as a daughter-in-law,
but when it comes to the business,
it's better to listen to me.
You have to follow him 24 hours.
You have to report all the details,
you can't leave anything out.
I understand, please don't worry.
Where did you go, that you're back now?
It's ddukbokki and fish sticks,
I bought them because Yeon Jae likes them.
Ddukbokki?
It was right to wait without eating,
Manager you have some too.
You must have been starving the whole day.
I don't want any,
Yeon Jae, you eat them all.
Here.
Is it delicious?
Of course it's delicious.
I'm so hungry, I'm hallucinating.
Hold on, I'll get you some water.
What?
You ate two bowls of ramen,
and you're eating this too?
That's true.
It would have been better if I had held on.
Sorry.
If you weren't hungry,
you should have said so.
Eating like that, what would
happen if you got sick?
So what if I got sick?
Manager thought about me and bought it.
Even if I stuff myself sick, I'll eat it.
Don't worry.
Delicious.
What am I?
Like a fool,
everyone can't wait to fight me.
Stop eating. You'll really got a stomachache.
Give it to me, I'll eat it.
I told you to stop eating.
Give it to me, why are
you acting like that?
Ddukbokki sauce.
I'll wipe it off for you.
Stop laughing.
Stay still, don't move.
Because our niece is treating,
it tastes more delicious.
If it's free, everything is delicious.
Yes, yes.
Listen to what I'm saying.
My father in law is looking
everywhere for you.
If he sends someone to fetch you,
you definitely can't go either.
If the truth gets out that
my father is Factory Manager Joo,
we're all done for.
That's something for you to worry about,
we have nothing to fear.
For our brother, we need to speak the truth,
and to take you out of that
family is also logical for us.
If I die, you die with me too.
Telling Father in law the truth,
do you think you'll get ten thousand?
We know, we know,
do you think we're outsiders?
What happened with Kyeong Ran?
How come there's no news
on finding Kyeong Ran at all?
That...
Actually, we found
Kyeong Ran a few days ago.
Right?
Is that true?
Where's Kyeong Ran?
Can I meet her immediately now?
Where does she stay?
Tell me know.
Yes, yes.
We've made several appointments
with Kyeong Ran to meet her,
but there's a lady that keeps getting
in the way, so it's all for naught.
Who's the girl?
Who is it?
Just the woman who took Kyeong
Ran away from the orphanage.
That woman, we don't know if she's
trying to do a deal using Kyeong Ran,
she changed all their numbers,
then ran away.
No matter what, you have to find her.
I'll forget all the things
you've done to me,
no matter what, you have to
bring Kyeong Ran in front of me.
If you're clothed in skin and come to the
human world, you have to at least do something!
Today, I'm not here as a nurse,
but I'm here because I have something to ask.
Is that so?
Tell me.
What is it you want to ask?
I'm sorry I haven't been able
to come clean with you all this while.
Actually, I'm the little lantern from the
Angel Orphanage that Madam supports.
You still remember little lantern?
What are you saying?
Little lantern?
Nurse Yoon is little lantern?
Yes, that child is me.
For 25 years, thank you for taking
care of me like I'm your own child.
Coincidentally meeting Patient
Shin Hyun Woo at the Yang Pyeong Villa,
really gave me a shock.
How could something like that happen?
Nurse Yoon took care of our Hyun Woo...
I came here today to look for my family.
You helped me,
do you know anything about my family?
Ah, that.
I only... wanted to help someone.
And very coincidentally,
it happened to be Nurse Yoon.
Then, do you know anything
about my parents or my siblings?
Of course. If I knew I would have told you.
I'm really sorry I couldn't help you.
No, my gratitude for your
constant help is greater than that.
In this lifetime,
the debt that I owe Madam,
I will pay it back diligently.
Then, I'll leave first.
Nurse Yoon.
It's a little strange.
Why have you never said...
that you were little lantern?
My special relationship with Shin Hyun Woo,
I thought I shouldn't let
your daughter-in-law find out.
What does that mean?
I don't know if I should tell you this,
but Patient Shin Hyun Woo regained consciousness
for a little while, at the Yang Pyeong Villa.
What?
Our Hyun Woo regained consciousness?
Then, why didn't you inform us? Why?
Could it be, that our daughter-in-law
told you not to say anything?
I'm sorry,
I should have taken every
opportunity to inform you, I’m sorry.
Madam, the fact that you're my sponsor,
please keep it from your daughter-in-law.
Then.
How could Ah Ran do something like that?
Hide the fact that Hyun Woo woke up?
Why?
What's the reason?
In the beginning, they seemed
so strong they wouldn't give way,
and then they gave way to
SM Furniture, in a show of losing,
the next step, I'll handle it.
All right.
I've asked Joo Ah Ran to come to the house.
Let's toast.
I've met the brother of the factory manager.
But he keeps claiming that he doesn't know Joo
Chul Ming, and denies ever meeting the President.
What?!
What are all these beggars
thinking, trying to slip away?
If they're really Joo Chul Ming's
siblings, they'll know me.
I'll go meet them myself, find out
where they live, and fix a time!
There were no mistakes, right?
Yes.
This woman...
I heard she's Jung Sang Hwa,
the President of SM Furniture.
President Jung?
Ahn Jae Sung is meeting up
with Jung Sang Mo's sister, isn't he?
Then...
You like chrysanthemum tea, right?
Father seems to have fallen in love
with someone who likes chrysanthemum.
The house always smelt like chrysanthemums.
When did you find out I was your mother?
Don't say it in that way!
Your whole life you were Madam to me,
you should live like that till you die.
The idea that you could
clumsily become my mother,
don't even dream about it.
I reject it.
- Joo Seung.
- Don't call me like that!
The Madam... that Dad waited for
every time he closed his eyes,
such a pathetic person,
are you going to send him away like that?
To other people, you're
like a charitable Buddha,
but, why are you so harsh,
on the person who's missed
you his entire life, why?!
I thought that would be the best
way to protect all of us, to save you.
Keep those explanations!
Just be honest,
and say you didn't want
to destroy your family,
that I could understand.
Think whatever you like.
I'm already prepared to accept
your hate and your disgust.
But, something has to be clarified.
Because you hate me, you and Ah Ran
did something horrible to our Hyun Woo, right?!
The day Hyun Woo died in the fire, this is
a photograph of Ah Ran at Yang Pyeong.
The Ah Ran that left at 5, and was still at Yang
Pyeong 2 hours later, how do you explain that?
Did Ah Ran go back to the villa?
Why? Do you know?!
Is it because you hated me,
that's why you killed our Hyun Woo?
Both you and Ah Ran?!
Don't try and stretch the truth.
Stretch the truth?!
I know you're angry at me.
But, Hyun Woo has no sins.
Now, just tell me all the truth.
No matter whatever you say,
I'll keep your secret till my death.
I mean it.
Hyun Woo Hyung,
died because Madam left
the gas on when she went out.
That's how Madam killed two children.
Me and Hyun Woo Hyung.
Do you understand?
If you want to push all your
sins now, to me and Ah Ran,
I won't let you do as you wish.
The grief of our Hyun Woo,
I'll settle it for him.
Even if my past is discovered, I'll do it too.
How my son died,
I'll definitely find out.
So it turns out this way.
I couldn't become Madam's son in the end.
Hyun Woo Hyung's death,
if you want to find out, find out.
But you better not provoke me.
You're here, President Joo.
Take a seat.
Who are you coming to see today?
Julie Jung, or Jung Sang Hwa?
From the very beginning,
did you get close to me with a motive?
The creation of SM Furniture,
was also done with me as a target in mind?
About that,
it's a long time ago,
I don't really remember.
The person who gave me
the design, was Sang Mo!
For his Noona to step out,
and plunge his woman into misery,
do you think Sang Mo will be happy?
If Sang Mo wanted my destruction,
he should have killed me, not himself.
Till the end,
you refuse to admit your crime, is that so?
All the men in this world,
wouldn't kill themselves because
they fell out of love, right?
I know the misery of losing a younger sibling,
but don't take it out on me.
This is the proposal to
merge Soul with SM Furniture.
Read it, and let me know.
Soul, taking over SM?
Of course.
If you want to reverse it,
and have SM take over Soul,
I'll file for bankruptcy and
wash my hands of it.
In that case, your investment would go to waste.
If there's something you want to accomplish,
you should accept my proposal.
Then, I await your reply.
It can't be.
If Mom knew, she would have told you.
No,
Madam clearly knew something,
but I don't know why she's hiding it.
He's meeting with Yoon Jae Hee?
I got it.
Ahn Jae Sung.
Now, I've definitely caught you by the tail.
Madam,
what should I do?
Before you find out the reasons
behind Hyun Woo Hyung's death,
looks like I'll uncover
Ahn Jae Sung's true face.
Take a good look at the photos.
Ahn Jae Sung knew
Jung Sang Hwa a long time ago.
SM Furniture and Ahn Jae Sung
aren't strangers.
Nonsense,
this can't be.
Even now, he's hiding
his meetings with Yoon Jae Hee.
Why?
Ahn Jae Sung and Yoon Jae Hee already
knew each other from Yang Pyeong villa.
Clearly he has ill intentions,
and circling around you.
Trust me.
If Hyun Woo Hyung comes back alive
and confronts you about your crimes,
I've already made preparations to bear them.
The person who can help you,
in this world, is only me.
But Shin Hyun Woo and Ahn Jae Sung,
are completely different,
even their looks.
Because he was burnt at the villa,
he most probably got plastic surgery.
Personality too, interests too, tastes too,
they're all completely different.
To fool you,
he could have covered it up intentionally.
Also, President Ahn is a
world-class equestrian.
How could Shin Hyun Woo,
who hates horses so much...
Do that?
Ahn Jae Sung is good at drumming too,
and good at cooking.
And he's gifted at sports,
it definitely can't be Shin Hyun Woo.
The fact that he's not like Shin Hyun Woo,
is the evidence that Ahn Jae Sung
is Shin Hyun Woo.
If he didn't throw out the horse-hating,
Western cuisine-hating Shin Hyun Woo,
there was no way you would believe it.
Think about it.
Is there something about Shin Woo Hyung,
something that he couldn't
change no matter what?
That's right.
Fear of heights,
because of his fear of heights,
he said he hated taking planes
the most, in this world.
Fear of heights?
When I was young, I fell from a horse, so I didn't
like to ride, and also became afraid of heights.
Then, race with me.
If it's not a game, it's not interesting.
Compared to spaghetti,
bean paste soup is better.
You know, that I prefer Korean food.
Maybe because I grew up overseas,
Korean food is more foreign to me.
Even now, I can't get
used to the taste of bean paste,
I can't eat it.
It's been a while, Nurse Yoon.
You're here?
Director is inside.
What did you do last night?
Did you meet President Ahn.
No.
It was a friend's birthday,
so I went to play with my friends.
Is that so?
Did you find it?
Here. Nurse Yoon's background.
There's nothing special
about her background.
Do you have family certificates,
or special personal information?
She was a nurse that was here before I came,
so there were no special requirements.
I think I heard someone
similar to a mother was sick,
but I don't know anything else.
I have to get a full understanding
of how Nurse Yoon grew up,
in order to get my information.
What her family was like,
Joo Seung, you help me find out.
I'll investigate President Ahn.
It seems you're really good
at making Korean food.
The taste of the bean paste
is really authentic.
It's fortunate that it's to your taste.
I always hear people tell me that I like Western food,
that I'm suited to live in the Western world,
actually, I'm very Korean.
Even though your brother isn't here,
how would you like to start afresh here?
If you wish,
I could help you with anything you need.
Don't let me have useless hopes.
During that period, I was really lonely,
so if you care for me,
I'll be moved uncontrollably.
I asked the secretary to buy
a cake, it must be here.
Eat more.
You're here without contacting
me at all, what's the matter?
I have something urgent to ask you.
So I see you have a guest.
President Joo.
Ah Ran.
The guest is...
Jae Sung?
Jae Sung and Julie Jung,
both of you know each other.
I didn't know the two of you had the relationship
where you went to each other's houses for dinner.
That...
President Ahn.
I thought you couldn't eat bean paste,
looks like your tastes have changed.
Or, maybe you lied to me,
or if not, you're someone else.
Get out, Ah Ran.
I'll have dinner with you another time.
What is going on?
How do you know President Jung of SM?
The two of you, is there a secret deal between
the two of you that I don't know about?
What is it?
Tell me quickly!
Don't be too excited.
I was just trying to help you.
Liar.
You're working with President Jung,
and planning to put Soul in danger, right?
What is your real motive?
Are you hiding something from me?
The last time, didn't Ah Ran say,
the sister of the person who died
because he had a one-sided love
for Ah Ran opened SM Furniture?
After I heard that, I thought Ah Ran
was in danger, and felt really bad.
So, because of Ah Ran,
I met the President of SM.
Are you expecting me to believe that?
If you don't believe me,
I can't do anything.
There's only one truth.
Just to get closer with President Jung,
I even ate the bean paste
soup that I can't eat,
I made quite an effort.
You suspecting me like
this, is rather chilling.
Joo Seung, it's me.
Continue watching what
Ahn Jae Sung is doing.
It's true that he has a special
relationship with Jung Sang Hwa.
Anyway, I feel like I'm
being kept in the dark.
If there's anything special, contact me.
Why are you here?
What if my family sees you?
You seem rather anxious
because of Kyeong Ran,
how could we lie around comfortably?
That's why, we should work
together to find Kyeong Ran, right?
If you acknowledge our efforts,
then we'll make public the telephone number
of the woman that took Kyeong Ran away.
I understand.
I'll do as you wish,
so tell me.
If it changes, I'll let you know.
You clearly promised,
don't pretend this didn't
happen after you find Kyeong Ran.
This is the number for our house.
Then, the person who took
Kyeong Ran away was Mother?
What is the reason Mother
took Kyeong Ran away?
That's right.
Mother supports the Angel Orphanage.
Then, our Kyeong Ran
could very well be there.
Ah Ran! Where are you going?
I'm really anxious.
We shouldn't have given
her such important information.
I came, because I have
something important to ask you.
Among the children that my
deceased husband was supporting,
was there a child called Joo Kyeong Ran?
Joo Kyeong Ran?
No, there wasn't.
There wasn't?
Then, was there a child, that my mother-in-law
or my husband took special care of?
Madam and her son, helped the entire
orphanage, not just specific children.
But, what is it because of?
No, it's fine.
The fact that I came here,
please don't tell mother-in-law.
If Mother changed the telephone number,
she must know about Kyeong Ran.
But, if I ask about Kyeong Ran,
they'll discover whose daughter I am too.
Aunt, it's me.
I've found out the telephone number
of the person who took Kyeong Ran away.
I'll tell you the number.
You have to find Kyeong Ran. You must.
Hello, this is Peng Chang Dong.
Peng Chang Dong.
This family is in Peng Chang Dong too.
Give it to me, give it to me.
Hello
Have you been living well?
I'm Kyeong Ran's aunt, the person
who contacted you before.
Ah, how could you change
your number like that,
did you think we wouldn't find it?
What?
Just to cut things short,
hurry and bring us our niece.
Trying to find our your address now,
is as easy as eating
cooled abalone porridge.
And you,
do you want to be arrested for kidnapping,
and have it printed in the newspapers?
Don't be shocked.
Let's meet and talk about it.
All right.
Tell me the meeting place
and time, and I'll be there.
And, please don't call this number again,
I hope only you and I
know about this matter.
Mom.
Why are you back at this time?
I forgot to get something.
You don't look too good.
Did something happen?
There were two strange people at
the house, they were looking around.
What?
Shut the door tight, and
don't open it to anyone.
Patient Shin Hyun Woo
regained his consciousness,
for a short time at Yang Pyeong villa.
Why did Mother take Kyeong Ran away?
To us, who had already lost our parents,
what was she trying to do?
Could it be,
that when Father's crimes were discovered,
she was going to use Kyeong Ran as a shield?
It's me, Joo Seung.
Did you find something out?
What?
Ahn Jae Sung is...
at the paper dolls convention right now?
Hyun Woo.
Ah Ran.
Why are you so scared?
It's like someone found out
something they shouldn't have.
It's just such a coincidence.
I didn't expect to see Ah Ran here.
But, just now, did you
just call me Hyun Woo?
Looking at the way you were making
the paper dolls, reminded me of Hyun Woo.
My husband used to love
making paper dolls too.
That's why I thought about
the past and came in to take a look.
I didn't expect to see Jae Sung here.
Is that so.
Looks like Shin Hyun Woo
has special hobbies.
But, I didn't expect that Jae Sung
would have the same interests.
Why didn't you say anything?
That you liked paper dolls?
You are really skilled.
The expressions, the color,
is really similar to my husband's.
Especially,
giving the dolls blush too.
My dolls have blush on their face.
That's Shin Hyun Woo's
trademark on his paper dolls.
Don't forget it.
How could that be?
I haven't learnt the skill for very long.
I was actually going to keep it a secret,
till I made some for Ah Ran as a present.
Is that so?
In that case, today's a really strange day.
I found the paper dolls
that you were hiding from me,
and I also saw you meeting President Jung,
that you said was for my sake.
Other than this,
is there something else I don't know?
Let's go and have fun today,
just like I always wanted
to do with Jae Sung.
Do you have time?
My deceased husband,
even though he was a good and kind man,
but he was terrible at sports.
He hated riding horses,
and was terrible at swimming and the rest.
But Jae Sung is great at
every sport, I like that.
How about a bungee jump?
I don't know,
I've never done it before.
Really?
What a coincidence.
You couldn't be afraid of heights,
just like my ex-husband, right.
Joo Ah Ran is suspecting me.
I have to be more careful.
The decisive factor has been discovered.
If she knows I have a fear of heights,
she'll decide that I'm Shin Hyun Woo.
Why?
Do you not have confidence?
No, it should be quite interesting.
I was just thinking of giving it a shot.
The aftereffects of the plastic surgery
on your entire body is very severe.
Your heart is getting weaker, unreasonably
working out is also very dangerous.
That's right,
even if my heart bursts here, I can never
be that embarrassing Shin Hyun Woo again.
Because the life that already
died in Joo Ah Ran's hands,
can never be revived again.
Show me the evidence that
you are not Shin Hyun Woo.
If you're really Ahn Jae Sung,
you have nothing to be afraid of.
Your destruction is right in front of you,
you can't give up here.
Taking everything you own,
and justly bringing you
to the judgment table,
what is betrayal,
what is fear of death,
I have to show that to you.
Even if you're Shin Hyun Woo,
there's nothing to be afraid of either.
Cowardly hiding and watching
for your opportunities,
you'll get eaten by the snake eventually.
Now the knife is in mine
and Joo Seung's hands,
what are you hesitating for?
Hurry and jump!
All right.
I'll try it.
Jump.
He jumped.
Shin Hyun Woo,
could definitely not do that.
Even if he changed his face and his voice,
he could not change his fear of heights too.
Then...
this person...
You were really as cool as
I thought you would be.
Did you not tremble at all?
I wasn't trembling because I was scared,
but I was trembling because Ah Ran was watching.
It's a relief you thought it was cool.
Hold on.
Did you go to the paper doll convention?
This can prove that Ahn Jae Sung
is not a person of this world.
Before Hyun Woo Hyung carries out his plan,
we have to think up an idea first.
Thank you.
I,
even though I really like Jae Sung,
I can't tolerate the feeling
of three people being together.
Are you still meeting Yoon Jae Hee?
You love me,
and you love Yoon Jae Hee too?
How can it be?
It's because she's a kind-hearted woman,
and I don't want to hurt her.
I'll take care of it slowly, don't worry.
That taking care of it,
could I help you do it?
If you were sincere to me,
give me that ring.
even if someone maligns you,
speaks evil of you,
I'll believe in Jae Sung's heart,
and walk till the end with you.
Even though I'm not wearing
it for its significance,
if Ah Ran wants it,
there you go.
Is there a Yoon Jae Hee here?
Yes, that's me.
Joo Ah Ran,
sent this to you.
This...
this is our couple ring.
This is President Ahn's heart,
stop clinging on to him.
Ahjussi, it can't be, right?
It can't be that Ahjussi
sent the ring back.
It can't be.
No matter how tiring it is,
he promised he wouldn't give it up.
This ring, is a magic ring.
Oh my, how did you do that?
It attracts when it gets
close by, I designed it.
Just like you and I.
What is with Doctor Nam?
You have nothing to do with our family.
I have something to tell you,
I'll arrive at 7.
I came because you didn't
pick up your phone.
What is with this ring?
Ahjussi didn't take it off, right?
You lost it, or maybe Joo Ah Ran stole it, right?
Let's just call it quits.
What?
That ring, I took it off myself.
During this time, I wasn't
sincere to you, sorry.
Today, I'm showing you my real heart.
My explanation is done, please go home.
Ahjussi, ahjussi!
Ahjussi.
What's wrong?
Why are you treating me this way?
I'm really tired too.
Please stop it.
Please open the door and
tell me, this is a joke.
Jae Sung is colder than
I thought he would be.
Nurse Yoon must be really hurt now.
Now that I've verified Jae Sung's heart,
I won't have suspicions with no basis.
The table has been set.
Ah Ran.
Marry me.