Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 17
Hello?
Mother.
Hello? Who...?
Mother, it's Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo? Is it really you, Hyun Woo?
Yes, Mother. It's Hyun Woo.
Are you really Hyun Woo?
My son, Hyun Woo?
Yes.
Where are you right now?
Tell me where you are,
I'll go pick you up right now.
Why didn't you come back if
you were still alive?
Just wait for a while. Then,
we'll be able to meet.
I'll call again.
Hyun Woo? Hyun Woo!
There's no mistake, it's my son Hyun Woo.
My son Hyun Woo is still alive!
It's me.
Attorney Lee just came by.
The Yang Pyeong villa under Joo Ah Ran
was transferred to Nam Joo Seung,
did you know?
What? To Nam Joo Seung?
All of the other assets were
transferred to you,
but the Yang Pyeong villa was transferred
to Nam Joo Seung. I'm surprised.
Is it some kind of settlement for a man that she has
taken advantage of, then thrown away?
That's not possible. No matter what reason,
Nam Joo Seung has no right to the
Yang Pyeong villa.
Although it all burned up...
it has evidence to prove two
people's evil actions.
No matter what, I will get it back.
Nam Joo Seung.
Do you also want to hurt my parents? [? He says something like his parents being stabbed in the heart]
What is betrayal?
I will let you feel what it means
to be betrayed.
Last year in October, the beautiful medical
director Nam Joo Seung,
placed car accident patient Shin Hyun Woo
in the Yang Pyeong villa
without any medical attention
The patient's guardians were led to believe in a
medical treatment which was in fact non-existent.
Not only that, it has been proven that he hired a
foreigner that didn't have a medical license,
and directed him to provide
the medical care.
For such unmoral behavior, Nam Joo Seung's
license should be taken away.
We're finally leaving tomorrow.
Are you going to drive a knife into
my parents' hearts too?
It's not uncomfortable. Don't worry.
Here are some information
about Design School.
After you get to America,
study furniture design more formally.
Like your dream,
you get a degree, find a job
and become a real furniture designer.
I will help you.
Me... study design?
It's not something that's impossible.
Every day, after getting up,
pack a lunch box and go to the library.
You'll learn linguistics,
then go to Design School.
I'll get a new medical license in America,
then go into neurology.
Like that. Then you'll give birth to a baby that
is half like you and half like me.
Think about it,
isn't that such a happy image?
Joo Seung, the image you have
of us together, give up on it.
Right now, my heart...
is filled with thoughts about Ahn Jae Sung.
I love that man.
If it's because of that person...
I can even forget revenge.
What are you thinking about?
I have a present to give you, too.
The Yang Pyeong villa that had my all,
was transferred to you today.
You are also your mother's son.
You have the right to accept these.
A villa in Korea is useless.
And, I don't need this.
Even so, you should accept these.
Who knows what will happen?
Director,
something of yours came by courier.
The sender was Shin Hyun Woo.
What? Our Hyun Woo?
What is this?
How could Joo Seung do something like this?
Secretary Kang.
Yes, President.
Go and get the records from when I was wrongly
hospitalized and a doctor's confirmation.
I was going to protect him to the end...
but now I can't put up with him anymore.
Why did you come to the hospital?
If you needed help,
you should have called me.
I only came because I have good news.
I heard your sister was looking for you.
My sister? Is this true?
I knew you would be happy,
I came when I got the news.
I'll try to set up a meeting for tomorrow,
so go and meet her.
Sister. My sister didn't forget me?
Where was she? Why did she only come now?
I missed her so much.
It's still a relief that you
can meet her now.
Before, I didn't know...
but I heard you real name was Kyung Ran.
Kyung Ran?
My original name is not Yoon Jae Hee?
Jae Hee was a name I came up for you.
Oh yeah,
you still have those red shoes, right?
Of course. It's the only thing that can
help me find my family.
When you go see your sister,
you have to bring them.
Your sister probably still remembers them.
I know, Director. Please make it so we
meet as soon as possible.
I'm fine with any time.
Kyung Ran. Kyung Ran.
So it's like this. Shin Hyun Woo
and Yoon Jae Hee
have known each other since the orphanage.
So that's why Yoon Jae Hee is helping
Shin Hyun Woo with the revenge.
What's the matter?
Why are in a department store?
Tomorrow is the wedding, and I feel bad that I
haven't bought you anything.
Tomorrow when your parents come,
they won't dislike me, right?
This is not quite it.
Jae Sung, look at this.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I want to give birth to a son that looks
exactly like you. What about you?
Pregnant?
I'm pregnant with Shin Hyun Woo's child?
Every time I think about how I carry
Shin Hyun Woo's child,
I feel more disgusted than when I have
snakes crawling all over my body.
Let's wait to have a child.
There isn't enough time to love you.
If it's okay, can we go see my parents?
After we get married,
we won't have much time to visit.
I want them to see their son-in-law.
Parents?
Mom...
Dad...
When they're in a good mood,
they would've had a drink.
Today, please drink as much as you want.
Dad. I'm getting married.
I've met a good person that
I'm getting married to.
So, don't worry about me now.
We'll find Kyung Ran too.
Today, I will fulfill...
the promise I made to the both of you.
Please rest in peace now.
Looks like there is a heartbreaking
story behind this.
How did your parents pass away?
In the company that they've worked
for their whole lives...
they told the truth and wrongly died.
It was made so it looked like it accident.
But it was a planned murder.
To save Dad...
my mom also passed away on the same day.
Is that the truth?
If both of them passed away,
the truth is unknown.
How did you know?
After entering the tiger's den,
I saw it with my own eyes.
They also took away my poor little sister.
Sister?
Although we haven't seen each
other in 25 years,
I haven't forgotten her for even a day.
Tomorrow, before leaving...
I must find and meet her.
What is the company your parents worked for?
If it's that kind of evil business,
I think it's best if I remember it.
It's at a place that you know.
It's at...
Wait a second.
It's me. Is it ready?
Alright. I'm leaving now.
Sorry. Something urgent came up
and I have to go now.
Made it look like an accident,
but was murder...?
It definitely was our Hyun Woo.
His voice changed a little,
but it's the same warm tone.
It's definitely Hyun Woo, no mistake.
Yes. It's Hyun Woo.
He sent me this today.
What is this?
Request to invalidate
Nam Joo Seung's license...?
Our Hyun Woo...
knew all about the things Joo Seung
was doing in the Villa.
Although he was lying with his eyes closed,
he wasn't sleeping.
Hyun Woo really woke up?
But sister-in-law didn't tell us.
How can we just let it go like this?
How could she have done that?
No, what is this?
Why is the Yang Pyeon villa under
Doctor Nam's name?
He even stole Hyun Woo's wife,
what can't he steal?
Look at Hyun Woo,
telling us what Joo Seung did.
He's telling us to not forgive what
Joo Seung did.
And, the last time he messed
with my medical records.
We should use this chance to make
him take off his doctor's coat.
-Honey...
-Our Hyun Woo is coming back.
If it's like this, will he forgive his
wife and Joo Seung?
This family and the company will come
back to the original place,
so I'm not worried about anything.
Director. Something big happened.
We must go back to the company and see.
Why, what is it?
The shareholders came to the company...
and are requesting for you to be
dismissed from your position.
What?
You went behind our backs and sold
the company. Is that true?
The news about Soul collapsing
is traveling everywhere,
how do you explain that?
Everyone, don't be like this.
Director, let's get away from here.
Your son died, but you still haven't
reported his death yet.
You unmoral jerk!
You must immediately transfer your
position to someone else...
and save the company even if it means selling yourself!
You jerk, do you understand?
Our SOUL didn't die!
I will be responsible for reviving
the company.
Just you wait! My son is still alive!
I, Shin Woo Sub,
absolutely will not lose. Ever!
You're Shin Hyun Min, right?
Yes. What is it?
The leadership power has been changed.
If you don't move out soon...
we'll have to force you to.
Stop all business.
We'll have to repossess your furniture too.
What? Repossess?
- Let's start.
- Yes.
Nam Joo Seung finalized everything
with the hospital, right?
Yes. He said he's going to America tomorrow.
It's like he hasn't even dreamed that
Joo Ah Ran is getting married.
But everything will be revealed tomorrow.
What exactly are you thinking of?
My heart can't rest and it's
driving me crazy.
If Joo Ah Ran find out who you are today,
the wedding will be ruined.
You don't know what
Director Nam is going to do.
There hasn't been a moment
where there isn't danger.
Life is about choosing.
Once you've made your choice,
you cannot be afraid.
I want to stand up from where I've fallen.
If the thing that went wrong
in my life was marriage...
I should go back,
and start anew from there, right?
I believe in you.
When you were Shin Hyun Woo,
or Ahn Jae Sung...
even when you're going to be Joo Ah Ran's
husband tomorrow,
my heart will remain the same.
It will stay here, and wait for you.
Do just as we planned. Do it well.
Let them be scared. Don't hold back.
They will reap what they have sown.
Please don't worry.
This house belongs to Ahn Jae Sung, right?
So why are you still here
and not moving out?
What are you going to do?
We never sold this house.
This is fraud!
Fraud? This house was bought with money.
How is this fraud?
While I'm being nice, hurry up,
pack your bags and get out.
You guys. Did this guy called Ahn Jae Sung
tell you to come here?
That jerk.
This is our house.
Before I call the cops, get out.
Cops? If the cops come,
you will be the one they usher out.
Come. Let's start.
Why are you being like this?
It's not like we can move right away.
Why are you like this?
Okay. I got it. I'll be right there.
Take care of your mom and sister.
I said that I'll take care of it!
What is this? Where's my car?
Oh that. The shareholders took it...
along with your corporate credit cards.
What?
They all want me to die.
I've worn out my shoes working so hard to
line the pockets of these people,
and they are kicking me out the moment
the company hits an obstacle?
These worthless jerks.
Get out. Get out.
What are you doing?
There had been no notice,
why do we have to move out?
Who told you to force us to get out?
Who sent you guys,
Ahn Jae Sung or Joo Ah Ran?
They were sent by me.
What are you going to do?
Oh right. It's you.
You want me to die, don't you?
You're using these ways to
get my family fortune...
and so planned for Hyun Woo to
have an accident, right?
What evidence do you have?
Don't be too proud.
Someday, the truth will be revealed.
There's no such thing as a perfect crime.
I'm the one that should have said that.
Through the passage of time...
did you think that your crimes
will disappear?
Did you think that the grudge of other
people will be so easily forgotten?
No. Even if the person died...
crime will not rot away.
Because of your actions,
a family has been stomped over.
While you've had enough to eat...
someone else was thinking about death.
Law and this world is all on your side.
I will step on that world until
it is crushed.
What crime have I committed? Let me hear it.
Why did you turn me into a criminal?
Even though we were poor,
I could have grown up in my parents' love.
Why did you turn me into
this poisonous child?
Because of the hurt you gave me...
my whole being is filled me poison.
Why don't you know?
Don't say anymore. We don't have anything
else that can be lost or stolen.
What you've done is enough.
What do we still have?
Why are you pleading with such a person?
Looks like you're just saying stuff
to cover up your own crime.
After our Hyun Woo comes back...
you're the one that'll be dragged
to the police station.
Really? Thanks for caring about me.
I think you should worry about where your
family's going to sleep tonight.
Lock the door properly. Don't let anyone in.
If you've lived your life right...
you should be able to find a friend
who can lend you a room.
Dad. Dad, don't be like this.
Dad. Dad, calm down.
Father.
How much did you love her,
if you've served her as the Director's wife.
and then left?
I won't live like you.
If I like it, I will fight for it.
Love will always remain on my side.
I won't let my woman
live as someone else's woman anymore.
Yes, hello?
The Medical Association?
What did you say?
What are you doing right now?
What are you doing in someone else's office?
We've received information about how
you were conducting malpractice.
We've also received information about how you
intentionally gave out false prescriptions.
Per request,
the Medical Association will investigate.
Who submitted the request?
Someone named Shin Hyun Woo.
It's a patient of yours, right?
Shin Hyun Woo?
After investigation,
not only is there medical punishment,
but also law punishments. Do you understand?
You can take them all away,
I'll never come back here.
As long as I get to leave with Ah Ran,
the physician's license is nothing.
With my abilities, I can give it up.
You've worked hard during this time.
If I hurt you, please forgive me.
Yoon Jae Hee.
What are you thinking about doing?
Because of your stubbornness,
your whole family has to sleep on the streets.
Does that feel good?
Are you still unwilling to hand
over Kyung Ran?
Alright, I'll bring Kyung Ran over tomorrow.
So please return the house to us.
Regarding whose daughter you are...
please keep it a secret from
Hyun Woo's Dad until the end.
Then, we will discuss this after
I meet with Kyung Ran.
Tomorrow, you will be contacted
by my mother-in-law.
They've been scared,
so they'll have to show us Kyung Ran.
Really? So everything is settled now?
But I'm busy tomorrow, so I will not be
able to make it on time tomorrow.
Please make sure you hold Kyung Ran there,
and wait for me.
If this completes without mistake,
I will transfer the furniture store
over to you as promised.
Don't worry about it.
Our nickname is Jinduk dog!
Once we grab onto it,
we definitely will not let go.
Director, what brings you here?
You've worked hard these days,
and I haven't had time to properly thank you.
This is a handbag, I hope you like it.
You don't need to be like this. Thanks.
Live a good life. You were a good person.
That...
What is it?
If Yoon Jae Hee was the one Madam
supported at the Angel Orphanage,
then, is Yoon Jae Hee Kyung Ran?
Why did it become like this?
The sister that Ah Ran's been looking for,
it's Yoon Jae Hee?
How did it become like this?
The sister Ah Ran wanted to see,
why did it have to be...?
Even if you have no appetite, eat something.
The situation is already like this,
did you think I'd be able to swallow food, like pigs?
The family fortune I've put my whole life
towards with blood and sweat...
is just going to fly away like that.
Mom doesn't look so good.
She needs to go lie down somewhere.
How about going to my store?
Even though it's closed at the moment,
it's still a warm place to lie down.
Let's just live there.
How can we sleep at a store?
Before getting our house back,
let's make a reservation at a hotel.
Did you think that Shin Woo Sup
can't come up with that much money?
President Park, I have something urgent,
so can you lend me some money?
I'll pay you back.
What?
Ownership issue?
Who is it that is spreading those rumors?
If you don't want to lend me money,
then fine.
Yoon Jae. What are you doing here?
Director, something big happened!
Just now Ah Ran came here,
and changed the lock on the store.
She said that the store's owner is going to change,
and asked me not to come anymore.
I tried to convince her.
That inconsiderate jerk.
What? We can't go into the store anymore?
I'm so ashamed. My whole life
I never that that there'd be a
day when I was poor.
What's the use of living?
Let's just all die together. Die.
Mom! Stay strong, mom!
This won't do. Help mom into the car.
She wanted to find her sister so much,
so I should tell her, right?
No. If I tell her now,
both of them will get hurt.
One person is the person Hyun Woo
wants to get revenge on.
Another person is the person helping
Hyun Woo get his revenge.
This coffee house.
Why doesn't it have any other people?
Today, I reserved the whole store.
Today is the last day of our single lives.
We should celebrate it.
I specially told them to make it like that.
Do you like the mood?
Excellent.
The you under candlelight is more beautiful.
Can I borrow your hand for a second?
I'm shaking.
Then lean onto me.
It'll be fine as long as you follow me.
Jae Sung,
you make so happy I could cry.
You make my hard past...
become like white snow.
I will be able to hold your hand
until the end, right?
Why are you worrying about that?
Once you've loved once,
you will always love, isn't it like that?
The bride that's getting married
tomorrow, how can she cry?
If I've met you from the beginning,
would my life be different?
Maybe I wouldn't have gotten
married with Hyun Woo.
If that person hadn't died...
we wouldn't have met.
That person and me,
will not be happy even if we started again.
A marriage that is destined for failure.
Everyday will be filled with
hatred and pain.
Jae Sung, it seems like the first
time I've said this...
but I really love you.
To protect this love,
I'm willing to pay any price.
You woman,
I can't believe even a crocodile's
tears can flow so freely.
Your beautiful tears...
I don't know what kind of thunder storm
they will become tomorrow.
I'm curious.
Why is everyone sitting like
they're being punished?
The people collecting debts won't
chase you here, will they?
What happened? I will...
Don't be too depressed.
There are times in life that you'll fall down
and experience storms.
How can it be possible that your whole life is
filled with sunny paths with fresh flowers?
Cheer up! If you're healthy, then you will
have a day when you will smile.
Sorry. I've never thought that
I would bring you trouble.
What trouble?
The house is too small.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Do we all have to sleep here?
Because you're all guests,
I'll give you this side.
That side doesn't have heat, and is colder.
But since there are so many people,
it probably won't be too cold.
Right. I should just leave without
saying anything.
While they're still missing
for each other and...
when it comes time that they
heal their wounds,
they should meet.
That should be fine, right?
Sister... will she recognize
what I look like?
Sister... why didn't she look for me?
She didn't want to throw me away, did she?
Sister,
I miss you so much.
I just want to call you again.
Sister. Sister.
It's finally today.
Have you prepared everything?
Yes. The people in the family
have all moved out.
There's no need to wait.
There's something I need your help with.
Can you call the reporters over?
To the wedding church?
Okay. I'll try and think of something.
Thanks.
But, when are you leaving?
After your wedding officially ends.
I've only accepted help from you. To let you go like this,
my heart doesn't feel comfortable.
After, I'll become like a brother to you in
place of Sang Mo, is that okay?
It's okay.
During this time,
because of leaving Sang Mo alone,
once I remember that I have
a brother near the sea,
my heart feels uneasy.
I only want to
place him in my heart and leave.
Today, let's go to my father's grave,
and also to your parents'.
If we're leaving tomorrow,
today's the only day we have time.
There's no time today.
To be truthful, I've set up an appointment
to see Kyung Ran.
Kyung Ran?
You know who Kyung Ran is?
Mother already set it up.
I've got to go there in a little while.
Kyung Ran may be different than
what you'd think she'd be.
After such a long while...
you both might be disappointed.
Do you have to meet?
No matter what she changed into,
and how she lives,
none of that matters.
My sister can meet me while still living,
what else can I ask for?
I still need some things...
so I'll hang onto my suitcase.
I'll leave directly from the hotel.
Let's meet tomorrow at the airport.
Miss Yoon? Where are you right now?
I'll go there right now. Wait a while.
Ahn Jae Sung, right now...
it's time to say goodbye to you.
Today at 11...
Kyung Ran will be at the Seoul Coffee Shop.
Before I get there, you must make her
stay there no matter what.
Okay. I'm hanging up.
How are you feeling?
I'm shaking so much.
You're so handsome today.
The bride is too pretty that she doesn't
even care about the groom anymore.
Really beautiful. Even God will be jealous.
Thanks.
But, where are your parents?
They said they've just arrived at the airport,
and should be getting here soon.
What if they're disappointed
when they see me?
We don't have anyone to invite,
so the church must be empty.
Because I was afraid of that,
I spent some money and got some guests.
What?
I heard it from someone that if
you give money...
there will be fake guests who
come to the wedding.
So there can be fake relatives,
fake friends.
Because I wanted to make you comfortable,
I also called some.
There's someone playing the
bridesmaid outside. Want to see?
Hello.
Here's the money I promised.
Until it ends, don't mess up
and do it properly.
The bride is really pretty.
Be close.
This way, later on, you can act
naturally at the church.
So we've met again.
You look like you have abilities.
What happened? Why are you here?
Last time you came to my wedding,
will the guests also come?
It's a team. Of course we all come together.
You didn't say anything, did you?
If you say anything, I won't let you live.
We've been doing this for a long time.
This is the basic, so don't worry.
Why did it turn out like this?
Why did you buy some clothes?
It's okay if I just wore mine.
It's not that expensive...
I just called someone to deliver it this morning.
Don't blame me, okay?
No matter who it is, sister or uncle,
if you want them to like you,
you must be nice.
Even after I meet them...
you will be like a mom to me.
Do you know my meaning?
Why are you saying stuff like that?
After, you don't need to bother me.
I'm happy!
When you came...
you just brought a pair of shoes with you.
Now, you've found your sister,
and it's because of your kindness.
This is all because of you.
I will do good.
I will hear that even if my parents
weren't alive, I grew up well.
Don't worry.
Oh, our Rosemary,
you're marrying a person again?
What are you doing here again?
We have nothing to meet over.
No, you sent us an invitation,
so why are you saying something else now?
President Hwang was busy,
so we came in place of him.
Before, you didn't let him know,
and got in trouble.
This time, make sure you tell him,
okay? Isn't it like this?
Invitation? Who sent the invitation?
Mother. I am Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo?
Hyun Woo? Where is he?
Where are you right now?
Tell me where you are right now!
I'm going crazy because I'm so anxious.
what? Hotel?
Yes. Bring father, Hyun Min, Hyun Jib,
all of them. I'll be waiting.
I got it. I'll be there.
Before I get there, don't go anywhere!
Honey, our Hyun Woo said he's at a hotel,
and told us to go there quickly.
That kid finally came back.
He definitely will not pretend that he doesn't
know when his dad is in trouble.
What are you doing? Hyun Woo told you to go!
Okay, I got it. Get dressed then come out.
I'll get the car ready.
He probably knew that you've
been forced out,
and booked a room at the hotel.
Why did he make us worry during this
time if he was going to come?
When I see him, I'll definitely use my
energy and beat him up.
Let's go.
Who were those people?
People my father-in-law sent.
I don't know what happened,
but I think they were here to intimidate me.
Really? We're leaving anyways,
so don't think too much of it.
But, you're not looking too good.
It's almost time for the official party.
Come. Can we go?
Miss Yoon...
Please talk with me for a while.
I have something urgent going on,
so I must leave.
Don't go. You can't go!
What are you talking about?
I'm saying this because I think of you.
Please believe in my words and stay here.
Only then will the wheels of the mistake
car be stopped. Only you...
Why exactly are you being like that to me?
This is my personal business;
I don't need your intervention.
I know your sister.
She has important stuff to tend to today,
but because she wants to see you,
she might ruin it all.
If you're really thinking of your sister,
please stop yourself from
going this one day.
You know my sister?
Sorry, but I don't believe in your words.
We've already set up a meeting...
and there's really no reason
to push it back.
Then. I'm going now.
You leave me with no choice.
I'll call your sister...
you say it yourself.
If you have courage to go after that,
then do as you wish.
Give my sister a call?
It's Joo Ah Ran?
What is the reason why the two of you
won't let me see my sister?
Hello?
Isn't this Ah Ran's cell phone?
The bride probably left her cell phone here.
She's at the church right now,
and can't talk.
Wedding church?
Who's the bride?
Joo Ah Ran.
She's getting married?
Where is it happening now?
Where is the church?!
This is impossible.
She's getting remarried to Shin Hyun Woo.
Doing such foolish things.
No, you can't go.
Two people's hatred...
let the two of them solve it.
Miss Yoon. You knew of it too?
You allowed it even though you knew?
Joo Ah Ran and Shin Hyun Woo getting remarried.
Isn't that ridiculous?
What are you doing right now?
No. You can't go!
Yes. Let's begin.
Holding Groom Ahn Jae Sung,
and bride Joo Ahn Ran's wedding.
The groom and bride are entering together.
Groom. Bride. Enter!
Isn't this song nice?
Whenever I hear this song,
I feel so happy and blessed.
Who chose this song?
Of course I chose it.
Why? You don't like it?
No, I like it.
Why are you shaking like that?
Don't be nervous. I'm here.
I'm okay.
Where did he tell us to go in the hotel?
Hyun Woo didn't say anything?
Yes. He said that he'll see us
at the Seoul Hotel.
12th floor. Wedding Ceremony.
Look at this. Groom Ahn Jae Sung,
bride Joo Ah Ran.
Joo Ah Ran? No way.
What? It's not Nam Joo Seung either.
Ahn Jae Sun and Joo Ah Ran
are getting married?
These guys. Where is the elevator?
Right now, the bow that will bound them
together for 100 years.
Groom, Bride. Bow.
These ridiculous...
It really is Joo Ah Ran!
How could something like this happen?
She's still in the process of getting divorced,
now she's secretly getting married?
Just now my parents and brothers
have arrived.
After the wedding ends,
I'll introduce them to you.
Next, we'll see a presentation of the groom
and bride's happy life journey.
Presentation?
I love you.
I love you Joo Seung.
Those are all lies.
Quickly, turn it off! Turn it off!
Was that... Ah Ran's real self?
Someone who proposed love
to 3 different men...
how can I trust you?
No. It must be someone's prank.
Where is Shin Hyun Woo? Come out.
Hurry up and come out!
If you have something to say,
appear before me!
Don't hide like a coward. Come out!
Joo Ah Ran.
Do you still remember me?
I'm the security guard that used to
work at the Yang Pyeong villa.
What are you talking about?
I don't know you.
The money you gave me,
I have the record right here.
You say you don't know me?
You locked up Shin Hyun Woo and the nurse
and told me to watch them.
I am the physician Joo Ah Ran found.
She told me that she'll give me a huge amount
of money if I pretended to be a doctor.
So I pretended to be Shin Hyun Woo's doctor.
I have also seen you.
From our villa, we could see your villa.
You always had a security guard guarding the villa,
which was weird.
Who are you?
Don't intervene in other people's business.
Shut up. Go away!
Also, there's another important truth.
One day, when I was getting some
air on my balcony...
I saw you running out of the burning villa.
The clothes you wore at that time,
I remember them very clearly.
But, after the incident, I heard that
in that villa, there was a patient
who was unable to move.
Lies! It wasn't me.
Someone told you to do this, didn't they?
They gave you money, didn't they?
I saw it too.
This woman was driving really fast,
and almost hit my child.
Not long after that,
I heard the ambulance's sound.
On one night,
I saw her push a person in a wheelchair.
It was too scary.
I had nightmares for a lot of nights.
Joo Ah Ran.
Why aren't you saying anything?
At least try to defend yourself a little.
The real Ah Ran that's hiding underneath
that pretty face...
how many are there?
Shin Hyun Woo, did you really kill him?
No. No!
I didn't kill! I'm innocent.
I didn't know of this.
Enough! Everyone stop!
Nam Joo Seung. What are you doing right now?
Other people's sacred weddings,
is this something that you can intervene in?
Hurry up and go back!
Must you be like this?
A woman you have once loved...
must you step all over her to get happiness?
You were treated that because of a reason!
The victim also have responsibility.
Don't say anything. Come with me.
Wait a minute, you have yet to account for the crime
you've committed against my brother.
Joo Ah Ran..
My innocent and kind younger brother,
why did you kill him?
After you stole his design...
and satisfied your wish, that is enough.
Why did my poor brother have to die?
Didn't I already settle my debt with you?
Why are you here again?
The person is dead. What debts are finished?
Using your snake tongue...
did you think saying sorry would
grant you forgiveness?
Crime, will eventually come back like a boomerang,
didn't you know?
Suicide was that person's choice.
He was depressed about his life...
strictly speaking, that's not
my responsibility.
Do you have evidence that I killed him?
The mentally unstable brother,
by neglecting him,
isn't that your responsibility?
My brother was afraid of that,
so he recorded your voice.
My brother's present
to the woman he loved.
Without you, SOUL is still doing
really well.
There are a lot of top designers on
the on the streets,
don't stay around and get lost!
Annoying! So annoying!
Why are you sticking to me like a parasite?
I don't love you. I love your designs.
So it's like this.
You killed Jung Sang Mo like this too?
How many secrets are out there
that I don't know?
Just now, the black box from Shin Hyun Woo's
accident had been found.
It was very damaged...
but I'm curious to see how
well it was restored.
Black Box.
If you have found the couple ring,
then you should know who
it is I love, right?
Nam Joo Seung is my brother!
And also my parents' directing doctor.
He is also my man!
No! No!
Why isn't she here yet?
She said she'd be here at 12!
Right. It's driving people crazy.
The person you're looking for doesn't
seem to be here yet.
Right. Circle round a few more times.
We must find our daughter. Go.
The coffee shop IS here, isn't it?
Do you want to go outside and
look for her? Hurry.
Sorry, but where is the wedding ceremony?
A hotel is for eating, and sleeping.
Why would there be weddings?
We're very busy, ask elsewhere.
Joo Ah Ran. How could you do those
things to Hyun Woo.
Are you still trying to live like this?
You're not satisfied with just
killing your husband,
but also forcing your in-laws
out on the streets,
and marrying some other guy.
Are you not afraid of the heavens?
You cruel and vicious person!
So it's like this.
This was all devised by you, wasn't it?
After I stole your fortune,
you feel wronged,
so you hired people to act as witnesses,
and made a ridiculous video.
Compared to your son,
is losing your fortune that much worse?
You wanted to ruin my wedding,
and did all this, right?
Just like you said...
crime will not rot away,
and will grow bigger.
So now the truth has been revealed.
Yet you still don't admit it, do you?
I'll be the last witness.
Nurse Yoon! Don't say anything!
Don't do something that you'll regret.
No, it's because I was too clear,
during this period of time,
about Shin Hyun Woo and his family's
many sufferings.
So I must say them. I must!
I am a nurse that tended to Shin Hyun Woo
at the Yang Pyeong villa.
The Joo Ah Ran and Director Nam here,
they prevented me from giving treatment.
They gave up on the patient completely,
and left him to die.
Shut that mouth!
You don't know anything yet
you appeared here?
Get out right now.
Not only that...
she poured hot water on the patient,
causing life-threatening damage.
She also tortured him mentally.
Shin Hyun Woo,
after regaining consciousness,
feared his wife's revenge.
He hid the fact that he was still awake.
Joo Ah Ran, before causing the fire,
was a murderer that killed
her husband's soul.
Jae Sung, we've gotten into a trap.
They're all framing me.
Truthfully, Shin Hyun Woo died
because of a gas explosion.
I wasn't at the scene at all.
The accident had nothing to
do with me at all.
What if I don't believe you?
You have to believe me!
Plug your ears, close your eyes,
only listen to me.
A wedding ceremony is not needed,
let's just leave.
Just like we planned,
let's go to a new country
and begin a new life.
I love you. Didn't you say you love me too?
So, the past doesn't matter.
Let's leave!
Let's leave right now!
You took away someone's life,
and then you that ruined
everything in their life.
But for your own happiness,
you're still standing here?
You're shameful and ridiculous.
I'll make sure...
that all of your crimes come crawling out
of your mouth like bugs.
Until the day you die...
you'll pay for all of your crimes.
What? Who are you?
You still don't know?
The Romeo whose heart was stolen.
The one you killed..
your husband Shin Hyun Woo.
PREVIEW:
The Ahn Jae Sung that said he loved me.
Look closely at reality!
It is more painful than death.
I will let you have a true taste of what it
feels like to be worse than death.
Are you really my son Hyun Woo?
Yes.
No mistake,
it's our son Hyun Woo!
Are you really going to turn yourself in?
Leave it to me.
I want to get married to Jae Hee.
Marriage? As long as it's not with
Joo Chul Min's children.
This wedding cannot be. I don't approve.
Jae Hee is not the same as Ah Ran!
Actually, they're the same!
That man. I definitely cannot give
him to Yoon Jae Hee.
Who are you?
Are you going to do it to the end?
Do you still not understand?
Your Dad, killed my parents in front of me.
Let's see whose crime was bigger.
You should be able to tell without calculating, right?