Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 13
I'm asking you who Rosemary is,
why aren't you answering me?
Who's Rosemary?
It's my first time hearing such a name.
You saw President Hwang's wife?
You're still making excuses
saying you don't know?
Everyone knows about your past,
only we don't know.
Every night you're in men's arms
pouring wine and joking.
You're hiding such a dirty past and
you want to marry Hyun Woo.
This shameless, scary
Husband, what are you talking about?
What's Rosemary?
Who's pouring wine?
So it's like this...
you're a drinker and you act
like a classy American
lying to my kind brother
and marrying him?
This is a great rotten story.
So it's really like this?
So sister-in-law is such a scary person?
There's no need to say anything more...
I won't accept her as my daughter in law.
Money earned by pouring wine
and given to us to buy furniture.
Hurry up and burn these furniture.
Instantly!
Episode 13
Husband, husband, calm down,
husband, husband Please don't get angry,
I'll clean it. calm down.
Is this a situation to calm down?
We've been using blankets bought
with dirty money to sleep
Wearing suits, this is so unlucky,
how can I take it?
Since you already know,
I don't need to argue
I'm a poor orphan, I left home in
high school to a nightclub.
Because living needs money...
With a 40 degree fever I still go to
the nightclub dancing and pouring wine.
Not everyone without parents
live like you!
You think money is dirty?
To make the treasury full, father fired
workers and lied to agencies
Getting these money is a clean thing?
The one stealing money is father, not me.
Impolite...
being thief and trying
to blame someone else.
A tricked marriage,
and begging strongly isn't enough...
who do you dare teach a lesson to?
Ah Ran, what kind of attitude
do you have in front of a elder
Hurry up and get out, hurry.
Father, you've mistaken...
You will definitely apologize for the smack.
Because my furniture seems
embarrassing today...
Tomorrow, you will thank
me for the furniture
For now, good night.
This... this...
The celebrity and the president
isn't your dad's friend..
they're the nightclub customers right?
Even my brother doesn't know..
If my brother helped sister-in-law lie,
then it's a lie.
I met Hyun Woo when I was in the nightclub
don't dirty his pure love.
I'm tired, please go out
Okay, you better watch out...
let's see when you'll still be so strong.
I'll watch carefully.
This is even better...
I don't need to act nice anymore.
From now on, it will officially start.
Even if you people unite holding a knife,
I won't be scared at all.
It's here, it's time to let everyone
slowly know my existence.
Slowly show everyone
that I'm still alive.
Then, if Joo Ah Ran finds out first,
what do we do?
Joo Ah Ran will think that it's
Nam Joo Seung's plan of threatening.
As a result, Joo Ah Ran and Nam Joo Seung's
war will be even more thrilling.
The war will start now.
Hyun Woo hyung is definitely still alive
Hiding behind Ahn Jae Sung's
face tricking me
Need to find evidence. If I don't attack first,
then I'll get controlled
Shin Hyun Woo, 180cm tall
Blood type A
No facial surgery, appendix surgery...
allergic to peanut, seasonal skin infection.
There's no good news to read.
What's this?
Star Electronics and Soul Furniture
sign investment, big business is born.
What is this? I'm the leader
and I don't know about investing.
Dad, isn't this sister-in-law
and President Hwang?
It is, what's sister-in-law planning now?
If it's not a trick, what would
a big business invest in?
This is scary, hurry up and
bring that thing down!
Yesterday, Star Electronics
and President Hwang...
decided to give our Soul a major investment.
Now it's the nation's biggest furniture business.
How do you feel?
Who told you to worry about this?
I won't give you the company's business.
You know Soul's condition
and you're still saying this?
SM Furniture emerged online
and Soul's sale decreased.
There's no help for it.
If this continues on, I won't guarantee
that we won't go bankrupt.
Bankrupt? Who was the one that
helped the company get to this place?
Ever since you got control, Soul started
to get unstable, everyone knows.
Hello? I'm Shin Woo Sub.
Yes, President Park.
Investment?
It's not worth celebrating,
but thank you.
Let me go.
Not afraid of death, you dare trick me?
President made the decision..
If President appoint the nightclub couple
stole the business secret.
The impact on the community would be big.
Those few cents were that disappointing?
Listen carefully...
the water has already spilled.
For the sake of the company's image, I won't correspond
But our company's money,
even $10 won't go out.
I don't know about the company's investment,
I don't have anything to say.
Come!
I can't, no
Don't think this world so easily...
Considering the past,
this time I'll let you off.
What is this?
Joo Seung Oppa delivered it.
Joo Seung Hyung? Let me see.
NNJ? This is...
Right, it's the couple ring from in the car
the day of Hyun Woo's incident
You held onto the ring last time right?
Hurry and bring it.
Okay
This one
Yes, the same initials.
the same heart shaped ring.
The ring's owner is...
It's Hyun Woo Oppa and sister-in-law.
NNJ, is Nam Joo Seung and
Joo Ah Ran's initials.
I'm like a fool, how can I find out now?
But, if this ring was young
in Hyung's car...
then it's evidence that
Hyung knew their relationship.
Then, that day in the car,
would it be sister-in-law?
So, this couple ring is Joo Ah Ran
and Dr. Nam's, right?
It's definitely right.
I'm sure they've seen each other
before Hyung's incident
If Hyung seen this couple ring,..
that day, he definitely had
an argument with sister-in-law.
This is how everything happened.
How can there be such a thing?
Maybe it's not true, not true.
Sister-in-law is Sister-in-law,
but it's Joo Seung that I can't forgive.
I can't forgive Joo Seung Hyung
Hyung Woo Hyung loves him like a brother.
How can he backstab him?
I think Secretary Nam isn't
like that either.
If Uncle Nam finds out,
he'll be so angry.
He has always been following our dad
like a shadow, being awful to our family.
Before this is clear, keep this
as a secret to your Dad. Please.
Did you see today's newspaper?
Star Electronics will invest into
Soul Furniture
So, can you help me one last time?
Increasing the factory so suddenly
needs a lot of money
After Star Electronics' money comes,
I'll return it immediately.
I'm so sorry,
I bought a few buildings in Sony
and used up all my money
Anyhow, Leader Zhu, I'm so sorry.
Receiving such a big investment
from a big company
Compared to my brother's news,
it's has much more ability
Brother?
I guess my little brother knows
a bit about you.
I heard from my brother, that's why
I invested such a big amount.
For not being able to help,
I'm sorry, See you later.
What do I do?
Star Electronics’ investment is gone.
How can I get money?
It might be the end.
Right, only one person can help me.
President Joo, what happened?
I just missed you, so I came.
I didn't think I'd be so lucky
to hear to sing
The atmosphere is so unique,
what song is it?
A story of a man who feel
in love with a prostitute.
I really like this song.
Once I sing this song, I'll want to
start dating without myself knowing
Feel in love with a prostitute
President An can have this kind of love?
Of course. If the woman won't hide
her past and her occupation...
love cannot start from lies.
What's wrong with the company?
You don't look so good.
A woman doing business is so difficult.
There's no one with discuss with,
no one with help me.
What ring is this?
I wear it with my girlfriend
I personally don't like these things
But my girlfriend begged me,
so I wore it.
Girlfriend? You're not talking about
Yoon Jae Hee are you?
This. My girlfriend probably not
willing so I can't tell.
If you're leaving later,
I'm going to leave now
Why do you want to see me?
President An gave you this ring, right?
I think I told you last time.
Please don't interfere with
my personal life.
If you called me because of this.
I'll go in first.
You arrogant woman.
Acting like you don't know in front of me.
Behind me you're hooking up with men.
You like President Ahn's wealth?
So you're dazzling in front of him?
However innocent you act,
you think President An doesn't
know what you're up to?
Since President An already knows,
I don't need to be worried
If you trust President An,
then you can relax
President An has good insight.
You think he'll randomly like any woman?
Miss, if you're like this,
does the hospital head know?
What?
Hurry up and take off that ring.
I can't share with you a man that I like.
Being jealous of a woman like you
hurts my pride
Now that I look, Miss is a very weird person
Lying down Shin Hyun Woo patient,
worrying about the head of the hospital
Now you're liking Leader An
behind the hospital head?
Why aren't you focused on one man?
You shouldn't be like this
for a dead person
Don't worry about my business
If mention Shin Hyun Woo to me again,
I won't let you go.
Okay, from now on I'll only mention
Shin Hyun Woo in "Pyong Chang Dong"
I'll end the reasoning with you today.
You dare look down on me.
What? Commercial?
Yes, we received a notice rushing us.
What's going on? He told us awhile ago he
was handling the mortgage.
It's been so long and it's
still not resolved
Do you use your mouth to do business?
Because of Star Electronics' investment,
not needing to quickly return
all the money is a lucky thing.
If we're supervised by this,
then there's a problem.
I want to kick out the rules,
because only Star Electronics can endure it.
Why's there a phone call?
It's not even time for our room
to be cleaned.
Hello?
I'm Kim Mi Yoo, who are you?
You found who took Jing Ran?
We looked through the documents and
found contact to the person who took Jing Ran.
That's what I said. If you look carefully,
there's definitely a record.
Give me a pencil, pencil, yes.
I'll ask you next time, I'll hang up
Did you hear?
They found our Jing Ran
Wait. When we talk like this and switched
telephone numbers, it's too wrong.
Let's call first.
We can really earn money
Hello?
25 years ago in the Pyul Gang orphanage,
you adopted a little girl?
Can I ask, who are you?
I'm the girl's aunt, I found someone
to get information...
They said you randomly took my niece.
How can you take away a baby
you're temporarily taking care of?
Where is my niece now?
What are you calling? It seems like
you have the wrong number.
Stop talking trash,
just tell me where my niece is!?
This person, you think I can't find
your house with this phone number?
Sorry...
Please give me some time
because I didn't raise the child.
The condition now is unclear.
Give it to me.
Hello...
I'm a person who can't live long.
The doctor said surviving until
tomorrow is difficult...
Before I die, can't I see me niece?
She's always shining in front of me
Hello, Hospital Head,
I'm Shin Hyun Woo's mom.
I have an urgent situation
to discuss with you.
The child I adopted her uncle and aunt
are looking for her.
So it's like this? I heard she had a sister,
I didn't know she had an uncle.
If you promised, of course you have to go.
After I contact her, I'll let her go.
What? My uncle is looking for me?
Of course I have to see him.
If I see my uncle, I get might
some news about my sister
Where is it, Hospital head?
You don't have any meetings tonight?
I know a place with delicious pasta.
Want to try it together?
Okay, let's go with my car together.
Wait in the car,
I'm going to make a call inside.
Okay.
Please say it.
Hurry and go to Sam Sang Dong's
entrance, it's urgent.
I have an important meeting
right now, I can't go.
You have to come out
It's Nurse Yoon's lover.
If you don't come out, you'll regret it.
It's helpful to fix Nurse Yoon's feelings.
I'll wait for you.
Excuse me.
What's the matter.
Did something happen to uncle?
An Jae Seung, it's your turn
to show your real heart.
Today I'll let you end.
Putting two woman on top of a scale.
What happened, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What? Let me go, President An, save me
What are you doing to a woman.
Who sent you here?
Go away. I only listen to people
who give me money.
If you don't want to die, leave
You little
President An, save me.
It's the people sent by Father.
President An
President An!
Stop the car. Before I call the police,
stop the car.
Jae Hee, why are you here?
Why is it like this? What would I do
if something happened?
There's no need to help Joo Ah Ran and die.
Sorry, there's no time to talk.
I'll call you.
Ahjussi, ahjussi
Please give me a little time. A little.
Ahjussi, don't go.
It's dangerous
What's Joo Ah Ran for this?
He's following right?
Yes.
Yoon Jae Hee, now you're awake?
Even if you're stupider you'll know
where An Jae Seung's heart is
That little Jin Ran, how come
I can't see her anywhere
We've waited for an hour already..
Could it be, that the person who adopted
Jing Ran is in the middle playing tricks?
She also wants some profit.
It can't be that she knows we want the
furniture store and want to split it in half can it?
Who give?
Looks like we need to scare her.
Then she'll bring Jing Ran out.
Wait
Hello? I'm the person who
just called, Jing Ran's Aunt
What's the reason behind
why we still can't see Jing Ran?
You want to get sued with kidnap?
What's an adult doing bringing
a child to business
Before we go to your house and corrupt,
hurry up and bring Jing Ran out.
Do you understand?
What are you doing?
Why'd you unplug the telephone line?
You came? There's always weird
telephone calls coming, so
Weird phone calls?
What's that?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Switch the telephone number
tomorrow and it'll be fine.
We used the telephone for almost 30 years,
why do we have to change?
What is it? Weird telephone
calls calling home.
Excuse me.
Did a 50 year old man come by?
Oh, that one.
He left about an hour ago.
An Jae Seung, My luck is worn by you.
The danger behind getting
you isn't anything.
President An, are you okay?
You're really hurt.
Father sent some men to take Soul
away from me. I'm scared.
But you shouldn't have jumped out of the car
So your own life is nothing?
I'm not afraid of death..
when I knew you were chasing behind.
All my fear faded away.
So risking my life jumping out.
If I still alive...
the first thing I'd do is confess to you.
I.. like you.
Until now, I thought a lot of men liked me..
But...
the one man I tried to get,
you were the first.
An Jae Seung, you're finally trapped by me
You were so worried about me,
now you're like a warm sheep
Joo Ah Ran, you only have this move?
You think this plan would work?
Trick me all you can.
But it'll be your end.
Unni, how are you?
Today, uncle contacted me.
Although we didn't see each other...
the fact that I have a family
makes me happy.
Does uncle know Unni's news?
Unni, you're looking for me too right?
I miss you...
I miss you, Unni.
Even if the company closes,
we still need to let sister-in-law out.
Why don't we let go of
Star Electronics investment?
That can't do.
This isn't a childish act
This involved thousands of lives.
How can we just close down?
Let's accept the investment.
Saving the company is important.
I need to look at the investment book.
Let your sister-in-law come back
She shut her phone.
She's definitely with Joo Seung Oppa
That scary thing.
So unlucky.
Sorry for coming so late.
I have something to say.
I'll go in for a bit.
My house is messy, sit here first.
It's okay. Our daughter-in-law
didn't come here?
No. Is it to make sure?
Last warning, Don't see Ah Ran
Why?
Because she's Shin Woo's ex-lover.
Whatever is unhappy, I will block
Really? So full of love towards your son.
Block it. I have confident in taking Ah Ran
I'm curious in who will win
What? You're doing tricks
to a leader's wife?
Taking away Hyun Woo's wife.
Will Doctor Nam be happy?
Of course...
I'll be happy.
Miss's unhappiness is my happiness
What are you saying?
How can you say that?
I thought we could communicate.
Looks like I was wrong.
A child abandoned by his mom.
How good can she get?
Even the mother who gave birth
to him won't acknowledge him
There isn't much hope, right?
In the future it'll be even worse.
Miss, what do you think?
Look for President Shin and tell him
an interesting story he doesn't know
I don't want to ruin that family.
So I've been holding it in.
I suddenly feel really angry.
What are you talking about?
Miss doesn't know.
Only a story only my dead father
and I would know
Miss doesn't not know, she forgot.
Did I say something wrong?
I don't understand what
Doctor Nam is saying.
I have to go back.
It can't be he knows everything
It can't be. Impossible.
Did I tell President Ahn about this?
Actually...
not long ago a man
who liked me passed away.
The man's sister wanted to take revenge
on me and opened SM Furniture.
What?
That woman wants me and Soul Furniture dead
Help me, please.
I definitely cannot give up on Soul
Why so you miss Soul so much?
Is it your dead husband's company?
Soul has my lonely dead family's soul in it.
Giving up on Soul would be like
giving up on my life.
Then how can I help you
You continue to take control of Soul
You have the ability and the wealth
In return,
I'll be yours forever.
You seem to know well
how to seduce a man.
Okay, I'll think about it...
But, what's the real reason behind
President Shin pushing away daughter-in-law?
In the end, it was still because of me...
they're afraid that I'll take away Soul.
They still didn't report their son's death.
Lost his parents since birth..
None of my in-laws can help me,
and I can't fight my father as is.
I didn't know President Joo has
this kind of pain.
Can I sleep here tonight?
I don't have anywhere to go.
If Leader An won't take me.
I'll only die.
I can't let such a pretty person
walk around on the street.
Just sleep here tonight.
Lending a blanket to a woman,
you're the first. Good Night.
The pain will hurt a lot.
Why don't you treat me as a woman
I've already been ready to accept you.
A real man will care like a jewel.
Good night, I'll sleep on the sofa.
Ahjussi, why do I seem like a fool?
To take revenge on Joo An Ran...
you're sleeping with her. This I know.
We've already reasoned...
But I feel like I'm going crazy.
Really...
There's only this way?
Hello?
Did sister-in-law sleep there?
If you want to leave the house,
let her clean first.
Sleeping everywhere like that, it's so dirty
it makes people feel uncomfortable.
What? Didn't she come home?
You really know how to act.
But I won't get tricked.
This world has no secrets.
What you two did to my brother,
will eventually be revealed to everyone.
Thank you.
Is it Doctor Nam?
Pick up. Hiding won't solve anything.
Tell him you were at my house.
Let him understand.
It's me..
Listen carefully...
Listen to me first. Last night
I was at Leader Ahn’s house...
Listen to me, don't say anything
Leader Shin's prescription you
changed I already know
Only you used an excuse to fire a guard.
You can't even think of an excuse
The CCTV evidence has been confirmed.
What?
There person who used Miss' phone
to send a message was you too.
It's been confirmed with the
communication company.
What should you do? Bring these
evidence to find Leader Shin..
Or...
tell Hyun Woo about how the
mansion got on fire.
Tell these to him.
Or...
Tell him the truth about Ji Jun
being your father.
How is it? Like your wish,
if President faints, that isn't bad.
No way. What are you talking about?
Where you are you? I'm coming.
No...
There's no need.
I'm going to Pyong Chang Dong.
President An, I'll get off here.
I have something urgent.
Joo Seung.
This is Joo Seung's dad.
Why's he with mom?
My dad and mom who abandoned me
How can this be?
Then mom is Joo Seung's mom
What do you know about my parents?
If you're going to play tricks
on dead people, leave.
I'm here to help you
Who killed your parents...
only I know in this world.
It's shattered. Not one is left.
All is shattered and dead.
Your wish is my wish.
Nam Joo Seung, so it's like this.
You're using me to take revenge
on the mother...
who abandoned you.
You didn't help me because you loved me
You're using my parent's death...
to break my family?
I still didn't know it was like this?
Hyung, why'd you come?
Open the door. It has something to do
with the comment with President.
Just a little while.
I'm busy now. Call you later.
Joo Seung. I was wrong.
i don't know what to do.
I won't see President An anymore.
I promise.
So please forgive me.
We'll start over
Stop lying.
I can never trust woman like you anymore.
You tell the truth. then I go to jail.
What do you get from it?
Then you'll lose everything
Something that's not good for us both,
why do you do it?
Let's go on a trip today.
Do you still remember the seaside
apartment we were in together?
I'll arrange my company things,
then I'll go...
I trust that you'll be coming.
Nam Joo Seung...
The crime of you lying to me
this whole time.
I'll return it to you today.
President An
If you're not busy today,
take a walk with me today?
To thank you for yesterday,
I booked a seaside apartment.
It has a new view, you might
like the vacation villages.
Then we're set.
I'll get ready.
Mom...
What happened yesterday?
No matter what we say,
you're still our daughter-in-law.
But you won't come home at night.
I can't endure it anymore.
Sorry.
The family seems exhausted looking at me,
so I'm avoiding them.
There's no place to go,
so I slept on the company's sofa.
This ring, do you still remember?
We found this ring in Hyun Woo's car
on the day of the incident
Of course I remember..
It's Hyun Woo
and another woman's ring right?
No. This ring isn't Hyun Woo's
Yesterday, Doctor Nam sent
the same ring to our house
This ring and you and Doctor Nam's
couple ring right? Right?
How can this be?
Hyun Woo already knows about you
cheating on Doctor Nam right?
So you two argued. So the incident
happened in the rain right?
Sitting in Hyun Woo's car is you, Ah Ran.
No. Did mom see it that day?
I was clearly at home.
Doctor Nam wants to frame me,
so he's planning something
Lies. I'm Hyun Woo's mom
If you and Doctor Nam has anything
to do with Hyun Woo's death
I won't let you go,
Even if we search again,
We'll still search what happened
that day...
You watch.
To forget about your son.
You killed the son you acted
you didn't know for 30 years?
What are you talking about?
Mom, you watch.
For the dead Hyun Woo...
what will you do about your living
son who went to jail?
That's it.
Have a good day.
What exactly do you know?
Ah Ran can't be.
Joo Seung, what should I do?
Mom fainted.
She's in the emergency room now.
Her condition isn't too good.
Looks like I can't come to the
resort today. Sorry.
Ah Ran...
Pick up.
Hurry and Pick up!
Just wait...
Wait till I get there.
Without my approval,
you have to chance of dying.
Let's look at the sea next time.
Let's go inside.
The view inside is also really good.
Then, okay.
It's really a good room.
The view is perfect,
and the interior is quite magnificent.
I didn't think that because of this trip,
Ah Ran would spend so much effort.
Really, from now on
I'll call you Ah Ran. Can I?
Of course.
From now on,
I'll also call you Jae Chung.
Jae Chung, come here.
The sea is so wide.
Looking at the never ending ocean...
drinking bittersweet wine,
dying is also a happy ending
Ocean, woman, flower, wine.
It's really a perfect happy ending.
The happy ending is still missing something.
What is it?
Ah Ran, wait. I'm still not drunk
from the wine and ocean.
Isn't this too fast?
I've been waiting like this. Do you know
how long I've waited for today?
I never thought I'd be so thrilled
and shaking with a man.
It's the first time I actually
feel like a woman.
If it's like this...
I want to get ready
to welcome you. Take a shower first.
Joo Ah Ran, until the end
you're still treating me like a fool.
Jae Chung, what are you doing?
Joo Seung.
To be with that person...
you said Miss was extremely ill?
When I spent a whole day
arranging this room...
you were playing with that person?
I came to start over.
But you betrayed me!
You have the right to talk like that?
The one who betrayed me first was you.
You still won't shut up?
Why won't you say it?
that my mother-in-law...
is your real mom.
You were mother-in-law’s outside son.
Why'd you keep it to yourself?
You're angry that mom abandoned you...
so you want to ruin this family?
So you pulled me into your revenge.
No, Ah Ran, it's not.
You don't love me.
It's only for your personal revenge...
you used me.
Did I say anything wrong?
It was like this from the start.
But now it's not.
We really love each other.
Our trust has shattered.
I can't trust you...
you also can't trust me.
Also, we're not anything.
Don't hold on to my heart...
my heart is flowing.
My heart is already not here.
Ah Ran!
It can't end like this.
If I didn't love you...
when Shin Woo died, revenge
would have already ended.
I stayed because of you.
Return everything back
to its original space,
first I need to reveal An Jae Seung's mask.
I secretly researched on
SM's Leader Chung's background.
Really? What did you find out?
In America, she's a rich,
big business woman.
Not long ago, because of her husband's death,
she received a lot of fortune.
With that much wealth, she just needs
to try then she can swallow up our Soul.
What should we do?
How about I arrange a meeting.
I'll go with you.
Really, could you do that for me? If you want me to
apologize to your brother I will gladly do it.
If the value of designing is less,
I can fill it in.
If you want to fill it up,
you need a lot of money.
We need to get it no matter what.
Right. SM Furniture's President Chang.
I heard that compared to Korean's name,
American's name is more well known.
What's America's name?
Julie Chang.
What? Julie Chang?
No way, Julie Chang is actually
Chang Shang Mo's sister.
Then Soul's money is all
in Julie Chang's hands.
What can I do?
I'm collapsing.
Soul being stolen is a time problem.
At the end I still need to be poor?
Plastic Surgery Department
The man who just left,
was that his prescription?
I'm sorry, that's a little difficult
I'm his relative, he seems to be
keeping an illness away from us.
It's for the patient,
please help me out.
He's taking so many pain relievers
and antibiotics.
What's the matter?
Please confirm the deposit book.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, the person who just left,
said that he left his bankbook here.
Oh, I'm sure I gave it back to him. Ah,
you must be talking about Shin Hyun Woo?
Shin Hyun Woo?
Shin Hyun Woo!
You think I can't recognize you
after you change your voice?
I know how to check who Hyung is.
Follow 24 hours, don't let anything leak
What doesn't seem like Shin Hyun Woo,
is An Jae Seung is Shin Hyun Woo's evidence
My name is Shin Hyun Woo!
Please wait, shortly I'll return
with my original name.
Unni, don't forget about me!
The one who brought Ah Ran is mom?
Miss, why did I live in here?
Did you do something that
got Uncle Nam really angry?
It's only because Joo Seung wants
revenge that he's like that.
I thought this was the best way
to protect us both
to save you,
Is it because I killed Hyun Woo?
Miss killed two sons like that.
Hyun Woo and I.