Temptation Of An Angel
Honey!
Jae Hee!
Episode 20
Where did you go, that
you're only returning now?
Do you know how worried I was?
It's a relief, that you're all right.
I'm tired, I'm going to rest.
I know it's tiring for you,
but there's no evidence, why do you
have to have suspicions first?
Didn't Manager Jung say,
all the screws were loosened,
if it wasn't intentional, how could
something like that happen?
If you believe that, Jae Hee, then there's
nothing that we can do about it.
Please don't be moved anymore.
Didn't you say you would believe me,
and go all the way with me?
Even so, how could I change
the fact that I'm Joo Kyeong Ran?
Just like Ahjusshi isn't
Ahn Jae Sung, but Shin Hyun Woo,
the blood in our bodies
cannot be changed.
Mother
Yes, Mother.
Why are you crying?
What?
What happened? Why did an
accident suddenly happen?!
Madam jumped into traffic,
in order to save her...
Mom, why did you do that?
Were you afraid that Dad would blame you,
so you wanted to kill him yourself?
Is that it?!
I'm sorry.
Stop saying sorry!
You hid the fact that you gave birth to
Joo Seung Hyun from Dad for thirty years,
to Mom, is there anything
else that is real?!
- Mom, you're a hypocrite too!
- Stop it!
Dad is still lying in the operating theatre.
Do you think he'll feel
good if he hears us arguing?
Oppa, you should be the one to stop it.
It's because of Joo Ah Ran
that our family is in this state.
Why did you bring Joo Ah Ran's sister here?
Take that woman away immediately!
Shin Hyun Ji!
Doctor! How's the situation?
He should be fine after
the operation, right?
Is he really badly hurt?
When the accident happened, his spinal
nerves suffered a great amount of damage,
and there was a lot of bleeding,
the situation isn't good.
What does that mean?
My father...
Will he die?
Doctor...
no matter what, please save him.
It doesn't matter what happens to me,
you can take anything from my body.
Doctor, as long as you can save him,
it doesn't matter what condition he is in.
Let Ah Ran take me away!
The one who is guilty is me,
why is he being punished?
Ah Ran made a mistake,
she punished the wrong person.
How about the car?
I abandoned it, and ran away.
I've been taking the subway.
Good job.
Even though it's tiring,
hold on for a while more.
No matter if it's Hyun Woo
Hyung or President,
we can't let them do anything, we have
to prepare for it, and then retaliate.
Shin Hyun Woo wasn't even in the villa,
how could they say we attempted
to kill someone by setting the fire?
Even then, there is no
evidence that I set the fire.
Even so, that side has
the black box from the car.
With that evidence, we can't escape,
it's enough to convict us
of attempted murder.
This feels like when I was 18 again.
I knew that Aunt was going
to sell me to a forty year old man,
I was hiding everywhere like
a crazy person the whole night.
I really don't want to remember the feeling
of being chased everywhere again.
No matter what, we have to push
Hyun Woo Hyung into desperation,
so he'll stop pursuing you.
Even if he's convicted of identity theft,
he will never let you off.
The spinal nerves are severely damaged,
looks like he'll be paralyzed
from the waist down.
What?
Paralyzed from the waist down?
Honey.
It'll be a great blow to him.
How about hiding it from the patient first?
Then, I'll leave first.
Father!
How could our Father...
He lived by his pride all along.
Betrayed by his wife,
and now unable to walk,
how is he going to live?
Hyun Woo.
Yes, Father.
Are you awake?
Can you recognize me?
-Father.
- Dad.
Where's your mother?
I'm sorry.
I didn't die, and I'm still alive.
It's good that you're still alive.
If you died,
I would follow you all the
way to hell to torture you.
Why did you save me?
You should have just let me die.
You made me guilty for the rest of my life,
how am I going to face you?
I'm fine.
Shin Woo Sub...
will not die like that.
If you were hit, your bones
might not been left behind.
That's why I survived.
Dad, don't talk too much.
You had a big surgery,
so you have to rest more.
What surgery did I have?
Look, I can even talk now.
It means my injuries aren't too bad.
Your mother can stay,
the rest of you can go back.
It's too noisy.
What's the matter in
the middle of the night?
Did something change?
President Shin Woo Sub,
is in the hospital right now.
He's paralyzed from the waist down,
because of a traffic accident.
What?
In the end, God still punished him.
But, it's not enough.
Compared to what he did,
this is only the beginning.
I beg you, please stop.
How far do you want to go?
No matter what he did, the pain he's
suffering right now is enough.
Just that little pain, and you
can't watch any further?
That person...
has enjoyed what our parents
couldn't for the past 25 years.
Property, glory, he's taken it all.
Now, even if he's on a wheelchair,
at least he won't be begging on the streets.
So, you hope the President dies?
Then, our dead parents can come back?
What is it that you want?
The days you lost, you won't be able
to find them back through revenge.
You will only lose more through
the process of your revenge!
Revenge is not about seeking out the past.
But it's the reason for my life now.
The reason why I'm living now,
is for Dad and Mom.
No, more accurately,
Look at us right now.
You're being pursued for crimes,
and I can't even meet
the person that I love.
Is this the way our
parents wanted to see us?
I beg you,
if you want me to return as Kyeong Ran,
go look for Shin Hyun Woo
and beg for his forgiveness.
Then,
I'll give up the marriage too.
What a fool.
I have no confidence to stay by your side,
and no face to see the children.
The day you're discharged, please let me go.
Where can you go?
I want you to stay by my side, and serve
me till the day my coffin lid is shut.
Is it because I'm an invalid,
that you want to abandon me?
Just shout it out like you used to.
Joo Seung is my child, and I turned
you into this, why are you so calm?
Hate me, scold me to your heart's content!
The way you are right now...
it's making me so pressured,
I can't breathe!
Honey.
Joo Seung is your child,
I knew that a long time ago.
What did you say?
When I came back from business,
Secretary Nam told me that Joo Seung
was his child, and brought him to me.
But it was really strange.
The minute I saw him,
I felt like he was my child.
The child that my wife
gives birth is my child.
What other way can there be?
Honey.
When I got up at night,
and saw you crying at night,
the fact that I won't be
able to forgive you is true,
but I really feel something
for that kid Joo Seung too.
Ho...
Honey.
I'm wrong, honey.
I thought you would neglect
this crude and rough husband,
but looks like you hated me with a passion,
and even had a son with Secretary
Nam who was closest to me,
and took revenge on me.
That's how much you hated me?
Why didn't you say anything?
Why didn't you tell me you knew everything?
I lived in fear that you
would find out every day,
it really wasn't a life at all.
If I told you I knew,
then you wouldn't be by my side.
And, you would take Joo Seung,
to a place where I couldn't find you.
The Joo Seung now, doesn't treat
us like parents but enemies.
He wants to kill Hyun Woo,
and steal Hyun Woo's woman too.
It's all because of me, the children I
birthed, are bleeding and battling.
This crime, how am I going to redeem myself,
how?!
How?!
Call an emergency meeting,
and call another credit bank.
No matter what, we have to
gather all our liquid assets,
and exchange it for an extended credit date.
Also, make an appointment with another bank.
After hearing what happened to the President,
the credit banks are getting uneasy.
We have to do all we can.
Do as I tell you.
The creditors' response seems
to be pretty favorable.
- Have you contacted the bank yet?
- Yes.
This is Shin Hyun Woo.
Yes?
The police station?
Shin Hyun Woo, you said
that your wife Joo Ah Ran,
wanted to kill her paralyzed
husband, so she set the fire.
Yes, that's true.
Then, who is the Shin Hyun Woo
who is sitting in front of me right now?
In your vegetative state,
how did you escape the fire?
And looking at the evidence that
the Yang Pyeong police just sent over,
there was a silicone wig found in the villa.
Does that mean, you pretended
you were in a vegetative state?
The fact that I woke up,
Joo Ah Ran was aware of this.
That's why she locked all the doors
from outside, and turned the gas on.
First of all, we will cooperate with the
Yang Pyeong villa to investigate this case,
and we also have to find hard
evidence that Joo Ah Ran is a criminal.
I will cooperate with you.
Oh, right.
According to Joo Ah Ran's statement,
Shin Hyun Woo, you used Ahn Jae
Sung's name to work before.
You do realize that constitutes
identity theft and fraud, right?
You're under investigation
so early in the morning.
Ah Ran and I, will definitely
not die by ourselves.
No matter what, we will catch Hyung and President
by the throats, and fall in the water together.
What?
You despicable person.
Father is still lying in
the hospital from his accident,
and you want to play this jealous game,
because your mother got snatched away?
What?
President...
traffic accident?
Why? When?
Listen carefully.
The crimes that I committed under Ahn Jae Sung,
I'm ready to accept punishment for them.
I won't negotiate with people
like you in order to avoid this crime.
Joo Ah Ran and you,
I'll make you stand in front of the judges.
President...
He was in a traffic accident?
We don't need to say anything else.
Look at this photograph,
and if you still want to marry that person,
we won't stop you.
Dad.
Mom.
Aigoo. When they were children,
Ah Ran and Kyeong Ran were so close.
They never fought,
and Ah Ran took care of Kyeong Ran
like a mother, wasn't that right?
That's right.
Blood is thicker than water, how could
Kyeong Ran not take care of her family?
Then, is she a beast or a human?
So, my dad and mom looks like that.
Eyes,
nose,
mouth,
is so similar to mine.
How could I have lived till now,
without knowing?
Actually, your father, is a person
whose fingernail doesn't even look like mine.
He was so proper, as a President.
Oh, my Hyung.
Aigoo, looking at this,
I should have died first.
What are you saying?
If you left, how would I survive?
Kyeong Ran,
on behalf of your parents,
you can't forget your sister either.
If you listen to me, from now on,
you have to live differently from before.
The furniture, the showroom,
I'm not asking for anything.
This person,
did you drink too much?
Since we're born onto this earth,
we have to live like people.
These people...
Where has everyone gone,
leaving the patient alone?
I don't wish to talk to you.
You get out of here immediately.
Even so, you can't abuse
someone who came to visit you.
It was a little inappropriate to come
empty-handed, so I bought some flowers.
I'm sorry you're in this state.
What are you trying to do now?
Why did Joo Chul Min's
family come to visit me?
Didn't you hear me when I said to get out?
I heard you were paralyzed from the waist down,
but your temper hasn't changed a bit.
But don't misunderstand,
that you can cover your past.
Ah Ran.
What?
Who's paralyzed from the waist down?
You still don't know?
What you did 25 years ago,
how it has come back to you?
What is going on?
Who turned my legs into such a state?
Was it you?!
My...
My legs!
Your shadow won't grow longer anymore.
How much of your assets you
have gained by underhand methods,
is how deep the evidence of your crimes.
Father, what is going on?
What are you doing here?
Do you not know Father's
condition right now?
Who did something to my body?
Return it to me!
I can't live like this!
You should have just let me die on the bed,
why did you save me?!
Honey!
Just blame me, I thought
you would feel better.
Who wants to die?
you have to hang on
all the way till the end.
President has to spend
his entire life on a wheelchair,
to redeem the crime
of killing Ah Ran's parents.
Madam, you have to push President
in a wheelchair your entire life,
to redeem the crime of abandoning me.
Get out now.
I don't want to see you.
Disappear!
Stop being so petulant.
Were you the only one on this earth who
was abandoned by your parents?!
At least you still had your father,
and had such a good education.
Even if a bad seed was planted,
a child who would pull a
knife against his mother,
there is none in the world.
Let me go!
Do you think I'm pushing the
blame because I didn't get a toy?!
I, wasn't abandoned,
but brutally killed.
but brutally killed. At least, Madam
killed me brutally countless times in her dreams.
I lived like this my entire life,
walking around as a ticking bomb,
how much anger and unease
she must have felt.
The feeling of being pushed
away by your mother,
does Hyung know?
Joo Seung, your hate,
I'll help you unleash it.
This is Soul's last check.
You personally hand out the last invoice.
If you can't get it paid by today,
Soul will be bankrupt.
Joo Ah Ran.
What are you going to do?
I want to give you the chance
to push Soul down.
I understand.
I'll do it.
All right.
You want to fight to the end, right?
Then I have no choice.
I delayed time, to give you and
Jae Hee time to reconcile.
Looks like there isn't a need.
The black box in the car,
and the fingerprints from
the Yang Pyeong villa are in here.
As long as I turn this to the police,
the two of you are over.
All right, go ahead,
I think you want to give the President
in a wheelchair a last present.
We'll do as you wish.
Stop it.
I'll just go die.
Stop all this revenge!
The children I gave birth to,
are biting at each other and arguing,
I can't watch this anymore.
This isn't life, this is hell!
This hell!
Was created by President and Madam.
I will always help Ah Ran, to redeem all the
crimes President committed 25 years ago.
Mother.
Mother!
It's time to go for a checkup,
I'll bring you over in a wheelchair!
Don't help me!
I can do this.
Do you think, that I can't
even move my own body?
Don't look down on Shin Woo Sub!
- Are you fine?
- Let me go!
I can do this.
I can walk.
What happened?
Didn't you say that there
weren't any more invoices to pay?
It's an invoice that Joo Ah Ran filled, selling
furniture to other companies at lowered costs.
The cost is about 13 hundred million.
The bank can't help us anymore.
Oh right, a letter came for
President Shin Hyun Woo this afternoon.
Ahjusshi,
even though I want to deny it,
I can't help the fact
that I am Joo Kyeong Ran.
At this moment, I feel
like I understand my Unnie.
Even if I start my life anew now,
I might become like her.
Please, forgive all the crimes
my Unnie committed.
The period where I loved Ahjusshi,
I was really happy.
This...
is Kyeong Ran's shoes.
Why did Kyeong Ran give these to me?
Maybe she means she
doesn't want to come back.
Does that mean she chose Shin Hyun Woo?
Kyeong Ran was my last hope.
In the end, this dream too,
was cruelly crushed by them.
Now, there's no reason to hold back.
Send the invoice over,
and bankrupt Soul.
Open the door.
I know you're in there,
I have something to ask,
open the door!
After we told him we were going to
send the invoice, he seems pretty desperate.
Madam.
Is there anything else to say?
That invoice, do you
really have to change it?
Do you really have to bankrupt Soul?
In the end, you came to
beg me for the company.
On my behalf, couldn't you just
tolerate it one more time?
No matter what, to Hyun Woo,
and Hyun Woo's father,
Soul is something very important.
I beg you, please, Joo Seung.
Hyun Woo,
Hyun Woo.
When are you going to
stop talking about Hyun Woo?!
I'm also a child that you birthed painfully.
Why am I not worth the dust
on Hyun Woo Hyung's fingernails?
Why can't you see the metal
stake that is pierced through my heart?
It's all right how much you hate me.
As long as you let Soul go,
I can tolerate it, even if you throw
rocks at me, or step on me.
You might as well just kill me here,
just don't touch the other family members.
You mean that because of Hyun Woo,
you can sacrifice anything?
That means, that I can't agree to it.
Hyun Woo, I must see the way
he kneels in front of me and begs me.
There is something you don't know!
The person who killed Ah Ran's parents,
wasn't Hyun Woo's father, but me.
What?
Ah Ran's parents' accident,
was caused by me.
The person who loosened the screws was me,
and the person who ran away when
the Manager sat on the forklift was also me.
I killed him.
I planned all of it.
Stop lying.
What reason would you
have to kill Ah Ran's parents?
You wanted to pin the President's crime
on your head, that's why you said that, right?
Ah Ran's father,
knew about the relationship
between me and your father.
He coincidentally heard that
we had a special relationship,
and even had a child.
Ah Ran's father was fighting with Hyun Woo's
father every day, because of poor materials.
I was afraid, he would spill
my secret in the end.
So you killed the factory manager?
Are you expecting me to
believe this right now?
Your deceased father,
knew this too.
What?
After he found out that
I killed Ah Ran's parents,
he felt very guilty,
that's why,
he asked you to take care
of Ah Ran after his death.
No.
Now you know?
The person that Ah Ran needs to seek revenge
on isn't Hyun Woo, or Hyun Woo's father, but me.
The mother that gave birth to you.
No,
no,
no!
I handed over Kyeong Ran to the orphanage,
because I felt guilty
about killing her parents.
Because I felt guilty
for destroying a family,
I've never had a peaceful day.
Stop lying.
It's not possible.
Don't even say another word!
But Hyun Woo Hyung isn't guilty.
Being born by such parents is a crime.
When I was serving alcohol to old men,
that man, should have been
sleeping in a comfortable house.
Let the forgiving words be
carried away by dogs.
Joo Ah Ran.
Don't resent me.
The crimes you committed will be punished.
I've always hesitated because you were
the sister that Kyeong Ran missed,
but you've pushed me to the end,
there's nothing else to hold on to.
What?
Mother was the one who
tampered with the forklift?
Could it be...
It's true.
I was afraid my past would be exposed,
so I killed Ah Ran's father.
Besides killing him, I didn't know any
other way I could shut his mouth.
That can't be.
How could such a soft-hearted
person like Mom...
I wasn't myself then.
I could only think of saving Joo Seung.
If your father knew...
I thought he would kill Joo Seung.
Then in the end,
Joo Ah Ran was right?
Our family to Joo Ah Ran,
is an enemy that can't even be revenged?
My mother,
because she was afraid her
own family would be split apart,
was someone who destroyed
someone else's family, is that it?
I'm sorry.
Can you use sorry to forget everything?
Two innocent people died,
and two children were orphaned Jae Hee's
parents who died, not even knowing the reason,
and the pain that Joo Ah Ran
and Jae Hee suffered for 25 years,
how are you going to repay that?
How are you going to redeem yourself?
What do you want me to do, you tell me.
I don't even have the right to die now.
Turning your father into this state,
where else can I hide?
Why did you do that?
My mother,
how could she do something so scary?
I know I have no right to say this to you,
but, can you let Ah Ran go?
Then, what would my life become?
The pain of dying,
the pain of plastic surgery,
was all for putting my
life on the line for revenge.
Now for Mother, you want
me to put everything away?
I can't do that.
Mother's crime, you take
on the responsibility.
Don't take your heinous crimes,
and leave any of it for your children.
I'll do whatever I wish to do.
I want to hand over concrete
evidence of the traffic accident
and the fire at the Yang
Pyeong villa to you, Officer.
If you look at this,
you will know who the two
people who committed the crimes are.
Concrete evidence?
What is it?
Mother killed that woman's parents.
Now, how am I going to punish that woman?
Pulling out a knife against Joo Ah Ran,
is equivalent to pulling
out a knife against Mother.
Nam Joo Seung.
Hyung, you know too?
The criminal 25 years ago, was Madam.
What do you want to say?
Was it,
Hyung who asked Madam to come look for me?
You thought if I knew my mother did it,
everything would become ugly?
What?
Don't have any hopes for me.
No matter what, I was a beast my
mother refused to acknowledge.
Now, or in the future,
I'll make any decisions for me and Ah Ran.
I came to say all this.
Saying that, does your heart feel better?
Looks like you don't want to acknowledge
your mother, and stay by the woman you love
That doesn't change anything at all.
You're the son of Jo Kyung Hee,
who killed Joo Ah Ran's parents.
Hyung, you're the same too.
Didn't you overlook the
enmity between both our families,
and love Yoon Jae Hee?
But, at least I'm not denying the past.
I'll beg Jae Hee to forgive Mom.
Till my hands are scraped raw,
till my kneecaps are begged through,
till the day my heart stops,
I'll beg for Jae Hee's forgiveness.
Isn't that the last thing
I can do for the woman I love?
No.
I won't tell Ah Ran anything.
From the beginning she wasn't my mother.
Now she says she's my mother
and wants me to carry around such shame.
Isn't that too despicable?
The good days are over.
Why is she coming back as a criminal?
Even though we can't
overlook Mother's crimes,
but, you can't accuse Mother.
The choice that Mother made then,
was because of you.
Stop saying such irresponsible things.
In order to keep the secret from Dad,
she did such a horrible thing
to Ah Ran's parents.
To prevent her child from
being swallowed alive,
she went to bite other people's children.
That was only a choice Madam made.
I didn't do anything.
I'm clean.
I don't wish, because of Madam,
to become a criminal.
This is Ah Ran's last invoice.
I'm going to change this invoice right now.
What Ah Ran hopes for,
is what I hope for.
Are you ready?
You are the son of Jo Kyung Hee,
who killed Joo Ah Ran's parents.
Yes.
Wait till the bank is
closing before doing it.
Then, Shin Hyun Woo will have no way either.
That's right.
When is the real Ahn Jae Sung coming?
He'll get here on the first plane tomorrow.
No matter what,
we have to get him on our side.
We have to paralyze Shin Hyun
Woo with the crime of identity theft.
Do it slowly.
If you do it so diligently,
I'm going to get fired.
If I stop I'll think of other things.
I'll prepare it, and clean the rooms,
you just rest.
I'm really comfortable,
but why would you come to Nun Island?
No, I just came to clear my head.
The view here is good, so is that air,
I really made the right choice.
All the unhappy things,
seem to have ended up on the beach.
There is no hate, no dissent,
and there's no need to fight,
it's comfortable here.
Ahjusshi,
you have to be strong.
I'll miss Ahjusshi, but I'll hold it in.
But, I'm worried,
that Ahjusshi will be tired.
President, the last invoice just came in.
There's not much time to settle it.
Don't say anything to my father.
But tomorrow's papers,
will definitely publish that we're bankrupt.
Hurry and do it.
Just follow this and publish it.
No... what?
Don't tell any of the stockholders,
just you, Secretary Kang, and I will know
Go gather the legal personnel immediately.
I understand, President.
Thank you, Nam Joo Seung,
for giving me courage.
I don't know why I've
lived so diligently until now,
running around so tirelessly to earn money,
I thought everything would
be good as long as I had money.
But now, I would return that money,
hundred-fold, thousand-fold,
as long as I can get my
two legs back to walk.
I really deserved it.
Not being able to go to school, and being
unknowledgeable was always a regret of mine.
So I only knew how to hit
and torture my family members.
Now, I'm getting punished.
Don't say things like that.
Think about it.
The crimes I committed
aren't just one or two.
When Ah Ran's parents died,
I was greedy for that compensation,
so I made a fake check.
I forced them to sign a fake agreement,
I've done a lot of things
against my conscience.
Importing inadequate material, turning them
into high end furniture and then selling them,
making double account
books and evading taxes,
my life is really interesting.
At first I could die, but I'm alive.
In the future,
I should do everything I haven't done.
Honey,
I'm the worst mother in this world.
It was me that killed the
parents of the sons' greatest love,
and turned them into enemies.
I called you because there was something up.
After I get discharged, I want to
officially accept you into my family as a son.
But,
you have to break up with Joo Ah Ran.
I can't do that.
You have to do so.
Although I knew my best friend, your father,
and my wife betrayed me at the same time,
I never asked why Secretary
Nam did that till the day he died.
Because, I took you as my own child.
You know I'm Madam's son?
I'm not an idiot,
how could I not know?
But I didn't treat you differently
from Hyun Woo and Hyun Min.
Because, among my sons, you're most like me.
What's the use of saying this now?
If you knew everything from the beginning,
why didn't you say so?
Then Madam wouldn't have
to hide anything either.
I'm regretful that I didn't
work up the courage earlier too.
This is the title deed that was placed
in your name not long ago.
No matter how difficult
the company's situation was,
I never wanted to touch it, not once.
You settle what is yours.
It's cold. Let's go in.
President, dropped this.
Then.
Since you made it to medical school,
you can be a doctor.
Good job, good job!
Once you graduate,
I'll build you a big hospital.
Jae Hee, where are you?
What can I do for you?
I really really miss you,
and I'm so guilty I'm going crazy.
You don't care if the company goes bankrupt,
and you only care about your love life?
Jae Hee left,
and she even emptied her house.
What?
Where did she go?
When?!
I don't know either.
No matter as Yoon Jae Hee or Joo Kyeong Ran,
she's had a tiring life.
This is all because of you!
I looked so hard for her, what is
going to happen if I never find her again?!
It's not enough to snatch my parents away,
now you want to steal my sister too?!
This never ending battle,
when is it ever going to finish?
Are you asking because you don't know?
Till either you or me,
when either one of us
has absolutely nothing.
Soul Furniture,
announces bankruptcy for the first time.
Director, it's Jae Hee.
Is it true that Soul Furniture is bankrupt?
They are bankrupt.
But what is scarier, is that Teacher
Shin stole someone else's identity,
and is being investigated for fraud.
The Jae Sung from England
is coming back today, Jae Hee.
Jae Sung,
Ahn Jae Sung Oppa?!
This is the title deed that
your father gave to Joo Seung.
Sell it and use it to
pay off the debts first.
If we can't stop it today,
we'll become bankrupt.
No.
This is the share that
Dad left to Joo Seung.
I don't wish to keep Soul
using underhand methods.
Today, I'll handle all of
the stocks under my name in Soul.
What does that mean?
Won't you lose ownership then?
Compared to ownership, it's more
important to save the company first.
What?
Jae Hee contacted you?!
Now, you're going to pick up
Ahn Jae Sung from the airport, right?
I'll take him to the station
to get his statement done immediately.
It'll make everything
easier and better for us.
He's also from the orphanage, keeping him away
from Jae Hee, might be beneficial to us.
I'll wait for you in front
of the police station.
But, the police station is too quiet,
it makes me nervous.
We sent the invoice back, but there's been no
movement for Shin Hyun Woo, I think it's strange.
Shin Hyun Woo isn't doing
anything, like a cripple.
He's been stabbed in the back
by the person he loves the most.
Let's go, we're going to be late.
Ahjusshi, has the boat to Nun Island left?
It just left.
Ahjusshi.
Jae Hee.
Ahjusshi, how can you be here right now?
What can we do about the bankruptcy?
Why are you not handling the company matters,
what am I that you are coming to look for me?
Without Jae Hee, I can't do anything.
Everything I do, I think
about Jae Hee all the time.
I'm worried I won't be able
to see you for the rest of my life.
We don't have time to do this right now.
Today, Ahn Jae Sung Oppa
is coming back from England.
The real Ahn Jae Sung.
Joo Ah Ran wants to convict Ahjusshi for fraud,
that's why they called Oppa.
Let's go.
Yeon Jae, you know how to knit?
I told you everything that
requires my head I can't do,
but everything to do with my hands, I do.
I'm knitting a carpet to put on Father's
knees when he's sitting on the wheelchair.
To make Father a little happier,
should I add a little pattern?
Thank you.
How could you have such adorable ideas?
If you have wishes, you have to act
in order for them to come true.
Suddenly, such an awful person appears
and demands his son, would he give him up?
Am I that good?
Besides having the fortune
of having wealthy parents
and letting Yeon Jae live
a little more comfortably,
I don't have any other good points.
Even during the college exams, I couldn't
get into a college, that's why I went to America.
What is this, what is this,
I knew you had a slow brain,
but I didn't think you had stones for brains.
It's totally destroyed, totally destroyed.
When we get married and have children, they'll
definitely be the first in the entire country.
You think that's easy?
It won't be easy having
a child that's the best.
Yeon Jae, let's, get married at Christmas.
That was originally the date
Hyung was supposed to get married,
since it's reserved already,
let's just do it.
I want Yeon Jae to enter the family earlier,
so our family can be happier.
Christmas?
Ahn Jae Sung, when you were in England,
did you know your identity had been stolen?
Right, do you know the Shin Hyun Woo here?
Shin Hyun Woo,
is our company's Korean representative.
No.
He's lying.
I'm the representative of the
English company, ROBBINS.
Not long ago, when we picked a Korean
representative, we picked Shin Hyun Woo.
That can't be.
ROBBINS is an imaginary company
that Shin Hyun Woo used for revenge.
Did you talk to Yoon Jae Hee before this?
Nam Joo Seung, please sit down.
I thought this could be of use,
so I brought the legal
documents for ROBBINS.
These,
are all the documents that show that contracts
in Korea that have been handed to Shin Hyun Woo.
After I've looked through the documents
and completed my investigation,
we'll listen to both sides.
What happened?
Did the real Ahn Jae Sung say everything?
The fact that his real name has been stolen,
he wouldn't remain unmoved, right?
You seem curious, so I'll tell you.
Ahn Jae Sung is the legal
representative for ROBBINS in England.
Hyun Woo, is the Korean
legal representative.
That can't be.
How can this lie be even plausible?
From the beginning, did you plan to pretend
to be Ahn Jae Sung and snatch Soul away?
You're smarter than I thought.
But everything that Hyung did was a fraud.
I'll find out.
A fraud?
Getting back what's mine is a fraud?
If you are so confident, do it.
You tell the banks,
no matter what, you have to
stop Soul from bankruptcy.
I beg you.
Shin Hyun Woo's asking you to do this?
Even though you say it's for our parents,
there's no reason to hate Hyun Woo.
What has that person done to you?
He loved you so innocently,
and was thrown into death by you.
But, why do you still torture him this way.
I want to take revenge for Joo Seung.
The life that Joo Seung had, having the same son,
yet being abandoned by his parents,
I have to comfort him too.
Do you know?
I've called the police to this coffee shop.
I told the police that I'm with the criminal
that set fire to Yang Pyeong.
Now, the police are rushing over.
Are you crazy?
Are you going to hand your
sister over to the police in the end?
I gave you every opportunity
to repent, but you refused.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to block the invoice, or are you
going to be investigated by the police?
Get up, follow me.
Let go of me, let go of me!
Now it's time you let go of Yoon Jae Hee,
and return to being Joo Kyeong Ran.
Then, I'll forget everything
that you did to me as Yoon Jae Hee.
No, I don't want to.
Do you not understand why
I returned you the red shoes?
That's because I don't
want to live as Joo Kyeong Ran.
Don't cling on to me.
Joo Ah Ran's sister,
Joo Kyeong Ran, died 25 years ago.
Now, we're not sisters anymore
Even if we hear of anyone's death,
let's not look for each other.
How could you...
Let's die together.
Living like that, we might as well die.
Let go of me!
Why should I die with you?
If you want to die, go die by yourself.
I promised Mom I'd take care of you.
So if we die, we die together.
No! I'm not dying!
Let go of me!
Look clearly!
Here, is the river where
Mom and Dad's ashes were scattered.
You don't remember,
but we sent Mom and Dad away here.
The day that accident
happened was my birthday.
The day I was born,
became my nightmare.
When we were young,
watching your parents die,
do you know what that means?
Not even paying your last respects
and the feeling of losing your parents,
do you know what that feels like?!
Everyone in the world said I was cheap,
a burden, and pointed fingers at me.
I thought you could at least understand me.
I thought you could comfort me for
all the pain that I suffered all this time.
That's why I hung on till now.
Pouring drinks for other people,
and jumping on tables to dance,
it wasn't tiring once I thought of you.
I thought everything would be worth it,
as long as you understood me and comforted me.
I really didn't imagine, that we would be
doing this in front of Mom and Dad's ashes!
Now, do as you wish.
Turn me over to the police,
kill me for Shin Hyun Woo,
do as you wish.
Being able to see you,
was enough.
I thought you died of
hunger a long time ago.
Knowing that you're still on this earth,
is enough.
Unnie.
The people I miss,
aren't Mom or Dad.
It's the Unnie, that put
on the red shoes for me.
Unnie's warm hands,
I've been missing that for 25 years.
But how can I forgive Unnie?
If I help Unnie,
Unnie will become a coward
that runs away for her entire life.
It's not too late now,
hurry and turn yourself in.
Then, the rest of my life,
I'll live for you Unnie.
I promise.
I don't care even if I
turn into an accomplice.
I'll stay by Unnie's side,
and repent for you till the day I die.
I'm heading to the hospital right now.
Shin Hyun Woo bribed
Ahn Jae Sung to hit me hard,
and I can't let things be as well.
That's right.
In the end, everything will come to light.
Rather than running away like a coward,
I should just turn myself
in with my head held high.
Shin Woo Sub has lost so much,
it's time I let him go.
I'm afraid you didn't see today's papers,
I brought them for you.
What are you doing,
you can't.
Soul Furniture, announcing
bankruptcy for the first time.
What is going on, didn't you
say the invoices were settled?
I did it.
Ah Ran bought the last invoice,
it was in my hands, and I turned it in.
In the end, you chose to
become enemies with us, is that it?
Will you only be comfortable if
you stab a knife into your mother's heart?
You settle this.
After we eventually end up bankrupt,
it's not possible for me
to even think about forgiving you.
The mastermind of this entire thing,
was President's family.
You have no right,
to talk about forgiveness.
President, you don't know, right?
The person who killed
Ah Ran's parents, is Madam.
What... What are you saying?
Are you crazy?!
You didn't know that Madam
did something to the tires, did you?
The person that killed Ah Ran's parents,
plunging the two sisters into tragedy,
was Madam!