Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 19
Jae Hee, don't. Don't move there.
Ahjussi.
Don't, Kyeong Ran.
Don't.
I promised Mom I'd take care of you.
No. No. Impossible. Impossible.
Jae Hee.
No, Kyeong Ran.
Jae Hee. Jae Hee.
Ahjussi, Joo Ah Ran isn't my sister, right?
Don't talk anymore, we'll talk later.
Hello? This is the Log House.
We have an emergency patient.
Hurry and come here. Hurry.
Cruel, evil.
You still have to hurt Jae Hee?
The things that you've done to me,
plus the things you did to Jae Hee today,
I won't forgive you.
Ahjussi.
Joo Ah Ran isn't my sister, right?
Dad, Mom.
Kyeong Ran can't be like this.
I'm afraid to be left alone.
Please.
I will give it my best.
But looking at the crimes,
we can only discuss with your brother.
Because the other person from
the traffic incident already died.
Episode 19
There's setting fire, jail, and
improper use of public funding.
There's no way to escape.
Then an incident 25 years ago
can't achieve punishment by law?
A case that as passed the
appeal date can't be penalized,
so there's no need to investigate.
Then if it's using someone else's
name to establish a company,
and signing a fake contract,
would these actions be punished?
Then of course we can punish him with
the crimes of forgery and fraud.
Right.
I need to find the mask of Ahn Jae Sung
that Hyun Woo Hyung used.
There has to be a real Ahn Jae Sung
living out there.
Ahjussi.
What happened?
You woke up? Are you okay?
When you fell, you suffered an impact and
you were temporarily in a coma.
You rib was scratched, don't move.
Luckily your head and other
places are normal.
Where's Joo Ah Ran?
We didn't come together.
Joo Ah Ran is really my sister?
Can't be.
How can that type of person be my sister?
A person who has lies all over her body.
She gave us such hard times.
How can such a scary person be my sister?
Doctor Nam and Joo Ah Ran
made this with this for sure.
It has to be. They wanted to escape
being investigated by the police.
So she pretends to be my sister.
If she's really my sister,
she wouldn't tell people to
lock me up in that place.
Right.
She hasn't paid for the crimes she's done,
and yet she still harms you.
Don't think about Joo Ah Ran anymore.
Just take care of your own health.
I have to tell the nurse that you woke up.
Then.
What about us?
If Joo Ah Ran is really my sister.
Ahjussi and I are impossible.
That won't happen.
No matter what happens,
I'll watch over you.
I won't let you cry, don't worry.
Why did you come here?
Did you come to see how
much harm there was?
Jae Sung, go out.
The two of us have to talk.
What do you want to do to Jae Hee again?
Leave this room immediately.
I will never trust a woman like you again.
Ahjussi, I'm okay.
There's nothing scary anymore.
You go out first.
How's the wound?
Are you okay?
Aren't you ashamed of those words?
You... are really Kyeong Ran?
Time really doesn't have mercy on people.
You and the face that I
imagined are not the same.
Me too.
The sister that I dreamed about,
isn't the way you are now.
In order to reach your own goal,
you can kill people.
A scary woman is my sister.
I feel ashamed.
If I can escape, I really want to.
There is something that you don't know.
Shin Hyun Woo's dad is the
one who killed our parents.
Our innocent parents were crushed
by the car Shin Woo Sub ruined.
I witnessed it 25 years ago.
That family to us, is our enemy.
What?
Shin Hyun Woo and I getting married,
pushing Shin Hyun Woo to death,
was to get revenge for our parents.
I won't believe Joo Ah Ran's words.
What you said about 25 years ago,
do you have confirmed evidence?
I've never heard Ahjussi say this.
I only believe in the words my lover says.
The words you say now,
I think they are only
excuses to escape crime.
Because of one man.
Your parents' hatred,
Your sister's sorrowful live,
You're going to ignore it?
How can you blame me?
When I take revenge by myself and bleed,
Do you know how lonely and tiring it was?
Don't find any more excuses.
How you're living is just your own choice.
Even if you don't have parents,
not everyone has to take this crooked road,
and live thinking about evil ideas.
Even though I had hard times
and grew up in an orphanage,
at least I know that I shouldn't
play with people's lives.
Don't blame one's self,
and corrupt my parent's reputation.
Why won't you hit?
Saying such upright words,
then hitting me with that hand.
What are you doing now?
You want to hit a sister lying
in the hospital, hurt by you?
Are you still considered a human?
Even a degraded bug would
recognize their own siblings.
How can you be so cruel?
Leave immediately.
Hurry and leave.
You say I'm cruel?
Then what are you, who knows my little
sister and still wants to marry her?
After stealing my whole heart,
you want to marry my little sister?!
Aren't you more cruel?
When were we a married couple?
Our marriage was a lie in the first place.
That marriage ceremony
can be said to be invalid.
So?
So two people have to marry?
Starting from this moment,
I have no sister.
We've lived separately for 25 years,
I just need to pretend she's dead.
You are no longer my little sister.
You're just Yoon Jae Hee.
Right.
If I'm your little sister.
I'd rather die than return
to Joo Kyeong Ran.
I want to live as Yoon Jae Hee
for my whole life.
Rather than having a fake sister,
Why don't I live uprightly as an orphan?
How I thought I would reunite
with my sister wasn't like this.
I've anticipated it for so long.
I've waited so anxiously.
I never thought that reuniting
would hurt each other like that.
What should I do?
In the room my sister locked me up in,
I actually found out that
that person was my sister.
Joo Ah Ran, get your mind straight.
Looking like a fool, why are you crying?
Your little sister already died.
My parents and her all
died being crushed by wood.
I don't need a brat like Yoon Jae Hee.
President, I have something to say.
Don't say it.
What crime do you commit when marrying?
Why won't you let people talk?
What other explosive news
do you have to say?
Perhaps, you have a child?
Or did you remarry and
get a new husband?
How many more secrets
do I not know about?
Tell me truthfully.
Right.
I have a lot of secrets I didn't tell President.
My husband left a
debt of over $10 million.
Last year he was bit by a
dog and used $2,300,000.
It really feels like it's getting worst.
I also need to pay my
little brother's tuition fee.
His brain is also stupid.
He's still in 35th place after
studying 3 days and 3 nights.
Yeon Jae.
But I also have a lot of good points.
Not only do I eat a lot,
I'm also really good at cooking.
I really know how to cook and
I can hammer needles.
Also,
When I was in school,
I was the class representative.
I have a lot of hair,
so the children don't need to
worry about having a little hair.
And.
What are you doing?
Enough.
Those are enough to qualify as my wife.
Don't think you're the best again.
Who's thinking that they're the best?
So what if you've married once.
You need to know that compared
to the fake Joo Ah Ran,
do you know how beautiful
the truthful Yeon Jae is?
My parents also like you a lot, Yeon Jae.
Where do you need to go?
You want to escape from me?
Let me go. I'm begging you to let me go.
No matter how much I deny it,
I'm still Joo Ah Ran's little sister.
How can I love Ahjussi like that?
Nothing has changed between us.
I only love you as my woman,
and you also love me.
It doesn't matter who's woman
and who's sister you are.
Our heart didn't change.
What reason is there for us to separate.
Ahjussi.
Don't leave.
Be by my side.
If you leave, I really won't have confidence.
You will regret it later.
This might be our last chance to separate.
No matter who makes you sway,
We have to endure and persist until the end.
The road that you have to walk
later will be even more harsh.
But I will never give up.
You also have to believe me.
You can never let go of my hand.
What are you doing now?
Setting your mind straight to
deal with them is not enough.
You can still drink this down?
Today I need to drink.
Kyeong Ran is like a swollen
piece inside my heart.
I want to use a knife to chop it off clean,
and forget about it.
So today I have to get drunk.
You know where Nurse Yoon is?
You found her?
At the hospital.
She tried to escape from the room
I locked her up in, and got injured.
What?
You locked up Nurse Yoon?
It's really an interesting fate.
An older sister locking up
her little sister, hating her.
A little sister who doesn't recognize
her older sister, blaming her.
We're no longer sisters.
Joo Kyeong Ran already died.
Only Shin Hyun Woo's woman,
Yoon Jae Hee, is left over.
Stop saying what you don't mean.
How much you miss your little sister,
I know clearer than you.
Why are you saying these
words to hurt your own heart?
I won't.
The more I miss,
the stronger the feeling of betrayal is.
I won't let go of Shin Hyun Woo
and Yoon Jae Hee.
I need to ruin my enemy and his
wife with my own hands.
You have to change the situation like this?
You have to make a sister that she
hasn't seen in 25 years her enemy.
And only then your heart's
hatred will be solved?
Stop provoking unwanted trouble.
Joo Ah Ran losing the qualification of
being a sister isn't because of me.
It's not too late now.
Let the little sister return to Ah Ran's side.
This is the last choice Hyung can
do for the two people that he loved.
Don't think that you can use Jae Hee
as a shield to beg for forgiveness.
Joo Ah Ran is Joo Ah Ran.
Yoon Jae Hee is Yoon Jae Hee.
I don't care how much I love Jae Hee,
I won't forgive the woman
who ruined me and my family.
This is what humiliated my life.
Even if Yoon Jae Hee becomes unfortunate.
Even if she becomes unfortunate.
Nam Joo Seung.
Don't think that your love is that that great.
You're not loving Joo Ah Ran,
you're ruining that woman's whole life.
Why don't you know that because of you,
her sins are getting deeper and deeper.
The one making Joo Ah Ran's sins
heavier isn't me, it's you, Hyung.
If you didn't pretend to be a dead person.
Ah Ran wouldn't have set fire, right?
Today it looks like you are really pitiful.
Secretary Nam took pride in you.
Luckily he never saw you like this.
Don't casually talk about my father.
In the world, no matter who,
they just need to insult my dad,
and I will kill them all.
President, Madam, and Hyung, you.
You pitiful brat.
[Fax: Ahn Jae Sung's Profile]
You found the real Ahn Jae Sung?
He's in England now.
He was originally from Angel Orphanage.
Looks like it's the Ahn Jae Sung
that Yoon Jae Hee introduced.
What are we going to do when we get him?
We have to charge
Shin Hyun Woo with fraud.
He stole someone's identity
to build a company,
and he took away Soul that you had
and its orders and real estates.
The contract only needs to have
Ahn Jae Sung written on it.
Then the contracts that
Shin Hyun Woo signed were all frauds.
If that's the case, then he must have also
lied about purchasing Jang Heung Pension.
Shin Hyun Woo can't have bought that
community with hundreds of millions of dollars.
We just need to confirm that
the real Ahn Jae Sung is in England,
then searching up what
Shin Hyun Woo did isn't too hard.
We're already being charged,
we can't sit and wait for death.
Hello? I'm Joo Ah Ran.
What?
Promissory note return?
Then do it like that.
If it is due, of course I have to return it.
What does that mean?
Promissory note.
Because the company is in trouble,
The promissory note that Soul passed
out needs to be returned.
Not married yet and turning everything over,
my heart didn't feel comfortable.
So I never signed my name
on the promissory note.
I can't believe that I'm being helped.
Now, when Shin Woo Sub thinks that
he's won the game and is celebrating,
I really need to hit him on
the back of his head.
How much is on the promissory note?
Considering Soul's condition now,
it's hard for it not to close down.
Dad's company closing down.
Son being searched for fraud.
I really need to live life to know.
I heard the person you love is sick.
Why did you still come here?
I said you didn't need to send me.
I won't feel depressed.
I wanted to come myself.
Also, this is a present.
I used Chang Mo's design to make these.
It's really too pretty.
Thank you.
I will treasure these forever.
It's like seeing President Ahn.
Right.
This is for the Jang Heung
Pension that I own.
I might never return to Seoul.
So I'll let President Ahn run it.
Even though I'm really thankful,
I don't want it.
Now, I want to use my own
abilities to make Soul stronger.
Until now, you've helped me with these,
To outside people, it's already enough.
To President Ahn, I'm only an outsider?
Why are you using such
depressing eyes to look at me?
What I mean is,
I treated you as a comrade whom
I shared pain and revenge with.
I believe in President Ahn's abilities.
If you have any difficulties,
feel free to contact me.
We shall shake hands and bid farewell here.
How's your health?
I'm okay.
Making you worry, I'm sorry.
You already know that
Ah Ran is your real sister?
Even though it's hard to believe.
the two of you really are sisters.
Because the factory President
died in my husband's factory.
I always felt sorry.
So I raised the factory
President's two daughters.
Madam.
No matter what,
it's your sister's failed marriage.
Can you can still marry and live with a man
who was once your sister's husband?
No matter if it's by law, or by morals,
it just won't work.
I can't repeat this and let
everyone become unfortunate again.
I'm begging you.
Nurse Yoon, you, let go of our Hyun Woo.
If Nurse Yoon can't decide,
Hyun Woo won't let go of you, Nurse Yoon.
Not because of love,
Even if it's because he feels sorry,
he won't let go of Nurse Yoon.
Madam, I love Hyun Woo.
To me, who is an orphan.
Ahjussi is my whole dream.
Because of Ahjussi,
I was able to go to college.
I worked hard and lived to be nice.
I'll do well.
I have confidence that I'll
be a good wife to Ahjussi,
and be a good daughter-in-law
to his parents.
Why are you so selfish?
If you're like this, Nurse Yoon,
do you know how tired
our Hyun Woo will get?
My son,
No matter what happens.
I won't allow him to marry two sisters.
Even if it's one time,
Can't I just think of my own happiness?
I don't want to lose Ahjussi.
Even if I throw away the
name Joo Kyeong Ran,
I still want to marry Ahjussi.
I'm begging you, Madam.
I'll pretend that you understood my words.
I'm leaving.
Take care of your health.
Think of this as returning
everything that we owe you.
No matter how much you hate Ah Ran,
I trust Nurse Yoon.
Only Nurse Yoon can save Ah Ran.
If Nurse Yoon begs Hyun Woo Hyung.
Maybe the crime will be less.
No, I don't want to.
I won't do anything for Joo Ah Ran.
I know what she did to Hyun Woo.
She isn't free of crime just
because we're blood related.
You sister has her reasons for doing so.
She's not doing this because
she wants to live better.
You want to talk about my
parents' wrongful treatment?
No matter what the reason is.
The traffic incident and setting fire
can't be considered normal actions.
The person who did such cruel things,
And still dragging me to
an empty room, is Joo Ah Ran.
You might not be able to understand now,
But no matter what,
both of you are related by blood.
Don't wait until Ah Ran turns
more unfortunate to regret it.
Don't wait until it's too late,
help your sister.
I will refuse.
If you refuse, I won't let go of Hyun Woo.
I'll use all the plans that I can think of.
and push Hyun Woo to the unfortunate cliff.
Nurse Yoon, choose yourself.
You still think you can threaten me now?
Rather than cooperating with
President Nam and Joo Ah Ran,
I'd rather choose to be unfortunate.
Hyun Woo and I, will definitely marry.
The date as already been set.
I won't let the two of you control our life.
Lawyer,
Please start the case between
Shin Hyun Woo and I.
What? The promissory note came back?
What does that mean?
When did I issue a promissory note?
It seems to be Joo Ah Ran's doing.
When she was collecting funds,
it seems like she issued promissory notes.
If you don't return it immediately,
the company will be in danger.
Damn.
Where can I get that much
money all of a sudden?
I also had to pack my luggage
and got kicked out.
I just returned, brushed off the dust,
and sat here.
Oh, my head.
Why can't there be one
day where I can relax?
Hurry and call Hyun Woo.
Our Jae Hee is so pretty.
Ahjussi is already really handsome.
Yes, Dad.
I'm trying on hanboks with Jae Hee.
There aren't many days remaining
before our marriage,
so I have to prepare everything.
What?
Where did you go?
I went to confirm the promissory
note's condition.
Soul Furniture is already in danger.
Did you start the case with Shin Hyun Woo?
Yeah.
I don't think it's fair that my
doctor's license was cancelled.
If Hyun Woo wasn't dead,
Then the fake treatment I did was fake.
If we're talking about lying,
the patient is the same.
Then, me setting fire wasn't
to kill Shin Hyun Woo.
Shin Hyun Woo already made
a fake person and escaped.
Then that wouldn't be considered as murder.
Shin Hyun Woo.
You're jumping into the
trap you dug yourself.
Stealing another person's identity,
acting as a dead person.
It's a movie directed by you to seek revenge.
Right.
Did you know that Hyun Woo and Nurse Yoon
have set their marriage date set?
Marriage date?
Yoon Jae Hee.
Looks like you're busying
preparing for the marriage.
You're not married yet and yet you've
moved into Shin Hyun Woo's house.
Aren't we pretending that
we don't know each other?
Don't look for me ever again.
it's not convenient seeing you.
What are you doing now?
You listen carefully to me.
No matter what happens,
I won't send you to an enemy's house.
I waited 25 years, just to see that face?
I'm still the same in feeling
despair for my sister.
We lost our parents.
You were crying because of hunger
while I had you on my back.
I was accused of being a thief
because I wanted to feed you.
Even if I had to go through garbage to
find food, I would give you the best.
After I left you.
I looked for you on the
streets like a crazy woman.
But in return you're going to
do be like this to me?
The sister that I anticipated,
isn't one who stole other
people's food to feed me.
Even if I starved,
I want a sister who is
honest and upright.
A woman who's heart is filled
with hatred and is so twisted,
is a person that I look down on.
What?
I have to marry Hyun Woo.
If you feel sorry towards Hyun Woo,
then sincerely congratulate
Hyun Woo's marriage.
Then redeem your crimes broadly.
This is the last warning I can
give as a younger sister.
Up until she transferred
everything to my name,
she never mentioned anything
about a promissory note.
Joo Ah Ran is such a tricky person.
She has nothing, how could she
have given away all of her fortune?
Then what should we do now?
The promissory notes amount is really big.
No.
What face does she have to
pull our family into water?
Hyun Woo, what are you doing?
I let you give her to the police to arrest her,
What's the reason for you to hesitate?
Is it that Joo Ah Ran
knows one of your weaknesses?
No.
Right now, I'm thinking about how I can
withstand these promissory notes.
First we have to discuss how we can extend
the time of the promissory notes.
If it doesn't work,
We can only use our estate money.
Right.
I'll bring out my store and apartment.
No matter what, we can't let it close.
Finding this company wasn't easy.
How about asking Julie Jung?
That person would definitely help us.
She left today.
This isn't coming along.
The company might have a bloody storm.
First we need to set up Hyun Woo's wedding.
Tomorrow, we'll simply eat a dinner
and that will be the engagement.
We don't know what tricks
Joo Ah Ran will use again.
You need to get engaged,
then she'll give up on you.
Okay.
What?
The engagement ceremony is tomorrow?
Honey,
Why are you in such a rush?
Hyun Woo returned not long ago.
You only have to do it,
why do you have so much to say?
Hyun Woo's divorce result already came.
Just do it like that.
Ah, money is a really nice thing.
Your face hasn't changed at all
compared to 25 years ago.
Aigoo. Your home looks really fancy.
You clean it very well.
Why did you come here?
Didn't I say not to come to my house?
Now we have to bargain.
If you don't bring over our Kyeong Ran.
We're going to stay here.
Looks like you still don't know.
Ah Ran and Kyeong Ran already met.
What?
That's what you say.
Aigoo, I knew this would happen.
That's why Ah Ran lost contact with us
and locked the doors for the wedding.
What does this mean?
We made porridge for a dog.
Aigoo. I'm going crazy.
That's why I said.
If you had gave in to our Kyeong Ran earlier,
We wouldn't have done useless things.
What's the use of putting a parent here?
I have something to ask of you two.
Can you do me a favor?
If you do this favor,
I won't mistreat you.
Engagement?
Joo Ah Ran will continue
blocking our marriage.
We can't always be controlled by her.
I'm also worried that your soft
heart will make you waver,
I won't waver..
I already promised you.
No matter what difficulties there are,
I won't let go of Ahjussi's hand.
Even if my parents were
alive to block my marriage,
I'd still want to marry Ahjussi.
Be strong.
Tomorrow,
everything will return to its original place.
You came back.
Where did you go?
I went to meet someone.
Tomorrow,
Hyun Woo's engagement ceremony,
I have to take care of a special guest.
Special guest?
Just wait.
I have to give a meaningful present
at Hyun Woo's ceremony.
Just my family breaking up isn't fair.
Your family will also have a storm today.
Aigoo, you're Kyeong Ran.
I told you you can't lie
about blood relationships.
She totally has her father's face.
This is definitely Joo Chul Min's daughter.
Yes, I would recognize you
even if we were in the streets.
Who are you two?
We're Kyeong Ran's uncle and aunt.
Who are you?
Uncle and aunt?
Where did Jae Hee go?
Why did you come by yourself?
She saw her Uncle's family.
She'll be here soon.
She grew up in an orphanage
and still has an uncle?
It's a engagement ceremony,
why don't you invite them.
We'll visit officially.
We were so angry we couldn't even sleep.
How can you marry Ah Ran's ex-husband?
You didn't drop from the sky.
You are our Joo family's child.
How can you marry your brother-in-law?
Ugh. I'm so embarrassed I can't talk.
Just pretend that there was
no engagement ceremony.
Come with us to get some air.
Driver, drive faster.
Did Joo Ah Ran tell you
to block my marriage?
So you came to find me?
Driver. Please stop.
Don't stop. Keep driving. Keep going.
No one can stop me from my engagement.
I have to get engaged.
Driver. Please drive to Kuang Hwa
Police Department.
Police Department?
Hurry and reject. Go. Go.
My head hurts.
Let's decide at the police department.
Oh my god. This person, do you
want someone to go to jail?
Listen. Stop there.
Stop. Stop.
Kyeong Ran. You come out also.
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch.
Ahjussi. Hurry and go.
Kyeong Ran. Kyeong Ran. Aigoo.
You brat.
Down here is a toast full of wishes
for the groom and bride.
Please raise your cups.
Everyone together. Cheers.
What are you guys doing?
Where do you think this is?
You..
Because we're guests you didn't invite,
were you surprised?
Our wedding was also full of
people who we didn't invite.
I should thank you for that.
Joo Ah Ran. Nam Joo Seung.
Leave immediately.
Aren't you too unreasonable to a guest?
This person is Director Jung who worked for
President since the start of Gam Yu Furniture.
We invited him because he had
something to say to President.
Director Jung,
what do you want to talk about?
Today is an important family reunion.
Let's meet some other day.
Long time no see, President Shin.
Secretary Nam's son and Leader Joo's
daughter have grown up.
It's already been 25 years since the incident.
Director Jung.
Do you know how my father died?
Please say it.
What's the real reason
behind the car incident?
Only Director, you, can say it clearly.
That person left really pitifully.
The car suddenly lost
balance and tipped over.
After investigation, one of the
tire's screws was found loose.
Who purposely malfunctioned the car?
At that time, President Shin meant to not
tell the police and let it quietly calm down.
That right, President Shin and President Joo's
relationships weren't that good.
What are you talking about now?
The person who fixed the tired,
was you, Shin Woo Sub.
You were relaxed because
the recourse date was passed.
Even if the law forgives you,
I won't forget this crime even if I die.
Nurse Yoon. You should come to our side.
You still don't know that you and
President's family don't match?
Right. I left out something important.
My father had two daughters.
Coincidentally, both of them are here.
What? Two daughters?
The older one is me.
The younger one is Yoon Jae Hee.
Dad's soon to be daughter-in-law.
What?
Yoon Jae Hee.
My younger sister, Joo Kyeong Ran.
Why did she want to use a fake name,
Yoon Jae Hee,
and become this family's daughter-in-law?
You know without me saying right?
It's my parents' hatred that called
both daughters to be in this family.
How can this be?
Thank you Joo Seung,
things went smoothly.
I can't believe that there would be
someone to prove that day's incident.
What do you plan on doing now?
I need to put a deadly flaw
onto Shin Woo Sub's morality.
Let him be swallowed by society.
You don't need to be behind
bars to be considered in jail.
You're going to give all the things
President Shin did to the media?
This time I need Kyeong Ran to help out.
She needs to do something
for our dead parents.
You knew that Yoon Jae Hee is Ah Ran's
sister and you still want to marry?
Yes.
You crazy bastard.
There's no other woman to marry,
So you're going to marry the younger sister
of the person who turned you into this?
Why does it have to
be Joo Chul Min's daughter?
Of all the woman in this world,
is there only Joo Chul Min's daughter?
Honey, calm down.
Your blood pressure might rise.
You also knew.
Why didn't you block it?
Are you still considered a mother?
This marriage cannot be completed.
Don't say that it's your life.
Even if we have to scoop
our family up from a flood,
I won't accept her as my daughter-in-law.
I didn't know from the start.
I found out that they were
sisters after deciding to marry.
But we can't separate like that.
The one time I had to leave Jae Hee,
No matter if I was Ahn Jae Sung
or Shin Hyun Woo,
I was a bastard that couldn't do anything.
Even if you say it a million times,
my answer will be the same.
I can't be a family with that type of family.
Yoon Jae Hee definitely
approached you with a plan.
Dad. A package came with your name.
Open it and look.
What is this?
It's a silk and a letter.
Isn't this Secretary Nam's uncle?
What?
Secretary Nam?
But who is this child?
Who is Mom and Secretary Nam
carrying in this picture?
It looks like a family picture.
Who is playing these kinds of tricks?
Joo Seung that bastard.
He wants to threaten
me with his dead father?
Is that child Joo Seung Hyung?
I heard Joo Seung's mother
died a long time ago.
Mom thought he was so
pitiful that you took care of him.
Then what is this silk?
Mom, tell us.
Are you and Secretary Nam related?
The grudge between Shin Hyun Woo's
family and our family is true.
You have to believe it.
You are allowed not to accept me,
But you can't deny that
Shin Woo Sub killed our parents.
Are you listening to me?
Joo Ah Ran is a suspect of setting the fire.
She's also a criminal
who killed her husband.
No. No. No.
What should I do?
I'm a sinner towards Sister.
I'm a sinner towards Ahjussi.
No matter what choice I make,
I won't be happy.
Was it you?
Did you send this picture to my house?
Besides my dad,
the only person with that picture is me.
You didn't know?
Madam is my mother.
Shut up.
Then when do I need to die until?
Why does it have to be like this?
Because of President's family happiness.
It doesn't matter if I'm
not a person of this world.
President and Madam are the same.
Both of you are selfish people
who only know of their own family.
No matter where you go, disappear.
Don't start arguments in my family.
Don't appear in front of my eyes ever.
Then let go of Ah Ran.
Persuade Hyun Woo Hyung
to get Ah Ran off the hook.
Then both of us will leave.
Are you threatening me now?
I'm not threatening, I'm discussing.
The more you abandon Ah Ran,
the more publicized your secrets will be.
Does the war that injures
both sides need to continue?
I really raised a tiger.
In this world,
no matter how weak the animal is,
As long as it wasn't abandoned by
it's mother, it will become strong.
What do you have to say?
When did you start knowing,
that your mother was my mother.
It was when Dad passed away.
But don't worry.
I never wished to be
treated as your brother.
Then why did you send
that letter and picture?
What do you want?
What I want?
Of course it's Madam's family
becoming unfortunate.
It's too lonely wanting only one
person to become unfortunate.
You bastard.
A family arguing is pretty exciting.
You should accept it also.
Is it to take revenge on the
mother who abandoned you,
that you helped Joo Ah Ran
go against my family?
This is how you thank the
mother who gave birth to you?
This is how you thank me, who loved and
took care of you and became your brother-
What do you know?
What would you, who grew up
in a honey jar, know?
When I was sick,
I never once called mother.
With a life like a beggar.
For the past 30 years,
Madam was never my mother.
She's only a President's wife
who is so cold and scary.
So you want to kill me?
You want to kill me,
me, who hogged your mother's love.
Is your goal to let your
mom become miserable?
When no one was there,
if she put food in my bowl,
I wouldn't hate her so much.
Behind me,
If she spoke to me nicely,
Then maybe I would understand everything.
But she totally forgot about this son.
This is more cruel than getting abandoned.
Will you become happy
after your mother's hurt?
If you're still considered Mom's son,
Letting Mother become unfortunate,
you won't get freedom.
How could that be?
My revenge hasn't ended yet.
There will soon be a lawsuit
letter sent to your house.
The real Ahn Jae Sung might also come.
You should get ready.
No, maybe he's already at the airport.
The real Ahn Jae Sung?
[Killing Devil: Shin Woo Sub]
Who did this?
What were you doing looking
at these getting taped up?
Hurry and rip them off.
Sorry President.
Every newspaper and media got a call,
revealing President's past.
What?
No matter what, we have to block this.
No matter how much money we use,
We have to prevent the news
of this from coming out.
No, no. I'll have to go to the
police department myself.
Hurry and get the car ready.
Yes, President.
Those bastards.
Find the person who posted these up.
Arrest them for ruining
my reputation and fraud.
They also took the media.
I can't hold this in anymore.
If it's something that happened
25 years ago, we can't investigate it.
But is this true?
If you don't believe me,
you can look at my company's secret books.
There is proof of the incident,
there's also a record of the fees.
Who did it?
Nam Joo Seung or Joo Ah Ran?
The one who reported it to
the media was Joo Kyeong Ran.
Do you know her?
Joo Kyeong Ran?
Ah.
Yoon Jae Hee.
Mom, tell us.
What is this secret
that you're hiding from us?
No matter what the truth is,
we'll accept it.
Hyun Min, Hyun Ji, I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
What's the reason for mother being like this?
I'm about to go crazy.
Joo Seung is my son whom I gave birth to.
It's Hyun Min's brother.
Also Hyun Ji's brother.
Mom.
This is impossible.
Joo Seung is Secretary Nam's son.
Sorry.
Forgive mother.
How can mother be like this?
Secretary Nam was always
like a brother to father.
How could someone who came
to our house for 30 years..
You hid this from father for 30 years?
So when I said I wanted to marry,
you rejected, right?
Taking revenge on father like that,
isn't it too low?
If you hated father so much,
you could have just divorced.
I hate mother. I feel embarrassed.
I always thought father was too harsh.
I felt sorry for you.
But it was like that?
The one who betrayed father and gave
our family such humiliation was you!
Hyun Min.
Jae Hee is Ah Ran's younger sister.
Joo Seung is my younger brother.
Is it like that?
Why aren't you saying anything?
If we knew earlier,
then we wouldn't be unfortunate like this.
It's all my sin.
I know there's no point in saying anything.
But, why were you so
harsh towards Joo Seung?
Would you still be a mother when
you stabbed a knife into his heart?
If I didn't do that, I felt that I
would be discovered by your father.
If your father found out.
Joo Seung and I wouldn't live on.
No matter what,
I didn't want to ruin this family.
That heart is real.
Stop finding excuses in ignoring
Joo Seung and making him lonely.
It's because of mother's motherly love.
Since you gave birth,
at least become a mother.
How could you not know,
To us, you were so caring,
To another person,
you became a deadly poisonous medicine.
Mom, you're just a cruel person?
You've received a great impact.
Go and find father.
Ah. Ah.
Ah!
Hyun Woo. I came back because I
didn't want you to not have a father.
Was I wrong?
To give you a perfect family,
and the crime of letting ,
Joo Seung not have a mother
I've received my punishment now.
President.
Buy some wine. I want to drink.
Even though you're really tired,
I want you to know,
What?
The debt company sent their last notice.
If we can't block the promissory note by
tomorrow before the bank closes,
We'll go through the
first stage of bankruptcy.
Bankruptcy?
Soul needs to go bankrupt?
No. No.
This is all because of Joo Ah Ran.
Joo Chul Min's daughter comes into our
family and my family goes bankrupt.
Then I'm a fool who's sitting
here waiting for death.
Secretary Kang.
Yes, President.
Contact the police department.
Let them start investigating
the fire incident.
Looks like Hyun Woo is softhearted
because of Joo Ah Ran's sister.
What that bastard can't do, I'll do.
Is it Ah Ran?
Is Joo Ah Ran inside?
We have to investigate the
fire incident in the mansion.
Joo Ah Ran isn't here.
Also, this isn't Joo Ah Ran's
house, it's my house.
If she comes over, I'll contact you.
Please leave.
Then we'll wait outside.
It's me. Don't come home.
The police are looking for you.
If you receive investigation
then you'll definitely be charged.
I'll do something about it.
Find a hotel or sauna and hide.
Don't use a car either.
Can you hear me?
What do you want me to do?
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
If you want me to leave, I'll leave.
If you want to divorce, I'll agree.
Who agrees on divorce? Divorce?
Stop dreaming.
What deed am I doing by divorcing?
Turning the family into this.
You want to live peacefully,
is that what you mean?
Then what do you want me to do?
Do you want me to be a sinner
to you and the kids,
and bow down waiting to
die for my whole life?
What did you do right?
You're still talking back.
I won't forgive and I won't forget.
You'll live like a criminal without
knowing when you'll die.
You'll pay for your crimes for betraying
your husband and then leave.
I'm also human.
I can also get angry. If you hit me,
I'll also scream because of pain.
I'm a person with feelings.
Did you turn crazy? You.
Yes, I'm crazy.
I should be crazy since
you torture me like this.
Even if I'm a maid who prepares
your food for my whole life,
You can't treat me like this.
Now you're going to talk
about making food?
Then, do other Ahjummas
not do that and play?
Don't say that everything is my wrong.
If you've looked at me
even once as your wife,
No, looked at me as a human.
I wouldn't have given birth
to Joo Seung painfully.
Ah. What you mean is that
you're wrong was my fault.
I really regret not leaving you that time.
Not resisting against your violence.
I endured it because of the children.
I really regret.
I want to give up on being your wife.
I don't want to beg for forgiveness.
I want to go on my own road.
Honey.