Temptation Of An Angel
Final Episode 21
President, you don't know, right?
The person who killed Ah Ran's parents,
is Madam.
What?
Is this fellow crazy?
You don't know that Madam was the one
who tampered with the wheels, right?
The person who killed Ah Ran's parents,
and the person who plunged
the sisters into tragedy,
was Madam!
What are you saying?
No matter how much you hate your mother,
you can't spout nonsense like that.
If you doubt me, ask Madam directly.
Who was the person who
tampered with the wheels,
who was the person who
killed Ah Ran's parents,
tell him everything!
Honey,
forgive me.
Then, it's true?
How could you?!
It's not!
The person who brutally trampled
on Ah Ran's entire family...
was Madam.
Up till now,
can President's family point fingers
at Ah Ran and blame her?
Hyun Woo is still alive,
but Ah Ran's parents are dead,
who should be punished?
Do you not feel shame?
All the guilt is mine,
why are you blaming Hyun Woo?
It doesn't matter if it was
the traffic accident,
or setting fire to burn him to death,
from the beginning you should
have tried to kill me.
It's not too late yet!
If dying is your wish,
I'll grant it.
- Ah Ran.
- You want to die?
What are you waiting for?
My father and my mother are waiting for you!
Ah Ran, wait a while.
Let go!
Hurry in.
I've talked to Joo Ah Ran,
she doesn't seem to have any intention
of extending the invoice period.
What should we do?
By the end of business hours today,
you'll officially be declared bankrupt.
Don't worry too much.
I've already made preparations
for the official declaration.
What?
I've separated Soul and SM.
Soul was originally a wedding present to
Joo Ah Ran when we got married.
Now, I am going over with
no regrets to SM Furniture.
Then, if Soul Furniture goes bankrupt,
will there be no impact on SM Furniture?
It's difficult right now because
there is no capital,
but I just have to act like the beginning,
gritting my teeth and running a little more.
Compared to this,
I have something to tell you Jae Hee.
I can't believe this.
Last Episode
The person who has been
sponsoring me all this time,
is the person who killed my parents.
Then,
with my parents' lives,
I traded it for clothes,
presents,
and even college?
Is that right?
Don't feel burdened,
to Mother, it was some kind of redemption.
Why was she so cruel?
She didn't have to kill someone innocent.
Maybe she was afraid her
secret would be exposed,
and lost her mind.
If only she was calmer and more rational,
things would have been better.
Yes, Father.
What?
Do you know where this place is?
Because of you, my parents didn't
even know why they died.
This is my parents' grave!
In this cold water,
only the ashes of my parents are left.
What do you have to say?
I'm sorry.
I will apologize.
If you want me to die, I'll die.
Apologize?
What's the use of an apology?!
Can my dead parents come back?
Can my tragic life be changed?
Because of you, I became a lunatic,
I became a criminal that
tried to kill my husband.
All of this, how are you going to repay me?
Follow me.
Ah... Ah Ran.
It's me.
Where are you right now?
I'll go there.
Forget it.
I don't need your help anymore.
The person who should have died
wasn't Shin Hyun Woo, but Jo Kyung Hee.
No...
Ah Ran!
You can't, Ah Ran!
I've found out the location of the taxi that
Ah Ran is taking by the car plate number.
It's better if you go look there,
I have a bad feeling.
Yeo Ju.
If it's Yeo Ju...
It's the wooden lodge where she held me!
You said you wanted to
die to apologize, right?
Then just die in front of me.
All this is already out in the open,
there is no other choice for you.
Do you want to pour it yourself,
or should I do it for you?
Ah Ran.
Why?
Are you afraid of dying?
I know you hate me,
but I still want to apologize to you.
Because of a criminal like me,
stop doing things that destroy your life.
If you want,
I will die quietly by myself.
Stop pretending to be pathetic.
Do you think I'll let you off this way?
There's nothing else to destroy
or abandon in my life.
Traffic accident, murder charges,
running away, arson,
ten fingers are not enough.
Someone like me,
even if I kill the people
who killed my parents,
is not enough for me.
Alright.
Let's die.
There's nothing else to hold on to,
or to cling on to.
Life, if we suffer through our life,
it's hell.
Now...
I want to shed this burden too.
When you die and meet my parents,
you have to kneel and beg
for their forgiveness.
When they forgive you,
I'll offer a cup of wine at your tombstone.
Joo Ah Ran, stop!
Don't come over!
If you come over, your mother will die.
What is this?
The crimes that you've
committed aren't enough,
what else do you want to do?!
Kyeong Ran, you stay out of this.
My hands are soiled,
I'll end this by myself.
Don't watch anything.
Just pretend you don't
know anything forever.
Please listen to me and stop.
I'll stop pursuing everything
that you've done to me.
I haven't handed the evidence to the police.
It doesn't matter if you do!
Now, I've met the real culprit.
You've suffered so much too,
now, you should let your
mother suffer it too!
What...
What are you doing now?
I,
don't have a mother,
or a father.
I've missed my family so
much all this while.
It's been so hard to find my sister.
I don't want to send you to
prison and leave me alone.
If something happens to Madam,
you'll never return to being my Unni.
If you still want to light the fire,
light it.
Here...
I'll die with Madam.
You can't,
you can't... my poor parents.
What will happen to my poor parents?!
I put it on you because the smell
of the gasoline is too choking.
Why do you do something
like that so casually?
Did you endure it for me?
I said we would die together,
you got scared, right?
What does it matter to me if you died?
I just didn't have the courage.
Actually, I...
have something to tell you.
When I found out you were my Unni,
I prayed to the Heavens.
I don't need an Unni like that,
quickly take her away.
I was afraid to break up with Hyun Woo,
that's why I had such frightening thoughts.
I'm really...
horrible, right?
I have something to confess too.
When our parents died,
it was the day Dad was supposed
to go away for business.
But I wanted a birthday celebration,
so I was throwing a tantrum.
To have dinner together,
to buy presents together.
If Dad had gone away like
he was supposed to,
they wouldn't have died like that.
I'm afraid to say it's my fault,
that's why I push the blame
on other people more,
that might be the case.
What's the reason you demanded to be
let out of the hospital so quickly?
Where did Mum go?
Did Mum... get into trouble again?
Don't blame your mother.
When she comes home,
don't say anything,
and treat her with warmth.
Horrible person.
She must have endured so
much pain for so many years.
If I had told her I knew about her
relationship with Secretary Nam,
all this tragedy wouldn't have happened.
All this is my fault.
Mum!
Father, what's going on?
Did you get discharged?
I won't be able to walk even
if I stay in the hospital.
I got a lot of painkillers, don't worry.
Is your Mum alright?
Yes.
Joo Ah Ran was taken away by Jae Hee.
But...
But what is this smell?
Isn't it gasoline?
You said you were with Joo Ah Ran,
could she have poured gasoline on Mum?
No!
I'm going in to shower.
Is Oppa a fool?
You risked your life to undergo
full-body plastic surgery,
but where's the Oppa that wanted
to take revenge on Joo Ah Ran?
If Oppa can't do it, I will.
I won't let that woman,
Joo Ah Ran, go!
Are you looking at the photographs?
That was when I was younger,
I was quite ugly, right?
If our parents were alive,
you wouldn't be living like that either.
When you went to school,
did anyone tease you for being
from an orphanage?
So what if I did?
It was just because they didn't know better,
I was fine with it.
You don't need to lie to me.
What is an orphan,
what is poverty,
I've felt it in my bones too.
What you see might not be true.
Orphans and people in poverty
don't have to live unhappy.
Because they have dreams,
tomorrow might be a happier day.
Compared to this, Madam's life is hell.
Thinking about the way she lived,
she's already made her repentance,
let's just forget it.
How can we forget it?
25 years turns her into an innocent victim,
but makes me a cold-blooded murderer.
What in the world do I have to forget,
or to forgive?
[Madam]
The person who gave birth to you was Mum,
the person you hate is also Mother!
You feel it's right to personally send the
person who gave birth to you to her death?
What do you plan to do with Joo Ah Ran?
I don't know what would be
the right call to make either.
To you and Hyun Woo,
even though this might sound ridiculous,
but could we absolve her crimes legally?
Because,
Ah Ran has lost a lot too.
I share the same thoughts as your mother,
because if your mother is
a criminal, so am I.
If Ah Ran comes to any trouble,
our family won't be free either.
Sending Ah Ran to jail,
you won't feel comfortable either.
Then, I'll become the real culprit
of the traffic accident.
If they find out that Joo Ah Ran
is the driver,
then she'll be convicted for running away.
Just take it that you're
repenting for the crime
that your mother committed 25 years ago.
Prepare yourself,
please.
You grew up beautifully.
I really wanted to...
do everything for you like a mother.
But after we've really met,
I can't do anything for you.
Like you said,
were my methods wrong?
The two of us are living such tiring lives,
why can't I have the same thoughts as you?
I'm sorry Unni.
Tiring Unni out like that,
from loving Shin Hyun Woo,
and Unni loving Ahn Jae Sung,
our parents wouldn't want to see
the way we take revenge too.
Hyun Ji!
Did you see the flashdrive in my room?
I left it on my bed.
I didn't see it.
What is it?
Ah, it's really important,
where did I drop it?
Ah Ran...
we've decided to accept her.
If there's a need,
we'll write her a recognition letter.
No matter what,
help her to forget the past
and start afresh.
Hyun Woo Hyung,
has agreed too?
Of course.
Hyun Woo's father feels the same way too.
If there's time,
can you go somewhere with me?
Joo Seung's father,
it's been a long time.
I never thought there would be a day,
where Joo Seung and I will come
and see you together.
The day you died,
I stayed outside your hospital
door and never came in,
you can understand, right?
My cowardice,
please forgive it.
The life that was supposed
to end a long time ago,
because of you,
I lived a long time.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Joo Seung.
Just once...
Could you call me Mother?
From the beginning, I never had a mother.
In the future as well.
Joo Ah Ran.
Even if everyone in our family forgives you,
I'll never be able to.
Everything that you did to our family,
I want you to pay it back one by one.
It's the police.
What are you doing right now?
Where is Joo Ah Ran?
I don't know.
From the black box and the fingerprints
that Shin Hyun Woo provided,
we've come to a conclusion.
The traffic accident at Chang Yuan,
and the arson at Yang Pyeong,
the suspect is Joo Ah Ran.
Shin Hyun Woo.
The person who reported
it was Shin Hyun Woo?
This is the spinach I made,
I'm good at cooking.
Try the fish soup too.
I was really determined,
and went to the market to buy a big fish.
Wretch, why are you showing off?
You think no one else can do it?
At Aunt's house,
I made food till I had calluses on my hands.
After we eat,
shall we shower together?
I shower by myself every day,
no one scrubs my back for me.
Where are you going?
If you don't want to, it's fine too.
Are you in a bad mood?
Didn't you want to shower?
We have to fill the tub.
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
Who's crying?
It's just tiring.
Don't save money,
go to the spa to get your
back scrubbed sometimes.
I can do it for you when I'm around,
but I don't know what will
happen in the future.
Why are you saying that?
Hyun Woo said he won't pursue the past,
everything will be alright from now on.
Don't think about those things.
[Joo Seung]
Ah Ran,
hurry pick up the phone!
The police are after you!
Joo Seung, it's me.
Why are you not picking up your phone?
Something big has happened.
Hurry and run away from there now.
Shin Hyun Woo has handed over the black box,
the police could be on their way!
I got it.
What happened?
The police are after me.
I have to go out.
It's too dangerous by yourself,
I'll go with you.
Kyeong Ran, you stay here.
I don't want you to be tired
out because of me.
Where are you going to go?
That's right.
You can go to the Angel Orphanage.
I'll call the Director,
you can go hide there for
a day or two first.
I'll clarify the situation
before calling you.
It's cold, you have to watch
out for your health.
Take a cab.
During this period of time, use my phone,
got it?
Unni!
Unni,
you have to be fine.
If something happens,
I will really hate you then.
Kyeong Ran, so you're a crybaby,
how silly.
Unni will come back soon,
why are you crying?
Unni will be back soon,
I promise.
In order for things to happen this way,
did you try to give us some peace?
Is this the end of your revenge?
Like a hypocrite,
you only said the good things,
from beginning till end, you didn't
shed a drop of blood, or a tear,
and you're expecting Ah Ran to die?
It's a misunderstanding,
I never handed the flashdrive over.
Then who did?
Besides the victim, who else is there?!
Don't be agitated, let's think of a way.
Once the flashdrive's content is exposed,
everything Ah Ran did will be uncovered.
Then, even when we write the letter,
nothing will be of use.
I have to make a trip to the police station.
What?
Shin Hyun Ji?
Since we already have concrete evidence,
we have to launch a formal investigation
against Joo Ah Ran.
The police are arresting her right now.
I'm sorry,
but could you give Joo Ah Ran more time?
If the victim submits a letter that
he doesn't want to pursue charges,
what will happen?
Although it can be used for
reference during the jury,
running away from the police,
is something that cannot be pardoned.
I'm the main perpetrator!
Joo Ah Ran isn't guilty.
Prison,
or the detention center,
please just lock me up.
There was Joo Ah Ran's face
in the black box,
what are you talking about?
It's not true.
Joo Ah Ran,
is only my helper.
I hate Shin Hyun Woo,
and told her to kill him.
That woman was just persuaded by me,
I'm the real murderer!
What?!
Who wants to marry who?
Father's health isn't good,
and I know I shouldn't be saying this,
but, I want to hold a simple
wedding ceremony,
with just our family.
Please agree to it.
Are you just informing us,
after you've set the wedding date?
Oppa, are you crazy?
Hyun Min.
How can you surprise your father like that?
Let's talk about this another time.
What's there to talk about another time?
You personally saw how your Hyung
went to hell for a woman,
how can you make decisions like these?
How can my children have such
taste when it comes to women?
If we look at it in perspective,
there's nothing wrong with Yeon Jae at all.
But, if you use your heart to look at her,
she's actually a really good person.
Our family needs to have
someone like Yeon Jae.
Please believe me,
and accept Yeon Jae.
Hyung and I,
is it so hard to come to terms?
Where did we go wrong?
The one mother that gave birth to us,
doesn't know why we came
to such a hateful point.
Today's tragedy,
is a punishment for my past.
That's right.
I've always been thinking,
that taking revenge on Joo Ah Ran
was the only way to recover my life.
Because of that misguided thought,
I've split up my entire family.
I've been hurt,
by my own knife.
What's the use in saying such things?
We have to protect Ah Ran first.
Even if I sell my soul to the dark side,
I can't watch Ah Ran suffer anymore.
Let's go visit the victim's family first.
Regarding Ah Ran's crimes,
Mother has also agreed to write a letter.
If Mum's crimes are exposed,
it would be beneficial to Ah Ran as well.
I'll try my best to delay the police.
Is this Kyeong Ran?
Unni, you're fine, right?
I really want to go see you, Unni,
but I'm afraid of being followed,
so I can't go.
You've eaten, right?
I have.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I've heard of the community
center at Gangwondo.
I've been there once,
if you go there, you'll be safe.
Hyun Woo, and Director Nam,
are also working really hard for Unni.
The victim's family has also
agreed to write a letter,
everything will be fine.
Right now,
you've been living for our deceased parents.
Right now, Unni, you have
to live for yourself.
If that's the case, you have to forget
the past and forgive everything.
If you don't forgive,
Unni will come into misfortune.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Kyeong Ran.
I want to ask you something.
Till now,
you still love Hyun Woo, right?
It might need some time,
but I'll take care of it.
If I had to choose someone,
between Unni and Hyun Woo,
my answer is,
Unni.
I have to hang up.
The director is waiting for me.
Goodnight.
My sister.
How embarrassing,
and how much she must hate me.
Thank you for calling me Unni.
I really really wanted to hear that.
Appearing in this disgraceful way,
I'm really sorry.
Unni.
So?
Must you hold the wedding today?
I'm sorry.
But,
I want to keep my promise,
to my wedding.
Even if no one comes to my wedding,
I have to hold it.
I will prove it to you for
the rest of my life.
Hyun Min,
Hyun Min!
Why is this fellow so worrisome too?
Has he gone crazy with the idea of marriage?
Honey,
just give in to Hyun Min this once.
I don't want Hyun Min to get hurt,
and to live with the woman he loves.
As parents, we shouldn't expect anything,
but to think of Hyun Min.
Are you going out?
I'm going to Seoul.
The police are looking for you,
will you be fine?
You know that you're going to the community
center today, right?
Yes.
Before that, I have something I need to do.
It won't be too long.
I'm sorry.
I can't give you a proper wedding,
so we can only come to the photo studio.
But to repay you for the lack
of a wedding ceremony,
I'll definitely let you put on
a beautiful wedding dress.
So what?
More than that, I feel uneasy that
we're letting down your family.
How hurt they have to be right now.
I'm a bad woman.
Suffer a little on the wedding day,
but it's alright if you make
them happy in the future.
I'll do well.
Be strong.
Here, look here!
Look a little closer.
Here... One, two...
Dad!
You came?
Father, thank you!
Let go of me.
I didn't come to see you get married.
Your mother insisted on coming
to take a family photo,
so we came to take a photo.
Then, let's hurry and take a photo.
Mother, and Brother-in-law, come over.
Ahgassi too.
- Here...
- Father, you have to smile!
Ahgassi too!
Alright, look here.
Let's take another one
What is this?
Is this a wedding car?
The preparations were a little rushed,
so we couldn't prepare anything.
Here's a card for four days and
three nights in a hotel,
have fun.
Hurry and leave,
do you want to spend the night here?
Honey,
I'll go out for a while,
to make preparations for
Hyun Min's wedding room.
I want to go out and catch a breath too.
What breath?
You've only taken care of the old man for
a couple of days, you're tired already?
She might feel a little empty
because of Hyun Min's wedding,
Hyun Ji and I are here too,
let Mother go.
It's cold out,
so you should take my car.
Don't catch a cold just because
you have to take the bus.
Thank you.
Yes, this is Pyeong Chang Dong.
What?!
It's me.
I was about to call.
The police station just called.
They've just received the letter,
so on the whole, they're
going to handle it lightly.
Ah Ran, you can come back now.
Mother.
Mum.
Why is your hand so cold?
What in the world,
how long were you out in the cold?
Hyun Ji,
quickly get a blanket.
Mum is really cold, hurry!
Even if you die,
I can't forgive you either.
You might as well just take me with you.
Let's go together!
Mother.
Mum, mum.
Mum.
Mum, mum
Mum!
No.
Stop.
Don't go.
Don't go!
From now on,
I won't do anything.
Just stay by my side.
I still have a lot to tell you.
Thank you for giving birth to me,
I'm sorry I kept hating you.
I still have a lot to tell you.
Why did you just leave like that?!
I wanted to call you Mother too.
I'm sorry, Mother.
We've just begun the investigation
on Jo Kyung Hee.
The accident happened because
of the problem with the brake.
A problem with the brake?
That can't be.
At the workshop last week,
everything was fine,
how could there suddenly be a problem?
According to the experts,
someone intentionally tampered
with the brakes.
Is there someone you can think of?
That's right.
Joo Ah Ran!
A person who has ill intentions
to our family,
there's only that person!
Don't say anything you don't have proof of.
Oh, right.
I saw Ah Ran behind the potted plants,
she was hiding in a corner staring at us.
Then,
Joo Ah Ran, like your mother,
tampered with the brakes?
Could it be?
Go find out where Joo Ah Ran is...
No.
Ah Ran couldn't have done that.
Where I'm going,
don't tell anyone at all.
I don't think I need this
hand phone anymore.
Take care of your health,
and live well.
If there's any difficulty,
please contact me.
It's me.
I'm going to pick your Unni up.
Where is your Unni?
Alright, I get it.
Joo Ah Ran,
did you have to go to the extreme?
No matter what, she's my mother.
If you loved me at all,
you'd have held back just a little.
Joo Ah Ran!
Joo Seung.
Did you really...
do it?
Don't come over!
Don't take another step.
Why did you do it?
Everything was getting better,
why did you have to do it?!
If you loved me at all,
you would have held back.
Was the love I gave you,
that insufficient?
Stand there!
If you come over, I'll die.
That's impossible.
How could you...
my mother...
Joo Ah Ran!
Stand there!
Stay there!
Joo Ah Ran!
Stay, there, Joo Ah Ran!
Joo Ah Ran, stay there!
Stay there!
Don't come over.
Don't come over!
Joo Ah Ran.
It's no use running away.
Turn yourself in now.
That's right, let me go.
I've never asked for anything,
till the day I die,
can't I hide here, just to live here?
Repent for all the crimes you've done first.
Here, come here.
I don't want to.
I won't go to prison.
Thinking about how I lived
brings me to tears.
Do you still want me to waste
my life in prison?
Now, I want to live like a person.
Like our Kyeong Ran said,
the rest of my life is for me.
I want to do the things that I wish to do,
and to live thinking about myself.
Don't feel sorry.
Right now,
I'm really really peaceful.
During this period of time,
I've been really tired,
I want to rest now.
I met, the person I really
wanted to see, Kyeong Ran,
and I undid the knots in my heart.
Now, there's nothing left to hold on to.
Mum, Dad,
you must be really happy to see me, right?
At this moment,
I suddenly really want to see Ahn Jae Sung.
The man I really loved,
should be Ahn Jae Sung.
I've never told him this.
Please tell him,
I'm sorry.
Also,
if you find anything useful in my body,
give it to someone who needs help.
The main suspect in the murder of
Madam Jo at Pyeong Chang Do,
Ms. Joo's body, has been found
by someone this early morning.
The police suspect that
the main suspect, Ms. Joo,
had a personal grudge against Madam Jo,
and tampered with the brake on
Madam Jo's car, killing Madam Jo.
[Deceased: Joo Ah Ran]
I can't understand.
How Unni,
would do something like that to Madam.
Stop thinking about it.
Be it Mum,
or Ah Ran,
they've gone to somewhere peaceful.
At that place,
both of them are innocent.
She told Director that
at the community center,
she wanted to live out her life,
as a volunteer.
Then, I don't understand,
why Unni would do something like that.
Since she already made such a decision,
why could she not forgive
Madam till the end,
and live diligently till the end.
If I knew this was going to happen,
I should have let Ah Ran and Joo Seung
leave at the beginning.
Why was I,
so insistent on my revenge?
Unni.
Go well.
In our next lives,
be my Unni again.
Then...
let's not separate,
and not hate each other,
and not fight.
Ah Ran,
didn't want me to tell you
for the time being.
The death report.
Why would Unni file a death
report for Joo Kyeong Ran?
She wanted you to live under
the name of Yun Jae Hee in the future.
So in that case, there would
be no problem if you wanted
to marry Teacher Shin.
What?
What does that mean?
Mother asked to look at the brake?
She came to our auto club,
and asked to take apart the brake.
Then, everything was fine,
and the accident happened.
Could it be...
Joo Seung.
Every year when I received
a birthday present from you,
I shamelessly anticipated it, and was happy.
There wasn't one I didn't like.
The pearl necklace you sent me,
the scarf,
the blouse.
They were all so precious,
thank you very much.
All the crimes I committed,
I'll take them away.
Forgive, the Mum that only left you pain.
But in this last moment before I leave,
I've never regretted giving birth to you.
Father, Hyung and younger brother,
are the last presents I leave for you.
Then,
Mum...
She...
Ah Ran...
1 year later
Unni.
Have you been well?
You haven't been cold, right?
I know you miss me,
so I brought a photograph.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
Yes, Ahjussi.
No,
what about you, President?
I've been really busy, I have no energy.
Occasionally, I see the news in the papers,
congratulations on your big expansion in SM.
Madam, today is her death
anniversary, right?
Yes.
You don't know the news
about Joo Seung, right?
He seems like he's still travelling around.
Once in a while, he sends a postcard
so I won't forget him.
I told him he had to come home
for Mum's death anniversary,
I don't know.
Losing the two people he loved
the most in one day,
that pain, won't disappear so easily.
Right.
I applied for the name,
Joo Kyeong Ran.
Is that so?
Good job.
Then, I'm going to leave.
Director is sick.
I have to cook for the children.
Like a snowflake floating towards you,
don't hesitate, don't stop.
Don't hide.
I want to float into your arms,
and become part of a snowdrift,
an everlasting snowdrift.
There,
are the two people I occasionally protect,
One is my wife.
One is my mother's son.
One person is dead,
one person is tragic.
But why am I not happy right now?
If I had handed the crimes
of those two people to God,
would our lives be different?
Joo Ah Ran,
you've won.
Because, the last person who cut
off the tail of your revenge was me.
My mother's crimes,
for forgiving them before you left,
thank you.