Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 16
Joo Ah Ran, right?
I'm the police.
Let's take a trip to the station.
What is the matter?
October 13,the traffic accident
that took place on Chang Won Street,
here is the statement for the real criminal,
Joo Ah Ran.
Who wrote this?
Shin Hyun Woo this.
Shin Hyun Woo.
That's ridiculous.
How could a dead person write a statement.
Let's talk about it in the station.
Come to the police station immediately.
The police came to look for
me all of a sudden,
with Shin Hyun Woo's statement, saying that
I was the perpetrator of the traffic accident.
I'll go now.
Try and delay some time.
Don't panic,
and speak as little as possible.
Shin Hyun Woo...
your real intentions are finally revealed.
It's me, Jae Sung.
Are you busy?
I have to reserve plane tickets.
Where are you?
I have something on, I'm far away.
I'll call you when it's done.
My husband is dead.
Someone must be using my
husband's name to play a trick.
The death certificate hasn't been issued,
how can he be dead?
The fingerprint on the statement,
has been verified as Shin Hyun Woo's.
If Shin Hyun Woo is alive,
then call him to come here.
If not,
we can't cooperate with this investigation.
That's right.
When my husband met with an accident,
I wasn't even there.
If it's true...
I want to confront Shin Hyun Woo.
And then,
I'll accept my punishment willingly.
Episode 16
Really...
really,
Shin Hyun Woo is alive?
The words on the statement,
is definitely Shin Hyun Woo's.
Even if he's alive, we don't have to worry.
We already know the intentions
and plans of the other side,
and we definitely won't suffer easily.
How was the search for the plastic
surgery results at the medical insurance company?
I'm about to go now.
Get up.
Because of the rule against
personal information,
we cannot make personal
medical information public.
Hold on.
If Shin Hyun Woo is alive...
he must have carried out bank transactions.
We have to look into the banking transactions
that Shin Hyun woo made after the fire.
It wasn't even him,
what's there to look into?
Only one side can win.
Let's go look for the police...
and prove that my husband disappeared
in his vegetative state, to seek help.
Then, we'll find the bank
that cooperated with Shin Hyun Woo,
and look at the CCTV,
it should have Shin Hyun Woo's face on it.
It's Ahn Jae Sung!
How can that be?
Then...
Nothing has changed.
We just have to do as we planned,
organize everything and get out of here.
Ahn Jae Sung goes back to being
Shin Hyun Woo,
and before he reveals everything,
we have to be on a plane, no matter what.
Why are you in a daze?
Are you that disappointed
that Ahn Jae Sung is Shin Hyun Woo?
Did you really...
fall in love with him?
No.
- I just can't accept what I've been through.
- Don't think about it.
He just returned the favor.
Today, I'll take care of
the hospital and the apartment.
You do the same thing.
I know.
He camouflaged himself
so perfectly as Ahn Jae Sung,
yet, he got still hilariously
got caught by the CCTV,
if it wasn't for revenge,
would he have changed his face?
When he found out that we left,
he would wail and cry to the heavens,
wouldn't he.
Heaven is on our side.
What happened?
The fact that Ahjussi is Shin Hyun Woo,
have they found out?
If the two of them leave,
won't Ahjussi's revenge end?
He's waiting so long, enduring so much.
Please arrange the seats a little closer.
Yes, I know.
So the guests can look forward
a little easier.
Please change the lights.
It's me, Ah Ran.
I'm looking at the wedding hall.
In order to welcome the most
beautiful bride,
I can't be sloppy.
I have something to say,
let's meet.
I'll call you once I'm there.
Yoon Jae Hee.
You knew everything right
from the beginning,
and you were planning to fool me?
I have nothing,
that I can say to Madam anymore.
Don't toy with me.
If I have a crime to shoulder,
God will give it to me.
Who are you to meddle between
a husband and wife?
Husband and wife?
Since when were you husband
and wife with Shin Hyun Woo?
If you were really husband and wife...
would you lock your husband in
a countryside villa that had no doctors?
If you were really husband and wife...
would you be intimate with another
mean while your husband was fighting for his life?
Now you're unbosoming yourself.
So, the Shin Hyun Woo that couldn't take it,
you wanted to help him?
From that guy's vegetative state
to his plastic surgery, you wanted to help him?
Then,
that man would become yours?
I heard,
you're getting married to President Ahn.
The beautiful bride's mouth
is a little uncouth, isn't it.
This time,
please, don't betray President Ahn.
Ahn Jae Sung.
Yoon Jae Hee.
You actually made me become this pathetic.
Manager, what are you doing?
If Hyung comes back, I want to
change all the furniture in Hyung's house.
Hyungsoo is out too, in order to forget
the nightmare, I want to change it all.
After she moved out,
what is Ah Ran doing?
There's nowhere she can go.
How can there be nowhere for her to go?
She probably went to the house
of the man she's crazily in love with.
But,
what has Yeon Jae been doing?
I've been decorating the newlyweds' section.
A new house, just like the newlyweds,
I tried to decorate it.
How is it?
Is it childish?
No.
It's warm and touching, it's good.
Just like Yeon Jae.
Really, really, really, really.
That...
Should we...
lie down and try it out?
We have to know how comfortable
it is before we introduce it to our customers.
Yeon Jae,
what should we do if customers come?
Hyun Min, it's been a while
since we laid down together.
Ahjussi, it's good.
Hug me.
Hug me tighter!
You're really humorous,
and cute and charming.
Why are you so cute, witty and lovable?
I really want to put you in a gourd,
and take you out every day.
You probably couldn't fit me into a gourd.
Yes, Father?
Father,
what do you mean?
The MyeongSung investment is fake.
This is a fax that just came
from MyeongSung.
The intention that they had to invest in Soul,
there isn't any in the future.
I was fooled again by that fox.
After we uncovered her job at the bar...
she tried various ways and means to get by.
After she got some time, I don't
know what else she was planning to do with Soul.
Secretary Kang.
Get me Joo Ah Ran's sales report.
Yes, President.
This definitely is fake too.
She must have withdrawn
all the investment in Soul...
and then pulled her tricks.
Everyone work up some energy...
and thoroughly verify the sales
reports from all the different showrooms.
Yes, Father.
Secretary Kang.
You're here.
I wanted to eat lunch with you,
so I was waiting.
We have to book the plane tickets, right?
Could you give me your passport?
My friend works at a travel agency,
I'll book the plane tickets.
I've already asked someone to do it.
Don't worry,
you just have to show up at
the airport on time.
Hold on.
It must be Shin Hyun Woo.
There can't be a passport
with Ahn Jae Sung's name on it.
How did he survive?
Was he not at the villa during the fire?
But why didn't he come back?
Who did he want to drive insane,
that he pulled these tricks?
It's a good shot, right?
The last time we went to the park,
I took it,
and I put it here to look
at it every time I thought of you.
I'm hungry,
let's hurry and go.
Yoon Jae Hee.
Don't misunderstand.
The other time Jae Hee brought it,
and it wasn't nice to throw it away,
so I left it.
This photograph has no other meaning.
Do you expect me to believe that right now?
Your love, sometimes there are two,
sometimes there are three.
I can't believe this kind of man,
and fly to America.
Let's break up.
What did you say?
We've even booked the wedding hall.
Now, you want to cancel the wedding?
The person who betrayed our trust first wasn't me,
but Jae Sung.
Let's not talk about anything else,
but I can't start with a man
who thinks about other women in his heart.
You won't regret this?
A woman who leaves once,
I'm not a man that will chase after her.
Of course.
Our destiny ends here.
Let's not meet till the day we die.
Ah Ran!
Shin Hyun Woo is back.
The person who was always
by my side was Shin Hyun Woo.
I have to get away quickly.
Once that man opens his mouth,
it's all over.
Joo Seung, it's me.
About us leaving, hurry.
It's too scary,
I don't even want to stay another day.
Our son, Hyun Woo,
disappeared during the fire,
he must be living somewhere now,
so I came to look for help.
I was just about to look for Shin
Hyun Woo's family, good thing you came.
Actually, yesterday...
a statement about the traffic
accident at Chang Won...
came from Shin Hyun Woo.
What?
From our Hyun Woo?
The statement says that,
at the time of the accident,
the driver was Joo Ah Ran
and said that she ran away
after the accident.
Then, our Hyun Woo...
Can you contact him?
Where is Hyun Woo?
Where can I go to see him?
Please tell me, Officer.
The phone number didn't show up.
I contacted him,
and told him to show up before 3.
During this period of time,
we'll ask Joo Ah Ran here as well.
Then,
you're saying that at 3,
our Hyun Woo will be here?
Hello?
Yes,
I'm Joo Ah Ran.
What?
To have a confrontation with Shin Hyun Woo?
Shin Hyun Woo is going to
the police station?
It's me.
Don't be nervous.
No matter what, face it calmly.
Hyun Woo Hyung is not showing up.
No, he can't show up.
If he wanted to use the law
from the beginning,
he wouldn't return in Ahn Jae Sung's skin.
Furthermore,
there is no evidence...
the police can't do anything to you.
Joo Ah Ran one-sidedly called
off the wedding?
Even though she gave me a different reason,
but, I feel like she's found
out my identity.
You mean she knows that
President Ahn is her ex-husband?
That's big.
We haven't received all the assets that
are under Joo Ah Ran's name, it can't end here.
If she knows I'm Shin Hyun Woo,
there will be no way to capture her heart.
No matter what, she'll find a way to escape.
If tonight, Joo Ah Ran and
Nam Joo Seung leaves tonight...
our game is over.
No!
We definitely cannot give up.
In front of Sang Mo's altar,
I promised to dispel any remaining
hate he had.
Because I believed you,
I made it here.
No matter what happens, don't disappoint me.
Now, at the police station,
they're waiting for me to
confront Joo Ah Ran.
If I don't appear...
then, it's equivalent to putting
wings on someone who's about to escape,
as well as confirm the belief,
that Shin Hyun Woo is Ahn Jae Sung.
Looks like the confrontation has
to be postponed.
That's why I said...
it looks like someone is playing a trick.
That fake statement,
please remember that it has no legal implications.
No!
It's definitely a statement
that our Hyun Woo sent.
If that's the case,
why hasn't he appeared by now?
There are two reasons.
One is that the contents
of the statement are fake.
Or, the fact that he's alive is a lie.
My son is alive!
He won't die from that little burn.
Are you more comfortable thinking that way?
A son that's dead and can't come back,
or a son that's not dead and can't come back,
what's the difference?
Tell me!
Did you hide Hyun Woo?
If not, Hyun Woo does not have
a reason to hide.
What did you do to Hyun Woo?
The traffic accident, the fire at the villa,
it was all done by you!
Before I reply,
Mum has to explain herself.
Nothing else is needed.
Tell me!
Where is Joo Kyeong Ran?
What?
Joo Kyeong Ran?
Where did you leave that child?
Tell me!
You have to tell me.
I don't know where you heard that from,
but that has nothing to do with you.
Who says it has nothing to do with me?
What?
Did you leave that child at the
Angel Orphanage?
What did you do to that poor child?
For someone who is so cold
to even the own son that she birthed,
would you look at someone else's child?
How cruel Mother is as a person,
Mother knows best!
What are you doing?
You have no reason to know!
Bring Kyeong Ran here.
If something happens to that child,
I'll never forgive you.
Not just Shin Hyun Woo,
I won't let the rest of your children off!
Are you fine?
Oh, I'm fine.
Let's just go.
How does Ah Ran know about Kyeong Ran?
Joo Ah Ran,
Joo Kyeong Ran...
it can't be?
President, we've found out where the restaurant
that Joo Chul Ming's brother is at right now.
Is that so?
Toad like creatures.
This time we can never let them go.
Call the restaurant,
and tell them to lock it up!
Lead the way.
I might as well just
pull my teeth out with pliers.
Eating soup and rice, what good is my teeth.
I still have to brush them in the morning,
how annoying.
Then just go pull them all out.
As you grow older,
people should be more sensible.
The money hasn't even fallen
from the sky yet,
and you want to eat galbi that much...
Where are the people?!
Is it this restaurant?
How did they find us here?
Shut up and let's run away!
What should we do now?!
Looks like you got some courage.
You think by threatening me,
I would take out even 10 dollars?
Secretary Kang.
Call the police immediately.
Wait...
what crime did we commit,
that you have to call the police?
That... Your wife was the
one who took away our Kyeong Ran,
will the police leave it alone?
So,
hurry and give us our Kyeong Ran!
Who took who away?
Do you want to get arrested
for threatening and blackmailing me?
That...President,
we are really wronged.
That is.. President, your wife,
took my dead brother's daughter,
and she's hiding her and not
giving her back.
Can we just stand on the sidelines?
What, daughter?
What is the matter?
Who is Ah Ran?
Who are her parents?
You know, right?
I don't know.
I've never met them.
Are Ah Ran's parents still alive?
I heard they died on the
same day when she was young.
They died on the same day?
Why?
Is it someone you know?
No.
Then, go home safely.
Ah Ran... how could it be?
It can't be.
That's ridiculous.
You tell me honestly.
What happened to Joo Chul Ming's daughter?
Honey...
That family said,
you took their daughter away.
- What does that mean?
- It's not that!
It was really sad for her to lose both
her parents, so I just helped a little. Really.
You helped them?
Are you crazy?
It's fine that we gave them
so much compensation.
All my hard-earned money...
what charitable heart was that?
Hurry and tell that family,
where their daughter is,
and chase those leeches away, immediately!
I really don't know.
I helped after the accident,
but I haven't heard anything after that.
Those words are true right?
Then, if those fellows hang around our door,
call the police.
I don't ever want to hear the
name of the annoying Joo Chul Ming again!
I know.
Ah Ran.
Let's meet.
I have something to say.
Ah Ran.
Ah Ran!
Looks like our destiny ends here.
Let's not meet till the day we die.
Because I believed you,
I've come this far.
No matter what, don't disappoint me.
I hoped that Ahjussi and
Joo Ah Ran wouldn't get married...
that would be a good thing for me.
But why...
am I not happy at all?
Looking at Ahjussi’s sadness...
my heart hurts so much it's
going to explode.
Ahjussi!
What's wrong?
Where does it hurt?
Ahjussi!
Don't look at me,
don't look at me!
I don't want you to see me this way...
go home!
Ahjussi,
must you definitely carry out that revenge?
If I can't fill Ahjussi up with my love,
if there's only that way,
I lose.
Marry Joo Ah Ran.
Even if you can't return to my side...
I will let Ahjussi go too.
With me...
Marry me.
Your sister...
even if you don't show up,
we can use someone to find her.
If she's living somewhere,
we'll find her.
No.
I must see Kyeong Ran with
my own eyes before I leave.
There's no time.
Just now, Madam came,
and asked about your parents.
Whose daughter you are,
they could probably guess.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Everything will be fine
as long as I find Kyeong Ran.
We have to go to the showroom
to take a look.
There are documents I have to take care of.
Is this Doctor Nam's apartment?
The lights are turned
on in the apartment right now.
It seems she hasn't left yet.
She transferred the hospital today,
it seems she's about to leave.
Before that, you have to hand all
the evidence to the police.
Are you done with your treatment?
I'm going to the hospital right now.
What?
Shin Hyun Woo is in the hospital right now?
Shin Hyun Woo!
That was clearly Shin Hyun Woo.
With a burn scar even.
That was definitely Shin Hyun Woo,
no mistake.
Not Ahn Jae Sung.
I can't be completely sure.
Shin Hyun Woo was sitting next to her.
Just like at the villa,
it might be a model of Shin Hyun Woo.
I have to be careful.
Is this Korea Hospital?
I just wanted to check...
was there a patient by the name
of Shin Hyun Woo?
He just left after being treated for burns?
I understand.
Then...
is it really Shin Hyun Woo?
Ah Ran.
When have you been home since?
Just now... Did you go out?
No.
I came home really early,
I've been home since.
The last time of entry, 6.20 p.m.
Then...
just now, that person was
really Shin Hyun Woo.
Why?
Is something the matter?
Just sit down first,
you don't look so well,
I'll make you a hot cup of tea.
That's right.
He has identification cards and a passport,
he can't be Shin Hyun Woo.
Jae Sung.
I'm sorry.
I must have been crazy.
I actually didn't believe you.
What kind of person are you to me?
Forgive me.
I'll do anything to appease your anger.
So...
you saw me being captured on the CCTV,
and came to the conclusion
that I was Shin Hyun Woo.
The two of you went on the same
day to the same bank, isn't that strange?
That bank is close to our company,
so I'm a VIP there.
I was too impulsive,
and I didn't think too much,
I'm really sorry.
Thinking about the fact that
Ah Ran doesn't trust me up till now,
it hurts me.
The reason why you can't trust me,
is my fault.
We'll hold the wedding as planned,
and then go together to America.
The company matters are almost settled,
and I have nothing to hold on to here.
The reason for your sudden rush,
is it because of your ex-husband?
Is there a reason Shin
Hyun Woo shouldn't be alive?
That man...
won't quietly let me go.
Even though we're in the
process of getting a divorce,
he'll grab me by my ankles,
and get in the way of my future happiness.
From now on...
I want to be happy as the woman of one man.
Just like other people,
to fight as a couple over something small,
to birth a baby that looks like you,
and have him call me mum,
to go to the amusement park,
to have water fights,
in a garden that has a
sign with our last name on it,
I want to live like that.
If I could be greedy for things like that,
please don't abandon me.
Now, the life that you're dreaming of,
is the married life, that I dreamt of once.
Even though I was trampled on by one woman.
Since it's a choice between life and death...
you have to be happy.
I only want one thing.
No matter who you're with...
as long as Ahjussi is content.
I'm happy too.
Don't wait for me, go sleep first.
There's a lot to organize,
I'll sleep at the showroom tonight.
See you tomorrow.
Joo Ah Ran,
it's been a long time.
Have you been well?
I came to this earth to see you now.
I'm looking forward to seeing you.
From, the Romeo who had his heart stolen.
The Romeo who had his heart stolen...
That was the nickname that
only I and Shin Hyun Woo knew.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Who let you in?
We inspected closely,
there's nothing special in particular.
However, there is quite a bit of male clothing,
and medicine to treat burns.
Is that so?
I get it.
Go out first.
For a place where a girl stays by herself,
there's quite a lot of male clothing.
Antiseptic, sedatives,
what are these?
Hurry and get out.
This is my house.
You're still lying to me till the end.
You've been hiding Shin Hyun Woo,
and giving him treatment?
I have to go to work,
please let me through.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You took Shin Hyun Woo from the hospital.
Where did you hide him,
what tricks are you trying to play?
Now you know.
That's right.
I love Shin Hyun Woo.
The person I love isn't President Ahn,
it's Shin Hyun Woo.
Is that so?
To hide Shin Hyun Woo...
all this time, you've been pretending
to be in love with President Ahn?
Anyway, he's not a man you loved.
What's wrong if I love him?
Betrayed by his wife,
a car accident,
and a fire,
that person's body and mind
are already riddled with bullet holes.
If I love him,
and care for him, what's so wrong with that?
If you like Shin Hyun Woo that much,
then the two of you should run away,
and live quietly like dead people.
Why did you come back?
Why do you want to force people
to their death?
Are you that scared?
Now, kneel in front of
that person and beg for mercy,
sincerely repent,
and say you were sincerely
accept the punishments for your sins!
I don't have any thoughts of
begging for forgiveness from that person.
My wounds are still being ripped apart...
what does that person's pain
have to do with me?
The way you look,
arrogant because you saved someone's life...
there won't be a second time.
God is fair.
Ahjussi...
I'm fine.
I'm actually feeling refreshed.
In front of Joo Ah Ran,
I could even say I like Ahjussi out loud.
It was good.
President!
Something big has happened!
President has sent an auditor,
to redo the last 6 months of sale figures.
The sales section and the invoice
section has to be investigated.
What?
Did people in the two sections
spout nonsense?
No.
No one said anything to anyone.
I understand.
Go and work.
That old fox might have suspected
something again.
If Soul is not snatched away,
I can only transfer all
my assets to Jae Sung's name.
No...
Care makes everything go smoothly.
Before that, I have to verify something.
If Jae Hee didn't help...
all my plans would have been ruined.
It's all because of
Ahjussi’s model of Shin Hyun Woo.
As planned, Joo Ah Ran even
called the Korea Hospital to verify it.
Luckily I asked a nurse I knew,
if not, we would have been in trouble.
Thank you.
Although it's hard, you understand me.
Please don't say that,
I'm actually sorry.
Even though I know how Ahjussi
got to this step...
I was like a child, and only wanted
you to look at me, and throwing a tantrum.
What I really wanted,
wasn't Soul Furniture, a house, or assets,
and even though I know that damning Ah Ran,
won't change my life at all.
But...
I just want to comfort my broken spirit.
To say, you did the right thing,
it wasn't you fault.
If not...
I'm afraid I won't have hope
to continue living.
Wait and see...
the days when the bandages are taken off
Ahjussi’s heart, those days will definitely come.
Oh, right.
What happened with the CCTV
that captured Ahjussi’s face?
I'm sorry,
but could I take a look
at the CCTV I saw yesterday?
That's right.
Shin Hyun Woo and Ahn Jae
Sung are two different people.
No matter how god-like
Shin Hyun Woo's hands are,
he can't create a person who
breathes and walks.
Ah Ran, it's me.
Right now?
Is it really alright?
We aren't even married yet...
transferring all the assets under
your name to mine, will make you uneasy.
If you're not happy, let's not do it.
No.
If we don't do this...
all of Soul's assets will
be stolen away by my in-laws.
You don't know how greedy my
father-in-law is.
Then, in that case...
transferring the ownership of Pyeong Chang Dong,
and all of your brother-in-law's showrooms too,
isn't that a little too much?
No matter what, you used to be a family too.
Those people...
don't have the right to enjoy those assets.
Sucking people's blood
dry in order to get that wealth,
of course they have to lose it this way.
Alright.
Then...
the stock that I received from
President Joo,
I'll give to President Ahn.
You've even transferred SM Furniture,
what use is there if I keep it?
Thank you, Julie Jung.
What's there to be thankful for?
Just treat it as compensation
for my brother Sang Mo's crimes.
Lawyer Lee,
the transfer documents,
please don't make any mistakes,
and handle it detailed.
Yes.
For documents of these standard,
even if President Shin Woo Sub
files a lawsuit,
there will be no problem legally.
Is Ah Ran really Joo Chul Ming's daughter?
If she's that person's daughter,
what else could she know?
If she knew everything,
and married into our family...
That's a really happy family photo isn't it?
You...
That happiness,
who destroyed it?
Who is the person who killed Mum and Dad?
Was it Father-in-law?
Of course Mother-in-law
wouldn't know either.
All...
Do you know all of it?
Is that why you got close to our Hyun Woo?
- Is that so?
- That's right.
That was the case.
Then,
for the death of your parents...
you caused the death of our Hyun Woo?
The traffic accident,
the fire at the villa, was that all planned?
At first, I didn't plan to kill Hyun Woo...
but, I couldn't die because of Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo dug his own grave.
If you hated us,
you should have killed us...
why did you touch my son?!
Because, I wanted to take away
what was most precious to your family.
You want me to find your sister, right?
Alright.
Then, bring my son first.
Don't bargain with my sister.
She's a poor child who doesn't
know anything.
Where's my sister?
If you have a shred of conscience,
give me my sister.
Before you find my son,
don't even think about getting anything!
Now, I'll go to the police station, and tell them
you're the real culprit of the traffic accident.
Then, find our Hyun Woo.
As long as you get your retribution,
I'll take my own payback!
No!
I'm about to leave with Jae Sung.
I can't be caught by the police.
It's me, Joo Seung.
Something big has happened.
Persuade Mother,
Mother is on her way to the police station,
she says she wants to tell them everything
about the traffic accident and the arson!
What?!
I just want to be happy with you now.
In order to get happiness for Dad and Mum,
I can't even live,
expressing my love for you.
Now, happiness is right in front of us,
we can't give up halfway.
Didn't I promise you?
I'll protect you till the end,
and give you happiness.
I'll meet Madam.
You wait.
If you're trying to help Ah Ran,
go back.
I don't want to hear anything.
What are you doing right now?
Get up immediately.
Although you've never treated me like a son,
this is the first time,
and the last time,
I'm begging you as a son.
Ah Ran's crimes,
help me cover them.
I can't do that.
It's not because of Ah Ran,
at least once in my life,
I could be Madam's son
Just once!
For me...
Hyun Woos' grievances,
you could keep an eye shut.
For the son that was born illegitimately...
is that a request that's too much too?
This is not a crime that can be covered up.
If we don't investigate Ah Ran's crimes...
Hyun Woo could never appear
in front of us again!
This photograph...
to me...
is the only family photo I have.
Although Madam denies it,
but to me,
you're my mother.
I...
love AH Ran very much.
Even though the whole world
points and stares...
the heart that loves Ah Ran,
is bright and true.
Together with Ah Ran...
I want to build a new family,
and live together..
with no empty spaces as parents,
I want to live with the woman I love.
Is that impossible?
Hyun Woo Hyung is alive.
He's not far away.
I...
will send him to Madam's side.
I promise.
Where's our Hyun Woo?
You know it?
Madam won't make things
hard for you anymore,
don't worry.
Even if that's the case,
you're still her son.
Once her heart softens, she loses to you.
I only got you some time temporarily.
There are no secrets forever.
Let's go to a new country
and forget the past,
start anew.
Just like we've never been hurt before,
and then,
fall in love all over again.
Joo Seung.
There isn't much time left
to spend with Joo Seung either.
Joo Seung, for loving such
a woman like me, thank you.
I will occasionally think about you.
What are you doing?
It's so dark,
yet you don't turn on the lights.
Mum, you put up the Christmas tree so early?
Honey...
our Hyun Woo was here.
It must be our Hyun Woo.
Look at the paper doll,
that's Hyun Woo's art.
Is it real?
This tree,
did Hyun Woo Oppa make it before leaving?
Yes.
Oppa is still alive, and is thinking of us,
that's why he came secretly.
He hasn't forgotten us.
Hyun Woo, this kid.
He's clearly by our side,
yet he's not returning.
It must be for something serious.
President, something big has happened.
What is it?
According to your instructions, we
inspected the showrooms of your daughter-in-law.
We found these documents.
What is this?
The transfer documents for Soul Furniture.
Who's transferring Soul Furniture?!
Hyun Woo's stocks,
and the house at Pyeong Chang Dong,
and Hyun Min's showrooms.
How can that be?!
What is it?
Maybe Father-in-law knows that
I've transferred my assets over to Jae Sung.
Looks like...
I'll have to stay here tonight.
Let's just do that.
If possible,
you can stay here before the wedding.
Really?
Anyway, I don't have to go to
the company anymore...
so I'll just stay here,
and prepare for the wedding.
But...
when are your parents and
siblings coming from America?
The wedding is tomorrow.
On the day of the wedding,
I think they'll go straight to the church.
They don't seem t be very free,
because of their work.
So, they can only greet you in the church.
What a miracle.
If people say the same thing with
the same mouth,
it might come true.
Who knew I would live in America.
I'm so touched...
and I'm anticipating,
our new married life.
Jae Sung really...
When did he put this here?
The Juliet that steals heart.
You're leaving without even seeing me?
Wait a little longer.
We'll meet again.
I really want to see how
you look in a wedding dress.
It clearly says...
the only I crime I have,
is that I tried very hard to run the company.
I'm sorry that things turned out this way.
Don't lie.
The two of you planned
to take over the company, right?
You're looking at the wrong person.
Is that how you do business?
You use the resort as an excuse
to get closer,
and what have you prepared for this thing?
I, only used legitimate methods
to take over Soul and the house.
Here
These are the details of my
investment in Soul.
This is ridiculous.
Toads,
also go toward the light.
How could you take the entirety
of someone else's assets,
and take it over in one morning?
Return me my company!
I can never give you my company.
Before my son comes back,
he has to die in that house!
Dad, are you alright?
Dad, calm down!
You should send him to the hospital.
As your request...
if you want to leave with Joo Seung,
do that.
What a charitable act.
But...
give the house,
and Hyun Min's showrooms back to us.
No.
The house, the company,
the showrooms...
I can't return you a single one.
A family built on blood, will
end with blood.
The crime of trampling on our
family for money...
you have to pay it back with money.
That's fair, don't you think?
Do you know what it is like,
living on the streets because we had no money,
that lonely and pathetic life?!
It cuts to the bone, doesn't it.
If you hand over our Kyeong Ran...
I might consider returning you the house.
The Shin Woo Sub who only
graduated from elementary school,
fought for money to buy this house.
Dad, after I'm married, I want to
stay with my wife and children in this house.
How can that be?
I want to stay here with my children too!
Then, isn't it alright if we
all stay together?
Should we build another floor?
Director.
I'm Hyun Woo's mother.
Kyeong Ran...
No,
Jae Hee...
Her sister wants to see her.
Can you contact her for me?
Hello.
Mother.
Hello,
this is...
Mother..
I'm Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo?
Are you really Hyun Woo?
Yes, Mother.
It's Hyun Woo.
In the end, you want to kill me right?
If the law,
the world is all on Father-in-law's side,
I will trample this world.
I'm so happy, yet I keep shedding tears.
I'm so in love with you.
What kind of betrayal that was,
I will let you feel it in your bones.
Marrying Joo Ah Ran,
does that make sense?
Is that what Ah Ran really is?
Where is Shin Hyun Woo!
Come out immediately!
Don't meddle in other people's business.
Don't show your face again!
Joo Ah Ran,
did you really kill Shin Hyun Woo?
It's all a lie!