Temptation Of An Angel
Episode 15
Ah Ran.
Marry me.
Even if you approached me
because of my money,
it doesn't matter.
Use me, need me.
Everyone says love is
selfish anyways.
I've married before.
Even if I have problems
with my husband's family.
It doesn't matter?
You don't know anything about my past.
For you, what I want to
know isn't your past.
It's how much you love me now.
I don't care if you're whoever's
daughter-in-law, whoever's lover.
If it's Joo Ah Ran,
I'm confident in loving
you until the end.
Why did you come? I'll listen to
the important things first.
Episode 15
Once Ah Ran arrives, I'll speak.
Ah Ran's like this, Doctor Nam's like this.
If we have nothing to
listen to, please leave.
No, you have to listen.
Until now, I've been following you.
From this moment on,
however I want it done,
it'll be done that way.
What is this attitude?
You want to separate from us starting now?
Is there anyone in the world that acts
friendly with people they hate?
I'm not like a pig that would blindly seek
approval from a hateful master.
There's no reason to endure
Madam's type of treatment.
You scary person. Who do you
dare talk to like that?
Even if it's like this,
I treated you like my own son.
If I was really your son,
you wouldn't remember and mention every little
thing you've done for me over the years.
What?
I don't want to be treated
like Hyun Woo Hyung.
I was never once this family's son.
Even when I ate warm rice,
it always caught in my throat.
And because of the cold stares on my back,
I was never once comfortable here.
To President, I'm only Secretary Nam's son.
To Madam, I'm an annoying person's guest.
Then.
Mom... Dad...
Help me.
Even if it's leaving through
the back door with the king,
don't let Ahjussi leave me.
I lived not asking for anything else.
Help me grant my wish.
I mentioned you to my parents in America.
At first they only thought their son only
did business and didn't want to marry.
After I said I love a woman,
they're busy getting ready.
Have a wedding ceremony in Korea,
then go to America to expand my business.
It's so tiring.
With Jae Sung by my side,
I feel really fortunate.
I'll arrange my things quickly,
I'll have to go.
I'm not confident in waiting that long.
Right, it's not much,
I prepared a present.
Open it when you get home.
You're still here? You're a lot
more stubborn than I thought.
Woman like you also has a true heart?
Are you not afraid of the sky?
Carrying too many crimes,
how will you go to hell?
Got pushed away by Jae Sung, looks like
you're releasing your anger on me.
My good mood today,
I don't want you to ruin it.
Today, to me and Jae Sung,
is a special day.
You can only live like this?
You have so much, and you
have a man who loves you.
Why's your heart so poor and twisted?
President Nam is also your object
that you used to abandon?
Love in the end is a game.
After you lose the game,
just admit that you lost,
then you wouldn't be sad.
If you feel so sorry for President Nam,
pick him up and use him.
You're a person who speaks with no value,
you don't seem like a woman.
This time I've hated you.
But today I feel bad for you.
You let your mom in pain after giving
birth to you, just to live like this?
You're a pitiful person.
Why did you come here?
Why is it so difficult to contact you?
Did you go to Doctor Jun's?
Yes, but.
Then you should know
Hyun Woo Hyung is still alive.
Now you have no other choice.
Plane ticket for a week after.
Arrange everything and leave this place.
The faster the better.
Now you're letting me go
with you to a foreign country?
Madam's actions are abnormal.
Our actions being found
out is a time's problem.
You'll leave with me, right?
If you reject,
then find President with these
photos, and tell the truth.
Are you threatening me now?
Choose.
Stay here trapped with crimes,
or leave and start a new life.?
I don't care which side.
As long as I'm with you, I don't care.
Arranging the business isn't hard,
but we need to find Kyeong Ran.
There's almost an answer.
Give me some time.
Then, stay at my apartment from now on.
This place is too dangerous.
No, Mom knows Kyeong Ran's traces.
After my parent's incident, she
seems to have taken Kyeong Ran.
We have to find her no matter what.
Okay. Take care of your
health. Get her tight.
This, what ring is this?
Never seen it.
It was pretty, so I bought it.
Hurry and go. Someone might
come out of the house.
Tomorrow in the cafe in front of the community
cafeteria, if you don't bring Kyeong Ran out,
then I'll bring the police officers in
your house then see what you'll do.
At first I wanted to make the present
better, but you found out.
Because I thought of Ah Ran
while making it,
be happy and receive it.
I love you. Jae Sung.
Marry me.
Plane ticket for a week after.
Arrange everything and leave this place.
That's right.
I won't let Joo Seung know. Leave this
place silently and it'll be okay.
The real love comes now,
it can't be blocked.
Mom, Mom, why are you in my room?
Scary person, are you still considered a human?
What is this for?
The world's witches aren't like you.
Scary, tricky, dirty.
One Hyun Woo isn't enough,
so you pulled out a Joo Seung.
Then you want to make Joo Seung cry?
What is your motive?
Who exactly are you?
Who am I?
I'm your daughter-in-law.
Shin Hyun Woo's wife,
Joo Seung's lover.
Looking at it, your destiny and
my destiny is pretty deep.
Mom's son loved me.
Shut your dirty mouth.
I'm dirty?
Then what is this?
Lying to Dad,
giving birth to a son of Dad's secretary.
What qualifications do you have to blame me?
Everyone in the world can throw stones at me.
Only one person, only you can't do that.
Right, I deserve to die,
but your crime won't fade.
What did you do to Hyun Woo?
Tell me, tell me quickly.
If you want to know, check yourself.
If not, tell Dad. Ask for help.
So, Joo Seung will be safe, right?
Using Joo Seung as your captive
to cover your crime. Right?
So you're using Joo Seung?
You know why I became this
family's daughter-in-law?
It's Joo Seung who sent me to this family.
Because he wanted to take
revenge on you, so he used me.
Feeling innocent isn't Mom's two sons.
It's me, Joo Ah Ran, you know?
This girl, came up so late.
Why do you look so sad?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Is me seeking Ahjussi a bad thing?
I have nothing, I can't help Ahjussi anymore.
I should let him go now, right?
You girl. What's after the other?
Mr. Shin is in a very tiring state now.
You're grumbling about love?
I'm scared that he won't come back.
I trust Ahjussi, but Ahjussi's heart,
Ahjussi doesn't know himself.
If he still has feelings for his wife that he loves.
Then what should I do?
Stepping on your own life.
How can he love a woman that
turned his whole world around?
Mr. Shin isn't a rash person.
Among the children who my husband raised,
is there one named Joo Kyeong Ran?
Right, have you ever heard
the name Kyeong Ran?
Kyeong Ran? No, I don't know.
Actually, daytime.
No, what am I thinking?
Hurry and get the blankets.
Dad, Mom.
Now I can do it.
I'll come back soon.
Actually, I'm the little lantern from the
Angel Orphanage that Madam supports.
If you don't bring Kyeong Ran out,
I'll bring police to your house.
Then what will you do?
Hyun Woo Hyung died because the gas
Madam opened and let go exploded.
Like that, Madam killed two children.
Joo Seung sent me to this family.
Because he wanted to take
revenge on you, so he used me.
No, no matter what I have
to go and resolve this.
If Hyun Woo's dad finds out,
he'll kill everyone.
What? The Angel Orphanage in Paju?
My wife went there now, right?
Okay. Good work.
Aunt, it's me. Go to the place
I told you to go. Quickly.
That woman might want to hide
Kyeong Ran. Hurry and go.
What are you saying now?
Okay, I got it.
I'll go now.
Hurry and get up.
Now my shop and house are about to be taken away!
It's so early, where are you going?
So early, coming without
caring about my manners.
The child that I raised is
named Yoon Jae Hee.
Yes, yes.
That child is the nurse that
took care of my dead son.
I'll ask for you one more time,
you can't tell anyone that
I brought the child here.
Don't even tell Jae Hee anything.
I have something to ask you.
Is Jae Hee's real name Kyeong Ran?
Yes. I don't know much about the child.
Actually, your daughter-in-law
came looking for a Kyeong Ran.
My, daughter-in-law?
I said I don't know the name, and she left.
But now that I think about it,
there used to be someone
looking for Kyeong Ran.
Daughter-in-law knows about Kyeong Ran,
then who won't know this secret?
How many of my weaknesses do they know?
How did you come here?
I called a taxi.
We called a taxi because we were in the rush,
but who know the fee was so expensive.
Oh, besides us, did anyone else come here?
Is there? I didn't see anyone.
Looks like they just came.
Ahjussi.
I thought it was a woman.
Let's go wait in the office.
They will come, let go in.
Okay.
I saw you weren't home,
so I came here to try my luck.
I was worried when I came,
you look good.
You're okay?
I let you go just like that yesterday,
I didn't get any sleep at night.
Please go back. I'm on the
afternoon shift so,
I need to clean and wash the
children's clothes then I can go.
Jae Hee.
Saying I'm okay is a lie,
even if the revenge gets bigger,
you can't just take of our ring like that.
I hate myself for not trusting you.
So I won't say anything.
Jae...
The child before I think I've seen before.
What did you see? Hurry and come.
- I'm not wrong, I'm sure I've seen her.
- President, I'll go first.
Excuse me, sorry.
Can you drive me a little?
Anywhere is okay, just where
I can call a taxi will be fine.
Hello?
I want to confirm today's meeting.
You have to bring Kyeong Ran out.
Okay, please don't come to my house.
If you do, you won't see your niece.
Mom, why are you so anxious?
Who is Jae Hee?
Do you have a secret our family doesn't know?
Okay, you can let me off here.
No, since I have to go back to Seoul, I'll drive you.
It's our first time meeting, I'm so sorry.
Um, but
Where did you buy this scarf?
I have the same scarf.
It was a present.
But this scarf is for men.
It was given by my son, my eldest son.
Afraid that I was cold, worried about me.
Mom, you know?
Endure a little longer, I won't
let you cry because of me.
Really? My eyes are about to fall out.
An ant didn't even come in.
You said you will bring Kyeong Ran,
then don't worry and wait.
Okay, okay.
We're not even training a dog,
what are we doing so early in the morning?
What did Ah Ran say?
She said when she sees that
woman, she'll come herself.
Ah Ran that girl, she has
no manners towards us.
To her own sister, she's as nice as can be.
Right.
Jae Hee's Uncle is right.
Tell Jae Hee, get a hold on Madam.
A kind person like Madam, what's the matter?
What? Jang Heung Pension has 60% of the furniture
but we've collected none of the money?
How does this make sense?
They said they were unsure of
the originality of the designs,
so they are going to pay after
all the furniture is set up.
Stupid, how can you manage
business when you're so stupid.
Besides pulling money outside,
you're not good at anything else.
Right, how is Joo Chul Min's brother's wife doing?
Even though we sent people to follow,
but she keeps going from sauna room to sauna
room, so I'm having a hard time finding her.
That slippery eel... wait until I get a hold of them.
I'll teach them a lesson.
I won't let them do anything bad anymore.
Yeon Jae, it's me, Yeon Jae.
President.
After the prince saves the princess, what happens?
The princess saves the prince.
Eat this spicy rice cake.
Wake up.
It's so early in the morning,
why are you sleeping?
What?
So it was a dream. I should have
finished what I did, really.
Where did you go so early in the morning?
Jang Heung Pension.
If we go to America after we marry,
I have to arrange that.
Jae Sung is so busy, it makes me too anxious.
I saw SM furniture's President Jung,
I want to finish the talk about uniting,
so if we unite, I hope Jae Sung comes to sign.
Me?
If I use my name,
it will only leave fuse behind.
If I say I owe ROBBINS debt,
then I can't use my name to find fault.
Since we're marrying, it doesn't
matter who's name we use.
We'll follow your safe plans to work.
I will listen to you and help you.
My parents keep urging me to marry early,
they said they want to
meet Ah Ran earlier.
Okay, I'll quickly arrange
my family and the company.
Starting from now will be the real life?
I have the right to be happy.
No one can envy my happiness.
I've been exhausted for so long,
it's about time to be happy.
How is it? Did you decide?
You're a smart person.
You decided to go with Julie Jung, then Jung Sang Hwa.
I'm sure you settled things out in
a way profitable to everyone.
Yes, I just need you to follow two conditions.
Then SM furniture will be given to Soul.
Good idea. What are the two conditions?
Kneel in front of my brother
and confess with your heart.
No matter how you argue,
you playing and using my brother is the truth.
Then let's do that.
Since to me, he is a talented designer.
What's the other condition?
All the designs that Sang Mo designed,
please add his name.
Like that, he will rest in place in heaven.
That isn't hard.
Is that all the conditions?
Then tomorrow I will come
ready with a proposal, bye.
Yes, we're waiting here.
That woman still didn't come.
She just called saying she's almost here.
I already said Kyeong Ran's sister is
almost coming, hurry and come.
Earning money is hard.
Why is it so complicated?
It's a big money. All this
hard work is worth it.
Also, honestly, we don't need
to use our own money.
Where can you find this type of business?
You're right huh. In honor of getting
a furniture store let's have a drink.
Okay.
- Cheers.
Okay, I got it.
President, Joo Chul Min's brother's wife
seems to be near here.
Really? Hurry and turn back.
They still didn't come?
They said they'll be here for 10 minutes already.
What kind of woman is that unreliable.
Since she said she's coming,
then she could be here soon.
We need to know anyways.
So I'll tell you the woman who
took Kyeong Ran is my Mom.
- What? Mom?
Then, President Shin's wife took
our Kyeong Ran, right?
Oh my god,
Having your parents killed in
the same day is too much,
And now they've taken your sister?
This woman should be hit
and killed by lightning!
But, how can you appear here right now?
Then, whoever's daughter you are,
will be found out soon.
It doesn't matter.
I just need to get a hold of my Mom's weak point.
Mom won't say who's daughter I am so easily.
I don't know what you two
are saying. I'm busy, I'm going.
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
Why is Hyun Woo's wife seeing these people?
What did my father do to your family?
There has to be something innocent. I'll...
What are you doing here?
Dad.
You know these people? Right?
No.
No long ago there were threatening
phone calls, so I couldn't help but meet them.
At the end, I don't know what
they're talking about.
Threaten? What are you threatening?
What? If you want to know something,
ask me personally,
I will tell you.
Secretary Kang, what are you doing? Get them.
Yes, President.
It's your business again.
Was this your plan? Did you hire
those people to get to me?
Father, did you make any
huge mistakes in your past?
Hearing from them,
Dad killed their brother's wife.
Is that the truth?
What? Killer?
Since Dad already knows,
then please resolve it yourself. Then.
They said they were workers from the factory
You can't have purposely have killed
those unfortunate people, did you?
Mom, you look pale.
Are you sick?
I need to rest a little.
Who is it? Don't open the door to random people.
It's a delivery, I'll go get it.
What is this? It was delivered.
There's no address or name.
Give me.
This is Hyun Woo, our Hyun Woo.
What Hyun Woo?
Are you talking about Oppa?
Oppa.
What is this? What happened to his face?
Why is there a scar?
Mom, this is weird.
Oppa was unconscious, how could
he stand with his two legs?
A dead person's picture.
How can this?
Mom, look here.
The picture's date says December 15.
When the mansion caught fire,
it was November 27.
How can Oppa take a picture on that date?
There was a time at Yang Pyung Villa when
patient Shin Hyun Woo was conscious for a time
Hyun Woo is alive.
He is definitely alive.
This hospital clothes. Even if you
have the flip the hospital over,
you have to find Hyun Woo. Hurry.
Okay, I'll call Dad and Hyun Min Oppa.
Should I have to call sister-in-law too?
No, don't tell Ah Ran anything.
We have to find Hyun Woo, it's us.
Hyung is still alive?
How can this happen?
Is this real? You're not joking with me?
Okay, then I'll come.
President, what are you talking about?
Yeon Jae, my brother's still alive.
After the fire, a picture from the hospital
was delivered to my house.
- Then Hyung is alive.
- Oh my god.
Wait, I have to go home.
Wait, wait. You can't drive in this excited state.
Alex, Alex, no, Relax. Relax.
Don't get excited. Calm down.
Don't worry. Leaving Yeon Jae herself, I won't leave.
I'll call you later.
Leaving me alone, won't leave.
Does our President really like me?
Children's Mom. Hyun Ji, where are
you? Is children’s mom, right?
Our Hyun Woo is still alive?
What's going on?
Dad, look at this, Hyung is
really alive. Hyung isn't dead.
I said so.
How can Hyun Woo die?
What kind of son is that brat?
How can he disappoint his dad?
He made a mess in this family.
He can't just leave with no responsibility.
Husband, we have to hurry
and find Hyun Woo first.
The burns looks really serious.
We have to first find hospitals specialized in burns.
What are you doing? Separate.
From Seoul to Jeju Island,
go through all the hospitals.
Secretary Kang, hurry and hire
some people. Find outside, hurry.
Yes, President.
I'll go with you.
But, Oppa is alive, how can there be no calls?
It can't be that he lost his memory, right?
Brat that lost this memory,
how can he remember the
address and send a picture?
Just wait, maybe he'll appear in front of us.
Husband, I have to go out.
Just a little while.
Nurse Yoon, please tell me.
Where's Hyun Woo. Nurse Yoon
knows where Hyun Woo is, right?
What are you talking about?
Which hospital is Hyun Woo in?
Nothing can happen to Hyun Woo.
I have to find him and bring him home.
What hospital? Isn't Shin Hyun Woo already dead?
A picture came from Hyun Woo.
Even though the face has some bunts,
the eyes, nose are perfectly normal.
And also, both legs are standing on the ground.
Nurse Yoon, go in and work.
Yes, President.
A picture came from Hyun Woo Hyung, is it true?
Tell me, did Ah Ran hide Hyun Woo somewhere?
After making my healthy son into a vegetable.
Now turned to a dead person,
and took him away from us?
I will find him.
Because I am his mom,
I'll find him no matter what.
Because you're his mom,
so you're finding him, right?
Then who is my mom?
Your son is living good and roaming around.
Why are you acting like you don't know?
Why aren't you finding?
If it weren't for me protecting you, you
wouldn't be a person on this world anymore.
Me abandoning you is how I saved you.
Parents who abandon their children
always repeat like a crow.
Did you listen to a talk in college?
Abandoning children,
is for the best choice for the child, is it like that?
Don't treat Hyun Woo as
a opponent and be jealous,
you don't have that qualification.
Because of you and Ah Ran,
innocent children are suffering.
But Hyung has a lot.
A proper family, proper manners.
And also a mom.
Why did you like me?
You knew that I was a married woman,
why were you so stupid and chose me?
I won't ask for your forgiveness.
I'll let your heart hurt, I'm sorry.
This is the trace that you once lived in this world.
Even though you left,
the furniture that your designed
will remain forever. I guarantee.
Here. It's the document stating
that SM will be given to Soul.
Even though my brother was
unfortunate, you are really lucky.
Company and men are following your wishes.
Because of the pain I've experienced,
I'll apologize to you with my heart.
To not disgrace Sang Ho's designs,
I'll take good care of Soul Furniture
You're not picking up?
It's a phone call that will give
a headache, I won't worry about it.
After we marry, we have to live
in America for a bit. Don't worry.
After daughter-in-law comes,
my parents won't care about anything.
They say they want to go on a vacation.
Really? How good.
But isn't she curious about me?
No. She absolutely trust my insight.
As long as it's the person I love,
then there are no conditions.
Nurse Yoon, try to contact Ahn Jae Sung, it's urgent.
He won't pick up my calls.
Now we're not related.
You really don't know where Hyun Woo Hyung is?
Like Madam said, which hospital is he in?
This... I don't know.
I'll leave first. After you're done you can leave.
Ahjussi, why is it like this?
Now everyone knows Ahjussi is alive.
I'm afraid something will happen.
I'm about to go crazy.
Please help me confirm,
is there a person named
Shin Hyun Woo who came here?
He might have had a overall make-over.
Please help be check the patient record.
Okay, please wait.
You say Shin Hyun Woo, right? This patient...
We don't have that patient.
Our hospital is afraid of the risk,
we don't do overall make-over.
Lies. Did Shin Hyun Woo tell you say this?
I... saw Shin Hyun Woo come out of this hospital.
Tell me, I have to know.
If you came to mess,
I will call the police. Please leave.
I'm finding someone by the name of Shin Hyun Woo,
he's received a make-over surgery.
Even if you have to go through
the whole world's records,
you have to help me find him.
A patient named Shin Hyun Woo,
has he come to his hospital before?
He has a severe burn on his face,
please look thoroughly through the records.
Jae Sung, what is all this?
The schedule is too tight,
so I made a decision.
Sorry for not discussing it with you first.
It's so pretty.
Compared to me, you know how to pick jewelry more.
I was worried that you wouldn't like it. Thanks for your praise.
Do you need to invite a lot of people
during the wedding ceremony?
No, my family is the orphanage.
I also have a little sister,
but she won't make it.
Then, one invitation card should be enough.
You even booked the church already?
But, how can you be so fast?
Since we are going to marry,
there's no need to delay it.
On my side there's only my parents and brothers coming.
There's no special arrangements.
This day at this time, leave some time out.
This day, is the day I become your man.
Thank you. I will be your good wife for my whole life.
I'll help your occupation,
I won't hide anything from you.
Even when I turn old,
I still need to be the cool woman by your side.
You won't hide anything, just
thinking of it makes me feel happy.
Let's go to the next place.
It's so pretty.
Within the brides that I've seen,
you're the prettiest.
I like the wedding dress a lot.
A person who has never married, how
do you know a woman's heart so well?
I don't know much about woman's heart.
But i know some about Ah Ran's heart.
Joo Ah Ran. Laugh more.
Be happy more.
If I need to shatter your happiness miserably,
I need to go up a little more.
Jae Sung, hurry and try out your suit too.
I want to see how handsome
you look, hurry and change.
Then okay.
It's me.
Why weren't you picking up my calls? Where are you?
Right now I'm discussing the uniting with Julie Jung.
What's the matter?
Hyun Woo appeared.
The whole family is looking for Hyun Woo in the hospitals.
What's the meaning?
He took a recent picture and mailed it home.
Let's meet up now.
Hyun Woo Hyung, he might come home tonight.
Then we will be over.
No way, send a picture?
Shin Hyun Woo is already dead.
The gas exploded, how is it
possible to still be alive?
The details I'm not sure, but it's
confirmed that Hyun Woo is still alive.
We need to find your way out.
Are you listening to me?
Ah Ran.
How am I?
What's the matter? Are you okay?
I wanted us to look at the church.
Looks like we can't today.
Sorry. Everything might have been
too sudden, so I got frightened.
Before the wedding ceremony,
you absolutely cannot faint.
I have to see your pretty,
happy expression in the church.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay soon.
How is it? Did you go to the hospital?
Did you find Hyun Woo?
I don't think he's in Seoul hospitals.
None.
I've been asking around in
the regional hospitals
There should be news soon.
No matter where, how, him being alive is the most important.
But, sister-in-law doesn't know about this?
This time we received divorce papers,
so what if she knows.
Thinking about this, there are many weird things.
the gas exploded and the house is gone.
Oppa who can't move is fine.
This can't be explained.
At the scene, they found Oppa's tooth. How is that?
Right. If Hyung didn't wake up and escape,
how is he fine in the picture?
Hyung can't have a consciousness, right?
It's not an impossible thing.
If Joo Seung Oppa and sister-in-law were lovers,
they couldn't take care of Hyun Woo Oppa.
Even if Hyun Woo Oppa woke up,
it's possible that he didn't tell us.
Then, the fire, was it purposely set?
The bolt found in the mansion,
wasn't it locked from the outside?
When Hyun Woo comes back,
everything will make sense.
That brat, what condition is he in?
His own mom faced the trouble of
being accused of killing her own son
and he still won't come home.
If it goes on, what something
happens to his parents.
Maybe, Hyung won't come
home because of sister-in-law.
If sister-in-law locked Hyung in there,
How is it? Did you find Shin Hyun Woo?
He's hiding on purpose,
how can we find him?
He's probably hiding behind laughing at us.
Then, we can't just let go and not care.
No matter what, we have to find him first.
Even if it looks like hospital, we have to search.
Maybe it's not a hospital, it's besides us.
You're talking about President Ahn again?
It's not President Ahn.
Just in case, I confirmed,
it's can't be Shin Hyun Woo.
He doesn't have acrophobia.
He doesn't have an appendectomy scar
and he doesn't have a peanut allergy.
If he had a make-over because of revenge,
he would throw away Shin Hyun Woo totally.
There's no evidence that he had a make-over.
I asked the health insurance,
to check if there was Shin Hyun Woo's medical record.
Tomorrow, everything will be found out.
Help me, Joo Seung. If Shin Hyun Woo
is alive and comes back,
the car accident, and the Yang
Pyung Villa fire will be exposed.
If they know that Shin Hyun Woo is alive,
the family isn't telling me anything.
Maybe they've contacted him a while ago.
Shaking here worriedly can't change anything.
We can only arrange everything here,
and leave this place.
The play ended like that?
It's missing the credits.
That will be our play's climax.
Doctor Nam keeps being suspicious.
what will happen if he doesn't make it to the credits?
In the end, God will help the
righteous people. Including Sang Mo.
Ahjussi, I laughed a few times today.
Even though I'm tired, I'm still doing good.
Before you sleep, think about
me and laugh once. Jae Hee.
[You cannot miss when you eat. You have to eat rice with brazed cow meat.
[When Ahjussi is sick, I'll be more hurt]
[Ahjussi, you have to drink milk everyday]
[For a cold, drinking water is the best,
[You have to drink 1L everyday]
Ahjussi, no matter what your motive is,
marrying Joo Ah Ran twice, I oppose.
I have to tell the family about your existence.
Ahjussi.
You're not home. It's so cold, why are
you outside? Hurry and go home.
Ahjussi's family is looking for you, you know?
Yeah, I sent a picture.
It's about time I go back.
But why do you have to marry Joo Ah Ran again?
You can't. I'll block it.
This isn't revenge, it's not anything.
Why are you hurting yourself
and get deeper into danger?
Jae Hee, even if you block it,
I have to marry Joo Ah Ran.
How can you say that?
Without me, Ahjussi can still be happy? Is that it?
Jae Hee, the person you love isn't Shin Hyun Woo.
Ahn Jae Sung starting from the beginning,
was born to get revenge on Joo Ah Ran.
Leaving you now, is Ahn Jae Sung,
not Shin Hyun Woo,
why don't you understand?
Nurse Yoon, why did you come to my house?
I wanted to know if you found patient Shin Hyun Woo.
Are you really curious because you don't know?
Or are you using your innocent face
and acting like you don't know?
Leave for today, there's nothing.
I'll tell you tomorrow at the hospital.
Right, the one marrying Joo Ah Ran is Ahn Jae Sung.
I don't need to feel hurt.
Let Ahn Jae Sung leave, then Shin Hyun Woo.
I just need to wait for my real,
Daddy Long-legs and it'll be fine.
What is this place?
You two dare come in our house together?
And you're trying to leave so quickly.
Today, I have to take Ah Ran
away from this family.
What? Hyung, are you crazy?
Hyun Woo Hyung being alive is already confirmed.
In the divorce procedure, Ah Ran.
has no reason to stay in this family.
You scary person.
Because of this wretched woman,
you want to end relations with our family?
Thank you. now my ears have been yelled at.
I don't need to feel sorry anymore. I can leave.
Actually when we marry, we don't need to get President's permission.
I came because of the kindness these days.
Doctor Nam, how can you say that?
Hurry and disappear from our eyes.
Go and make a family, or have
10 children, we won't care.
Don't ever appear in
front of us in your life.
Go up and pack your things.
Hyun Ji, go prepare the rice.
At times like this we need to eat, to cheer us up.
If you won't want that brat to play with us,
the whole family needs to cheer up.
How are you? See if you need to bring anything.
Passport and checkbook you have to bring.
Right, if Shin Hyun Woo comes back,
the only one that can help me block is Nam Joo Seung.
First I need Nam Joo
Seung's help to live on,
then I'll marry Jae Sung,
and quietly leave this place.
Nam Joo Seung, since we have
to go different roads anyways,
[Statement
I, Shin Hyun Woo, October 13...]
You're tired.
Let me leave this place quickly.
I don't have the energy to breathe.
Change any of my assets
you can into cash,
and deposit it in my bank account.
Okay.
This place is full of our memories.
After a few days, this
place would also be gone.
Occasionally I will miss this place.
Rest for a while. I need to meet a person.
[Nam Joo Seung]
I, who grew up without a mother,
has a person who takes
care of me like Hyung.
Compared to my busy father,
I liked that Hyung more.
He was a deep loving and warm person.
But, starting from a time,
that Hyung became the person
I hated the most in the world.
Why? Is it because of Joo Ah Ran?
No.
You can say I'm a child that has
never drank his mom's milk.
I have a sense of inferiority to child
who get their mother to themselves.
I don't know what it is,
but I really feel inferiority.
Let me ask one thing.
Feeling betrayed from the woman you love and
feeling betrayed from the parents
who gave birth to you,
which one is deeper.
Yes, because I've never been
disappointed by my parents.
Right, giving birth until now,
I've never felt hurt or betrayed once.
So, the feeling I get from Ah Ran,
will hurt even bigger.
What?
Do you know?
The cruel mother lion,
to raise their children strong,
will bite the weak lions to death.
The happiness that you're enjoying,
might be the value for stepping
into someone else's life.
So, your happiness, isn't timely,
it's also not pretty.
What are you talking about now?
I endure one punch, and another punch,
what's bad about that?
Lastly, the person who hit be first
wasn't Ah Ran, it was Hyung, you.
Hyung thinks that the punch
he suffered was the biggest.
But, Hyung's sharp knife tip,
didn't hurt Ah Ran and I the deepest.
It will be Hyung's most loved family.
You're still not drunk,
you still think that I'm Shin Hyun Woo?
Hyung is lacking courage
and is being childish.
Might as well come back as Shin Hyun Woo,
and get your revenge properly.
If it's like this, I will also suffer.
At the end, tomorrow,
everything will be made clear.
Acting as Ahn Jae Sung,
tonight will be the last time.
Enjoy it.
I was the one that first hit.
Today I'll arrange this house,
I'll also arrange the hospital.
Although it's not a lot of money, it won't
be a problem starting over again.
Don't worry too much.
Okay, I also need to go to the marketplace.
Then I'll pack the things that
I need when I leave from Soul.
Are you Joo Ah Ran?
I'm a policeman.
Let's go to the office.
What's happening?
The criminal that caused the
car accident on October 13th
that happened on the highway
from Seoul to Chang-An.
The real suspect is Joo Ah Ran's statement.
Who wrote this?
Shin Hyun Woo.
Shin Hyun Woo? It can't be.
How can a dead person write a statement?
Shin Hyun Woo's fingerprint
has been confirmed,
talk when we get to the office.
If you hate us, you should have killed us,
why did you touch my son?
You want to take away
what is precious to you.
You're lying to me until the end.
Who do you want to kill? Bring that man out.
Joo Ah Ran, to see you now, I come out.
Romeo who's heart was stolen.
It's Ahn Jae Sung.
Before Ahn Jae Sung helped Shin Hyun Woo
take care of everything,
he went on a plane.
At the end he was caught by the bank's CCTV.
Even God is helping us.
If I don't come out,
then it's like giving wings to
someone who needs to escape.
Shin Hyun Woo, you're
finally showing your face.