Xiao Xiao, stay in here
no matter what, don't come out, okay?
I'll be right behind the wall
In 370BC, the Warring States China
Zhao Nation dispatched 100,000 warriors
led by Xiang Yanzhong,
to attack Yan Nation
LIANG stands right on his path to Yan
There's no way she can
resist Zhao's mighty troop
and will be definitely taken as buffer
Their only chance for survival is to
ask for the help of Mozi warrior
who are experts in defending
but...
as Liang teeters on the edge of peril
Mozi warriors...
still didn't arrive
Father, we must fight
Zhao's Commander
Xiang Yanzhong is a brilliant strategist
His advance troop has already arrived
We have to take action now
before the arrival of their main force
we must surrender
otherwise, we're all done for
Fighting with bare hands...
ends up the same...
My Lord
what if the Mozi army
were to make it here?
Assemble at the Gate, quick
Get the horses ready
Move on, quick
Hurry up
Come on, hurry up
Cavalry Chief
Who told you to ride out?
Your Majesty's decree
All cavaliers await at the South Gate
for General Niu's order
General, the surrender notes
and cavaliers are ready
Open the Gate
Someone's approaching from the West
Who are you?
Mozi, Ge Li
Mozi has finally arrived
Open the Gate
Take this
Zhao soldiers... they're here
Zhao's hostile force
They're furious, shall we inform the King?
Who are you?
How dare you trespasses on our camp site
This is General Niu of LIANG
I'm here to deliver the surrender note
Send cavaliers to pass them
our surrender decision
Yes
Attack
You think surrendering and not fighting
can please the Zhao?
And stop the war?
Zhao's army is huge
you want us all to get killed?
When they take over Liang,
you'll still have to suffer
Ministers will be killed
soldiers will be captured
your families will be ruined
women will be dishonored
Why?
Are you contented with this?
Why don't you give a try?
Though...
we may die in the battle
but at least you'd tried
and if we can make it
we'll make it worth
We can't give up our homeland
What shall we do then?
Sir, please lead us to defend
Yes, lead us
Take action now, Mozi
Zhao army is already here
Can you give me your bow?
Their distance is too far
Give me
To fight or surrender?
No one is allowed to intrude into my city
Protect the General
General Gao...
General Wei commanded us to retreat?
Retreat
Thank you
Good job, they'd retreated
They are only the vanguard troop
It's just the beginning
Retreat
Your majesty
Proceed
A Mozi arrived and
drove away the Zhao's vanguard
Congratulations, My Lord
Liang is saved
Nonsense
My Lord, please take care
My Lord...
Your Honor, the King was drunk
Back off, the Prince is coming
Come on, good boy
The King is not feeling well
your request had to be put back later
Enemies are right outside,
we don't have much time
By the way
which cities have you protected before?
This is my first time
You are the only one they sent?
How about the jade pendant?
Did you bring it?
It's still in the Mozi Hall
It was our token for Mozi's help
How can you forget?
Let me have a look
General Wei
why...
Just a little modification...
and double the shooting range
Why do you stop my attack?
What for?
We don't need to attack
Liang had already sent
someone here to surrender
Then, why are they shooting me?
Give out my order
block off all the paths to Liang
poison all its water source.
No one is to go near Liang
without my order
Yes
That just...
gives them time to defend
Don't worry
we'll discuss
when the Commander arrives
Sir, Prince Liang Shi offered...
you to rest here for the night
Thank you
Cavalry Chief
Who did the arrangement?
He's here to protect us
It's the Prince's order...
The Prince? How can he...
My Prince was convinced by an outsider
and stimulated the Zhao's vanguard
They will definitely retaliate.
I'm sure your majesty understands
What is your suggestion?
Your servant believes that...
Don't hesitate? Say it.
Ge Li persuaded the people
and offended the Zhao
against your decree
We must arrest Ge Li
and hand him over to the Zhao
That will placate them
and show My Lord's sincerity
If Xiang Yanzhong and his troops arrive
Liang will be in great danger
Royal Tutor wants me to...
turn against the Mozi?
My Lord
this is the only way to save Liang
What about the Mozi?
They would be furious
Ge Li didn't bring the pendant you sent
his identity is unclear
My Lord
Proceed
The Prince came to see
your majesty with Mozi Ge Li
Bring Ge Li to the Main Hall alone
Yes
Long live My Lord
Ge Li
Yes
I've heard that you've never lead troops
or protect a city before
Facing Xiang Yanzhong's force
how will you save Liang?
Zhao's target is Yan Nation
they won't risk their mission on Liang
The battle with Liang
must be fast and clear
Survival or not
depends on how long Liang can hold
How long will it take to repel the Zhao?
If Liang can hold up to one month,
Zhao will retreat
Ge Li
You think...
how long can Liang hold?
That's up to your trust on me
I trust you unquestionably
Then, I urged you to
hand over all command to Ge Li
The utmost care must be taken
orders must be clear & strict
efficiency is most important
Right
It seems that...
Liang is going for a long siege
Yes
But what if...
...I mean if you were killed?
What else can we do?
How about...
not fighting?
Not to fight?
Right
That's all on your will
My will is strong for that
Then tie up Ge Li now
let Prince Liang Shi...
bring him to the Zhao
That will stop the war
You can bring along your families
go to Zhao Nation
and plead for forgiveness
You then hand over Liang to the Zhao
All men will become slaves
Then...
the people of Liang will suffer no war
If your majesty prefers this
Fine, Ge Li will do all he can
Please
The king sees his people as everything
My decision is... at all costs
Liang Shi
Yes
You must obey Ge Li's command
Apart from the Royal guards
Mozi Ge Li will command all troops
to resist Zhao's invasion
Anyone who disobeys his orders will be...
be-headed
Our enemy will poison our water source
from now on
we must not use any water
flowing into Liang
We'll have to dig more wells in the city
Collect farmer's harvest
select several locations in the city
as food storages
All food and water
will be under distribution
Direct all water drainage
to the farmland and let it swamp
Swamp the farmland?
We'll starve ourselves of food
With appropriate allocation
our coffers will last us for a year
Then what?
We'll have kept the city
but there'll be nothing left
If we lose our lives,
what good will come of that?
Even if we block off the East
enemies will attack us
from other directions
The west and north
give us natural barriers
Enemies will not
attack from those directions
How about the south?
Why don't we spend more effort on it?
Every city must have one weakness
this is where our enemies will attack
so as to control their attack
Gather all the strong men
we've to build a bulwark
at the south in seven days
Can that be done?
Mr. Ge Li
how can we build a bulwark
in such a short time?
It would take at least a year
to bring the stones from the mountain
Knocking down the palace wall?
How can you protect the palace?
Are you revolting?
These stones are for building a bulwark
The bulwark
is our first line of defense
If we lose the city
the palace will be lost too
Protecting the city means
protecting the palace
Ge Li
can a bulwark built in such a short tim
defend Xiang Yanzhong's troop?
To defend Liang in such a way...
This is not only defending
it's also a psychological tactic
The bulwark has to be built precisely
matching with the main wall
The efficiency of the Liang people
will definitely threaten our enemies
Your highness
please allow cavalry to
help with moving the stones
to speed up the process
Cavalry troops represent
the superiority of Liang
how can they be used to move stones?
I believe that...
this may prove My Lord's love
and care for his people
Right
With their help, seven days will be enough
Unload and move on quickly
The sun rises in this direction
Sunlight will be the strongest after 3 hours
Move back
There's drinking water outside the Gate
Go by the side
Move on quickly
Record the landscape
Yes
Let's go the stream
Go
What a disgrace, never-ending warfare
There's war everywhere
I don't want to run anymore
You want to die here?
That Mozi looks quite capable
maybe Liang can hold
Why don't we just give them the city?
Who cares who we pay tax to?
Quiet...
Quick, unload these alcohols
Yes...
Cai Qiu...
Don't go
Come back
Just let the baby cry...
Be quiet
What is it?
Zhao troops arrived
Don't let the baby cry
Keep quiet
Don't let her cry
- Let me hug her
- Give her to me
Don't hurt the child
Stop the crying
Let me hug her
Don't let the baby cry
Give her to me
Give her the child
Stop her crying and keep quiet
sister...
My child
Shut up
We are all going to die
Stop crying
You flee because you don't want to fight
we're also tired of killing
We're heading to Yan Nation
and just bypassing Liang for supplies
How come Liang confused our purpose?
Is there someone persuading you?
A Mozi came...
his name is Geli...
Only one?
4,000 people persuaded by one person
to fight against 100,000 soldiers?
We dare not
Leaders must earn their respect
Zi Tuan, you'll lead the archers
Will you take the command?
Why don't you take Ge Li's order?
How dare you
Your skill and experience is not up to mine
how can you be the leader?
You're not qualified and hiding the truth
Guards
Take him
No
Stop
Not up to the Prince's skill
will had to be imprisoned
I should be taken too
Leaders must earn their respect
Zi Tuan is not qualified
Zi Tuan's archery
had amazed me on the day I arrive Liang
Warfare is a matter of
strategies and cooperation
no single man can ever hold off an army
Right
For military tactics
we can only judge
when the enemy is at our doorstep
But for archery, let's settle it right now
the top of that pole is the target
you each have five shots
You start first
Quit now and I can spare your life
Please start
Even if you made it, you'll never beat me
You lose
Guards, take him
Wait
You're the best archer
best rider, and best fighter
all because you're the Prince of Liang
You should widen your scope
the world is bigger than you think
What's going on?
They're beating up
those who tried to escape
I dare not run again
Please stop, please
Do you remember
the location of Zhao camp?
We don't know
When we saw the Zhao's sentry
we just turn and run
Sir, Zhao's Commander Xiang Yanzhong
wants to meet with you at the South Gate
War on a board game?
So we know where we stand
Please
Commander
Just to check you out
you certainly are a fine catch
Small defeat means nothing,
it's just a board game
It isn't worth
wasting Commander's time on Liang
right?
It won't cost much
I'm not done yet
Neither am I
See you in the battlefield
General
Thank you, My Lord
I'd changed my words in surrendering
and I'd hand over all commands to Ge Li
General, I hope you won't take offence...
My Lord, I really don't mind
General...
Your servant is loyal to your majesty
I'm always at your command
I appreciate your generalship
and your understanding
General Niu, you're
always my great General
This battle is critical for Liang
If we can defend Zhao's first attack
Liang will have hope
Any questions?
No
We'll get everything ready
So, dismiss and prepare for the battle
Yes
Sir...
Mr. Ge Li...
What is it?
Cavalry troop is not yet
assigned with any work
Cavalry troops belong to the royal guards
I've no rights to command
Don't argue anymore
Usually...
People flee from war
do you really know what war is?
This is my homeland
When my father was still alive
he was always on the front line
I don't want to be despised
just because I'm a girl...
There's one very important job...
You're responsible for the square
Collect them to
the City East for distribution
We don't have much time,
the rest come with me
Yes
Wake up, everybody
By the command of Mr. Ge Li
give us all your excrement now
give us all your excrement
I can't take this anymore
I'm really cracked up
The Zhaos...
when will they attack?
Are they... waiting for us?
That's impossible
Ge Li is no dummy...
We've to think it through
We can't wait anymore
They'll really kill them all
Don't you know our wives
and kids will all be dead?
Quiet
We're here all because of your wife...
Forget it... it's over already...
it's over
...I killed my own child, he is still in...
It's over already
Everybody get up
and follow me out
What's going on here?
- What is it?
- Get up! Quick
Keep quiet
Quiet
What's going on here?
You... shut up
For no matter what reasons you're here
from now on
no one will care
You'll be sent to the front line of the battle
to fight against your enemies
Defeat your enemies
and you'll be freed
We're innocent
why do we have to give our lives?
Who are not victims in a war?
Answer me
Your anger and rages
your freedom...
is in your hands now
Fight for yourselves
and the innocents
Freedom is more valued only if
you defeat your enemies, understand?
Set
Shoot
Alignment
Hurry up, pass around the arrows
Look
The excrement really works
it puts out the fire
Spread more on the other roof tops
Front attack
Invade South Gate
Everybody get up and fight
Pour the sulphur
Shoot
Give me the stone
Pass it along to the wall
Yes
Hurry up
Move
Come with me
I'm not, not me
My Prince, there are
Zhao spies in the town
Dong
Go
You shouldn't be here...
You shouldn't...
Get back inside the Gate
Shoot
Bulwark had been taken,
two units are moving in
South gate was opened, we are moving in
You stay behind
Yes
Raise the drawbridge
Hurry up
Pull it
The drawbridge got stuck
we can't get out and rescue Ge Li
Attack
Three units are approaching
Focus the attack in the Bulwark
Cover Ge Li. Go
Shoot! Just shoot
Draw back
Ge Li
- Shoot him
- Pull
Close the gate
Remove the bodies, quick
Hurry up
Close the gate
Tear down Liang
Protect Commander
Close the gate
Stop crying
Close the Gate
Quick
Move back
What sound is that? Quiet
Come with me
Quiet
Zhao's retreating drum sound
- Zhao is retreating
- Really?
They're retreating, we've made it
The Zhao's retreating
Stay in bed
tend to your wounds
I'm fine
Where am I?
Dong's room
I'm sorry
He can finally relieve...
only that he cannot die in peace...
Brand new
It's okay, I'm fine with what I have
It isn't worth much
please keep it
Mozi shouldn't accept gifts
or else
people will think we are
helping others for their return
Not accepting gifts
doesn't mean no one suspect you
Wait...
You'd better stay in here
there're lots of people outside
Mr. Ge Li has recovered
Commander, we can't
postpone attacking Yan
My suggestion is...
Let's leave 4,000 soldiers guarding Liang
they'll surrender when they
run out of food and water
then...
we can then
take revenge for General Gao
Commander, what do you think?
This battle is no longer a personal affair
Liang seems meaningless to us, but...
we under-estimated our enemies,
and were defeated
You think...
we can defeat Yan
with our dispirited troops?
Do we have this courage?
I would like to have
opinions from other Generals
This dagger has poison
someone dropped it into my house
They're already here...
even if we don't do it...
they'll do it
You don't want to kill Ge Li, right?
You must have forgotten
your wife and son...
No
he came here to protect us
How can we do that?
Protect us?
He is giving up our lives
by putting us in the front line?
We're just lucky to be still alive
Even if we'd killed Ge Li...
can we save our families?
If we kill Ge Li...
who's going to save Liang?
I know where he is...
Take it
Go
Everybody listen
no matter what, armor or swords
collect all the useful stuffs
What are you doing?
Why do you want to kill me?
Drop the knife
Stay away
Guards
Drop the weapon
Mr. Ge Li, he's dead
I've one important announcement today
But before I announce
let's give a...
silent meditation to Pu Le,
who died yesterday
As usual
close your eyes
until the 10th stroke
Traitor
Little girl...
don't be afraid
why do you have to come to Liang?
It must be the Zhao
assigned her to kill Mr. Ge Li
Right, why do you want to kill Mr. Ge Li
Quiet
Bastard, how dare you are
Don't let her go! Kill her
Stop
Back off
Mr. Ge Li
Where are you going?
I'd like to make myself clear
Mozi will not accept any gifts
Thanks for your gesture
Sir
Why do you follow me?
You nearly got killed! Go back
Aren't you going to spy on Zhao Camp?
I always came here riding with the horses
I'm familiar with this area
Follow me
You're not going
This way is the shortcut
What are they carrying?
Soil
They're digging a tunnel...
To Liang?
Why are they dumping it into the stream?
The stream will wash away the soil
then, no one will know
how far they had dug
Let's go
Someone is up there
There they are
Get them
Can you swim?
Go, don't worry about me
Go, quick
Stop running
Surrender or you'll die here
You'll have to save me
Move
Breathe
You're...
very brave
If I didn't jump...
would you jump?
I would
But I'll kill you first
Is that what you Mozi
would have done sanely?
You think killing you is rational?
How are you going to kill me?
Push you down the waterfall
Do you feel better now?
Can you walk by yourself?
Quiet
There's nothing
in the West City and the barn
where are they going to attack?
They'll dig a few tunnels,
there'll be more than one exit
we can't be sure whether
we had blocked them all
I'm not blocking them off
I'm letting them in
No
they must be collaborating
with the force outside
I know
we're going to defeat
our enemies in a dragnet
After ten days
we can dig three tunnels
in here, here and here
Commander, what do you think?
Can you speed up the process?
If our soldiers can enter the City
Liang will not be able to defend
Three days later
will be the advent of winter
Longer night time
is an advantage for our attack
Commander
Someone was spying on us
a few days ago...
The longer we take
our enemies may
find out the tunnel exits
Gather all the slaves
three days later
we'll attack from here
Warriors, get ready
Commander...
The exit was blocked, move back
Attack
Pull
Drop your weapons
and your lives will be spared
They're here
I'm just a slave
I don't want to come
Stop him
let me go
Kill him
What are you doing? Please let her down
Stay back
Please... please, let her go...
Please... don't...
he'll really kill my sister
The Zhao force me
I don't want to come
Please, please...
Please give her back to me
Please let her down
Stay back
No please
Let her go...
let the child go
She's innocent
I just know how to dig tunnels
they force me to come
Get ready
Kill
Shoot
Defeating enemies in a dragnet
Quiet
Xiao Xiao, it's okay
Let go of the child
I promise
no one will hurt you
Give her to me
Please...
Give me
Xiao-xiao...
Stop
Let him go
Move back
Everybody back
Everybody move back
Sir, are you alright?
I'm fine
All of you assemble at the Square
Hurry Up! Go
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Let's go back
Don't come back
Go along the stream, you'll not be found
Why don't you kill me?
Why do you ask such a foolish question?
Why...
should people kill each other?
I must take revenge for you
It's all my fault
I shouldn't make you suffer
They're inhuman
Congratulations on
your astounding victory
The King would like to reward you
Please come with me to the Palace
Reward?
General Niu...
can't you see all these dead bodies?
They were our enemies
Aren't they humans?
When enemies is trying to kill me
I'll have to defend or even kill him
but killing someone because of hatred...
it's absolutely wrong
What a pity
Every man has his weak point
Mozi Philosophy is not
for ruling a country
This Mozi clan will fall...
I'd like to be excused
You seem very appreciative of Ge Li
I acknowledge his defending skills
That's where it should end
Mozi philosophy is only
applicable in times of war
They're not suitable in times of peace
You must be clear on this
Yes, my Lord is right
Understood
Watch him closely
Yes
don't let him getting off the track
General Niu
Yes
you must pay close attention
all those revolting thoughts
shall never spread in Liang
Yes
Are you okay?
I'm fine
The weather is getting cold...
I know you don't have
any warm clothing...
so I took out my father's coat
and see if it fits or not
I can adjust it...
Just fit, thanks
I'll return it when I leave
When?
I'll leave when this battle is over
The battle should be over soon...
very soon
Did you go to the Square last night?
No
You assigned me
to keep guard in the North
I'd heard the Zhao army was defeated
Many of them died...
lots of them
They're still...
moving their bodies out for burial
Defeating enemies
in a dragnet... is that right?
I remembered
my father told me this
when I was a little girl...
When you start questioning
what is right or wrong
you are uncertain with
your faith and beliefs
Is it only war can make you stay?
I thought...
you are always looking for peace
Sorry...
What for?
You're always like that...
You're so protective with everything you do
You always ask whether you're right or not
Is it really that important?
Even if you know it's right
but for some people...
they prefers to be wrong
I would want to tell you
no matter it's right or wrong
I just want to be with you
You talk about universal love all the time
You should know how to love
you know
Ge Li arrives...
Liang will survive
Ge Li stays...
Liang will be safe
Ge Li goes...
Liang cannot hold
How about if Ge Li leaves?
Just those small pieces?
Anyway, melt it quickly
Commander
It is time to retreat
News from our spy who
returned from Zhao Nation
Proceed
News from Zhao Nation
The King of Qi has ordered
an army of 200,000
setting off five days ago
to attack Zhao Nation
Zhao Nation is preparing for the war
Thanks for your majesty's blessing
If that is the case
Xiang Yanzhong will be called back
Liang will be saved
However, the news of
Zhao's retreat must not spread
I plead My Lord
to withdraw all power from
Ge Li immediately
otherwise, people will think it is Ge Li
who defeated the Zhao troops
We have to demolish any chance
for Ge Li's supporters to rebel
You think Ge Li will rebel, General?
I don't think so
Why are you so sure?
Because...
Because there is no such need
Ge Li's popularity
is now higher than the King
he doesn't need to do a thing
Right?
Someone defending Liang
under false pretenses
and initiates rebellion by
imposing personal adoration
Doesn't it sound the same as rebel?
General, what do you think?
I agree with Royal Tutor
but lack of evidence
General Niu
Yes
if you restores your military power
would you be able to put down the riot?
And arrest all the rebels?
They're back
How's it?
Commander
Liang must think that we had retreated
We're just left with 1,000 soldiers
Commander
shall we call back part of
our army for the attack?
Victory will come
when there's no way to retreat
This battle has to be fast and clear
We'll end this up with Ge Li
New boots?
No problem, Mr. Ge Li
it will be ready when you come back
I disagreed on the massacre last night, but...
You can't stop them...
I always think that killing enemies
is a kind of glory...
where will you go after the battle ends?
Wherever needs me, I'll be there
What if Zhao is being
invaded and ask for your help
will you go?
Of course I would
You've wiped out their army
then turn around and save their lives?
Those you'd defeated before...
will they accept your help?
Frankly speaking
I'm never sure
whether those people I had helped
really appreciate what I've done for them...
Then, Mozi's universal love
is just blind talking?
Nothing is perfect
I just want no regrets in my life
Blacksmith
is the pot ready?
Sure
Mr. Ge Li is a true hero
He's humble and skilled
Just the opposite to our royals
If our King got a bit of his talent
Liang will be undefeatable
Mr. Ge Li
we are all set
Let's go
Is this really going to work?
That's psychological tactic
Can you really cook Zhao food?
I can guarantee that
the Zhaos will be miss home-
Here are the firewoods
Put it here
Thank you
Pass me the seasoning
Mr. Ge Li...
How is it?
There's no one is the Zhao camp
They retreated?
Yes. It's abandoned. Nothing's there
You guys first go back.
I'll go and check it out
Come on
Let's have some meat
Is that Zhao's food? What a great smell
Open the Gate
Ge Li is back
By order of the Royal Court
Ge Li is defending Liang under false pretenses
and initiates rebellion by
imposing personal adoration
Be arrested, otherwise
you will be killed
General...
Ge Li!
I'd always suspected your motives
How dare you seize my land
I'm going to kill you today
Take me hostage
My Prince...
Thank you
Draw back
Move back
Open the Gate
Ge Li, let go my Prince
the King will pardon you
Prepare Ge Li's arrows
Yes sir
Thank you
Mr. Ge Li
Sir...
may I follow by your side?
You should go back
Staying in Liang is much more important
Don't you wish to see more people
passing on Mozi's thought of peace?
Remember
those who know how to defend a city
cannot bring peace to the world
Peace lies on the kings of all nations
Understand?
Ge Li, release the Prince
Ge Li had released me
I'm coming back
Stop
Sir
Thank you
Let's go
We're not going back
Where're you guys going?
Let's go home
We've got no home
The Prince is coming back
Get ready
Yes
Aren't they...
retreated already? Why...
What sound is that?
Shoot as far as you can
Run
Quick
Fire
Run
Mr. Ge Li
Don't come back, go
Go
Search for the bodies
Come with me
My Lordship Liang Shi has fallen
Your servant has killed
the Prince by accident
I'll never be forgiven
However, Liang is still
under the threat of riot
I plead with you my Lord
to let me accomplish
my mission in a hundred days
I swear I can eliminate all Ge Li's league
I will take my punishment after that
Please, My Lord
Liang Shi...
is my only son
he was the future of Liang
You ruined the future of Liang
Pardoning you?
That's ridiculous
But taking into account of your loyalty
and all you've done in defending Liang
moreover...
protection of Liang
cannot lie on outsiders
I'm in a hard position
I'll accept your plea. Hundred days later
your accusation will be denounced
Thank you, My Lord
Why are you taking me?
What have I done?
General, what's happening here?
The King's decree
capture all the rebels
Rinse again with water
What have you asked me for, Sir?
The King ordered you to kill Ge Li
Why didn't you shoot him last night?
Ge Li has done nothing wrong
He saved all the Liang people
You disobeyed the King's command
You will be punished
What do you guys want?
Let go of me
Stop
Sometimes, I really don't know...
what is cause and effect
There's no cause and effect
You saved them,
and they turn against you
Mozi...
doesn't ask for returns
Are all Mozis like that?
How come you came here alone?
Mozi...
didn't send anyone to Liang
You came here on your own will?
How many cities can you protect?
There are never ending wars and battles
peace will only come
when the seven nations are united
I believe universal love
is the only path towards peace
Mozi's "universal love" is loving everyone
that means you don't know
whom you should love
Where are you going?
To Liang
and let someone I love
know that I am safe
It's all underground stream here
and you're injured
It's too dangerous, I'll go for you
Your Majesty
these people were in league with Ge Li
They are traitors
My Lord...
I have nothing to do with Ge Li
I know nothing about his rebellion...
Immoral, selfish
When everyone praise Ge Li
respect him and listen to him
Will you say such things?
I'm just a farmer,
I just want to live my life
I don't care who's a hero
I just miss my family, my child
my home... My Lord...
Your city is in great danger
and you are just self-seeking
Don't you know
how many unfortunate lives
we had lost to save our city?
Without Ge Li
we never would have been saved
Guard
Sir
Slap her
Yes
You are the descendants
of my loyal servant
and you grew up with my beloved son
I'll have mercy on you,
I'm granting you death
you'll have a Royal funeral
you'll be honored as Calvary Princess
and buried with my beloved son...
It's all rubbish
You just want me
to be a burial item in your son's tomb
You want all of us
to die under you verdict
so as to prove and
show your power
But if it wasn't Ge Li
and those who died in the war
Would you still be able
to abuse your people?
Shut up
This girl no longer
belongs to the royal families
She was in league with Ge Li
She will be executed in the public...
ripped to shreds by five horses
Execute
Execute them all
Yes
Execution
My Lord! My Lord
Report to the King, Yi Yue was muted
Yes
Warriors
behind this slope, there is a city
in that city, there're 4,000 people
but under the ground outside this city
there're 5,000 warriors
friends and brothers who came with us
we can't just leave them there
they were killed even after
throwing down their weapons
their bodies were even
tossed from the Wall...
we'll fight for our
fallen brothers to our last soldier
Start
What's that?
Anything you want to say?
What did you see?
There's nothing
Look! Over there
Zhao is attacking again
Shoot them
The Zhao's here...
Protect the King
Hurry up, protect the King
My Lord, this way
Get more soldiers up here
Wait! How about us?
All soldiers report to you captain
Bring her back to the prison
Come with me
No! Stop
Stop
Stop shooting
Go, quick
Go
General...
General, let's go
Go?
This is betrayal
If you won't leave, neither will we
General
whatever we do...
we're all rebels
All your men have been...
dispersed already
or you would like...
to see us all get our wrists broken?
Fight for our homeland
Bring more arrows here
Kill all those who tried to run
and all those evade
What's going on, sister?
Come, quick
Xiao Xiao, stay in here
no matter what, don't come out, okay?
Alright
I'll be right behind the wall
Run?
Get the horses out, quick
Hurry up
Kill all those who run
Go
General
The archers had
taken down the North Gate
around 800 of them had escaped
Abandon the North Gate
get all soldiers to the Bulwark
await for my command
Yes
General
it's over
we should...
surrender
We can't surrender...
General, Ge Li said
if we surrender, we will end up even worst
General, Ge Li said that...
Stop talking about Ge Li,
there're only us now
General...
Any arrows left?
Listen
We can't rely on others
We have to hang on even if we have
only one soldier left
General...
the enemies are here. Leave now
Everybody, run now
Let's go
General...
run...
This person is the great General Niu
Commander
defending the city is Ge Li's intention
we're suppose to hand him over to you...
but he had escaped
Ge Li...
by tomorrow's noon time
if you don't come back...
we'll burn down the City
and its entire people
Please lead us to fight back
I am willing to give up my life
So do we
If we go back, more people will die
Why can't we end this war...
in a rational way?
You really want to go back?
...is it worth it?
If this can really stop the war
and save more lives
why not?
...is it worth it?
Bring all the men out,
leave the women here
Go, quick
Keep moving, hurry up
Commander, I think Ge Li will not come
We'd taken Liang already,
why don't we go back?
We can reach our main force
and return Handan
and protect our homeland
Isn't that just another battle field?
There's only victory & defeat
we have taken Liang
but it's not a victory
Ge Li had lost
His theory is impractical,
idealism leads to jealousy
He can't even gain the trust
of those he helped
He was totally beaten
There is no winner in this battle
I know Ge Li had lost
but...
I had to defeat him myself
Someone is coming
Mr Ge Li?
Close the Gate
Commander
on the battlefield
we had a fair fight
and no regrets
You've taken Liang already
why do you have to kill all its people?
Nonsense
You think war is a game?
They fought for you
you failed
and with no responsibility
you left
It's you...
you bring them to the battlefield
Fine
It's totally between you and me
Will Commander end
all this with me alone
on the gate tower?
No matter who wins
please spare these people's life
It is all between me and Ge Li
Only one of us can
walk out from the Gate Tower
No matter who he is
everything will end
What are you waiting for?
Let's start
Forget it
As you had said
no matter who get out of here
this whole thing will be over
Go now, Ge Li is willing to stay here
Good strategy
I promised to retreat
just because I want to defeat you
but now, you give up
I am leading 100,000 soldiers
but before attacking Yan,
I'd already lost 5,000 men
and afterall, I didn't get Liang
but at least...
now...
I can kill you
and take revenge for my men
Don't use the dead ones as an excuse
to cover up your savageness
War...
will only cause more death
Both the dead and
the living ones have to suffer...
Enough
In battlefields
survivors are the winners
Survivors are winners?
Though you survive
can your 5,000 soldiers come back?
Retreat
end this war now
or else...
the rest of your men
will also lose their lives
My auxiliary troop has arrived
General Wei, we're besieged
Warrirors
Fight
Everybody fight and drive the Zhaos out
That way
Ask yourself
Is it for the soldiers
or for your own savageness?
Please leave
don't let any more people lose their lives...
Go now
I was defeated
I'm staying here
Please go
Commander...
Survivors are the winners
Commander
is victory
more important than your life?
My life must be meaningful
Please go
and tell my people to leave
I can't help you
You bring them here
you should save them
There is someone I have to save
Yi Yue...
Shoot
Don't run
Attack
Yi Yue...
Can you hear me? Are you there?
Yi Yue! Where are you?
Yi Yue...
Commander, we must leave now
You all leave now.
General Wei will lead you home
Commander...
This is my command
I want you all to leave
Back to you homeland
Yes
Listen
Aim at their feet
Ready
Shoot
General Wei, the Commander ordered you
to lead our retreat
Retreat
Leave now
I'll stay with the Commander
The commander ordered you
to lead our retreat
We came together, we'll leave together
Right! We came together
and leave together
Yes, we'll leave together
I'm not leaving
Go now
Take the General
Let me down
I'm not leaving
Let me down, that's my order...
Let me down
I order you to let me down...
Shoot
Yes
Archers
Get ready
Shoot
Long live My Lord
Where's General?
Xiao Xiao, stay in here
no matter what, don't come out, okay?
I'll be right behind the wall