For Paradise Film Distribution Company
a Paradise producers' centre production
SW-AURUM Film company
Arthur Smolyaninov
Anna Starshenbaum
Olga Popova
Gosha Kutsenko
Ivan Okhlobystin
Sergei Puskepalis
Andrei Leonov
Irina Hakamada
A film by Vera Storozheva
Written by Natalia Nazarova
Director of Photography
Oleg Kirichenko
Production design by
Sergei Tyrin
Music by Gary Miller
sound by Eugene Chaiko
Costume design by
Marina Ananyeva
Irina Lunina
Makeup by Galina Ustimenko
edited by Mikhail Igonin
Young man!
You have snow on your head.
A foreigner!
You all just walk hatless...
...and then say it's cold in Russia.
Executive producers
Anna Popova
Armen Adilkhanyan
Russia? So I'm in Russia?
Yes, in Russia.
Where else?
Produced by
Tatiana Sergeenko
Vera Storozheva
I'm so sick of this planet.
General Producers
Gevorg Nersisyan
Armen Manasaryan
Arthur Nersesyan
Yes!
Sasha, Happy coming New Year!
Oh, it's you, dad?
What time is it?
5 p.m.
What?
It's 5 p.m. in Kamchatka.
Daught!
I'll be passing through Moscow today. Any chance
you could shelter two homeless volcanologists?
Dad, I was actually going to see some
friends.
Who's the second one?
My colleague, Seryoga.
He's a great guy.
He's an Alpinist,
he can even roast potatoes.
All in all, you're gonna like him!
Dad, I already have a boyfriend...
...with such a pretty whiskered snout!
If whiskers count for you,
he could grow his own!
What?
Who?
- I said 'no problem, he can grow his whiskers'.
- Dad, I was talking about my cat!
Dad!
Jeeze!
Happy coming New Year!
Hi, Valer! Dad will be coming to see me for
this New Year.
Wait, your dad? But we were planning to go
to Rodion's place, no?
Then we'll have to celebrate it with my dad
first and then go to Rodion.
Is there any way we could do without your
dad?
Who's that?
What?
Well, somebody just walked by. Who is it?
It's my cousin from Chelyabinsk.
Why did she have her panties on?
You mean she wasn't supposed to have
anything on her at all?
Babe! Whom are you talking to?
Go fuck yourself!
Babe!
In Chelyabinsk!
Toe loop.
Are you OK?
How can I be OK? It's been snowing for a
week!
And I'm sick of cleaning it.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts.
How about now?
It no longer hurts.
Hi! How about celebrating this New Year
with me?
What? You broke up with Valeric and
decided to give me a call?
Well yes, sure, I've been sitting here,
waiting for your call.
Never mind, if you don't want it.
I just wanted you to meet my dad.
Your dad? Meet your dad?
Do you just want to use me? So that I help
you with your exam?
You're sick?
Take a pill, will you?
No, I'm OK, and you are not gonna be OK,
today!
Know why? Volintsev will be taking the
exam!
No!
And we both know he hates geologist girls,
don't we?
Oh, you little toad!
Who? Me?
Now I see your true face, Nikolaeva!
It's the face of a person who doesn't
regard other people's feelings...
Come here!
Fuck!
...the sense of your uniqueness is a
profound illusion!
Seven billion people live on the Earth, and women make three
and a half billion. Five million of them are beautiful!
Come here, come on!!
Dangerous job, homie!
People throw bottles, eggs...
I said come here.
...you think you can lure a man with your
finger...
Why you kill good man?
Every week a Muscovite falling from the
roof...
...full of oneself, don't want to live?
Easy!
- Homie!
- Ambulance is on its' way.
Homie dead!
Such a nice guy!
It was an accident!
They still punish fiercely for an accident.
I know, I know everything. Come on!
Hey, look. He's alive.
Why you scare people?
We thought you lay yourself out. You alive.
Ok Vitya, grab your things. Hello!
So, who has fallen out of the window?
Me.
What do you mean? And this guy flew down
with you?
No, he...
I fell on him...
Ok, check him.
- And hold his head.
- Don't move!
Does it hurt?
I feel great!
I see. It's a torpid phase of shock.
Get the stretchers here!
...she fell from the roof. He push me,
and lay oneself out!
Hero of Russia!
Shut up, OK? I'm telling you it was an
accident!
Ok, sister. Please get in the car!
No, I can't.
What do you mean you can't?
I have an exam!
What?
You don't need to worry, really.
We both feel great.
Some fucking comedians! Do you think we
don't have any other calls?
So who's gonna pay for this false call?
Come on. Let's chip in.
Everything hurts. Everything broken inside.
I need take to hospital!
Get in the car.
We'll take you to the hospital.
Vitya, let's take this one at least.
Happy coming New Year.
If you make it, that is.
Vitya, let's go!
Look at her. Exam my ass!
Just talking big!
We should've called cops!
Fuck!
It turns out I can fly.
My name's Sasha.
My name is Seraphim.
What?
Seraphim. It means 'red-hot'.
Yeah, I could use some of it to warm up.
Gotta go!
Sorry for that!
Happy coming New Year!
Hey, red-hot!
Your coat is dirty!
And what should we do with it?
Damn!
The key's inside!!
I didn't even lock my door yesterday?
Stupid!
Come on in!
...you can remain silent, you can keep ignoring me,
you can't ignore the entire world...
...but one day you'll have to pay for that!
All because of you!
Why are you just standing there? Take your
clothes off, come on in!
Shall I take off my shirt as well?
What?
Sorry, I guess I got you wrong.
Quite wrong.
Here!
Put the kettle on.
And feed the cat.
The food is in the refrigerator!
This is not happening.
Why did you give him my chicken?
Cats love chicken.
Really?
I love it too!
Fuck!
Why didn't you put the kettle on?
I did.
Fuck!
It seems I've really knocked you off. Maybe
you should go to the hospital?
No, I feel perfectly healthy.
You sure?
This is how you put it.
Remember.
I'll change my clothes, and you dry the
coat, it's in the bathroom.
The bathroom's here.
Hot air!
Very hot!
Where are you from?
From Jerusalem.
I guess you don't have any hair-dryers
there, do you?
No.
Then how do you dry your head?
Head?
I'm sorry,
but why do I need to dry my head?
Yeah, right.
Want some tea?
Green, black? Tea!
Coffee?
Tea.
This tea grew on the slope of Sichuan
mountain...
...a Chinese girl by
name Xu Lin gathered it
...she loved a man by name Chu Young,
but married Li Zhen who works in a L.E.D.
factory.
And Chu Young hasn't married yet...
Creamy Candy - fudge with candied fruit!
Made by Red October factory!
Sweetened condensed milk, butter, syrup,
candied fruit, alcohol, brandy...
Aromatics, 411 calories!
Packer number 5.
Dyed blonde,
a single mother of forty-five.
Sorry, but she's 32 and her hair are red.
Two kids...
twins. Katya and Angela.
Sometimes she takes candies home.
If she doesn't stop, she'll be fired soon.
It's very sad.
Who are you anyway?
I mean what do you do to make a living?
I help people.
Some kind of a charitable organization?
You could say that.
So what's the name of the organization?
The heavenly host.
So you're a sectarian or something?
I'm an angel.
I see.
Me too.
Sometimes!
I'm sorry but you're human.
Feminine.
Look, host. I've gotta go, really, sorry.
Crystallography is a complex science.
How did you find out?
That was funny...
For instance, let's take an ordinary
snowflake.
It's a real crystal, formed by the collision of
droplets of water with field particles in the clouds!
Look at this beautiful shape!
By the way, have you read the treatise of
Johannes Kepler on hexagonal snowflakes?
In this treatise, the author
reflects on the form of snowflakes.
What are you doing there?
Catching a cab!
- With your hand?
- And with what else?
Fuck!
What are you doing? Let the car go, you
freak!
I said let it go,
or I'm gonna call the police.
I'm sorry, but why did you stop?
You won't believe.
I'm going crazy.
I feel uncomfortable
driving with the blinker.
It was OK before, but today it feels
uncomfortable.
So I began to persuade myself,
saying 'don't fret, man'.
It's an official car after all,
still I feel uncomfortable.
And I saw a girl running, in a hurry.
And I say to myself 'let's do something
good'.
I'm sorry, do you happen to be from
Jerusalem?
Do I look like?
No, just asking.
Well then, Johannes Kepler wondered why
the snowflake is strictly of a hexagonal
shape.
One of us definitely pitched on one's head.
Why? Because when the microscopic water
droplets in the clouds face with the field
particles and freeze...
...the six-pointed crystal
forms come about.
All right, look, snow-lover!
Do you have any gum?
A gum, you know.
Thanks.
Because of the structure of water
molecules, only 60 " and 120 " angles are
possible between the rays of the crystal!
What's that?
It's the very first gum. 1848.
Made by the factory of John Curtis. Called
"Licorice Lulu."
- What fucking Lulu?
- Sasha!
Happy coming New Year!
Who's this guy?
Seraphim! It's a pleasure to meet you!
My name's Vardar. The pleasure seems to
be mutual!
Shall we?
- He's a psycho, you stupid!
- A psycho?
He's so cute?
Hi!
My ugly cat gets on the ledge. Hi! I try to reach him, and then I slip,
and I fly down like a bullet! From the third floor!
That's horrible! Your whole life probably
flashed before your eyes?
What? What life? I'm falling down and
yelling 'Maaaaaa'!! And this guy was
standing beneath!
I'm falling down and yelling 'Maaaaaa'! And
this guy was standing beneath!
Do they take your exam here?
Well, in a way yes. But you'll need to take
the other door!
I'm sorry. What kind of exam is this?
Let me explain you that!
The man actually saved your life! And you
just call him a psycho.
Ok, he's not a psycho, but I don't know.
Somewhat inadequate, I told him to put the
kettle on, and he just put it on the table.
He hadn't seen a hair-dryer before, for
Christ's sake.
It's called 'Male consumer idiocy' which is
pretty much normal!
He stopped a car by holding
its' bumper with one hand.
I saw on TV a man pulling a train with his
teeth!
It took me 15 minutes to get here by a car
with a blinker on. And he just happened to
be here already!
Means he had another car with a blinker
around the corner which explains
everything. Maybe he works for the Federal
Security Service.
He's from Jerusalem.
Then it's some Israeli CIA.
He says he's an angel.
Angel?
So what is it you don't like in that?
Did you do the cheatsheet?
Have a look.
Here we have the crystal lattice, this is the
unit cell, and here is the polymorphism.
Are you kidding me? Is this the stone age?
It's a polycrapism, not polymorphism.
Know what!
It took me half the night to prepare them.
The order of the rector. Anybody who gets
caught with a mobile phone, will be out.
On cheatsheets there's nothing said in the
order.
Ok, Bandar-logs, everybody come down
here!
I'm not going to sit here
with you until the New Year!
Get your mark books ready.
Put your mobile phones on the table!
Why did you come? You're automatically
passed!
Let me have your mark book!
Come on, come on!
- Don't drink too much.
- I don't drink at all.
And I don't smoke.
- Happy coming New Year!
- Thanks!
Ok, whoever answers first, gets one extra
point!
Varv!
Varv, the formation of snow.
Right away.
- Lower, lower...
- Can't.
You!
What is it you're looking for in there?
Nothing!
No, you were looking for something, I saw.
Need any help?
No! Thanks! I'll be answering!
Your name?
Nikolaeva!
The law of crystal symmetry. The formation
of snow!
Back in the sixteenth century, the medieval
scholar, Johannes Kepler wondered why the
snowflake is strictly of a hexagonal shape!
You've been reading Kepler?
Yes, I love Kepler! And his treatise is
really something, it's such a great book!
That's interesting, please go on!
Snowflakes are of a hexagonal star shape
and there must be reason for that.
For if it is a coincidence, why there are
no pentagonal or septangular snowflakes?
You!
What are you hiding in there?
I can see everything. What do you have in
there?
I believe you! You'll make an excellent
geologist, give me your mark book!
I can see everything, everything, no, no.
What's there under your, under your skirt?
Under my skirt? My legs.
Yeah right! But your legs are with cheats.
This girl here is quoting Kepler,
and look at you!
I'll need to have those.
Yes! What?
Wait, are you sure?
My son was born.
Congratulations!
4 girls in 3 years!
I mean 3 in 4 years. My son!
Girl can't be a proper geologist.
She can't carry the rock, it's too hard.
And once she gets married...
...she can say good-bye to the field works!
Everybody gets A! Give me your mark
books!
Look, it was the first time
I heard about that Kepler.
No, really, I opened my mouth and it just
came out.
It's absolutely different when the words
just come out of your mouth by themselves.
Well? 10 o'clock at Rodion's place? Don't
forget the dress code.
Anyone who comes in jeans will celebrate in the
street. Finally I'll see Nikolaeva's legs!!
So you're not interested in mine.
Did you find a dress?
We have our concept changed.
Dad will be coming to my place, with a team
of volcanologists.
And what am I supposed to do there without
you?
An A, mom...
...what do you mean 'how'? I studied!
Sasha!
Sasha, I'm sorry, I was very rude, this
morning,
But it was too unexpected. I wasn't ready.
And then I thought 'why not?' I'd love to.
I'd love to.
How's that?
You'd love to do what?
Well, meet your dad, and...
Kolya...
Seven billion people live on the earth! You
have a huge selection!
Ok, let's go.
- Where to?
- You'll by the stand-by.
There he is!
Kolya...
that guy is insane.
He's been following me since this morning.
Do something!
Like what?
Like asking him to leave.
Will he leave?
Depends on how you ask him.
Sasha, let me do that.
Don't!
What's his name?
What's the difference?! Shall I'll go?
Stop!
You probably want to hit me?
Me?
I've already been hit today.
They even knocked out my tooth.
Is it OK now?
Ok!
Sasha!
He makes denture on his own!
Ok!
Kolya...
...you go, I can do it myself, got it?
Young man!
...turn around!
Turn around!
...and go!
Go!
Don't just stand. You go the other way!
Both of you!
The psycho...
the coward and the lover-boy.
Who's the lover-boy?
Valera.
I called him on Skype, and there was a
naked body with no head, but in panties.
Red panties.
So who was that?
Who's what? I'm telling you there was no
head, I'm unable to identify a person by
one's panties.
No, I think he's not a psycho.
- Why's that?
- He has a nice coat and rhetorical twists. He has a nice coat and rhetorical twists.
You're telling me you
still believe in angels?
Well, I concede their existence.
Hi, dad.
Sasha, we have a snow flurry here, so they
have delayed the flight!
And what about the New Year?
We can deal with that.
OK, see you!
He'll be late. Non-flying weather.
Just look at this. Our young volunteer is
repairing the trolley.
Sash, can I have him?
In your dreams. I'm gonna need him myself.
Come on in.
Seraphim! Could you please help me today?
Sure, angels were created to help people.
Ok, then could you please tell everyone
you're my boyfriend?
Ok, but I'll be around
only until 12 o'clock.
Well, that's just great,
exactly what I need.
Dog in the manger, like always.
Look! They're eating each other!
It's called a kiss.
They are French.
- Is that a French kiss?
- Yes, Seraphim, and if you want I could
explain it to you in details, but not here.
Easy! Get yourself a boyfriend and you can
explain it to him then.
Seraphim, what are you doing tomorrow?
I won't be here tomorrow.
Got that?
- Now relax!
- Can't! Until I gorge something.
Let's go there.
Come on, hurry!
Here you go, Bon Appйtit!
Thanks!
This is our favorite place. We often come
here, and play this game.
The game is called 'guess'.
There!
You have to guess his name and
profession.
It's Leonid, some middle manager.
Pavel, photographer!
He's name is Boris. He's a dermatologist.
Go check that out.
Just wandering there without knowing he's
being watched.
Yes.
It's very much similar to the
way we look at you from there.
So what do you feel up there?
Love!
His name is Boris and he's an artist!
It seems you flopped, mister Red-Hot! Turns
out it's not everything you know.
He's a dermatologist.
Well he guessed the name at least!
Never mind, maybe he was distracted.
And Seraphim here was just confessing his
love to me.
Already?
Shall I go?
No why?! I love you too.
That's cool.
No, wait. Maybe you could specify your
choice?
How?
I love you both.
- And you too.
- Thanks.
Lover-boy for sure.
What do you mean by saying 'I love you'?
Love.
I love everybody. Absolutely everybody!
It's some daisy chain.
Come on, let's explain to our representative
of supernatural powers, what "love" is.
Well, love is, when a man and a woman
meet and there happens a spark.
Spark?
Well yes, or attraction! When you go
around and don't think of anyone or
anything, and you don't notice anything...
and the pleasantry for life escalates, and
you eat without getting fat.
- So you're saying that love is...
- A game.
People play and play that game, and then
break up.
Break up?
Well, of course, everything tends to end
sooner or later.
You know, the summer, traffic, coffee,
cigarettes...
sugar, night...
...and love.
I don't think so!
That's the reason you don't have a
boyfriend!
Sorry!
- Where are you going? Stop!
- Can't you see a man is being beaten?
Are you some kind of a superhero? What do
you care?
Hey guys! What are you doing? It's New
Year coming. Leave the man alone.
What do you want, fat?
I'm fat?
- That's cool!
- Get up, hurry! Come on.
You like Negroes.
Hold her.
- Oh you bitch!
- Don't touch her!
Take your hands off her.
What do you want?
Take your filthy hands off me, macaque!
What's wrong?
Is this the shit I've been smoking?
I'm gonna feel sick.
Hey guys, what's wrong? Stop fucking
around!
Amazing! Amazing! This is quite an unique
case, sudden pigmentation!
You know, you come to my clinic. I'm a
dermatologist...
- Go fuck yourself, dermatologist!
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
Unbelievable!
Boris Anatolyevich, dermatologist.
Well, Boris Anatolyevich...
...Candidate of Medical Science, why did
you lie?
You know, when such a beautiful girl approached me in the street,
I couldn't work up the courage and say...
'I'm a dermatologist'.
Yes, you're so beautiful!
You have blood.
I'm a nice person,
the faculty of "gas field machinery."
My dad is a king.
I want to take care of you. For a long time.
As long as you want.
Great, you got the angel, I got the prince.
Let's go stitch up your face, Prince.
Wow! So my boyfriend is an angel?
I could imagine my father come and see I've
turned black.
He has no father, only mom.
Come on, I don't believe it.
I don't believe you're an angel.
Don't believe him, sis, I'm the angel!
- No, I'm the one!
- You're both angels, let's go.
I'm an Angel. He's not!
So you're an angel?
Well, come on. Since you're an angel. Show
me something!
What?
I don't know. Some miracle.
Come on!
What would you want?
What would I want?
As a child I had a dream...
...that I'm walking in the street.
Then I hear this voice calling me.
I turn around, and see this...
two meters tall...
handsome young man, who tells me...
Can I have your papers?
Hi!
Jeeze!
Do you need some special invitation or
something?
I don't have any papers.
How come?
Who are you? Where did you come from?
- Hey guys, he's a foreigner.
- All the more so.
Where's your registration, ghoul?
I'm not a ghoul. I'm an angel.
Then you're going our way, get in the car.
Hey guys. The New Year's near at hand, is
there...
an amicable way we could resolve this?
Amicable? What do you mean by that?
Well...
Five?
Ten?
Twenty thousand?
No way! We take no bribes!
This is similar to antlers!
You want a deer?
Well, yeah right, take me...
to your deer, deer.
A deer!
Three zeroes speaking, we have a deer
here in front of us.
A deer!
Just be here in a minute. We don't have
enough men.
- Here you go!
- Thanks!
Hurry or I'll break your balls.
Where did they go? They wanted this deer,
didn't they?
They did!
Now!
We got the deer.
The next shot!
Where are the loving couples?
Here they are!
Who are you?
Your assistant.
Then assist!
I need some looks. And I asked for a loving
couple...
...not the housing office
workers on strike!
Your green tea.
Hey guys, any chance you could stand in
the background for this shot, please?
- And what should we do?
- The director will tell you everything, you won't be paid of course! Is that all right?
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
So what do you think?
- Hi!
Marvelous!
All right, now, you've just met! You don't
know each other well enough, but you like
each other.
Don't look into the camera. Look at each
other! Eye to eye, up to the 'cut' command.
Should we kiss each other?
- Kiss?
No. There's no way you can kiss.
It's just the beginning of your relationship.
You just look at each other and the magic
feeling conceives in your soul.
Like a flower.
It's your destiny!
It's your destiny, understand?
I'll kill on the spot any of you who
looks into the camera or kisses.
Please approve the costumes.
Ready to shoot! Snow, wind-blower, camera!
Come on, guys, follow her.
Action!
- Action!
- Got it!
Camera!
Scene 36. Shot three. Take one.
Let's do it!
I can't, I'm sorry. Let me just...
Stop!
Young man!
Young man, you, come here!
Come here! You need to be in the movies.
Your face is amazing, it simply shines in
shot.
And mine?
Yours doesn't.
It just doesn't. You have to work on your
internal alimentation.
Ok, what do we have next?
SCENE 37.
Then they'll show it in theatres.
On such big screens.
Why?
What do you mean why? In order to...
Fuck! Simple things are so hard to be explained.
Why do you keep saying the word 'fuck'?
What does it mean?
Well, it means...
it's the analogue of another word, which
means...
...a woman of bad behavior, so to say.
What's her name? Do you know her?
Who?
That woman?
Oh, fuck! You're gonna blow my mind!
We just say it for no special reason.
Don't bark, Jorik!
Jorik!
Some fucking New Year!
The dog's dead.
Jesus!
Seraphim, do something,
Help us! Jorik!
Could you check him please? I think he has
a pulse. I'm afraid to!
- Anybody!
- Jorik!
Jorik!
It's gonna be all right.
Get up!
Come on!
Jorik, you scared me, you scared your
mammy, stupid,
- Thank you so much!
- Happy coming New Year, Jora!
Did you see that? How's it possible?
Hello! Yes!
So I'm the one who puzzles you?
Maybe you puzzle me?
Valer, look enough blowing my mind.
What?
Fuck you, Valer!
Do you think you could make someone so
ugly...
that all the girls would
not even touch him with a ten foot pole?
No, I can't!
Why the hell do I need you then?
And what do girls usually do with their
boyfriends?
I could tell you that...
but you'll faint then.
Please note, only the most powerful and
stable angels are sent to Russia!
Yeah right!
Ok, can you carry anything heavy at least?
I see. That's enough, put it down.
Thanks.
Seraphim, Seraphim!
I'm here!
- I'm here!
- I can see you.
Come to me! Now you understand.
I'm telling myself every year 'go
and get the presents beforehand'!
Presents? You mean gifts. Offerings?
Something like that. But not so smugly. It's more of an expression
of high regard, love, and so on. The thing is to guess.
By the way, what should I present to my
dad?
He wants skis.
- Skis?
- Skis.
Watch it!
This is an advertising campaign. Want to
try?
- Is this champagne?
- Yes.
We'd like to.
We need to pay.
No, there's no need. Put it back.
- It's free, isn't it?
- Yes.
Thanks!
- We can't do this!
- Everybody can do anything today.
Well?
Like it?
I feel dizzy.
That's good!
Let's go!
I feel so dizzy.
May I? Thanks
What happened to her head?
Because a woman with no head, is an ideal
woman!
Ideal woman?
Oh, that's just great!
This dress goes well with your head.
Present it to the girl.
Is it what guys do?
Sort of.
We'll take it.
What's this?
With this coin, King Henry of Navarre
redeemed from captivity his friend, Count
Antoine de Martignac...
...then it was among those with which the
Chateau de Royale castle was bought...
Then it was put in a chest where it stayed
for a hundred years, but was stolen during
the fire in 1745...
Stop.
We don't take foreign currency.
Where are you going? Stop, stop!
Stop!
He stole your coin!
The waiter!
That's OK, he needs it more than I do.
Just do something!
Nothing needs to be done.
He needs it more, really.
You're so saint that I feel sick.
The smell of a true man. How is he
supposed to smell?
It depends.
Try it!
Oh, Seraphim! That's enough.
Do I smell like a real man? Smell it.
Do I?
You smell absolutely different.
Sure, the perfume unfolds different ways
with different persons.
Young man, this is your aroma, take it!
- My aroma?
- Young man!
- You don't need it.
- But he said it's my aroma!
Just trust me!
Miss, please check this new aroma.
What is she doing?
Dancing.
Why?
She's in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood too.
But I'm not dancing.
Why?
In a whirlwind of gay couples whirl...
We've almost said good-bye to this year...
- Get a music centre for your briney...
- Seraphim!
- Everybody's looking at us!
- So what! I'm in a good mood. Let's dance!
Please! Come on!
Stop!
Put your hand on my waist.
- Where?
- My waist.
Let's dance like her.
I feel dizzy.
It's good, you're supposed to.
Nice job, old man!
I'm not an old man. I'm a guy!
Her boyfriend!
Well, man, your girlfriend is the prettiest
ever.
Thanks!
She's my girlfriend just for one day!
Girlfriend for one day?
Yes, sure!
I'm not your girlfriend at all.
Sasha!
Wait!
What?
You forgot the skis!
Keep them. You still have time to ski.
There's plenty of time till 12 o'clock.
Varv?
Where are you?
At home! Treating the prince. He doesn't want
to go to hospital. He prefers grandma's home.
Listen, I checked the encyclopedia. Angel
means 'a messenger'.
Sasha, if he's an angel, then there's a good reason for
that!! Understand? He's here to deliver a message.
So nail him down, and make him talk!
There's nobody to nail down, we broke up!
Broke up? Come to my place! Grandma
misses you.
Prince made some chops.
Hey, some Olympian! Olympian!
Just look at this guy.
What's he doing? Not bad, huh?
I'm gonna call you back.
- He's skiing for the first time!
- Oh come on.
Oh come on! Ninety miles an hour!
First time, my ass! No matter how good the
skier is...
the lay of line is too hard.
He loves hard lays.
Hey, shall we stop? The guy is gonna trip
over.
He's not a guy.
Step on it, please!
What?
Step on it!
Get out!
Sitting in my car. Get out! Get out!
Ok, I'm out.
How can you treat him like that? How can
you all treat us like that?
We love you, ready to break our necks for
you, so that you can give yourself airs.
- You'll step on it at home!
- What?
You know what I mean by 'it'!
You heard me!
Hey! Olympian!
They ski just fine.
Dad's gonna love them.
Sasha, I said you're my girlfriend for one day,
but for me that means my entire life. Do you understand?
No, no!
Love is a real and earthy feeling...
...and it requires another person to be
nearby...
- ...to feel his touches.
- Ok, touch me!
I don't believe this.
Wait. Wait!
Why? You wanted us to kiss each other?
Me? With you?
Look at yourself. You're not even a man!
But I smell like a real man!
No, you smell of magic!
Like an angel, I don't know. But that has
nothing in common with a man!
Ok, then. What shall I do? Tell me!
I don't know...
If a man asks such a question,
then he's not a man at all!
Let's go, Vitya!
Oh! It's them again. Skiing.
I'll hit them on the head with those
skis if something goes wrong.
- So, what happened this time?
- Hurry, please. I don't know, he just fell!
He fell?
- He won't say a thing.
- Nothing new!
Where does it hurt?
Here!
That's because you've been skiing with
broken ribs!
How come they're broken? He's been
walking today!
He's been flying today as well. Come on,
put him on the stretcher.
Vitya, just put him.
Your hand is so warm!
What does it mean?
- It means your heart pumps blood, for the
time being.
- The heart.
Are you sure you're an angel?
Could you please take
his skis off at least?
Don't just stand there!
Press your chest against!
I said 'press your chest against'!
I said press your chest against!
I don't get it. Is this a dance invitation?
You said 'press your chest against'.
Dear! See I'm bald?
That means I love women, and women love
me.
Don't breathe!
Give me your labs.
Blood, urinalysis.
Miss!
Are you waiting for X-Rays?
No.
Stay here, don't cry. Everything's cured
nowadays.
They'll fix you!
What the fuck is this?
- Why isn't it working? What's going on?
- Doc!
Doc, here are the shots!
I'm sorry, ma'am! But my X-Ray is broken.
The shots!
- I don't need these.
- Just do the X-Ray photography. Nobody
agrees to see us without it!
Pavlik, Pavlik!
Pavlik, come here!
Let the doctor see you.
See?
He's entirely black now.
Mom!
So he's going to be black
for the rest of his life?
Depends on him.
Does anything depend on us?
Everything.
No, if I completely believe you're an angel,
I'll go nuts!
People don't go nuts because
they believe in angels!
What are they doing?
Acting the goat.
Who's the goat?
Just put the skis. Here he is!
I love acting the goat!
Me too!
Of course, it's not exactly a slide.
We have some slide in Kamchatka...
where you're literally flying a mile and
yelling: mamaaaa...
...and mom is standing beneath and
laughing.
And then...
...she left me.
Left you?
On the 31st of December...
they went with dad to the mountains...
...there was an avalanche...
...and mom was gone,
They loved each other so much. And what?
Did that love save her?
No!
That's why I know I need to live here and
now, because nothing's gonna be then.
I'm tired of miracles.
I just want you to be an ordinary man.
An ordinary man?
How do you do that?
It's very easy. Ordinary people go on a
visit...
hide presents under the Christmas tree...
...watch old movies, make wishes...
And then?
Then they go to sleep.
And then nothing! There's only "here and
now".
And now I want to kiss you more than
anything.
Sasha, I can't do that!
But breaking into my life was not a problem
for you!
Seraphim!
Yes, dad!
- Sasha! I love you so much!
- What?
Don't be afraid of anything. I love you very much! Don't
be afraid of anything. My dear girl, I love you so much!!
What dad? Dad, I can't hear you!
Do you hear me?! I love you very much!
Hello!
No, no, no, no!
I'm sorry, please, I need a phone like this,
urgently!
One minute please!
As we were informed by the press-service of
Ministry of Emergency Situations of
Russia...
...Su-825 took off from
Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky 12:03 Moscow
time. After overcoming some 500
kilometers...
the crew discovered a combustion of one of
the engines
what disrupted the navigation systems. The
crew is doing everything possible to land.
The situation is complicated by bad weather
conditions. It's been heavily snowing there
for three hours now.
Miss, your cell phone is fine.
Hurry, please, my dad's there!
The liner has 132 people on board,
including 7 crew members. All services of
the airport are on high alert...
The subscriber's machine is switched o_ or
out of reach.
...they have special duty doctors,
ambulances...
It was the latest news in the last half an
hour, We will monitor all the further
developments.
I asked you to get my mom back...
you didn't...
If you take my father...
I will never believe again. Got that?
You could also, pray to the Guardian-angel!
Here he is!
This one deceived me completely.
- The Angel?
- That's right!
Hello! Dad!
Sasha, everything's ok.
I'm alive. Don't worry.
We just landed.
Daddy!
We'll be flying to Moscow in an hour. I'm
OK.
Hello, hello, dad!
Great!
Thanks!
Dad's alive!
May I?
Nice work. You deserved thanks.
Come on in. Take them o_.
Give me the candy.
Give it to me.
Keep your voices down. Or I'll
tell the Lord you're not behaving.
And I'll tell him you steal
candies from the factory.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry.
Are you the packer number 5? Red October
factory?
Why?
If you don't stop doing that,
they'll fire you.
Jeeze! I wasn't taking much.
I won't do it anyway!
Could you please tell me what time it is?
Sure!
- It's ten!
- She's gonna kill me.
You still had 2 hours left.
And you already vanished!
Rodion!
- You scared me!
- Why are you wandering here?
You should be at my place in half an hour!
Get in. Come on, come on.
So what's all that shit with Valera. He keeps
calling and telling me some angel stories.
Didn't he tell you anything about red
panties?
No. Nothing on that.
Stop here.
No, I don't help blinkers on principle!
Just stop it, will you?
Hey guys, could you please give me a ride?
It's only one block. The belt died!
Get in.
Don't you recognize me?
No, I'm sorry.
You actually took me to
the university today!
Me?
I have an official car. We're not
allowed to give anybody a ride!
I got this for my mom. For two years she
wouldn't talk to my wife.
And today she called...
jittering. She said 'God
was about to punish me'.
I asked 'what happened mammy'?
She answered 'my dog was run over by a
car'.
Because of that dog she pulled the chill on
with my wife.
One day she said 'my dog
is better than your Lena'
So did the dog survive?
It's not that simple.
This is what she told me.
There was a man with a woman passing by,
the woman put her hands on that dog, and it
revived!
Some paranormalist vets?
Yes, I laughed myself.
But she was so serious, she said 'God,
was about to punish me'.
Could you stop it here?
So, did you pass your exam?
This is the creative idea.
This firm really has some imagination,
although, I don't give a shit.
You can pick your wings!
- No, thanks!
- You have to!
Young man, any chance we could be more
careful? Thank you.
You stole our coin today?
What coin?
Of the 16th century. With which King Henry
of Navarre
redeemed from captivity his friend, Memory
any better?
- I'm sorry, I'm not aware of any coin or
Henry?
Young man, just keep up the work,
everything's OK. Sasha, come here!
I'm sure it was him?
Sasha, listen, thanks!
Look at me, look at me, look at me. Are you
OK?
Well, I fell out of the window today.
I think I have something for you in the
kitchen, let's go!
Rodion!
I won't let you out until you make friends!
What? Rodion! Open it!
- I'll break the lock!
- Feel free, you'll cover it with your
scholarship!
It was my sister, Marina, from Chelyabinsk!
Valer, I don't care either way.
Why are you being so disputatious?
I'm not.
Look! You're not saint yourself, are you?
I thought we're modern people, and
perfectly understand each other.
Valer!
- Do you ski?
- Yes, I do!
What's your personal record?
30 miles an hour!
It's very little!
And do you know that there can't be 2
identical snowflakes.
So what?
Or did you know that Henry of Navarre spent his
last coin to redeem from captivity his best friend.
Tell your tycoon skier that I'm gonna break
his face.
You can't do that! He can lift a bench with
one hand.
- Am I forgiven?
- Yes...
...now you can ask Rodion to open the door!
Rodion, open the door!
Now a kiss!
What are you doing?
He suffered so much...
and Rodik left all his guests to come get
you. It's New Year!
You won't understand!
Seven billion people live on the Earth, and women make three and a
half billion. And beautiful women according to the statistics...
Don't touch me!
So who's this guy?
I thought everybody's here.
Friends!
Imagine this picture - the park in the
morning, and a man is dying by the post.
Everybody just passed by, except him!
This is a man with a warm heart and powerful torso! If it
wasn't for him, you'd be coming in 3 days with red garlands!
How did you get here?
You invited me, remember?
Where have you been?
I brought your father's
skis and your dress!
Sasha, what dress? Do you guys know each
other?
Yes, sure.
- I'm her boyfriend.
- Then who am I?
You were her boyfriend yesterday.
Me? Yesterday?
Valera, Valera!
Marina from Chelyabinsk loves you very
much, she's waiting for you.
Where's my dress?
You came back for good?
Depends on you.
How's that?
Sasha, people have the
greatest gift ever...
the freedom. You have to decide for
yourself.
Can we be together?
Yes, we can live together, long and even
happy, and we'll have children.
But heaven for me will be closed forever
then.
Why?
They don't receive fallen angels.
What shall we do?
It's up to you to decide.
If you say so, I'll stay.
I feel dizzy.
Jeeze, you're saying all the time 'love,
love' and I learned just now what love is!
One!
I can't do this. I'm not ready.
Don't do this to me.
Five, six!
Ok, go! No, wait!
Wait, you kept telling me that for everything
there's a good reason. So, why are you here?
Eight! Nine!
You'll understand it someday.
Ten! Eleven!
Go.
Twelve!
Sash!
Happy New Year, sweet!
I had a phone call to take.
He flew away!
- You should've held him!
- I let him go!
- You shouldn't have done that!
- Don't cry, he'll be back.
Happy New Year Sasha! I'm at the airport!! But I won't be able
to reach home! My flight is in 2 hours! Could you come here?
Wait, Wait!
Here, forgive me,
I couldn't resist back then.
Keep it. You need it more than I do.
Dad!
Hey!
What?
- Great dress!
- Like it?
I lost Seryoga! What a fool?
Shall we go?
We were flying in circles over the airfield.
Everybody screaming, crying, praying,
and I called you, I thought I needed to hear your voice at least.
Dad!
Suddenly the plane started to dive down,
and everything was calm, and the light was
On.
In five minutes we safely landed. Can you
imagine it?
Yes!
Dad!
Did you love mom very much?
Yes, and I still love her.
It seems Reykjavik was just announced.
- Time to go.
- Dad! I got these skis for you!
How did you guess?
Great. I'll pick them on my way back! I
completely forgot!
In hurry we were pushed on different flights, and Seryoga forgot
his ticket. He'll be flying in a day. Could you pass this?
Yes, sure!
That's great!
Such nice hospital, doctors drunk, nurses drunk, the patient
with a dropper drunk too! No limits! You should've come!
Miss, is this the 5th building?
Seraphim?
My name is Sergey,
and you are Sasha?
San Sanich's daughter?
I came to see you. I lost him, and
he told me you have my tickets.
Well, do you have my airplane tickets?
Yes, sure.
Great, that was so stupid.
You're very much like your photo.
Which one?
Sanich has it on his wall.
It's not me, it's my mom.
I see!
- She's a very beautiful woman!
- Thanks!
Your mom.
Ok, I've gotta catch my plane. Thank you so
much. Good-bye!
Sergey!
Your jacket is dirty!
And what should we do with it?