Tropical
storm warnings are now in effect
for all of
the Gulf Coast.
We're looking at a strong Category
3, so board up those windows
and get ready
for a wild ride.
Folks, there are emergency
shelters being set up in King County
and Scarborough County.
Howie!
Johnny Gavineau.
You got the permit?
Yes, I do.
This is against
my better judgment.
Okay. Let's get to it.
Yeah, I gotta
get back to the coast.
There's a hurricane coming.
I got property there. I gotta
get the place battened down.
Never touch the cage.
Was he trained?
Trained how? Jump
through a hoop on fire?
He can do that?
No.
Well, does he just sit
there and look pretty?
I thought he
was a circus cat.
Circus don't want him.
Look, I'm starting
a safari ranch.
This is my
main attraction.
I need, you know,
a scary animal.
Scary?
Yeah. That's what
the tourists pay to see.
I don't think this
cat's scary enough.
I'm not paying top dollar for an
animal that doesn't scare anyone
and doesn't know
any tricks.
Now, maybe if
I'm paying less,
say, $5,000 less...
Mr. Gavineau, the only
reason we are talking
is because last month this
cat attacked a circus horse
while 300 of
your tourists
ran screaming
for their lives.
Chased her down,
did he?
Went 16 feet over a cage.
Passed 11 other horses
just to get to this one.
Silver Dollar
was her name.
He broke her spine
so that she couldn't move,
and then
he ate her alive.
You ever heard a horse
scream, Mr. Gavineau?
You want to know why
he went after that one?
Because
she was the pretty one.
And you're right,
Mr. Gavineau.
This cat,
he's not scary.
He's evil.
This is a waste of time
and my gas money.
I'll take it!
Plus your expenses.
Cat hasn't eaten
in two weeks.
That's how you show him
who's boss.
And when you move him, you
roll the cage with this.
Safari park, huh?
Well, good luck
with that.
Good luck with that.
Man makes his own luck!
Isn't that right,
Lucifer?
Tom, you there?
Tom.
Tom, come on.
Remember? I told you they
have fish here. You love fish.
They have all... Come look
at this. Come look at this.
See, look. Come here.
They have yellow fish.
Blue fish, purple fish.
I think they even
have clown fish.
Tom, come on. You're
gonna be happy here.
Mom would have loved
this place. Okay?
It took me
a long time to find it.
I know you understand.
This is your home now. You
cannot come to college with me.
Hey.
Please do not
screw this up.
So, you've been
living with your stepfather,
but you've
taken care of Tom
since your mother
passed away.
And after college,
will you once again
be taking on Tom's care?
Yes.
No red.
That depends on,
of course,
what's best for Tom
at that point.
I have custodianship, so I
will be checking in on him.
Sorry,
he does not like red.
Well, then let's
get things settled.
Tom, would you like to say
goodbye to your sister?
So, I'm gonna take off.
I'll see you in a couple
of weeks, all right?
No! No touch!
No! No, no!
No!
I'm so sorry.
I got his stuff out.
He likes this...
He likes this
God's eye and...
When he's walking,
he might need it.
Tom,
I want you to be calm.
Good.
Can you sit down for me?
Can you do that for me?
Can you sit down,
please?
Good.
Thank you.
You know,
who Tom is now
is pretty much who Tom
is always going to be.
People can sacrifice
their entire lives
taking care of
an autistic child.
Don't feel guilty
if you can't.
There seems
to be a problem.
Your check is being denied
due to insufficient funds?
No, that's... That's not
right. That little...
Do you have
another resource?
No.
What about
your stepfather?
No. There's money in there.
This is Mr. Fenton.
Hi, Mr. Fenton,
this is Kelly Taylor.
Hi, Kelly.
How are you?
Could you check the balance
of my account for me?
Your stepfather withdrew all
the money from that account.
It's closed.
When?
Yesterday.
So...
He said he was
changing your house
into some sort
of safari ranch?
I hope that's
not a surprise.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't really care about the
animal thing. That money was for Tom.
Kelly, sounds like you should
take this up with Johnny.
Thank you.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Okay!
Let's go! Unhitch it!
Hey, .hombres,
I understand that
the power of hurricanes
has almost doubled
in the past 30 years.
Now, whether that has
to do with global warming
doesn't much
matter to me,
but what does matter is getting
this place battened down. Now.
Hey!
Get me a rag!
Here, here, here. Shit!
I want you to keep
pressure on it, okay?
Like this.
Now, listen to me.
I want you to go to the
clinic down the road.
Okay. All right? They'll
take care of you.
They will not
deport you.
Now go.
And fast! He's gonna
lose that finger!
God damn it! I just said
unhitch me. We're staying here.
Get this place
boarded up!
Johnny!
Where are you?
What is this?
Johnny?
Where did the freezer
come from, huh?
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
That's a carnivore in there.
You understand?
Now, go back in the
house where it's safe.
Out here, not safe.
In the house, safe.
Now, go on. Run.
Hey! Where's my money?
What money?
My bank account.
You closed it.
Wait a second.
That's not your money.
Of course it is.
I went to the bank, I asked if
there were any other accounts,
they said just one,
co-signed by your mother,
so I took it out...
So, you stole it.
You doing drugs?
What?
Because drugs will damage
both the hippocampus
and the amygdala
portions of the brain.
That's where we
process memory.
Your memory's
a little foggy here.
I have to remind you that
your mom didn't leave a will.
She did.
Hey.
She wanted me to take care
of Tom. That's what she said.
Written on
a Post-it note.
Wasn't a Post-it note.
She wrote her wishes
for the future of you and
your brother on a note.
Nobody's happy your mom
swallowed a bottle of pills.
I also have
to point out,
in the absence of
any other information,
the money, this house,
goes to me.
Now, I don't know, if she'd
have wanted it any different,
she might have
written another Post-it.
Just don't do that.
Don't talk about her.
Look, I don't care what you
bought. I need what's left.
That's gonna be
a problem.
What?
I don't have it.
How? How could you
not have it?
You just got it out
yesterday, right?
I bought a tiger.
You're crazy.
People are gonna pay to stay
here, they want the real deal.
A Bengal tiger
is the real deal.
That money was for Tom,
for his care,
so that I could know
that he was all right.
Kelly, you don't have to put your
plans aside to help your brother.
Just leave Tom with me.
Damn it, Jose!
I said use the big screw!
Eat.
It's 5:30.
Want eat.
Right.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Look. Okay? There.
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
So, what are we
gonna watch today?
Want to try
something different?
Oprah? Ellen?
A little
History Channel?
Arrgh, matey!
Arrgh.
The Taylors.
Fascinating viewing,
even after the 785th time.
Arrgh.
Kelly, come closer.
I see my
8-year-old boy today.
We got
an 8-year-old pirate.
There's two, Tommy,
three, four, five,
couple more, six, my pirate,
seven, eight candles.
Let's light
those candles, Tommy!
Oh, it's a little
windy out here.
We got two.
We got two!
Make a wish and
blow them out.
Happy birthday, my good
boy. I love you so much.
I just want you to be
happy. Come on, nestle close.
This is Tom Lewis.
Hi, Mr. Lewis,
this is Kelly Taylor.
Hey, Kelly.
How's it going?
I'm glad I caught you.
Are you on campus already?
Is everything okay?
There's been a hitch.
Okay. What's going on?
Yeah, I'm just... I'm
gonna need a few months
to take care of
some family business,
and I'm just gonna
start second semester.
Kelly, you've deferred the
scholarship twice already.
This is about
your brother, right?
You're not his mother.
He has a stepfather.
Now, you need to make
the right choice here.
Otherwise, I am giving this
money to someone who needs it.
Mr. Lewis, I need it.
Okay, that's what
I want to hear,
because I am
really not kidding.
Kelly, if you don't show up,
there's nothing I can do.
That scholarship is gone.
Do you understand?
I understand.
This is
a big step for you,
but look how hard
you've worked for this.
Kelly, I really believe
you're making the right choice.
Thank you. Me, too.
Okay. See you soon.
Stop it, Tom.
I just need a minute.
This is my mad face, do
you understand? Stop it.
Don't touch!
Hey! Where did
you get this, huh?
This is Mom's.
Why have I not seen this?
What is this?
Have you taken
any of these, Tom?
Tell me right now.
Have you?
Seconal. Christ,
Mom, what weren't you on?
God.
Hey, Tom.
Time to go to bed.
After a
night of watching and waiting,
say good morning to
Hurricane Isabel.
Storm made landfall just
after 5:00 this morning.
We're talking
120-mile-per-hour winds
coming in
off the Gulf Coast.
If you're in
Montgomery County,
you are not in danger,
but don't worry.
We'll be here with
you the whole way...
Outstanding choice.
Hello?
Tom?
Damn it!
Tom, wake up.
Tom!
This is serious.
Tom, wake up.
Damn it.
You have reached
Montgomery County Emergency Services.
We are currently
experiencing a hurricane.
Please enter
your phone number,
and we'll call you
as soon as we...
Give me another.
Tom.
Where the fuck
have you been?
Come with me.
Come on.
Jesus.
Tom.
The tiger is
in the house.
Come on,
play the quiet game.
It's the quiet game.
Quiet game.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on,
come on.
Come on,
you piece of shit!
Damn it!
Let's go!
Come on!
Eat now. Eat.
Eat! Eat breakfast now!
Eat now! Eat!
Eat! Eat!
Want to eat!
Want eat!
Eat!
Want it!
Your breakfast.
Get dressed.
Yes,
stay in your room.
Tom.
Get dressed.
No touch. No touch.
I'm touching your shirt.
Look,
I'm not touching you.
No touch.
Come here.
Get out of there. Get
out of there. Get out!
What is this?
Enough with Mom!
Want her? Have her.
Where's the gun?
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Okay.
Move. Move.
Damn it!
Please let there be
a way out of this.
Show me the way out,
please, God.
Let there be
a way out of this.
What?
You bastard.
Are you out of
your mind?
It's in a cage.
It's not like it would be wandering
around the whole property.
How the hell are you gonna
keep this thing under control?
Starve it.
How's that?
You have
to starve them.
Hasn't eaten
in two weeks.
That's how you show a cat
who's boss.
And that's you?
I'm just trying to make
a go of it here, Maurice.
Uh-huh.
When Kelly goes to college,
and she will.
You know how
young people are.
Who's gonna
take care of that boy?
Well, you...
You've been a godsend
to those kids, Johnny.
KELLY: It's gotta be here.
Where is it? Where is it?
No! No touching!
I think we can go through the
laundry room, okay? You understand?
Let me go first.
Be very quiet.
No.
No, no.
Come on,
we gotta go.
No, stay!
Oh, my God.
So sorry
Mom left you, Tom.
She left me, too.
I'm sorry she did that.
But I'm not gonna
leave you, Tommy.
We're gonna get out
of here, right now.
And wherever I go,
you are coming with me.
No touch.
Don't move.
Go to the laundry room.
Go back. Go back.
We'll go around.
Get in the freezer.
I know you understand me.
Easy.
All right.
It's okay.
Tom, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Now, breathe slowly.
Just breathe.
Here's what's
gonna happen.
You're just
gonna fall asleep.
That's not so bad, huh?
I bet you're real tired.
Just close your eyes
and go to sleep.
Tommy, come on.
Come on.
Boy, Phil's
was a madhouse.
Everyone was there,
even Lindsay Bosier.
Tossing back
hurricanes.
Eight months pregnant. You'd
think she'd have more sense.
Some people, right?
Tom doesn't understand
what happened here.
He can't tell anyone.
So, you gonna
let us go?
You're not the only one
who wanted out.
Your mother was
gonna leave me.
You killed her.
Kelly...