23.976 English
[ Thinking ]
Dear Henry,
All I can think about
is White Fang and Alaska.
Alex, Belinda and I continue the repairs
on the hotel and will reopen soon.
I apologize again for leaving
you in the lurch, but...
after seeing the destruction
caused by the earthquake...
I now understand why they
were so desperate for my help.
In truth, though,
my heart is with White Fang,
and I will return to the claim
as soon as possible.
Thanks again
for taking care of him.
Or, is he taking care of you ?
By the time this letter
reaches you,
the ice will have thawed, and you will
have survived your first Alaskan winter.
Did you stand it all right ?
Spring is a great time
for adventures with White Fang.
Let him run, Henry.
Let him guide you.
He always knows the way.
Your friend,
Jack.
[ Barking ]
[ Henry ]
White Fang!
[ Barking ]
Wait up, boy.
White Fang.
[ Growls ]
[ Animal Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
[ Snorts ]
[ Growls ]
What the--
[ Barking ]
Sorry, boy.
Guess it's potatoes again
tonight.
[ Whines ]
[ Barking ]
C'mon, boy.
C'mon.
Atta boy, Fang.
Come on,
get a drink.
[ Growling Softly ]
Hey!
You lookin'for somethin'?
Huh, hey ! Howdy-hey there, boy.
Ha-ha-ha. Name is Halverson.
Lloyd Halverson.
Ha-ha.
I-I hate the name, so you
can just use what you like.
Now the, uh, wolf here,
I recollect him vividly. Ha-ha-ha.
I don't believe I know you,
though.
Where's, uh... Where's the other boy?
Uh, what's-his-name ?
You tell me.
Jack ! Hey ?
Jack, uh... Conroy !
Right, huh ?
Jack Conroy?
[ Chuckles ]
Always did have me a...
- mind for names,
all the good it done me.
- [ Snarls ]
Jack went back to San Francisco
about a year ago this time.
Is he, uh...
he your brother ?
Friend. He left me in charge
of his claim.
Yeah, me and Jack,
we, uh, set a spell.
What, uh... two, three years back,
when I was passin' through.
- I been west of here.
- [ Sniffs ]
Bellied up at least a dozen digs.
The whole country's been...
picked clean.
Sad to see.
What's your name ?
Henry.
Henry Casey.
You, uh... You here
all by yourself? Hm ?
Well, Henry.
How do I know you ain't killed that
other boy and just took over yourself?
- [ Barking ]
- Move on, Mister !
No ! Hold on, boy, hold on. I never--
Hold your water. I'm-- I'm leavin'.
- Get outta here !
- [ Snarling Fiercely ]
- Get a hold of him !
- He does what he wants.
Just don't move real fast.
[ Snarling Continues ]
I know what you're thinkin'.
You're thinking how you're gonna
spend your share. Am I right ?
[ Whines ]
[ Growls ]
My little pals.
Too many of you.
Gotta get you to Dawson.
Soon.
[ Metal Clinks ]
What is it, boy ?
[ Clicks ]
- [ Insect Buzzes ]
- Damn !
[ Soft Panting ]
[ Barking, Snarling ]
[ Snarling Continues ]
Yeow-ow !
Oww ! Ooh !
Oh ! Oh !
[ Barking ]
Down boy ! Down !
Agh !
Get this trap
off my butt, boy !
Or shoot me where I lie.
A-A-Ahh. Oh !
There'll be more
comin'through.
- [ Whines ]
- Gotta get that gold to a bank.
[ Moaning ]
Whatta ya say we...
drag out that raft ?
Float on into Dawson ?
- [ Whines ]
- We need supplies.
- You up for it ?
- [ Whines ]
- Okay.
We leave in the morning.
[ Whines ]
##[ Drum ]
## [ Haida Language ]
## [ Others Join ]
[ Whispering ]
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our--
I mourn the passing
of your father, Moses.
I'll pray for you
in your time to lead.
Thank you for sharing your food.
I'll return the favor.
We expect nothing
in return, god-man.
Get away from there.
Come on. Go, go, go.
- No, no.
- To refuse is an insult.
There is something of yours
I want.
Your soul, Moses.
Your soul.
- Safe trip back.
- You wonder why God's punishing you ?
We've done nothing
to anger your god.
And yet your people
are starving.
There must be a reason
for that.
My grandfather spoke often of the time
when the caribou would disappear,
a time when the thunder
in the earth would be followed
by the coming of the wolf.
If we are patient, we will be instructed
how to restore the balance.
These are stories, Moses.
You cannot live your life by that.
In your book,
there are stories.
If you care for your people,
you'll take them to live with
your relatives on the island.
You wear the same collar
as the one before you,
but your words are hollow.
Reverend Michael
underestimated the situation.
Why let this suffering
continue ?
Move your people
before it's too late.
It is good
you have a concern.
[ Haida Language ]
Thank you.
[ Wolf Howling In Distance ]
##[ Drum ]
##[ Continues ]
[ Eagle Crying ]
[ Wolf Howling ]
[ Moses ]
Lily.
You came to me in my dream,
you and the wolf.
You showed me the way.
You will leave in the morning.
- Where am I going, Uncle ?
- To bring back the wolf.
He will lead us
to the caribou.
- Where will I look ?
- He'll find you.
C'mon, boy. Boat's sailin'.
C'mon !
- [ Whines ]
- What is it ?
It's safe.
Look.
[ Whines ]
Don't you wanna go ?
Come on, boy.
Come on. Aw.
Good boy.
- Relax. Relax. This is the easy part.
- [ Whines ]
When the sun burst across the
horizon, it swept away the dark.
That's when Ice Woman,
your namesake,
led her people away from the ice
that crushed the villages.
This is her crest.
It will shield you
from danger.
Don't be fooled
by what you see.
The wolf is a powerful being.
He might not be visible to you.
He can change shape.
He might not be a wolf.
When I do find the wolf,
- what should I do with it ?
- You will know.
## [ In Distance ]
# Oh, my darlin'
Oh, my darlin'Clementine #
#You are gone
and lost forever #
- #And your shoes were number nine ##
- [ Whines ]
Hold on, boy.
It'll be okay.
## [ Haida Language ]
- [ Barks ]
- This look familiar, White Fang ?
- The water seems high.
Movin' right along, boy.
- [ Whines ]
- Hang on, boy !
[ Raven Cawing ]
[ Cawing ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Barks ]
Stay low!
Stay low, White Fang.
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
Ohh ! Oh !
Hang on ! Hang on.
[ Barking ]
- Hang on.
- [ Whines ]
- [ Yells ]
- [ Barks ]
- White Fang !
- [ Whimpering ]
- White Fang!
- [ Growls ]
[ Barking ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Barks ]
[ Gasping, Choking ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Barking ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Yelping ]
[ Raven Cawing ]
[ Barking ]
[ Barks ]
[ Whimpers ]
##[ Haida Language ]
## [ Continues ]
[ Growling, Whining ]
[ Growling ]
[ Whines ]
[ Whining ]
[ Raven Cawing ]
Who are you ?
Lily.
Where are we goin' ?
To my village.
Did you see a wolf?
Did he go
in the water ?
Did he
come back up ?
Where is he ?
Me ?
I don't understand.
Um...
Did he--
Did he get out ?
White Fang.
My gold !
I lost my gold !
- Sit down.
- No, no, no ! We have to go back !
- Be still !
- It's got to be somewhere
in this damn river !
I have
nothing left.
[ Raven Cawing, Dog Whines ]
She's here !
She's arriving !
[ Haida Language ]
To the water !
The canoe is arriving.
[ Haida Language ]
## [ Rattles, Chanting ]
##[ Continues ]
## [ Louder]
What's that all about ?
You.
[ Henry ]
Wait!
## [ Stops ]
Who is this,
Lily ?
This is the one, Uncle.
- This boy.
- I saw the change.
The wolf went under the water.
The boy came back up.
No, no. Now wait.
Just a minute.
No one changed
into anything.
The wolf was my friend.
I lived with him.
And I lost him
in the river.
You live with the wolf?
Yes, sir.
This is very good.
Welcome to our village.
I am Moses Joseph,
chief of the Haidas.
Henry Casey.
San Francisco.
Casey Henry.
Funny name.
Thank you.
Come.
[ Haida Language ]
## [ Chanting ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Coughs ]
At the time of my
grandfather's grandfather,
our mother, the earth, shook,
and part of the mountain
you call Devil's Thumb broke off.
Many of our people died,
but in return,
the Creator gave us
the caribou.
Each year they come to us
from Devil's Thumb.
For this reason, we respect
the mountain and do not go there.
For two years now,
the caribou have not returned.
Eight hunters went to find them.
They, too, have vanished.
Without the caribou...
the balance in our lives
is gone.
Without this balance,
my people...
slowly starve,
die, move away.
If my dream showed me
the way of this god-man,
I would ask my people
to move.
But the dream
told of the wolf...
that would lead us
to the caribou.
And now, Henry Casey,
you are here.
Me ?
Got the wrong man, sir.
I'm not much of a hunter.
I'm more of a miner.
That is very interesting.
Really.
That wolf your niece
saw me with...
was a pet.
He's the hunter.
He was something.
But he's gone now.
He could be alive inside you.
The wolf has the power to change.
Into me.
I guess that's okay
to believe, sir,
but I don't.
I'm no wolf.
[ Laughing ]
- [ All Chuckle ]
- I'm a man.
That's all.
[ Laughter Continues ]
This boy is free to leave
when he wishes.
Thank you.
I need supplies. I need to wire
San Francisco for some money.
There must be
a town near here.
When you are ready,
we can show you the way.
If it's all right with you, I'll stay
here tonight. I'll leave in the morning.
Good idea. Katrin can show you
where to lay down.
Sleep now, Casey Henry.
- We can talk again tomorrow.
- Okay.
[ Chuckling ]
He's a nice old guy, huh ?
Old guy is my father.
- Who are you in his house ?
- I didn't mean anything.
Henry, this way.
White Fang.
I should have known.
You don't see.
I didn't ask you
to bring me here.
- I sang the healing song for you.
- What's that supposed to mean ?
I gave you back your life.
Do you believe that stuff?
All you believe in
is your gold.
I'm grateful
what you did for me.
But I'm not gonna go to some
godforsaken place to hunt caribou.
We thought you were the wolf.
Sorry.
The wolf is a great hunter
with a warrior's heart.
You are like every other
white man.
Follow the river.
Before dark you will come to it.
- Major.
- [ Reverend ] You shouldn't be here.
I told you not to--
[ Indistinct ]
[ Reverend ]
Follow me.
- Yes, sir. Hyah !
- Let's go. Hyah !
Morning! Hi, there.
[ Henry ] I figured
the best thing to do is keep movin'.
- At least I wouldn't
be eatin'their food.
- [ Horses Whinnying ]
Then Lily,
the Indian girl--
She walked me to the stream
and pointed me here.
Why didn't you stay
and help them ?
Why ? I'll tell you why.
You're Indian, right ?
I thought so. So you probably
understand them a bit better than I do.
They believe...
s-strange things up there.
Like their dreams.
They need help.
I thought I saw some soldiers
while I was comin' in.
Where are they quartered ?
The army's in Dawson.
Huh-uh.
No, I just saw them.
You just saw somebody
passin' through.
So now you'll go home...
and forget these people
who helped you.
If I thought
I could help them, I would.
- They think you can.
- They think I'm the white wolf.
Maybe you are.
[ Conversing In
Haida Language ]
That's him, Uncle.
That's the wolf.
[ Moses ]
The other half. It's a good sign.
Good sign.
Don't be afraid, my brother.
Don't be afraid.
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Coughing ]
Sad, isn't it ?
[ Whooshing ]
##[ Drum ]
##[ Continues ]
[ Eagle Crying ]
##[ Stops ]
I'm goin' back.
[ Yips ]
[ Whines ]
[ Growling ]
Gentlemen.
Was there any mail for me yesterday,
Mr. Hale ?
- One for Rev. Michael.
- Uh, I'll take that.
How long you figure ?
Telegram will be there
in two, three days at the most.
Of course, when your money comes back
is another story.
[ Hale ]
At least a week, maybe more.
Can I get some credit ?
I'm leavin' for the village tomorrow.
I was hopin'to
take some food out there.
Sorry, kid. No credit.
I'll pay for it, Mr. Heath.
Give him what he wants.
All right.
I'm Leland Drury.
- Henry Casey.
- I couldn't help but overhear.
I go to the village often.
Their suffering is hard to ignore.
I have some mules
that know the way,
if you'd care to use one.
Yeah, thanks.
You're savin' me a trip.
Walks like a soldier.
Protestant.
[ Underbrush Crackling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Whimpers ]
You understand the problem.
I want him out of the way !
Do it now !
All right.
[ Mule Brays ]
[ Braying ]
[ Gun Clicking ]
This is for you.
Why would I wear this ?
I don't know.
I thought it would look pretty.
Pretty like a white girl ?
No. Tell you what.
Don't wear it.
See if I care.
Here, give it back.
What do I have to do ?
Look, I'm here!
And I came back
to find those caribou,
whether you
believe me or not.
Maybe one of these days
when this is all over,
you'll realize I'm not as worthless
as you think I am.
Henry Casey.
- He was here looking for you.
- Who was ?
The wolf.
- White Fang ? He's alive ?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure it was him ?
- Same wolf.
- Well, where is he ? Where'd he go ?
- Be patient. He will find you.
Lily. Go find Katrin.
Tonight we do the ceremony.
Mr. Heath ?
He's just a boy, Leland.
That boy could ruin
everything.
Do I have to do
everything myself?
##[ Chanting In
Haida Language ]
I shouldn't be down here.
Let the wolf
inside you free.
##[ Continues ]
## [ Continues ]
[ Wolf Howling ]
##[ Stops ]
[ Howling Continues ]
[ Villagers Muttering ]
That's White Fang.
Go. Go.
White Fang ?
Wait here.
Is that you, boy ?
- White Fang.
- [ Snarling, Barking ]
Aah !
- Hyeh ! Hah !
- [ Snarling ]
- Hyah !
- [ Snarling, Barking ]
- [ Barking ]
White Fang !
[ Whimpering ]
Come on, boy !
You found a friend.
Wow.
[ Moses ]
Henry Casey!
Moses.
Wanna come, boy ?
[ Panting ]
Okay.
That's okay.
[ Yelps ]
You missed me. I knew it.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Whimpers ]
The White Wolf.
These belonged
to my brother.
For the hunt.
I was wrong about you.
That's okay, Lily.
Sleep well...
White Wolf.
She likes me.
She likes me, boy.
This is tishlinjao.
Devil's Club juice
and saltwater.
For three days you will fast
and drink only this.
To hunt is a sacred act.
You must purify your body
to be worthy of the kill.
Your mind must be clear
of all else,
no distractions.
You care for Lily.
Yes, sir, I do.
Lily does not
yield so easily.
- She's tough.
- All Haida women are like this,
but Lily learned
when she was very young.
- Why's that ?
- Already death has
visited her three times.
Her mother, her father,
her brother.
All taken by the smallpox,
white man's plague.
So Lily has found
her strength.
It is out of your hands,
White Wolf.
Haida women do the choosing, and
the sun will set on top of my head...
before Lily yields.
Put her out of your mind.
That's not
gonna be so easy.
Drink this.
All the way.
Drink it all the way down.
More.
There you go.
[ Chuckling ]
That's a nice shot.
Hello !
Who's out there ?
Was that you ?
I can teach you.
Gently.
There's nothing else
in the world...
but you, this arrow
and the tree.
And you are all one.
Let it go.
[ Man Speaking
Haida Language ]
[ Peter ] We have the wolf.
Why do we need the boy?
[ Moses ]
They're one and the same.
[ Peter ]
In the dream, it was a wolf.
- Dreams have many shapes.
- But--
I know. I know.
This is very hard on you, son.
Be patient.
Your time will come.
[ Whimpers ]
Grandfather's bow.
- I couldn't take this, sir.
- You will need it.
Let Peter and Lily
come with me.
Women don't hunt.
Why ?
Old ways.
But, Peter,
can't he go ?
He's ready;
you know it.
I will speak
to the holy man.
How do I look ?
[ Women Chuckling ]
[ Speaking
Haida Language ]
[ Speaking Haida Language ]
You can go on the mountain.
You can hunt.
[ Screaming ]
Uncle, in the pack,
it is the female wolf who runs down--
- Lily, you can't go.
- But I am better than Peter
with a bow. You know this.
- Stop. My head aches.
- Who found the White Wolf?
He found you.
Moses.
What else
did he see ?
One will not return.
Where you come from
there are no women ?
You don't see them.
Only men.
No, no. There's women.
Beautiful women.
They're just too soft
for livin' up here.
- So you want a Haida girl.
- I want Lily.
My cousin's a princess.
Doesn't matter to me.
We don't buy presents.
If you want to tell a Haida girl
you care for her,
you come up behind her,
put your chin on her shoulder,
and you talk softly
in her ear.
That's it ?
- And she'll understand ?
- Or break your nose.
[ Chuckling ]
You don't choose a Haida woman.
She chooses you.
[ Speaking
Haida Language ]
Aw, man.
[ Bird Squawking ]
[ Lily ]
A miner's pack.
My grandfather's pole.
It tells of
a great Haida chief.
Bear clan.
His father, the Wolf.
Mother.
Calm Woman With Fish.
Raven.
My father.
To be remembered by a pole
is a great honor.
In my clan, there have been
many chiefs and warrior women.
I carry all of them
inside of me,
even those
yet to be born.
And they carry me.
We belong
only to each other.
And no one can
take that away from us.
Do you understand ?
Since I've been here,
I've even felt that way myself.
You know,
part of something.
I've never felt
more at home anywhere.
When you go back
to your world,
I hope you won't forget.
I'll never
forget you, Lily.
I won't forget you,
White Wolf.
The river delivered you
at my feet.
Lily,
there's gotta
be a way.
What do you
want me to do ?
Tell me. I'll do it.
- It's not possible.
- I wanna be with you.
- Don't talk like that.
- I want us to be together.
I'm LilyJoseph.
My grandfather was a chief.
I will marry
one of my own.
I wanna make this
my home.
I wanna learn your language.
I wanna be a part of this with you.
- That will change.
- No, it won't.
- You'll change.
- I'm not gonna change
how I feel about you.
You'll leave.
It's not possible.
- Lily.
- No.
Lily, please.
It's not...
possible.
Believe me ?
Believe me.
[ Bell Ringing ]
Get dressed, you pig.
- What for ?
- We're going to the village.
He brought us here.
A good sign.
Devil's Thumb.
[ Moses ] Beyond the mountain
you will find the path.
Follow it.
It will lead you to the caribou.
Morning, Moses.
Walk with me, Henry.
Have some good news.
[ Henry ]
Yeah, what's that ?
Friend of mine's shipping
a load of gold to Fort Tongass.
He needs someone to help
that we can trust. It pays $1,000.
That's enough to get you home and
then some, but you have to leave today.
I can't do that.
I gave Moses my word.
Tomorrow White Wolf leads a hunt
to Devil's Thumb.
White Wolf?
Henry Casey.
I'm losing my patience
with you, Henry.
These people might think
you're something special,
but I know you're not.
Now, I'm warning you,
don't go back up that mountain.
Warning me ?
What kind of
religion are you ?
The same as you, boy.
I don't know who you are
or what you want with these people,
but I know
it ain't right.
So why don't you pack up your things
and get outta here ?
- [ Snarling, Barking ]
- Don't show off at my expense.
It'll come back
and haunt you.
- [ Snarling Continues ]
- I said get outta here !
[ Barking ]
I'll pray for you.
Get the men ready.
The boy's going
up the mountain.
I brought you food.
Lily, I--
You were in my dreams.
- But that is where it must stop.
- Why ?
Because of who I am,
and who you are.
That is the way it is.
[ Peter]
Are you prepared to die ?
Nobody's gonna die.
You must be ready.
When I die, I will
come back as a raven,
live in the forest
behind the village,
make so much noise, no one
will be able to sleep. [ Caws ]
[ White Fang Barks ]
[ Barks ]
[ Growling ]
[ Twig Snaps ]
[ Limbs Crack ]
- [ Barking ]
- Whoa !
[ Barking ]
White man's tricks.
[ Yelping, Barking ]
[ Whimpering ]
I must cut him down.
[ Barking ]
What is it, boy ?
[ Whimpering, Barking ]
Peter !
[ Raven Cawing ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Gunshots, Barking ]
I could always
outrun a horse.
- Peter, no.
- Find the caribou.
Peter !
[ White Fang Whimpering ]
[ Whimpering ]
Peter.
[ Whinnies ]
Whoa !
- [ Moaning ]
- [ Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Explosions ]
[ Whimpering ]
Where's Peter ?
He went that way.
Lily, you should
go get help.
No. We stay together.
I'm goin' with him.
[ Barking ]
[ Eagle Crying ]
You found 'em, boy,
just like Moses said.
Look.
That's why the caribou
haven't returned.
That wall
is blocking the pass.
Come on.
Let's go find out
who built it.
[ Lily Screaming ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Barking ]
Are you okay ?
Where are we ?
Looks like the air shaft
of a mine.
Does your family
know this is here ?
This is a gold mine,
Lily.
- You know what that means ?
- Money.
Lots of money. That's why
they wanna keep you away from here.
- [ Men Shouting ]
- We gotta get outta here,
get some help.
The caribou will turn
and not come back.
- We can't help that.
- We need to knock down that wall.
- We need dynamite.
- Miners have dynamite.
[ Clanking ]
[ Thud ]
[ Rifle Cocks ]
Now !
[ Men Talking ]
Come on.
The hunters.
- This way.
- [ Henry ] That's Heath.
[ Heath ]
Come on! Get going!
[ Whimpering ]
Back to work !
- Back !
- [ Grunts ]
Stop ! Or I'll put a bullet
between your eyes !
[ Guns Cock ]
Is that you, Henry ?
Whoa.
Congratulations.
You're the first one
to get through.
Get back !
You sound
very sinister, Henry.
I've told you: You and I,
we have the same religion.
Gold.
Who are you ? I sure as hell know
you're not a preacher.
No. I'm just another
greedy American,just like yourself.
- I'm not like you.
- Oh, come on now, Henry.
You, if anyone,
should understand.
All this gold.
They aren't miners.
They never came up here.
- Who would it hurt ?
- Who ?
You starved these people
and stole from them at the same time.
That's not the way
I planned it.
I thought they'd move.
You're sick, Mister.
And you'll burn in hell.
Harsh words, Henry.
Very harsh words.
But I'm not gonna let you
turn on your own people.
I'm prepared to offer you a piece of
everything we take out of this mine...
from here on in.
What do ya say ?
It's not yours to give.
- Well, sure it is, Henry.
- Get back !
Do we have a deal ?
[ Groaning ]
Get him !
- Get him !
- [ Men Shouting ]
- [ Gunshots ]
[ Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
Come on !
- Lily !
- Go on, White Wolf!
Go ! Go !
[ Barking ]
[ Grunting ]
Leland ! Leland !
Let the boy go.
He's probably halfway
to Dawson by now to get help.
He's got dynamite.
He'll blow the wall.
- Get the girl.
- What ?
Get the girl !
Come with me.
Okay.
- [ Strikes Match ]
- I got him !
[ Gunshot ]
[ Ricochet ]
[ Growling ]
[ Barking ]
[ Grunts, Screaming ]
[ Muffled Shouting ]
Henry ! We're
leaving now, Henry !
Put her in the wagon !
[ Reverend ]
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Come on! Come on! Hyah! Hyah!
[ Raven Caws ]
[ Cawing ]
[ Gunshot ]
Hyah ! Come on !
[ Cawing ]
White Fang !
- [ Cawing ] White Wolf!
- Peter ! Wait !
Peter !
Where are we going ?
Hyah! Hyah!
- Hyah !
- [ Whinnying ]
Hyah!
Hyah ! Hyah !
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Yelping ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Lily ]
Henry!
Untie me !
- [ Groans ]
- I can't get it !
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
That's my gold.
Oh !
[ Panting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Shouting, Screaming ]
- [ Henry ] Here, boy!
- [ Whimpers ]
- White Fang !
- [ Whimpering ]
Here, boy !
[ Whimpering Continues ]
White Fang !
[ Grunting ]
[ Whimpering ]
Moses.
It's done.
Peter.
They couldn't catch my son.
They shot him in the back.
No.
That's impossible.
He was just running with me.
Right beside me.
Peter loved to run.
##[ Lily:Haida Language ]
Sleep.
I will watch him.
##[ Continues ]
[ Cawing ]
- Huh ?
- [ Cawing ]
[ Cawing Continues ]
Lily!
[ Barking ]
White Fang !
Come here, boy.
Come here.
- [ Yelps ]
- Here, boy.
Hey, boy, how you
feelin' ? Okay ?
Thank you.
[ Raven Cawing ]
That's Peter.
[ Caws ]
Just like he promised.
- [ Barking ]
- [ Cawing ]
Lily, would you stop ?
What is it ?
What's wrong ?
My gold.
[ Grunting ]
You found it.
Now you can go.
I don't wanna go.
Lily.
Lily !
Where will you go now?
I don't know yet.
Where's home ?
San Francisco.
But there's nothing
there for me.
Not anymore.
Nothing ? Not even
for a man with gold ?
Nothing
I'm interested in.
Nothing I want.
If you see Lily--
Thank you, Moses.
For everything.
It was you
who did the giving.
May the Great Spirit...
and all the spirits...
keep you and protect you.
You are a human being...
of courage and of honor.
When we speak of you,
it will be with pride.
[ Villagers Speaking
Haida Language ]
[ Man ]
Henry, come back in the spring !
[ Woman Shouting ]
[ Braying ]
[ Villagers Shouting,
Laughing ]
White Fang !
Come on, boy !
[ Barks ]
Let's go, boy.
Come on, let's go !
White Wolf!
White Wolf.
I choose you.
I choose you, Henry Casey.
[ Cheering ]
[ Whooping, Whistling ]
[ Laughs ]
Whoa !
[ Barking ]
[ Henry ]
Hey, White Fang !