You love me a lot...
So so.
Give me a beer and a brandy...
Who are your parents, kid...
RUJITZA is.
You're Zivina's child?
Fuck him.
He was my coach...
You look like him...
Your mum looks like him...
A proper lassie...
Known you when you were little.
Because you are old.
IT'S BEEN TEN YEARS
AND THREE DAYS,
WAITING FOR MY
SWEET, SWEET MOTHER
TO COME OUT OF JAIL.
IT'S BEEN TEN YEARS
AND THREE DAYS NOW,
WAITING FOR MY
SWEET, SWEET MOTHER
TO BRAID MAY HAIR.
I'VE BEEN ILL,
AND I'VE BEEN HEALTHY,
I'VE HAD MOONLIGHT,
I'VE HAD BRIGHT SUN
NEVER HAD MY
SWEET, SWEET MOTHER.
GLANCING AT MY BREASTS?
GLANCING AT THEM, YOU OLD BASTARD?
DON'T YOU LAY A FINGER ON ME,
MY SWEET MOTHER
WILL COME FOR ME,
NO ONE HERE
WILL EVER HARM ME,
SHE WILL WATCH OVER ME,
MY SWEET MOTHER.
THERE'LL BE BEER
AND FAGS,
THERE'LL BE MEAT
AND STREAMS OF BRANDY,
MY HAIR WILL BE NEATLY BRAIDED,
I WILL BE A GIRL
WELL LOVED.
A coffee, some fine food,
Couldn't give a fuck.
A sweet fruit juice, a healthy life
style, staring at the telly,
Couldn't give a flying fuck. O yes.
What do you have in store
for me, day?
...a load of shit, that's what...
,, Not Working Today!"
,, Singles Acomodation Hostel"
A fine peace of meat, I tell you
Such a fucking fine one!
The things that you brought, wow!
She comes over today
And flowers on top!
- The child's asleep.
- Good.
Let's have a wee drink.
No.
What's the fuck Beli?
You pussy!
Just a wee drink, mate.
Not me.
Suck it.
Huso, my old buddy,
You should see my son in law
No cock on him. Oh, yeah.
Get off,
Have a drink of water,
eat something.
It has to be nice when she arrives,
Go to bed.
Aw,
You broke my arm, you pussy.
Morning love.
Eat shit, get the fuck out,
Shame on you, you cunt.
You screwed up the welcome party?
The whore's coming out today.
I got the dog from downstairs.
Just picture that King,
She comes over to take my house,
- See what I mean?
- Yes...
She comes, and bam,
The dog swallows her.
She won't yake your house?! It's just
about fit for you and the dog.
Why whould she take it?
I'd give anything for Zivina's baby,
Anything, no doubt.
But the whore should die.
Die and rot, the whore,
Murdering my brother like that.
She murdered him, hey!
And when the day goes by,
And when the night has passed,
I'm on my way to my grave,
I'm on my way to my grave.
And when the flowers bloom,
When clouds all swell with rain,
I'm on my way to my grave,
I'm on my way to my grave.
And even though I'm young,
I'm on my way to my grave,
For I have no one,
No one to walk with me...
...all the way there
,, TO HIS BELOVED COACH ZIVINA.
THE KING."
Oh! How cold the soil is,
and I so long...
...for everything I don't have,
I don't have
I'm gonna work and work,
walk all the way to my grave,
if only...
...I had someone to walk me there.
Oh come my darling,
come now,
let's start our walk to the grave,
for I have no one,
no one,
to walk me there.
Are you hungry, dad?
Have you eaten?
You haven't, it shows...
I have, I have...
Don't fool me, love,
Eat something.
I've eaten.
You're such good girls,
My little birds...
Everything's the same at King's.
Give us a tenner if you go there.
I will.
She should go for a walk...
- Should I give her some money?
- Well, yes.
Granny's little bastard...
I wanna go somewhere.
No way!
It was my treat, shithead.
First time ever,
and I should kiss your arse.
Kiss it.
I have a house,
Around a house.
I have a pair of eyes,
Through the gate,
I have some bread
Around the bread.
I have a house,
Around the house.
I have flowers
Of all colours,
I have a drink,
Around the drink.
I have myself
And things to wear,
It's only you,
That I don't have.
Only my eyes
I do not have,
Arms I don't have
To hold me close,
No one to sing
My song for me,
Like long ago,
So long ago.
Arms I don't have
To hold me tight,
No one to sing
My song for me,
It's only you,
I do not have,
To look at me,
In the morning light.
Ah, Zivina,
My sweet brother...
You should see your daughter.
She's all grown up now.
King's so good
With your brother.
King is a proper man.
And I'm piece of shit.
He heard you. Cut the bullshit.
Ah, pal...
Everyone likes to live.
Well, he likes it too...
Just look at him...
Give my little brother a drink.
And the girl with him too...
Uncle's little beauty.
Uncle's pissed himself!
What are you laughing at?
You aren't even able to piss.
You'll piss inwards,
In your mouth,
You'll piss through your mouth.
That's how you look after
Your brother's child...
I look after her, and you're a whore.
Zivina, my brother
should have killed you,
Not the other way around.
My brother's six feet under,
And the whore walks in the sun.
Looking good, King...
You've got a fab watchdog here,
A fab one!
Home.
Let go!
A little something...
Do you do anything kid?
A little.
Don't.
You're not dangerous.
- You're not like your mother.
- What do you know?
The whole town knows.
Your father Zivina could carry bricks
In his shoes all day long,
And yet she did him in
With a butcher knife,
Your mother's vicious.
Zivina was beating her,
She beat him up once and for all.
Shut up...
I want to be with you.
- You're pretty.
- I'm ill. Get off, will you.
What do you want anyway?
Bugger off...
Put it away.
Bedtime...
Wow!
Someone's made some money abroad...
You look as if you were
on a holiday...
There's white on you head, King.
I'm just as I was.
Pour me something special...
I'm pouring...
What will you do now?
All sorts of things.
Good for you...
I love you, you know.
I don't love anyone.
Good for you.
Pour me some more...
I'm pouring...
Don't you need me?
You're all alone, King.
You're not getting any younger.
You're beautiful, Ruzica,
you make me hard,
Come over whenever you like.
That is it, Duchess.
Have you forgotten?
Cry when no one can see you.
Who was the one to visit you?
You were.
Who was the one waiting for you?
Just this one time, Ruzica,
Just this one time.
I'll never wait for you again.
Never again.
Why do you make me cross
Beli, you doll?
You've been making me
cross my whole life,
You snot.
Go on...
Doing great, doing great...
Don't, dont... Get up!
Let's go, let's go, let's go...
Go on, go on...
If I must have a life,
Why don't I have a mother?
Why don't I have a father?
Why are my sisters evil?
Why are my brothers beasts?
My mother is the gutter,
My father's the filthy stream.
My grandpa is the old sky,
My grandma is the long road.
If I bathe in a clear stream
Maybe, I'll come out young.
Someone might have me...
...for a wife.
...for a mother.
I don't like my mother,
I don't like the gutter.
What are you sitting there for?
I'm done cleaning.
Look at that...
What...
You've worked for a month,
You're only screwing things up.
What do you think life is about?
Did they leave together?
Did they?
Noooo!
What are you doing here?
What are you looking at, shitpot?
- You can't talk to me like that.
- Don't tell me what to do, bitch!
I am not a bitch. You are a bitch.
I should've strangled you
When you were a pound of meat.
I should've given you away.
I should've thrown you away.
I let you suckle on me,
for a whole year, bitch.
And now you turn into a monster.
Why are you sad?
My mother doesn't love me.
Who?
Me.
I don't know of anyone
Loved by his mother.
Your mother didn't love you?
You will.
No I won't.
My father might've loved me.
- Are you letting him have some pussy?
- Shut up.
She won't...
...you have to take it.
Shut up.
No one's throwing you out,
Better off staying with your folks.
Mine threw me out over
and over again...
Some bride.
Shut up, you.
God willing.
What do you want?
I'm bored.
I'm off to town...
Stay with me.
I'm going...
...for everyone to see me.
For whom to see you?
See if I give a fuck.
Shall I sleep here?
Go on.
Tell me something nice.
No.
Hope you die if you don't love me.
Hope to die.
Go there.
Here?
There.
You're looking at me, my love...
You're looking at me
And I'm thinking,
I'll die if you stop,
I'll die if you carry on.
I'd like to go with you...
...to the white world.
Here's a world for you...
Where is he?
Well,
You see,
He can take and mount that thing
And go where he pleases...
That...
Haven't seen my child
for six bleeding days.
You're used to longer than that.
You used to have a cock once, too.
It is what it is.
Look at how soiled she got here.
Fucking little fool.
She was a beautiful baby, dad?
You were a more beautiful one,
If you ask me.
She was bald.
Bald.
Did you love my dad?
Fuck off kid.
And my mother, did you love her?
As if you know what a mother is.
Did Zivina beat my mother?
Did mum and dad love each other?
Stop bugging me.
You want me to leave.
I want a break, baby doll,
I need some air.
You do like me.
Don't get boring.
- Did you get tired of me?
- What's the fuck to you?
I'm having a baby.
What?!
I'm having a child.
You stupid or what?!
Watch your mouth when you're
talking to me, you little scum!
If my father were alive today,
He'd fuck your dead mother.
My head hurts more and more
Ever since I laid my eyes on you.
Wait, I want to tell you something.
Both you and that slut of yours,
Can go fuck yourselves.
Let me tell you something.
I've been looking at you
my whole life.
I've looked after you my whole life
and you betray me.
You're nowhere to be found when there's
grief, only when there is fun...
- I didn't know...
- You come here now?!
I didn't know it...
I wish you were dead...
I'm not well.
You know how to fuck. Yet you
don't know how to buy a condom.
You're so stupid.
Shut up.
I'll be blind as a cock.
Blind as a cock...
Look,
That's not how King will do it.
- What do you want?
- A word with you.
I want to tell you.
I fucked it all up.
It's what it is,
I'm sick Duchess.
I'll go blind and then I'll die.
Nothing more.
Just a little while longer.
I want to make Rosa my wife.
Why her?
I'm fond of her.
She's pregnant with me.
That's why I sent her away.
You're gonna be a grandmother!
You're gonna be a grandfather.
What did you just say?
What are you saying?
Rosa is your child.
She's got nothing to do with Zivina.
Zivina knew.
He set out to kill you.
That's when I...
He gave her an ugly look, too...
...ugly...
What do you want me
to tell you, King?
Thanks for the chocolate,
You needn't have bothered.
Does he take care of her?
I couldn't give
a cunt's fart about that.
But thanks for chocolate.
All is gone, King, huh?
Is it hard... Huh?
It's always been like that for me.
Always hard.
By the crystal mountain stream...
There laid the woods and the greens.
And a worried maiden there,
Was speaking through her tears
Come back to me, my gallant hero,
come, so valiant and young
It's on your chest...
...on your chest, that I will die.
Your chest, all on fire.
We were born on the same year,
I used to carry your schoolbag.
My sister was raped,
My mother I never knew.
I was a child,
Grew up right then.
No one dared lay a finger on you.
You're the only one
who ever loved me.
Came to my house, ate and drank,
you're the only one
who ever loved me,
I'll wait for you in hell,
I'll take you by the hand,
That's where I will kiss you,
That's where I will...
...kiss you.
I'll go out for a while
And then I'll be back.
I'll be waiting.
Who's that?
Me, who else?
Check it out,
I got new tires.
And the heaters, and the handles...
A hundred horsepowers...
Can ride it to the end of the world.
I banged on, oh mother,
I toiled, oh father,
The pit took my days of youth,
The life took my days of joy,
Worked in foreign lands, oh mother,
Strangers'lands they were, oh father,
Bought a crazy horse
With greasy tires on it,
I own a pub, a great big pub,
Where people can rejoice.
The road was kissing me,
And the merry skies.
Now my old age is lonely, oh mother,
My old age is blind, oh mother.
I will never fly no more,
I will never kiss no more,
No more,
Never, no more.
I am the King,
Got me a daughter,
Got me a loving wife,
I am the King.
I banged on, oh mother,
I toiled, oh father,
The pit took my days of youth,
The life took my days of joy.
I am the King,
Who's got no eyes,
Who's got no nothing,
I am the King.
I'll never fly no more,
No more will I set eyes
on my loving daughter,
no more will I kiss my beloved wife.
A curse on the pit, oh mother,
A curse on life, oh father,
A curse on the king.
Who's gonna hear how I feel,
Who's gonna hear me cry,
Who's the King gonna cry to?
The King flees like a doe,
The King cries like a pussy,
The King is no more,
No more.
I am the King,
Who's got no eyes,
I'm the King,
Who's got no nothing,
I'm the King.
I know your scent.
What do we do now?
I'll let you have her.
Come tomorrow.
She must not know.
No.
Why won't you kiss me?
You're the only one I love.
I've been waiting for you
to stop being angry.
Kiss, I can't wait anymore.
- I'll never kiss you again.
- Why not?
You must kiss me.
No.
You have to!
- No.
- Please!!!
Mum...
Give me your hand...
Now the other...
You go with Beli now. You know.
Go on, mother loves you.
Go on, Beli, you doll,
That's how it is.
If you love Ruzica, love her child
and her grandchild too.
Go on...
Go on!!!
Alen Musovic - KING
- 1966-2009
We'll come to you, where you are,
To your festive tables,
To your shiny gardens,
We'll come to you, where you are,
Where you swine are fattened,
Where your gold is flowing,
We'll come to you, where you are,
We'll be saying, here we are.
We will drink from your eyes,
We will eat from your stash,
With golden spoons.
When the night falls,
When beloved night falls,
Our sad eyes won't show,
Our bare feet won't show.
We'll do it tomorrow,
And the day after tomorrow,
And then we will fall down,
We will fall down in rows.
Nothing will remain, oh!
The merchants will trade on,
The high and mighty
will stick to their kin,
There will be winter in spring.
The gutter is our mother,
Misery our sister.
Hunger rubs against her,
Our brother is the blade.
Blue sky is our father,
Blue sky so far away,
And the earth will kiss us,
Long into the night,
Closing our eyes,
Closing our eyes.