Hal is crying
Martha! Martha, what time is it?
Nine-thirty
Why didn앖 you wake me?
Because it압 Saturday
Harry? Want some breakfast?
What is it?
Pancakes
Later. l앐 working
Aw, Hal!
That little bastard been
bugging you again?
Don앖 call him bastard
Pardon me, Hal. l앏l get the paper
Why don앖 you go after breakfast?
Well, l want to look at the ads
l don앖 want to spend another day
looking at places we can앖 afford
l can go by myself
lt앇 be silly to leave here
Do you think the roads are clear?
They앏l be all right
Sorry l got mad at you
Hi
Watch it, honey. What압 this?
That smells good. Haven앖 had...
...anything to eat all night. Don앖
throw anything. Put them there
Harry, you look terrible
Your eyes are all red
You take good care of
your Daddy, don앖 you baby?
You just remember to eat those
Come on, Mac,
it isn앖 that cold!
Why youre hungry, huh?
Look what l got her, boy
There you go, huh?
There you go, Mac
ls this where Bill Schmidt lives?
Yes
Were friends of his from the army
ls he around...Bill?
We앇 like to say hello to him
He went to get the newspaper
Why don앖 you come in?
Thanks. Hey, Sarg!
l앐 Tony Rodr謁uez and that압
Mike Nickerson. Sergeant Nickerson
Maybe you았e heard Bill talk about us
He never talks to me about the army
Youre his wife, huh?
Sarg, l앏l introduce you...
l앐 sorry, Martha
Hello
Won앖 you come in and sit down?
Sit down
Bill won앖 be long
That압 a boy. Have
got friends visiting you...
Hello, Bill
Hello, Sergeant. Hi, Tony
Hi
Looks like you struck it rich
How many acres you got?
A hundred and seventy
Wow, that압 a lot, huh?
Well, it압 Martha압 father. Were
just care-takers. Free rent
Her old man pretty well off?
He압 a writer, Harry Wayne
He writes mostly westerns
Oh yeah, l았e read a dozen of his
books. Josephson had a whole stack
He works at night most of the time
Sleeps all day
Thanks
We couldn앖 afford this place
on what l앐 making
Harry Wayne, huh?
l thought he lived out west
No
What kind of job you got?
Oh, it압 in a plant near here,
that makes helicopters
Yeah, l know that압 funny
Theyre the same choppers we used
in Vietnam. l swore l앇 never go...
...near the army again. But the
work was there and l앐 doing it
Can앖 stop
What압 his name?
Hal
Hal!
Real cute little baby
Tired?
We았e been driving all night
You want a bed?
No
lf l앇 just lay down on that
sofa over there for a while
l앏l get you a blanket
Can l look around a little? l didn앖
know anybody had so much space
Sure
l앏l go with you
lt압 cold!
ls that your place, too?
Yeah. lt압 her old man압
ls that a lake out there?
lt압 a pond
Who압 dog is that?
That압 the neighbours
You got chickens, huh?
My uncle used to keep fighting
roosters in Puerto Rico. Bantams
This one압 too heavy to be a fighter
But he압 a lover
Shut up, Mac! Shut up!
Does he bites?
Harry wouldn앖 have a dog that
didn앖 bite, but he won앖 bother us
Who the hell압 that with him?
Just a friend from the army
There압 another one up here
Come on! You can walk on it
This ice is a foot thick
l thought you drained the water
and put a cover in the winter
No. ln the spring is drained,
painted and filled up again
Sounds like a lot of work
There압 a company...does it all
Everything압 taking care of, huh?
Yeah
We couldn앖 visit you last summer
We앇 have been sunbathing
But we were busy, you know
They threw the confessions out. Like
you read in the papers, ''Failed...
...to inform the defendant
of his rights
What about Reilly?
He압 still in
He didn앖 confess, see?
Boy, he is pissed off!
l mean, l앐 glad to see you
but l want... What?
l don앖 think youre glad to see us
What did you come here for?
l don앖 even know whose idea it was
We were both at Leavenworth
They gave us all our back pay,
for the whole years. We decided...
...why wait for transportation,
so we got the car
Jesus, what a bum! We broke down
outside Philadelphia last night
We had to wait all night in a garage
while a guy put a new head gasket
And we... started drinking
and talking about you
How did you know where l lived?
Sarge압 lawyer had your address,
in case you had to testify
l told it all the first time
Yeah, l know
Anyway, here we are
But why?
l just wanted to tell you...
What?
That l forgive you
Anyway, no hard feelings
No
We figured you must be worried,
thinking about what we might do
Yeah
So l wanted you to know that
as far as l앐 concerned...
...bygoes are bygoes
As far as youre concerned?
Yeah
Ssssss...Be quiet
He gets a little fussy sometimes
lt압 all right
l can앖 sleep anyway
Well, well. How is my baby?
Never mind, l앏l fold that
What?
Nothing
Do you want a paper to read?
No
Hey, you got a coke?
Sure
Where are the guys?
l think theyre still walking around
Thank you
Do you think l could...
...use your...
Yeah, sure. lt압 upstairs,
turn to your left. You앏l see it
Okay
Yes. Come on
There you go
Oh, you scared me!
You were in Vietnam with Bill?
Yes, madam
What압 it like?
Do you ever watch television?
Sometimes
lt압 just like it압 on television
Did you like it?
Like it? Nobody likes it
l meant the coutryside
ls it really so green?
l guess it압. After a while you
don앖 notice. Didn앖 Bill tell you?
Never talks to me about Vietnam
He was involved with some trial
...there, courtmartial
Yeah
You want stay for dinner? This is
too big. l앏l put in more potatoes
Maybe we can
Theyre there now, with my father
Want to meet him? He앏l like you
He was a sergeant, too,
in the Second World War
We never took any prisoners
in Guadalcanal. There wasn앖 time
We were outnumbered for
months. You don앖 know about that
You didn앖 even dare to leak into
the bushes. One앇 wait for you
And we didn앖 have the weapons
you guys got. Hands,...
...rifles, bayonets...any way
you got one of them was all right
How is your beer, Bill?
Fine
Maybe we need a little more wood
Even later, when we had ice cream
and movies, they used to come...
...and sit and watch. Bastards!
l admired them though. l don앖...
...think these North Vietnamese have
the guts the Japs did
But they keep on fighting
There, you don앖 know who압 your
friend. No sides but your own
So it압 easier to shoot everybody
Bill doesn앖 believe in fighting
You앇 got a job in a hospital,...
...patching a brave guys
l got shot at. By an old man...
civilian. He was scared to death
Did you shoot back?
Sure...over his head
You might have hurt him
What압 that?
God damn it, look at him!
Jesus Christ
Damn, look at that poor...
Spread some newspapers by the fire
Get some alcohol and some cotton
There he is
l told that son of a bitch
to keep his dog off my property
He can앖 keep him tied up all
the time! l couldn앖 find alcohol
Use whisky, for Christ압 sake
lt압 chewed almost all
the way through!
A three-legged dog. What
the hell l앐 going to do with him?
l told him next time the dog came
on my place l앇 kill him
Kill his dog, he means
You can앖 hit him with a pistol
l can damn well...try
You need a rifle
l았e got a shotgun, but at this
range it앇 just tickle him
We got a rifle in the car
Six point five millimeter
Yeah, it압 Swedish
The Great Dane again?
What are they gonna do?
ls your father
Harry, you can앖 just shoot
the man압 dog
Mac압 the one who picks the fights
Yeah, he압 tough
Let압 go
You need something to rest it on
Not at this range
l don앖 even really need the scope
Can앖 you stop them?
Legally he압 within his rights. That
dog attacked you once, remember?
Why the hell didn앖 you
shoot it then?
Perfect
Tony don앖 miss!
Nice looking dog
Do you want to bury him?
Bury him! l앐 gonna dump right
at that son of a bitch압 door...
...and let him do something about it
Those are the men, aren앖 they?
What men?
You았e to tell me about it now
We were just supposed
to look for supplies
By the third day we hadn앖
found anything and Nickerson began
to get edgy. We get to this village
lt was marked friendly on the map
But Nickerson got everybody out
and search the huts for arms
We lined them while he
and Tony looked the place over
They thought we gonna shoot them
l think Nickerson almost did
He was so angry about
not finding anything
Well, in the last hut
a girl was hiding
Nickerson pretended
she was a Viet Cong. Then he told...
...one of the old men in the village
that we took her as a hostage
What did she look like?
She was young, 15 or 16. Pretty
l guess that압 why she was hiding
That압 what her mother said
at the courtmartial
A couple of miles up the road...
Nickerson took her into the tall grass
The sound she made was...
...well, after a while
it was like...
...like Mac down there
lt was just...whining
And then Reilly went next
Josephson... Tony
And then they were waiting for me
to do it. l couldn앖 move
lt didn앖 take any thought of bravery
l just couldn앖 walk
Nickerson looked at me
For a long time, you know the
way he does...looks at you
He had a rifle in his hand
He handed it to Josephson, jerk
his thumb toward the grass and...
And you turned them in
When we got back to camp
lt was the bravest thing you앇 do
l should have stopped them. What압
the point of punish them afterward?
Criminals have to be punished
The Viet Cong do the same thing
Everybody does, every day...
Why blame these guys?
They were my friends, my buddies!
Let압 go home, boys
Sound off! One, two, sound off!
...three, four...
Take it on down! One, two, three...!
What did they come here for?
lt wasn앖 because of the scenery
Tony said thet he wanted
to tell me that...
What?
That there were no hard
feelings on his side
Shit!
l knew the Jerries were
in there. l take a granade...
...l pull the pin.
Got up, open the door...
...Oh, Officer
Come on in
Call the police
What would l say, l앐 afraid of
these guys? Yes! You know, l am
l thought about it every
day since it happened
But l can앖 do it to them again
They don앖 even know why they came
All right! Don앖 call the police
Here we go! Come on!
Pass it to me!
lf they bust up your meeting, it압
pigs. lf you need them, it압 police
Yes, that압 funny, Bill
Yes. Wait a minute
The football game is on
Harry wants to watch it on your set
Oh, Christ! l don앖 give a...
Sure, Harry. That압 fine
Hey, kid, you got the
set warmed up yet?
l didn앖 know it was on yet
Hell yes! Come on
Were gonna miss the kick-off
Hey, Bill...ayyyy!
See you in a little while
Bill, how do you adjust this thing?
Later
lt압 crowed. The Tigers
and the Blue Panthers are...
...in the playground. The match
will be interesting...
...cose both teams are equaled
at general classification
No player in the entitle
alignment is been missed
There will be tension
during the match
Thanks, kid. Want a drink now?
Yeah
Here it comes. Just in time
He dropped it. Atta boy!
Come on, baby!
Don앖 let him...for pete sakes!
Come on. Get him!
Hey kid, why don앖 you bring us
some ice and glasses in here...
...so we don앖 keep running
back and forth?
Look out! Look out!
Go, go, go!
Twenty-five yards!
Now let압 go!
There you go, kid
Theyre gonna beat them, right?
Come on now. Let압 not have
another funeral like last week,...
...huh, Mike?
The Blue Panthers try to
brake Robins압 stroke
Football is a great game. Elemental
Because it압 a conflict
That압 what life is about
lsn앖 it?
lf you make it
Always. Life against death
Like in Vietnam
We just see one corner of it...
...above the surface
Youre mixing your metaphors Harry
Look at the football field
Each team압 got one color jersey
That압 easy to see. But the world
is set up the same way
The communists on one side,
and us on the other
lf you앇 face that,
look at Vietnam in the context...
...and you앇 understand it
Right now Europe is stabilized
Power is shifting in Asia
Vietnam is the fulcrum
That압 what they tell us
You앇 better believed it, soldier
Looks like a duel between
the two players who...
...we are talking about
Tiger압 new man압 caught...
...the ball. A good opportunity
to show his game
How압 your beer holding
out there...Hal?
You never did like it
very much, did you?
Did you?
What the hell am l gonna do
with a three-legged kid, huh?
Come on!
Why he was out of bounds!
Let압 see the play-back!
Pardon. You know...l watch
football, l notice one thing
What압 that?
There aren앖 any Puerto Rican guys
playing. Did you notice that?
Yeah, why is that?
l don앖 know. They았e got plenty
of Puerto Rican baseball players
Yeah, stars. But not football
Theyre too small to play football
They don앖 eat the right foods
They eat too many chili peppers
lt압 a racial difference
The first part is ended
He got back in,
finds a lot of daylight
Racial difference. lsn앖 that illegal?
They can앖 play cose theyre too
small, not cose theyre Puerto Ricans
Some people are naturally smaller
than others. Like Orientals
l앐 not goddam slopehead!
Just an example, Christ sake!
When l was in college, that압
what it was all about. Football
Everybody wanted to play football
Even the guys that spend most
of their time in the library,...
...secretly wanted to play
football. You know why?
Why?
Football players got more pussy
Not that anyone got a lot
but the football players got more
A guy your size could play college
football if he was strong
The pressure the Blue Panthers
did during the second...
...time has decided
the final result of the game
Now the kids give it away to
each other. They don앖 ask for it...
nicely. There압 no challenge to it
So, who the hell wants...
...to play football? l asked
once some of Martha압 friends...
...if they wanted to watch a game,
they looked at me as if l앐 a freak
Where the hell is Bill?
He went upstairs
l don앖 know
Why shouldn앖 they act the way
they do if they get away with it
Nobody cares anymore
She압 a cute looking girl
Martha?
They aren앖 married, huh?
No
Get him, you stupid son of a bitch!
The baby압 nice
He smiles all the time
Broke his arm
No, he압 all right
Look at it. lt압 hanging there
Yeah, the baby is all right
l always wanted a grandson
l don앖 even know what this kid is
ls he my grandson? ls that
what l should say to people?
l don앖 know
Ya hemos visto todo
lo que hab眼 que ver
You know...he looks
a lot older. Bill
His hair is getting a little gray
Do you remember how he...
...looked when he first
got over? Like a little kid
Goddamn!
l hope dinner압 ready soon
because l got to get to the city
What압 your hurry, Tony?
l got to see about getting a job
Tomorrow is Sunday
There압 a guy l can talk to
Yeah, he앏l really give a job
to an old war hero like you
l wish you guys would stick around
a couple of days. lt압 great...
...to have someone to talk to
l bet you앇 like to use that...
...rifle again. There압 a moon
tonight and there압 a cop l know
He압 gonna be coon hunting
back in my woods. We could...
...all go there
Hell, they았e got two bedrooms...
...upstairs they don앖 use!
Right, Bill?
Yeah, theyre empty
Christ, what a weirdo! See that
l shot that bear and now look at it
Martha! What time is dinner?
As soon as we get the table set
What압 the matter?
Nothing
Nothing압 ever the matter
Harry wants them to stay a couple
of days. l don앖 think they앏l stay
Bill, this is our house and...
The hell it is. lt압 Harry압!
lt압 as mine as Harry압. Because
it압 mine, it압 yours. lf you don앖
...want them to stay,
tell them to get out now!
He was in some trouble
in Vietnam. Do you know about this?
We were it
Yeah? What happened?
l was leading a patrol
We found a woman, a Viet Cong
Had to shoot her, couldn앖 take
her with us and Bill turned us in
He turned you in for that?
Well, we had a little fun with her
first. That압 what made him mad
He didn앖 even touch her
l always thought he was half queer
There압 salad in the ice-box
l앐 surprised
you didn앖 slit his throat
l thought about it a lot
when l was in the stockade
But then, what압 it gonna get me?
Dinner is on the table!
Oh
Do you want to carve, Harry?
Sure
Mike
How do you like it, Mike?
Rare. Still moving,
if you got it
Tony, how about you?
A little rare
He likes it burnt
We forgot the water
Oh! Son of a bitch!
Will you let me look at it?
l hardly felt it
Come on, let me wash it
Hold still! You need some stitches
No...it압 nothing...
Harry, please don앖 drink anymore
l think you았e had enough
Harry...
That Mike압 quite a guy, isn앖 he?
Did he tell you what
Bill did to them?
What Bill did to them?
You all right, Harry?
lt압 just a scratch
l remember one time...
...a Filipino captain was
trying to make one of them talk
He took him out in a boat and...
...he cut off his hands. One by one
And he dropped them into the water
Harry, be quiet
And then... his arms
And he watched...
...the sarks eat them
Harry...
Martha...
l asked these boys
to stay a couple of days
Thanks, Mr. Wayne
but l really got ot get back
l think...there might be
a book in them. Yeah
Harry, they don앖 want to stay
Well...
We앏l talk more about it
tomorrow afternoon
l have a work to do
in the morning
Well...where압 my cap?
Thanks
l think...
Thank you very much
Harry...have you got your glasses?
Do you think he앏l make it?
He might bleed to death
l앏l check on him later
He압 a very interesting guy
Do you think so?
Yeah. He압 been through it
My mother couldn앖 stand him
Neither his other two wives
Well hell, l wouldn앖 want
to be married to him either
l았e had to get Hal압 dinner
We better be going
Let me make you some coffe before
you go, if youre going to drive
lt앏l just take a few minutes
Please, sit down
Bet it압 nice around here
in the summer
Yeah
Great chow
Martha is a great cook
Dammit, Hal, you know
you liked creamed corn!
Come on, Hal!
Miss, youre a pretty woman to get
angry. Wait till he압 hungry
A lot you know about it, don앖 you?
He has to eat his vegetables
Yeah. So he can grow up big
to be a football player
Bed for you. Hal has
decided he wants to go to bed
Say goodnight to everybody
Goodnight, Hal
Goodnight, bambino
Want to say goodnight to Hal?
Goodnight, Hal
What kind of job
are you looking for?
Who the hell knows!
You used to be interested in cars
Yeah. l think l앏l get myself
a job in a garage
To get the experience
The most important tool in any
garage is the stem cleaner. l know
...this guy named Feldman
He has a garage near the river
A guy comes in with his car
He doesn앖 know a thing about cars
But comes over and starts
saying, ''that transmission is...
...about to fall out''. He says,
Bill, ''and it압 a good thing...
...you brought it now''. Everybody
knows about the transmission
You know what l mean? You
tell a guy his valve lifters are...
...shot, he gets worried
But the transmission, you았e that
The guy comes back the next day
and Feldman shows him a...
...shiny clean transmission. lt압
the same! He used the steam cleaner
You know what l mean?
Gracias. Now...
Rebuilt transmission, right?
A 180 dollars, maybe even more
Hal, l simply can앖 stand another
night of this! What압 the matter?
Come on
Goodnight
With all that back pay,
maybe Feldman앇 let me buy...
...a piece of his place, huh?
Hell, l don앖 even know
if his garage is still there
Tony does all the driving. Will your
father mind if l았e a little?
He앏l think he drank the whole
thing himself when he wakes up
He압 really a famous writer?
He writes a lot of books and
a lot of people buy them. lt압...
...like a compulsion. When he gets
going, he stays all night writing
Theyre good books?
A long time ago,
they used to be
The first two he wrote
were really good serious books
But now he압 full of anger and
self-disgust. The books are empty
Theyre good stories, full of
dramatic events and...
...flashy characters. Easy to
read. l enjoy reading them, but...
...they are meaningless
l liked what he said about
being a book in Tony and me
Bill told me what you did
ls it true?
Sure, whatever he said
What made you do it?
Everybody was doing it
Why pick on me?
Why pick on that girl?
She was a Viet Cong
She was hiding from us
You proved she had
a damn good reason to hide
What do you think a Viet Cong
looks like...wear a uniform?
They don앖 look different
than anybody else over there
Listen, your husband cost me
two damn good years over there
He didn앖 cost you a thing
and you know it!
l forgot he압 not your husband
What kind of arrangement is that?
My living with Bill has nothing to
do with morality! Youre sick!
l see, you can judge me,
but l can앖 judge you
What hurts someone else is immoral
That압 the only standard you can have
And your father? lt tears his guts out
the way youre living
That압 his problem. lt압 different
from stick someone with a bayonet
ls that what Bill told you?
Sorry, all you did was shoot her!
We couldn앖 take any prisoners
on patrol. That was orders
The solution to the problem
Nothing can justify what you did!
l don앖 have to justify it
The Army already has
Why do you think l앐 here?
We were heroes to our boys
And Bill?
He got shipped out of combat area
lt was good cose you can get shot
Because he reported a crime
You got to do things in war that
you get locked up for in peacetime
Do you think l앐 some hoodlum?
l was an honor student in...
...high school. And l was a good
soldier, more than he was
l앐 glad
Oh, you got it safe here
You don앖 know until you
have been there, been shot at
What would you do,
lie back and take it?
Until you았e gone
through a village...
...handing out candy
bars to the kids
And then you see your best
buddie압 legs blowed off by a mine
...because the people you
gave the candy bars to,...
...forgot to tell you
Charlie was in town
That happened?
lt happened!
Youre right. l haven앖 been
there and l can앖 imagine it
Man....l couldn앖 wait to get
back to the folks
The first thing you notice in the
city is people. The way they walk,
especially if theyre important
The whole city is in a state
of warfare. Just like over there
Did you ever march in one of
these peace parades? Carry a sign?
Why?
l don앖 know. You liked somebody
who앇 march in a peace parade
l used to wonder over there what
kind of people went to those things
l thought they were long-haired
freaks with clothes like lndians
Bill asked me to marry
him once. Before the baby was born
He was gonna do me a big favor
Youre a real old
nut-cutter, aren앖 you?
Dance?
My uncle압 got a restaurant
Leave it in the sink
l could work there for a while
lt압 a big responsability,...
...having money to invest
What압 that?
Coon hunter
Coon hunters, huh?
Yeah, give it time, Tony
Hey, Sarge!
Let압 get the hell out here!
What압 going on?
That압 enough. l said that압 enough!
You better go now
Come on!
You really want to go?
Go away! Stop it!
Come on
What압 the matter with you?
Stop it!
Look out, Billy!
Shoot him! You았e got a gun,
haven앖 you? Shoot him!
Go on!
You앏l be okay, Bill
Lady, youre nuts
You think you can change...
...the rules in the middle?
Well?
Are you all right?