With the Japanese birth rate
falling below 1.3 per woman in 2003...
...thls is 'the era of few children. '
Government measures
to counter this have been in vain...
...and nothing seems to stop the trend.
Why have women stopped
having children?
Some cite women's advance
into the workforce.
Others blame uncertainty...
...over the country, society,
and their economic future.
Stlll others fume that today's women
believe they will lose their freedom..
...by having children.
Here now is one of these women.
Yoko Sasaki.
An English graduate from a top school,
she Is a magazlne editor.
Having a baby
is the furthest thing from her mind.
Did you read my flea-market article?
Rewrite.
Why?
It's repetitive, out-of-date,
and the English is wrong.
'Flea' isn't spelled 'F R E E'.
It's not?
That's a pretty basic mistake.
How do you spell it?
Look it up.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr Takahara...
I haven't seen that facing-page proof.
I sent that to the printer.
What? I haven't checked it.
It's my project.
As Assistant Editor,
you need to have some faith.
Last time I had faith,
you got that potter's name wrong.
Tell the printer to hold the page.
Oh, all right.
Good morning.
Good morning. Have I got
the conference room at 10?
I'll make sure.
Oh, and the Chief Editor
would like to see you.
About what?
Oan't it wait?
I'm busy this morning.
He says it's important.
Yes?
Good morning, Sasaki.
You're looking lovely.
Your whole look... I love it!
Diet? Exercise? How do you do it?
I'm getting a little metabolic..
I'm sorry, but I have a meeting.
Can we cut to the chase?
Oh... sure.
I was talking to the president.
He wants to start a new magaz ne.
For young women
white-collar workers.
'Fashionable', 'intelligent'..
...'contemporary'.
He asked me to run it,
but I've got enough work as it is.
I suggested you.
You're still a bit young,
but this is a job for a woman.
Well?
Um...
Uh, well...
OK?
Of course!
Oheers!
So your dream's come true, Yoko.
I guess so.
After decades of mak ng copies
and bringing tea...
It's not 'decades'!
How old do you think I am?
Fending off eager males
and sexual harassment...
More 'jealous' than 'eager'.
That's been hard.
They all hate competent women.
As...
...we both know.
So how's everything?
Still the same.
Did they transfer that
horrible sweaty old guy?
They promoted him.
Oan you believe it!
What?! Why?
Hey, it's a man's world.
They all hang out together.
That's right!
I'll tell you all about it.
Shall we get drunk, then?
Waiter, could we see
the wine list?
Ma'am?
Ma'am, we're here.
I had way too much to drink.
Good morning.
For cramps...
how about this?
That'll be fine.
Will that be all?
Something for
an upset stomach...
...and a test kit.
A test kit for what?
Uh, you know...
To see if you're...
Forget it. I'm in a hurry.
Oh, a pregnancy test kit!
Posltive
Ms Sasaki, are you in there?
What?
We're waiting for you.
Yes, I know.
I'll be right there.
Please.
In the hand-outs...
...are f rst-half sales figures
for Strade.
You can see that sales are down.
Soon our competitors
will overtake us.
How are they doing?
They're printing more copies.
What do we do, Sasaki?
Ms Sasaki?
I'm sorry?
Is something wrong?
Uh, no.
Her head seems full
of her new magazine...
It's true sales are down.
Our competitors have introduced
new titles. It won't last.
We have plans to f ght back.
Do they include you appearing
in the magazine again?
The model we took to Vietnam
got sick.
I had to fill in.
We'll regroup and do it again.
Is it worth redoing?
Do you have any ideas?
Yes.
May I?
Certainly.
I suggest we offer
a Strade original-mix CD.
It will contain music
from around the world...
...chosen by our editorial staff
as they travel the globe.
The Third Month
Hiratsuka Gynecology Cllnic
Hello.
Uh, h.
Come on in.
No, I'm fine.
Hey! Hey!
Oome on, come on!
It'll be OK!
Go on in.
Harue!
Mayumi!
Where have you been?
I went out to my in-laws'.
My husband had a business trip.
Wouldn't it have been easier
to just stay home?
Oh, hey...
Here's the reception.
Uh, yeah...
Here.
Thank you.
So the visit went well?
I couldn't lift a finger.
It's their first grandchild.
Um...
Yes?
I don't have an appointment.
Is that all right?
No?
Oould you fill this out, please?
All right.
Hey...
Oandy?
Uh... no, thank you.
Is this your first time?
Yes.
I hesitated there
my first time, too.
This is my fourth.
Fourth?!
So ask away.
What does your husband do?
You're not married? He is?
No, no...
I don't even know
if I'm pregnant yet.
Didn't you check?
Yes.
Then you probably are.
Those test things are pretty good.
They are, are they...
Be sure and bring him next time.
Men have no idea
what having a child involves.
My husband brings me here and back.
For the births he takes time off work.
You need to educate them.
Get mad if they complain.
Ask them, 'What matters more,
the baby or your job?!'
Ms Sasaki, the doctor
will see you now.
Ooming!
Good luck.
Right.
Congratulations.
You're in your th rd month.
I am, am I...
Is that bad?
This isn't a good time
for me to be pregnant.
Is it a complicated situation?
Not so much 'complicated'...
Have you told the man?
Not yet.
We're not married, anyway.
In any case, he should be told.
Even if that's hard to do.
No, no, it's not like that.
He's not married.
He's... in Vietnam.
He's Vietnamese?
No, no, he's Japanese.
He's in Vietnam.
We're not engaged,
he's not even a boyfriend.
But you're at least close enough
that you're pregnant now.
That was
a heat-of-the-moment thing.
Or the heat of the alcohol.
I have no intention
of having a child by him.
The child is not yours alone.
It's his child, too.
Hello? It's me.
I've called and called
and I couldn't get through.
What? You're still there?
Yes, I need to talk to you!
About what? Well, uh...
Are you coming back?
Well, come back! It's important!
Oan you hear me?
Go find a place with signal!
I told you, it's important!
I need to see you!
I can't go there! I'm busy!
Oh, all right! I'll tell you!
Are you sitting down?
A baby! I'm pregnant!
Whose?! Yours!
I'm pregnant with your child!
Damn it!
Th s way.
Well?
When was your last period?
One moment... uh...
I'm asking her.
I wouldn't know.
Is she, you know...
About six weeks.
She is, is she...
But how?
You're on the pill.
I give it to you every month.
He is not the father, I take it?
Get r d of it.
I'm sorry?
That's not enough?
OK, this is
to keep quiet about it, too.
Don't tell anyone.
I'm not having an abortion.
I'll take him
for everything he's got.
You planned this?
Of course I did.
The whole thing.
I assume you'll write me
a Oertificate of Pregnancy?
All right. Tomorrow, then.
Hello.
Where's the stuff on
the Vietnam special?
What? I thought
that was cancelled.
Who said that?
Mr Takahara.
The Ohief Editor agreed.
What are we going to run instead?
Don't worry.
I've got it covered.
If you don't like it,
talk to the chief.
There's a visitor waiting for you.
A visitor?
Yes.
Over there.
Who's he?
I don't know.
He said he knows you.
Hi.
I flew back steerage class.
What are you doing here?!
What am I doing here?
You told me to come.
Last night.
I couldn't stay there
now you're having my child.
I went straight to the airport
and bought a ticket.
Here.
What?
A souvenir.
Child?
What?!
Hey, wait a minute...
Everyone! Your attention, please!
We're pregnant!
Right?
Peek-a-boo!
So your husband came, too...
He's not my husband.
He's married?
No, he isn't!
Chocolate?
No, thank you.
He has to acknowledge paternity.
What for?
Otherwise he's not liable for support
and the child has no right to inherit.
Is that true?
Yes.
If he dies, you'll have nothing.
I doubt he has much
a child could nherit.
Maybe not.
Anyway, I still haven't decided
to have it.
What?!
See? I told you!
I got pregnant!
Looks that way.
That's ¥8,500.
Yuh! Aren't you happy?
Sure, I am.
It just hasn't sunk in.
Let's think of a name!
A name?
There's your receipt.
Not yet. We don't know
if it's a boy or a girl.
I'm sure it's a girl.
Let's give her a foreign name.
Like what?
Like Christel, that announcer...
Her dad's French!
When she gets bigger
I'll dress her just like me.
Then the three of us
can go shopping!
Yoko Sasaki...
Yes!
Come on!
See you later!
Hurry up!
You sure have a lot of stuff.
Hey, it's everything I own!
Oonsultation Room
Tetsuya Kudo...
Yes!
So you are the father?
Yes.
I'm glad you're finally here.
So... is it a boy or a girl?
We can't say for sure yet.
More importantly,
have you made up your mind?
Oh, dear...
That's a problem.
Hey! What's this all about?
Honey, you don't mean..
You don't call me 'honey'!
After all, what is there
between you and me?
It was just that Vietnamese liquor
you pushed on me after the shoot.
That damn nep!
You seemed to like it.
Anyway, it was just a one-off.
I was drunk.
A 'one-off'?
Well, you know...
A two-off, actually.
An error of youth.
'Youth'?
Shut up.
This was not in the plan!
Life's like that.
Sometimes one-offs
make you pregnant.
Anyway, I'd like
the two of you to talk.
Yes!
You're not going to do
anything stupid, are you?
Have the baby.
Do you hear me?
It's this way.
Have my child. Please!
What are you doing?!
Stop acting like an idiot!
Hey, wait!
Wait! I'm coming, too.
Go away!
Drive.
Ow!
Mother?
That Ms Sasaki
was here again today.
She's still thinking.
I hope she has the baby.
May I ask your name?
Thank you for your help.
Hello?
It's the superintendent...
Yes?
Not homeless.
Oontact Yoko Sasaki.
I found him
when I put out the garbage.
I'd have called the police, but..
Do you know him?
Yes... in a way.
I'll leave him to you, then.
What?! What?!
Hi.
I didn't have any money,
so I walked all the way.
It was past 2 a. m.,
and I didn't want to wake you.
But there was a beautiful moon.
It felt great.
I could use some coffee, too.
OK?
No.
Thank you!
Why are you here?
The doctor said
the two of us should talk.
I don't want to.
It just means we'll have a kid.
You won't be having it.
I will.
Well, yeah..
But I cooperated
in the production process.
I'm scared.
Having a baby w ll mean
a huge change in my lifestyle.
I won't be able to work
morning till night like I do.
Is your work that important?
Do you realize how hard it's been
to get where I am?
Good morning.
Where's everyone?
Uh... in the conference room.
Why? Is there a meeting?
These are the five ideas
for the new magazine's name.
We will decide based upon
what our competitors are doing.
Turning to page 2..
What's going on?
Uh, well...
Chief, what's going on here?
I thought I was runn ng this.
Oongratulations, Sasaki.
I'm told you're pregnant.
Uh, yes.
What a surprise! I never imagined
you having a child.
That's the greatest happiness
a woman can know, I guess...
...as the president
was just say ng.
Uh, Sir, I...
We had great hopes for you
as our first female Ohief Editor.
But we can't stand in the way.
Make a happy home
for your family.
But I don't intend
to stop working...
Sasaki..
...I understand how you feel...
I'm not hav ng the child!
But you already have it...
I'll go to the hospital right now
and have it taken care of!
Ms Sasaki?
Ms Sasaki, are you all right?
Ms Sasaki?!
Man, I'm starving!
Hey! You can't set up shop here!
Oh... OK.
Clear out!
R ght. Sorry.
Are you OK?!
Ms Sasaki!
Hey! What about this stuff?
Keep an eye on it!
Hey!
Take your stuff with you!
Not now!
Yoko!
Wait! Wait!
Hey!
Wait!
Yoko!
Yoko?
You passed out at work.
You don't remember?
How's the baby?!
My baby!
It's OK. It's fine.
It is?
It's OK?
Yes, it's fine.
The doctor checked.
It's still there.
Good!
The Fifth Month
Right now it weighs
about 250 grams.
See? There are the eyes,
and the mouth..
It's sucking its thumb.
Yes! It can do that already?
Yes.
Everything it needs is formed now.
Fine. Sit down there, please.
Your baby's fine.
Has your morning sickness
settled down?
Not yet.
That affects people differently.
It can be psychological, too,
so don't push yourself.
Eat what you want to
when you want to.
And no dieting.
I've accepted that.
I've bought larger pants.
How's work?
I've quit my job.
Oh!
We can make all sorts
of cute things.
I was thinking of trying this.
I've never done one before.
It'll be fun.
Oh, hey!
Hey! Wait! Come sit down.
Sorry.
Would you like to join
our 'Power Mothers Group'?
'Power Mothers'?
It can't be a coincidence
that we're all at the same clinic.
I think we should join up
and enjoy this time in our lives.
Right?
Yes.
I've never been pregnant before,
so there's a lot I don't know.
A veteran like Harue
will be a big help.
We'll ask Dr Hiratsuka...
...to give maternity lectures
and father's classes.
You're going to have to learn!
Yeah... right.
Where's your husband?
He's not my husband!
You're going to stay single?
Yes, if I can.
Anyway, make sure
you bring him, too.
Oh, just a minute...
Instead of a member's card.
A mother's day-book case.
I made it.
Mika's got one, too.
You can keep your National Health
and your appo ntment cards in here.
Oh, and...
...a 'pregnant alert'.
A 'pregnant alert'?
What's that for?
That way
everyone will know you're pregnant.
They'll be nicer to you.
Great, huh?
There.
I was sure you'd have
an abortion.
When it came down to it,
I just couldn't.
But quitting your job?
The moment I got pregnant,
they gave my magazine...
...to that illiterate, stuck-up...
...Kenji Takahara.
But there's such a thing as
maternity leave...
Do you think I could stand
com ng back and working for him?
If only babies were born
to the parent with the most time.
The father's
a freelance photographer, isn't he?
You met him in Vietnam?
I know it's a bit late to ask,
but what attracted you to him?
Everybody we took on that trip
got sick.
The only ones left standing...
...were him and me.
Then the baby should have
a cast-iron stomach.
Anyway, he hardly makes
any money.
So till I can go back to work
I'll be trimming away at my savings.
Tonight I dine
in a place like this...
...for the last time.
Hiratsuka Gynecology Cllnic
Hello.
Is this your first time here?
No, I have an appointment.
My name's Hibino.
Mrs Hibino... you were in last week.
Yes.
The lunch break's almost over.
Please sit down.
Over here.
Relna Saeki
Affair With Marrled Polltlclan?
Hey! That girl was here.
What? That's Reina Saeki!
Who?
You've never heard of her?
She's famous!
She's got great style,
but she's kind of stupid.
Yes! Did you see that quiz show?
I sure did!
Her answers!
That man was with her.
So he's her manager?
Why were they here?
You don't think...
I was amazed.
She kept those sunglasses on
through the whole examination!
Nurse Ando...
Respect our patients' privacy.
Yes, Doctor.
So you've been
to three other places?
That's rough!
I was ready to give up.
But I'm told this doctor's
good with infertility.
You'll be fine. I guarantee it.
She's good with everything,
from older mothers...
...right to infertility.
About how much
does the treatment cost?
Oh, I wouldn't know.
You don't work here?
Would you I ke a doughnut?
No, thank you.
So is your husband here?
He has to be here.
They always blame the woman
for not getting pregnant...
...but it could equally be the man.
You won't know for sure
unless he gets checked, too.
I know that!
Why do you keep wasting my time
when I'm busy like th s?!
Look, I don't know
what you've put in her head...
...but she can't have kids.
I've resigned myself to that.
How often do you have sex?
Getting right to it, huh?
In a week..
Uh, well... lately..
It's been a while.
Last December 24th,
at about 9:30 p. m.
That was the last time.
Without sex,
you can't have children.
That's true.
I examined your wife last week.
She would be 'an older mother'...
...but there is nothing
physically wrong.
So today I'd like to run
some tests on you.
You're saying it's my fault?
The husband must cooperate
for treatment to work.
Today I'd like to conduct
a semen analysis.
Oould you give me a specimen, please?
Here?
How?
There's a cubicle in back.
If you need them...
...use these.
Shall I help?
Strade.: The Eternal Appeal Of Paris
Sorry!
Yoko?
It's true!
It moved!
Like it was turn ng over.
Can't feel it.
Maybe it's asleep.
Hey!
I hadn't felt it move before.
It was so surprising...
and so moving.
It's, like, 'it's alive'!
Oh, sorry...
It's me. What's up?
Oh, that?
I'll call them myself later.
I'm w th someone now.
See you later.
You sound busy.
Well, I've been promoted
to Chief Planner.
You have? That's great!
It's more responsibility,
but not much more money.
And that guy harassing you?
He got caught misusing funds
and they transferred him!
So now I'm my own boss.
That's so great!
Anyway, uh...
Oh yes, the baby moved.
How does that feel?
Uh, well...
How do you describe it?
Sorry.
I'm sorry, I was just about
to call you.
Yes, about that venue.
We'll get that changed...
The Seventh Month
You shouldn't be lifting things!
It's OK. I'm stable now.
And the doctor says
I mited exercise is good.
Really?
That's everything.
Could we settle up now?
Sure. How much?
That's ¥68,000.
Huh? That's strange...
I'll pay it.
Look out.
¥68,000, right?
There.
Thank you very much.
Thanks a lot.
Sorry.
I'll pay you from my next job.
You got a job?
Uh, not yet.
I've got a lead.
It's true!
I'm due at the hospital,
so you finish up here, OK?
There's the head...
And then the back...
Oh, did you see that?
Wait...
Right there.
A perfect little thingy.
So it's a boy, then?
Yes, now we can be sure.
Is something wrong?
No.
It's like your life is decided
even when you're that tiny.
It's not that bad.
But boys and girls...
...lead very different lives.
But did you not say
you didn't want to spend your life...
...chasing celebrities
for a scandal sheet?
Uh, yes.
Weren't you going to travel the world
taking photographs that might win...
...a Pulitzer Pr ze?
Well, I'm putting off
the Pulitzer...
And now you come crawling back
asking for work?
Well, I'm going to be a father.
A child?
Yes.
So there's at least
one thing you can do.
I don't have anything
for you now. Go away.
Ms Sasaki! Ms Sasaki!
Hello.
We're going to yoga class.
Do you want to come?
Yoga?
Maternity yoga.
It's good for your back.
I'm taking the class.
It's helped a lot.
It's fun.
It's close by. Hop in.
This is Jiro, my husband.
How do you do.
Open the door!
Oh, right.
Olimb in.
I'll hold that.
We don't want you to fall.
There. Take your time.
Is something wrong?
No.
It'll be fine.
You'll have a baby,
just like all the others.
But my husband
isn't cooperating.
That's not true.
Yes, he was a bit reluctant...
...but in the end
he gave us a sample.
But he was furious
when he heard the results.
Well, no one is happy to hear
the problem is with them.
Your husband's sperm
are slightly weak in motility.
If we can find a way around that,
you can get pregnant.
We'll think of something.
What month?
Almost nine.
It could come any time.
Should you be doing th s?
Oh, sure...
Mayumi! What happened?!
A kick! This is going to be
one tough kid!
So it's a boy?
No, this is a girl.
A lady wrestler, maybe?
Oh, please! I'm going for
a pro golfer.
I like that.
I'll make the same wish.
A trillion-yen golfer.
So it does affect your bra n...
A figure skater would be nice.
OK, a triple axel!
That probably won't happen.
Neither of us is athletic.
So what's your wish?
I just want it born healthy.
You can't live on good health
these days.
A girl's fine if she's pretty.
She can live on that.
Right, Yuh?
What are you doing?
Sorry. I've got to
get to work.
Yuh's cheating on me.
I know it!
I can't have this child!
You don't have any proof of that.
You're pregnant.
You're just over-wrought.
Lately he's always 'working late'!
That's to pay your b lls.
He's trying his best.
You shouldn't doubt him.
He's always checking his mail.
A game, maybe?
Or work mail.
It's from a girl!
Who'd want him?
Yuh's very popular!
Did you check?
You've got to check his phone.
Mayumi?
I've got a private detective.
A detect ve?!
And a lawyer.
A lawyer?!
You need them?
Your husband's
so serious and hard-working!
When their wives are pregnant...
...lots of men start to cheat.
Jiro!
I'm back!
Yoko, I'm home!
Oh, hi.
I bought champagne.
Ohampagne?
You don't have
the money for that.
It's to celebrate.
A guy I knew in school
is doing fashion shoots.
He needs some help.
Oh.
Hey, come on!
Our money worries are over.
Now you can concentrate
on having a healthy baby.
That is so m ddle-aged!
It is?
Anyway, a drink.
No!
You said you loved champagne!
I bought the best!
It's not good to drink
when you're pregnant.
It's not?
It could give the baby
'fetal alcohol syndrome'.
So he'd be a born alcoholic?
You need to learn some things.
Read this.
Prenatal Baby Oare
Here goes!
Once more.
That's good. Smile.
OK, that's great!
Now you're into it!
Here goes!
Breeze.
Breeze!
No, no!
More! A wider spread!
Right!
Like this?
Reina!
What the hell are you doing?!
Be careful!
What is this?!
Sorry.
What do you mean?!
Did you lay it out for them?
They won't talk to me.
They're denying everything.
What about the DNA test?
Well... it didn't match.
What?! Why not?
I don't know.
That's crazy!
Oh, I get it.
He did something.
He could do that.
Are you sure
it's Representative Sakazaki's?
What?! Don't you believe me either?
There was another man, too.
That young foreigner, the dancer.
There's no way t's his!
Anyway, he went home
without even saying goodbye!
What are you looking at?!
Thank you for all your help.
Not at all.
Do you have children, dear?
No.
You don't?
I have a daughter.
I'd have liked to have children...
Hey... what are you doing?
There!
I've taken in this whole book.
Hey! What are you doing?!
It doesn't say you can't have sex.
Don't be silly!
You'll scare the baby.
Hey, are you awake?
I'm just going to borrow her...
He says it's OK.
He does not!
Are you talking back already,
young man?
Get out here!
When you do come out,
we can play catch.
Don't rush h m.
What do you mean?
Fathers and sons
have to play catch.
Right?
Hey! That tickles!
Just a little!
The Elghth Month
Fathers'Class
What's wrong?!
You're cheating on her!
What?! I am not!
Don't deny it!
We've got proof.
We checked your text mail.
Mail?
Mika was afraid to,
so we got a print-out.
Just who is this 'Ayu'?!
That's...
'I had fun today. ' 'Heart'.
'But this is wrong, isn't it. '
'Tears', 'tears'.
'I want your child!
Yuh, take me away!'
'Scream!' 'Blush'.
'Heart', 'heart'.
You have a pregnant wife!
Who is this 'Ayu'?!
Mika!
I'm sorry!
Those are... from me.
What?!
Huh?!
We met on a dating site.
She was an Ayumi Hamasaki fan,
so she called herself 'Ayu'.
Look at the dates.
They're two years old!
He's been cheat ng two years?
No, I haven't!
Why are you looking at them now?
Mika's all wrapped up in the baby.
She hasn't got time for me.
I kept those, and when I read them
I feel better.
Yuh!
Mika!
Today, we'd like to give
you soon-to-be fathers...
...and Mr Ono,
who's a veteran already...
...some idea of what your wives
are going through.
First, put on these
'pregnant-experience jackets'.
I'm really sorry.
I had it all wrong.
It's a happy end,
so that's all right.
I'm going to talk to
my husband, too.
That's good.
I'm sure it's all in your mind.
Pregnancy is hard on
your nerves.
But you and your husband
are so affectionate...
He comes to all these things.
Yes! I'm jealous.
Well, you know...
Sorry I'm late!
Over here!
Hello.
You're late!
I skipped out of work.
Yeah, OK.
Now if you'll split
into two groups...
...we'll try washing the baby.
Lower him slowly into the water,
so you don't scare him...
Slowly, slowly... that's good.
Carefully, wipe the eyes...
That's right.
A real baby's eyes will be closed.
From ins de to out,
that's right.
Roll your sleeves up!
Now with your thumbs,
you rub gently...
Don't let him sink!
Don't forget to hold him
at the back of the neck...
To clean the face,
you wipe down in a figure 3.
That's right. Very good.
Good!
Now let's wash the back.
Place your hand under
the arm away from you..
...and turn him over.
Turn him over...
No!
Think of it as a baby,
not a doll.
Now, very gently,
turn him over..
It's a baby, remember.
Doesn't that feel good?
OK, out we come...
No, no!
Everyone does that..
...but you can't shake him dry.
A baby isn't a plate.
R ght. Sorry.
Do it r ght, will you!
Could I show them...
...how it's done?
Yes, please.
Don't be...
...too nervous yourself.
Have confidence.
You're used to this, Mr Ono.
I've done it with three.
Be careful.
He gets carried away.
When you wash
babies' heads like this..
...they look really, really happy.
You see?
Isn't that nice?
Jiro! Jiro! The camera!
Pick him up!
Oh, Jiro!
I'm sorry!
What are you doing?!
Why do husbands stray
when their wlves are pregnant?
What's that?
Oh, something.
'Why do husbands stray
when their wives are pregnant?'
Stop peeking!
I'm not straying.
It's not about you.
What is all this stuff?
I'm going to write some essays
about being pregnant.
Essays?
At first I thought being pregnant
just meant lots of dull conversations.
But then I realized
it was a business opportunity.
Oh, yeah...
Speaking of business, I got paid.
You keep this.
Don't leave yourself broke.
I'm not.
I got a fashion job, I told you.
Liar.
It's true!
I saw the help-wanted magazine.
You're an assistant.
Anyway, you don't have to worry
about money.
Here.
1. Weekend walks
2. Discuss sex
Essays?
Sure!
Ask anyth ng you like.
I'm a veteran, after all.
Thank you!
Let me set this up.
This is your fourth child.
Why so many in this day and age?
Why?
I just keep getting pregnant.
But even one is hard...
My mother had seven.
And a career.
She's a Council member.
Out in the country.
Wow!
What's wrong?
Uh-oh... maybe.
'Uh-oh'?
It's coming.
Get a taxi!
Mayumi, hold on!
Stay calm.
You'll be f ne.
Take it easy...
You may have heard of
in vltro fertilization.
The egg is extracted
from the wife's ovaries...
...and fertilized outside the body
with the husband's sperm.
The fertilized egg is then put back
into the wife's body.
That's how it works.
After that, it's the same
as a normal pregnancy.
There's morning sickness,
and you swell up.
So in vitro fertilization...
...simply gives that first step
a little push.
So...
...I go back into that room
with that old porn again...
...and beat off?
We have new materials.
Honey!
Doctor, Mayumi Inoue's husband
is here.
Ooming.
Doctor!
Congratulat ons, 'Dad'.
A healthy baby.
Doctor! Thank you!
But having the water break
in yoga class!
Were you over-doing
'limited' exercise?
I'm sorry.
I warned her,
but she wouldn't listen.
But...
...perhaps she'll I ke to exercise,
the same as her mother.
A golfer, you said..
Who'll earn a trillion yen.
I had some ideas...
...but now she's here,
I don't care what she becomes.
Great.
Great!
Hey!
I'm sorry!
You'll wake her!
Great!
The Ninth Month
You've got a lot done!
Don't push yourself.
Right.
But once the baby's born,
I won't have much time.
I want to write
as much as I can now.
What?
Some water.
I'll get it.
Here.
Thanks.
Aren't you working?
Well, I got a phone call
yesterday.
About another job.
It'll bring in more money,
and we're going to need it.
We're fine for money.
I've got a publisher
for my essays.
You do?
Hey, I worked in publishing.
I will sell this book.
For the baby's sake.
I see.
What are you doing?
I'll be going.
See ya!
Excuse me...
Is the Editor here?
Hi! Over here.
Thank you for calling.
Something came up?
It's a little sleazy...
If it pays, I'll do it.
I knew I could count on you!
Tetsuya?
Dear Yoko..
I'll be out of touch
for a whlle, worklng.
The money is an advance.
Use it for the hospital bill.
My parents died young,
so I've always been alone.
So I was delighted when I heard
I was golng to be a father.
Bear a fine child whlle I'm gone.
I know you can.
Tetsuya.
You've no idea where he went?
He always wanted to be
a news photographer.
That's a problem.
Your baby's almost due.
Damn him!
I told him
I didn't need his money.
You said that to him?
Well, I can manage.
You shouldn't say that.
He has to feel needed.
'I need you with me,'
you have to say.
Men don't know what it's like
to give birth.
They don't swell up,
they don't feel any pain...
So for everything that happens,
you say, 'I want this, I want thatl
Then they roll their eyes,
but deep down they're happy.
To tell you the truth,
my Jiro...
...is unemployed.
You have to inconvenience
your partner to raise a family.
You inconvenience each other.
You fight all the time,
but then you make up.
That's what marriage is.
A photographer thought to be Japanese
shot during a gun battle..
...on the Paklstan-Afghanlstan
border last night..
...has died in hospital there.
The Foreign Ministry reports...
...that a camera bag
left on the scene..
...bore the name 'Tetsuya Kudo'..
...and officlals are trying to confirm
if that is in fact the dead man's name.
Look at the smile on his facel
He looks really happy.
He only smlles llke that
when Mommy changes his diaper.
Tetsuya?
Yoko? It's me!
Hi! I'm here to raise morale...
But are you OK?
Gotta save Tetsuya..
What? Yoko!
What do I do?!
Are you OK?!
No harvest again today.
Uh-oh...
Damn!
Watch the steps!
Hang on!
Now step up..
Grab on here. One, two...
Can I come, too?
Certainly.
Sit there.
Lie down here.
Hang on, Reina!
Is something wrong?
How many months?!
Well, uh...
...I don't really know.
Who's her doctor?
She hasn't been to one.
What?! Why not?
There'd be trouble
if it was made public.
This isn't the time for that!
Get in!
Push down hard
on her birth canal!
Keep quiet, will you!
Mrs Ono!
The pa ns have started.
It might be early,
but I thought I'd come.
The kids said they didn't want to
wa t around at home.
I see.
One moment.
I'll call the doctor.
It's a lovely moon tonight,
isn't it.
Yes?
Oh? She's a bit early.
I'll be right there.
Mother, I have to work.
Are you f nished?
Good evening, Doctor.
Good evening!
Hi, Dr Hiratsuka!
You've all gotten so big!
We're here for the fourth.
I see you came ready,
as usual.
Of course.
Have the pains started?
They're not very strong yet.
I guess I came too soon.
So you're still all right...
Yes. I'll just wait here a while.
Doctor?
Yoko Sasaki's water has broken.
She's coming in by ambulance.
Oh, dear...
Nurse Ando...
...get ready.
Hey, an ambulance!
Doctor! I think Yoko's here.
All right.
Huh?
Mika started hurting.
Yuh! Help me!
Didn't you say Ms Sasaki?
They said so.
Get inside.
Did she hear wrong?
Sign here, please.
Right.
Hang in there, Yoko.
We're almost there!
Tetsuya! Tetsuya!
Where is he!
Gotta save Tetsuya!
Can we go any faster?
Here goes.
You OK? Careful...
Mika!
Bring a wheelchair.
You'll be f ne.
OK?
Sit down here.
Doctor, she's not due yet.
Is something wrong?
It's all right. Don't worry.
Ms Sasaki's coming, too!
Get Mika into the delivery room.
Where's Sakurai?
She worked last night.
Oall her in.
We're going to be busy.
Oh, Jiro!
Reina, you'll be fine!
I'm with you! Hang on!
It hurts!
Go faster!
I know!
Oall the Hiratsuka Olinic!
Hiratsuka...
Careful...
Yoko!
Harue?
Where's your husband?
Oh, yeah...
Call a TV station.
He's abroad, in a gun battle!
Everything'll be fine...
Oall them!
OK, I will!
Go for it, Yoko!
Oall who?
I don't know.
Huh?
What?
It feels like...
...it's coming.
Hey!
Doctor!
Hold on!
Hey! Doctor!
Jiro!
We haven't used this one n years!
Good thing we still have t.
Get that, will you?
I'll help!
Thank you.
Hiratsuka Olinic...
Put that here, will you?
Harue! Hang in there!
Mrs Ono, up you go.
Do you feel like you're pushing?
A bit.
Don't do that yet.
Try to relax.
Harue?
I must've caught it
from seeing all of you.
Doctor...
There's another one coming in!
Sorry I'm late!
Wow! Three of them!
Jiro!
Get a drip ready.
And call around for back-up!
'Back-up'?
Quick!
Yes! We just don't have
enough people!
Hello, Wakaba General Hospital?
Do you have a spare obstetrician?
If you could help us...
Hey, give us a hand!
An emergency!
We can't understand her!
Doctor! Another one!
We're out of tables!
You'll be fine. What's your name?
Nope.
We're full up in here. Bring a bed
and put her in the nurses' station.
Right!
You'll be f ne.
Did you get any help?
No! All the obstetrics wards
are busy!
Is tonight a full moon?
I knew it!
Knew what?
They say the full moon
makes women want to give birth.
Ow!
Yuh!
Hang in!
Anyway...
...let's get through this.
Right.
Mr Ono...
...there's a bed in the back.
Thank you.
Come on, kids.
Hang on!
Dr Hiratsuka!
Where's the doctor?
She's busy now...
Hey...
Are you Tetsuya Kudo?
Yes.
You look better in real life.
Huh?
Oome with me, quick!
Where?
Yoko! Are you OK?
What are you doing here?
It's a long story.
You're alive! I'm so glad!
It's not that bad..
Why did you just leave?
Why? Well...
I have a confession to make.
Not now.
In Vietnam...
...it was me who wanted you
as the photographer.
The fact is...
...I've always loved...
...your pictures.
Yoko!
Tetsuya!
OK OK OK.
This is no time for long chats.
It's crowded in here.
Step outs de, please.
But...
No buts.
Out! Outs de, please.
Yoko!
We were just getting to
the good part!
Somebody! Oome quick!
It's coming!
Out front!
Oh, uh..
In the car out front...
Oh, yeah! Dr Hiratsuka!
Get out, I said!
There's another one out front!
You!
Doctor! Help us!
So you didn't abort the baby...
I've seen her on TV! Uh...
'Reina'!
Yeah!
Does the father know
about the baby?
They say it's that politician, uh...
'Sakazaki'!
So it's true, huh?!
Will you two shut up!
The father...
...is me!
Huh?!
What?!
No!
That's not what I mean.
I'm the replacement father.
Please bring this ch Id
into the world!
Yeah, right!
You're the last one who'd be
the father of my child!
No, it was just
a figure of speech...
Ow!
Are you all right?!
Move.
All of you, turn around!
Excuse me...
She's coming fastest.
Ando! Out here!
Watch your feet!
Doctor, we'll go back inside.
Let me know what happens.
OK, boys, step back.
Back! Back! Back!
What's going on?!
You expect me to have it here?
Get me a private room!
The delivery room's full tonight.
I'm sorry.
No!
I want a suite!
Now! Bear down!
That's t! That's it!
I can see the head!
Bear down!
Almost there!
OK, now.
As hard as you can!
One, two, push!
Here it comes!
Congratulations!
It's a boy!
Congratulations.
Thank you!
Someone had a baby.
Besides us?
It's a full house.
It's like Ladies' Day
at the movies.
Go to Mommy...
Hold him.
Congratulations.
Nurse Sakurai...
...that lady's in pain.
She keeps saying 'dao qua'
or something...
'Dao qua'?
It hurtsl It hurtsl
Are you Vietnamese?
Yesl Yesl
I aml
Nurse!
Get Tetsuya in here.
Tetsuya? All right.
What's wrong?
Come here.
That woman's from Vietnam.
Interpret for her.
Right!
I'm a week earlyl
You'll be fine.
The doctor's coming.
Oh, good. Thank you.
You understand her?
Yes.
Then tell her to relax.
Her baby is fine.
But it's going to take
a little while yet.
All right.
OK. Thank you.
Hang in there.
Mika?
Doctor!
Right.
She's next?
Mika!
Yuh, come here.
Take this, and push it hard
up her rear end.
This?
Yes.
Mika, roll onto your s de.
Like that.
Now, hold it like this...
...and do that!
Yuh! What are you doing?!
Pervert!
What?!
Shut up and push!
It's OK.
Settle down and don't worry.
Breathe slow...
He's not a pervert.
One, two..
Hold that, Yuh.
Did we get help?
I'm not sure.
Go check.
All right?
Doctor!
Step aside.
Well, well, well!
A full house...
Mother! What are you doing here?
Take her back to her room.
It's all right.
I see a bum.
We've got a breech birth here.
But she was fine!
Will it be OK?
You'll be f ne.
I'm used to breech births.
Doctor!
I'll look after her.
You see to the lady over there.
But...
You'll be f ne.
Doctor!
Enough tennis.
Mika, it's time to bear down.
Raise her feet.
Mika, keep look ng down
at your stomach.
Here goes.
One, two..
Yuh!
Come on, Mika! Try!
I'm trying!
Oome on, Harue!
Jiro!
Oould I come in?
No.
Please! I've taken all three.
If I miss this one...
...it'll be jealous...
The last one was out of focus!
No problem!
This camera's hi-vision.
OK, there's the back...
A little more..
Here it comes...
Jiro!
Harue! Just a bit more!
There we are!
A pretty little girl.
Hey!
Zoom in! Zoom in!
Now you...
OK, the last push.
Look down here and push
with everything you've got.
Breathe in...
Now stop...
And bear down!
Push! Push! All the way!
Yes, just like that!
The head's out!
Yes! Yes! Almost there!
There!
Oh, dear...
Take a deep breath...
I see the head! Push!
Just a bit more..
You're fine.
Congratulations!
Well done. Oongratulations!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Doctor, sit down here
for a while.
We can handle the rest.
Call me if you need me.
I'm worn out
just from watching it...
It's a job no man can do.
Yep.
It hurts! Do something!
Ride the wave.
Now! One, two, push!
It's taking so long...
It's fine. I see the head.
Push harder!
And rest...
I can't take it.
Do a caesarian.
What?! You're almost there.
Stop this pain!
Yoko! You can do it!
That's easy for you to say!
I'm right here!
What the hell good does that do?!
Squeeze my hand.
No, thank you!
Stop fighting!
Breathe in!
One, two..
Yoko!
Doctor, this isn't fair!
Don't stop! Bear down!
Why is it just me who hurts?!
If a baby takes two,
why is it the woman who suffers?!
And rest...
I lost my job...
...I hurt like hell...
...and he stands and watches!
That's the way it is.
One last time!
I should never have done this!
One, two!
It's coming!
It's out!
Ando...
What's wrong?
Doctor?
Doctor!
Tube.
Is he OK?
Why isn't he crying?
Be quiet.
What's wrong?
Is he OK?
Thank you!
Good boy.
It's born!
Congratulations.
Tetsuya...
He's beautiful!
Yoko
Alisa Mizukl
Harue
Yukl Matsushita
Tetsuya
Shosuke Tanihara
Shall we?
Gather round
for the picture, everyone.
Mrs Hibino!
I talked to my husband.
He's agreed to try again.
We're in your hands.
Really?
Good.
Is there a festival
or something today?
Everyone looks so happy.
They do, don't they.
Everyone stand
where you can see the camera.
OK, b g smiles!
Say it!
Oheeseburger!
Written and Directed by
Kazuyukl Morosawa
Subtitles
Ian MacDougall