Every baby in the world is born
with the secret of the universe.
What sounds like baby talk
to the average adult
is in fact a secret baby language.
Here, underneath the Bobbins
Day Care Center in Washington,
is the top-secret headquarters
of the Baby Squad.
Their mission-- use their brilliant
minds and high-tech tools
to discover clues and solve mysteries
all over the world.
But they had no idea
what they were in store for
with their first mission.
Oh, no.
The jewels!
The jewels have been stolen!
For the queen!
You two, with me.
- Search everywhere. Find them.
"Once upon a time there was a girl
named Snow White.
And she lived in a big castle
in this wondrous forest
with horses, beautiful trees,
and flowers around it."
Hi there. May I help you?
Did you get put in time-out?
Oh, no.
I'm the new music teacher
here for the kids.
Hey, kids.
I'd like you to meet
your new music teacher.
Hello, everyone.
-- "And then she met her prince."
And lived happily ever after.
It's time for breakfast.
Gracias, Kylie.
We do have a schedule to keep.
Vémonos.
Vémonos a la mesa.
Kylie, tu sabes.
Hello, General Haiger.
Bob, we've got
an unusual mission for you.
Let's cut to the chase, Bob.
The president wants you to go active,
effective immediately.
You and your brothers have done some
great work in baby communication.
Now, I've been involved in everything
from aliens to black ops, white ops,
ops that don't even have
a color yet,
but a team led by babies who can
solve crimes around the world--
pretty crazy stuff.
You see, General Haiger, babies possess
the knowledge of the universe.
If we can use that power
to help people
who truly need it,
you see, in theory-
Enough with the theories, Bob.
-- Bob, there's a young man outside.
Did you hire a new
music teacher?
I did.
That's Holden Hammer-smith,
one of our top new agency recruits.
Music teacher
is just his cover.
He'll be my liaison.
So-- so you're sending someone
to spy on us?
We're a spy agency, Bob.
It's what we do.
Bottom line--
we need results in 30 days
or your organization doesn't exist,
officially or unofficially,
and that's official.
Hammer-smith,
security code 643.
I've been here
for over two hours.
There are no geniuses.
Just a bunch of drooling babies.
Yeah. No, I got it.
- Mm-hmm.
No, somebody hit me
in the head with a ball.
Uh-huh.
There's poop everywhere.
Don't get me wrong, General.
They're all very cute
and probably smart for babies.
Maybe even one knows...
how to tie a shoelace,
but that's about it.
They're not gabbing.
They're definitely babies.
- I just sent them all to sleep.
Yeah, I ever got the car
and everything.
I don't know what
you want me to do.
Yeah, poop, droop-- everything.
No, I understand that, sir.
I-- I--
oh, holy mackerel.
I'll get back to you.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Good morning, team.
Gather around.
We've got work to do.
Argh! Argh!
Next time, try the elevator.
Bob Bobbins.
- Kylie Bobbins-- my niece.
- Nice to meet you.
Meet Holden Hammer-smith, sent by
the agency to observe and report.
Oh, brother.
He's a spy?
He's sure not a musician.
Shirley Jones here, sir.
The crown jewels
have been stolen.
The crown jewels, people.
Copy that. We're on it.
The crown jewels of London
are the symbols of the English royalty.
The collection
is worth millions.
the knight's golden scepter,
the princess's diamond necklace,
and even the imperial state crown
worn by the queen herself.
Gorgeous.
Does it come in my size?
You go, girl.
My little fashionista.
We love our royalty.
The whole country has got
its knickers in a knot.
Don't worry, we're sending a field team
to London immediately.
- Seriously?
- We are? Oh, my God.
Are you sure you're ready,
Uncle Bob?
We've run the simulations
a thousand times.
People, this is not a drill.
Finally, some real action.
Yes! Come on, give it up.
Our first mission.
They can't really be talking
to each other.
Yes, really.
But when it comes to an adult,
only a Bobbins can understand
baby talk.
I guess the Bobbins
have never really grown up.
- What's this?
- The Z-35 Vortex.
It transports people across the planet
through wormholes.
You know, quantum physics.
Pretty basic baby stuff.
Yeah, I majored
in quantum physics.
I'm pretty sure that I'm smarter
than these babies.
I guess we'll see, spy boy.
Kylie, you're leading up the field team
along with Skip and Alfred.
What's happening?
- Bob, are you sure they can do this?
- Okay, time to buckle up.
I have full faith in them, Betty.
They're geniuses.
But they're still babies.
We can do it, Mom.
Okay, Kylie is in charge.
You remember to do
everything she says, okay?
These are goody bags
for your first mission.
It's pancakes au broccoli.
Skip's dad loved it.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Yuck.
Kylie, this is
a Z-35 transponder.
You need to keep this
with you at all times
so we can triangulate your position
and get you back home safely.
Activating Z-35 Vortex.
Energy fields up.
Synchronizing phase fluctuations
with wormhole.
Programming Wormhole
to change your clothing
to the latest London fashions.
Be careful. Come back.
I'll miss you.
If we've adjusted
the telemetry properly,
you'll materialize in a corridor
right next to the Tower of London
where nobody should see you.
- It worked.
- Argh!
It actually worked.
It worked.
Yippee!
Whoo!
Hello. Excuse me.
Oh, hello.
Oh, look at that--
little babies, eh?
Hey, dude,
who are you calling little?
Here I was, trying to take
a little snooze here,
and little babies
sneak into my cab, eh?
Where are you from,
little babies?
Is this guy for real?
They don't understand me.
Or do they? Eh?
- Creepy.
- Where to, missy?
Actually, we're kind of lost.
Can you take us to the Tower of London?
Oh, the Tower of London?
That's where they keep the crown jewels.
They were recently stolen.
There's a lot of commotion over there.
I understand, but it's really important
that we get to the Tower.
Well, the customer's
always right, little babies.
So the Tower of London it is.
Buckle up now.
We're on the opposite side
of the road.
Looks like a big, giant donut.
There's Big Ben over there.
That clock-- 150 years old.
- Whoa.
The third tallest
clock tower in the world.
And there on your left side,
that's Buckingham Palace.
If you wave, maybe William and Kate
is in the window there.
- Do you know who lives there?
- The queen.
Well, that was some wedding, eh?
That was crackers, that wedding.
This guy's strange.
- He also needs a dentist.
- Yeesh.
- Ooh.
- Cheese.
- I love you.
I rule.
- I can't believe I'm here.
- Smile.
Well, here we
are at the Tower of London.
Look out for those royal guards.
No matter what you do,
it's impossible to make them laugh.
Did you ever hear that?
We'll see about that.
Looks like
he's in a doghouse.
Looks like a giant poodle.
Look, I'm dancing like
the Black Eyed Peas.
Come on, stop acting
like babies.
We got some work to do.
Let's go.
- He's not real.
- I think he's a toy soldier.
We've only just begun,
little babies.
You have no idea
where this will all end up.
I'm going to need a US Government
identification card
- to get into the crime scene.
- Copy that. We're on it.
Oh, my gosh, use this one.
Love Kylie's hair in this picture.
Yeah, but look at the outfit
in this one.
That girl can accessorize.
I don't know what you're saying,
but you don't seem
to be doing much work.
Men-- no sense of style.
Obviously.
Look at his shoes.
Men don't realize
it's all about the shoes.
I have more shoes
than pacifiers in my closet.
Got it, Jordan.
Thanks. I'm out.
Whoa, check out
the merchandise.
Alfred, don't touch that.
You break it-- you buy it.
I'm Chief Inspector Jones
of Scotland Yard.
- Can I help you, miss?
- Hi. Kylie Bobbins,
special assistant to the head
of the US State Department Secretary
here in London.
We would like to offer our assistance.
This guy looks
pretty smart.
You think you'll buy
the fake ID?
Brilliant, Miss Kylie.
And the children?
Uh, the secretary had to
leave town suddenly.
I assure you
they will be no trouble.
Babysitting today, eh?
As it so happens, I'm looking after
my own little princess today.
Children, this is my daughter
Shirley Jones.
Miss Bobbins, allow me to show you
what we've learned so far.
- Hello, mates.
- Hey, Shirley. What have we got?
Not a clue.
An almost perfect crime.
- They're searching high.
- We're searching low.
Follow me.
Being a spy is cool.
This is fun.
Getting a bit of
a reading here, mates.
Love the British accent.
Sweet, a clue.
Oops, my bad.
- Anything, young chap?
- Here, found a clue.
A bit of evidence-
a hamburger.
Um, that's okay.
Just scan it and then
use some sanitizer.
- Command center.
- Feeding the last of the clues in now.
Any results yet on your end?
A small footprint,
a baseball cap,
and half-eaten hamburger.
Somebody is a thief
and a slob.
Got that right, girl.
Using the graphical interface
projector sequence.
- Yeah.
- I love this job.
One of the thieves
snuck through the air vent.
Way too small
for an average-sized adult.
Once inside,
Mr. Messy Pants was distracted
when he had to
let his partner in.
DNA evidence suggests
an adult baseball cap
occasionally worn by a baby
with a very big head.
And a poor sense of style.
Must have used particle lasers
to cut the glass.
Something set off the alarm,
but they still managed to escape.
Analysis on the hamburger?
Get ready to get grossed out.
Small bite marks,
meat by-products,
almost 95% fat content.
There's only one place in London
that sells a burger that's that greasy.
- Yum.
- Lunchtime.
Here we are.
Excuse me,
are you the manager?
Yes, miss.
Master Nathan Guffman at your service.
You will love our special
fish and chips burger.
We're actually looking for the person
who was eating this burger.
Do you remember a customer
that was a bit suspicious-looking?
He looks suspicious.
Our clientele leans towards
working-class families,
not your suspicious types.
The big boss-- he's been
working hard to make this
the best burger place in the world.
- Beauregard Burger?
- Yes, miss. He's the big boss.
And that's his son,
Beauregard Baby Jr.
We also call him Big Baby.
You know, like his initials, BB.
BB? That's Big Baby.
A criminal baby?
That's not cool.
Do you know where I could find
Mr. Beauregard Burger?
Oh, yes, miss.
He'll be down in his office.
Here you go.
Here's his business card.
Thank you.
You've been very helpful.
All right, let's go.
Hey, we didn't eat
our food.
We should have
done takeout.
Oh, Master Beauregard Jr.
- Uppie!
- That is so cute.
Oh, such a growing boy.
You will do everything I say.
I will do everything you say.
What's going on?
UPPie!
Excuse me?
Mr. Burger?
A"!/body here?
Welcome.
Hi. I'm here to interview Mr.--
Mr. Beauregard Burger.
Who are these guys?
The Blues Brothers?
Well, well, well,
welcome to Big Daddy Burgers
corporate headquarters.
I'm Beauregard Burger.
Kylie Bobbins.
We spoke on the phone.
Yes, these must be
your nephews.
Please come into my office.
I'm doing an article
on how wonderful
your deep-fried fatty food
is for kids.
Finally, a journalist who's
not afraid to print the truth.
- Huh?
- Oh, Miss Kylie,
this here is my son,
Beauregard Burger Jr.
Perhaps your nephews would like to
go and play with BB while we talk.
Come here, boys.
So you're Big Baby.
And you're here with your aunt,
the reporter.
Interesting.
Cool outfit.
Does it come with
a baseball cap maybe?
Since you're new in town,
I'll give you some advice.
Stay out of
the Burger business or else.
Oh!
What's up, girl?
So we talked to the Burgers
and we didn't come up with anything.
But we did.
Infrared GPS scan of the footprints
leaving the Tower of London
leads straight to Big Daddy Burgers
restaurant.
Okay, so the crown jewels
must be here.
We got a bogey on the Garcia cam.
Prepping level-six distraction.
What are these babies
really up to?
Time for a diaper bomb.
Oh. av-vi-vi
Yeah!
I just changed you.
Shh.
- Shh.
Come on.
We have to sneak the jewels
out of here.
Have to sneak jewels.
You don't have to repeat
everything I say.
We don't have to repeat-
BB?
What's going on here?
I guess I'll have to
hypnotize you again.
UPPie! Uppie!
So that's how he did it--
hypnosis.
There must be a safe
in here.
Oh, I got it.
Sweet.
Holy hamburgers!
We did it!
Yeah!
Kylie, get out of there now.
They're heading towards you.
Come on, guys, let's go.
He's got the jewels.
After him!
Inspector Jones.
We received a mysterious call
that you might need help.
We were able to wrestle this
away from him.
Only the necklace?
What about the scepter and the crown?
He handed a bag to a large man
in the alley.
Probably one of his
less intelligent henchmen.
But we've captured
the real mastermind.
Mastermind?
But the real mastermind is right here.
Don't be ridiculous.
Mr. Burger helped us
crack this case.
This horrible man stole the crown
jewels and we called the police.
You're a true hero, sir.
It seems you were
outsmarted, Crybaby Squad.
Let's take this rubbish
downtown.
Right-0.
Hey, where did Big Baby
and his dad go?
Cheerio, Baby Squad.
We didn't recover the scepter
and the crown,
but we recovered
the diamond necklace.
A job well done, Bob.
But I hate to burst
your bubble, Bob.
The queen's Diamond Jubilee
is days away.
And I want the scepter and the crown
back before then
or else.
Haiger out.
Guys, you heard the man.
We've got work to do.
- One down, two to go.
Hold it steady.
Easy.
Ugh, Dad, let me do it.
Non, ce n'est pas possible!
Le tableau! Le tableau!
Thief!
The painting has been stolen!
- A droite! A gauche!
A droite! A gauche!
It's like Picasso.
Ah!
This is impossible.
Babies painting masterpieces?
0-0 Senora, these are
no ordinary babies.
I agree with you.
Operations switcheroo.
I mean, would an ordinary baby
create a masterpiece like this?
I agree.
They are all masterpieces.
No, no, no, no, no, no, senora.
- Well, they're wonderful.
- No, no, no.
- Look at all those colors.
- Yeah, I know. This is like children.
- They didn't do children's work before.
- It was like Picasso or something.
- Your positive reinforcement
- is terrific.
- Oh.
It's so much fun to trick
Mrs. Garcia, isn't it?
I agree. I just wish
she had more fashion sense.
Oh, get back to business.
We have Charlie le Clueless
on the line.
He's the son of France's
greatest detective.
Bonjour, mes amis.
Bonjour.
Hello, Charlie.
Tell us what happened.
A terrible theft at the Louvre.
It's a museum in Paris
that houses the largest
art collection in the world.
Any Suspects?
Beauregard Burger
and Big Baby
have both been spotted in Paris.
We feel they are involved in some way,
but we don't know how.
Could this be connected
to the missing crown jewels?
Does plaid clash with stripes?
In other words, duh!
Don't worry, Charlie.
We're on it.
What are they saying?
Mr. Bobbins,
I hate to complain...
Since when?
This whole baby talk thing-
I can't be effective
if I can't understand anybody.
I've got just the thing.
Try this.
What is it?
I built a baby translator
for you.
- Give it a whirl.
I've got the Z-35 Vortex
set for the correct azimuth.
But what about the ionospheric
phase shifting?
I can hear them!
I still have no idea what they're
talking about, but I can hear them.
- Duh.
- Welcome to our world.
Cool.
Gabi and Jordan, you're gonna be
on the away team.
- And Holden is going with you.
- Oh, yes! My first mission!
Holden Hammer-smith
in the field.
Hello.
Pick me up.
Let's go.
- It's going straight to his head.
- Nice.
Got a surprise for you
when you get to Paris, Gabi.
Ready?
This is the Z-35 Vortex.
You're going to take this
so we can triangulate your position
and get you back home safely.
Vortex power surge beginning.
35%. And vortex forming.
Transporting you to a storage room
right inside the Louvre.
Ohh-hh!
- Pretty colors.
- Hang on, guys!
- Good luck.
Hang on!
We're almost there, guys! Hold on!
Whoa. That was fun.
- Can we do it again?
- Take off your glasses.
Doesn't look like the Louvre.
Someone should call
a vortex repairman.
Whoa, the Eiffel Tower.
It's over 1,000 feet tall.
Actually, it's 1,063 feet.
Ha! I knew something you didn't.
Don't get a big head, rookie.
- Uh, sir?
- Oh.
Excusez-moi, monsieur.
- Hello.
- Whoa!
His nose looks like
the Eiffel Tower.
I was engrossed in my paper
and I did not see
two beautiful babies in my cab.
He called me beautiful.
He said two beautiful babies.
Whatever.
In France we adore
beautiful babies and dogs...
- Did he say "dogs"?
- ...because we are warm, loving people
overflowing with compassion.
Bonjour. Would you like
to buy a French beret?
Hey, get lost.
Casse-toi! Va-t'en! Va-t'en!
Oh, take it easy.
I am sorry.
I lost control.
But I have already been-
how you say?
--Ripped off by this bum
and his fake, phony berets.
They're not even French.
They are made in Vietnam.
This guy is loony.
So where would you like to go?
Actually, we need to go
straight to the Louvre.
That is the champion
of art museums.
My favorite painting
is in the Louvre.
Oh, yeah?
What's your favorite painting?
"Starry, Starry Night"
by Vincent.
- Van Gogh, right?
- Vincent van Gogh.
You are very smart
like a porcupine, eh?
All right, buckle up.
Oh, Paris. I'm in love.
Holden,
check out my picture.
So you said your favorite
painting was "The Starry Night"?
- Why is that?
- Well, because of the stars.
On a clear night, you can see
millions and millions of stars
and around each one planets.
- I like this guy.
- Planets that may have life.
- Bet he'd really dig my Cosmonauter.
- Imagine them.
- I think you're both crazy.
- Little baby ones, eh?
Now let's rock 'n' roll
Paris style.
Say, "Ooh-la-cheese."
Looking good, girl.
Call me Mademoiselle Jordan.
Yeah!
We finally made it
to the Louvre Museum.
Kids, this is
a billion dollars of artwork.
Please, no accidents.
Bonjour. I am Jean Le Clueless
of the French police.
- And I'm--
- Uh...
Jean Le Clueless is the greatest
detective in all of France.
I need but to observe.
Bien.
You are Holden Hammer-smith
assistant art expert
from the US embassy
here in Paris, sent to assist
in our investigation. Oui?
And these are
your two lovely nieces
whom you must play caretaker
to for the day.
I think we're caretakers
for Holden.
And you love to eat peanuts.
Hello.
It's in the fax he got from Alfred.
Duh.
Actually, that's pretty good.
Although isn't all that information
in the fax you received from our office?
Fax, fax.
What is this fax?
But I am correct
on the peanuts, oui?
No. Actually, I hate peanuts.
No, you don't.
You are mistaken.
But enough chitchat.
I have a crime to solve.
The culprit broke in,
evaded security.
And stole our most prized
possession-
the "Mona Larry."
Monsieur, don't you mean
the "Mona Lisa"?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
The "Mona Lisa" is still here.
The "Mona Larry"
is almost as valuable,
but it is
a 500-year-old painting
of a father
with his very large child.
Now you will excuse me.
As I said,
I have a crime to solve...
peanut breath.
Ooh-la-la, he's cuckoo.
He'd better watch out.
You break it,
you buy it.
This place is a mess.
Have someone
clean this, yeah?
Sorry about my father.
Sometimes he can be kind of
a little clueless.
Speaking of clues, the first thing
they taught us in the academy-
look for clues.
Hey, fearless leader,
down here.
To catch a big baby,
think like a big baby.
Grown-ups search high
and we search low.
Voilé, a clue.
- We're hot on the trail.
Keep detecting.
Yes!
Oh, cool.
Certainement. A clue.
A paintbrush with wet ink.
Oh, sorry about that.
Let me just-
This is not ink.
Hmm, barbecue sauce.
Peanut breath.
-- I've scanned and downloaded
the clues we found so far, Kylie.
Any results yet?
There's nothing on the paintbrush
or the beret, but the croissant-
it's filled with preservatives,
lard, and a ton of grease.
There's only one restaurant
in all of Paris
that would serve
such an unhealthy croissant.
Follow the smell
to Big Daddy Burgers.
My burger has a lot of grease.
Of course it does.
It's our secret sauce, Dad.
What is phase two
of your plan?
Oh, brother.
You forget everything under hypnosis.
Now that we have the painting,
we have to take the crown to the--
the Baby Squad!
How do they always manage
to track me down?
You need to stop being so sloppy
when we rob places.
I'm a baby. okay?
I'm used to having someone
pick up after me.
Let's go.
Hello.
Something tells me they don't serve
Caesar salad here.
Excuse me.
How rude.
Hello. Hey.
Anyone? Right here.
Hi.
Why do all clues always lead us
to a greasy hamburger joint?
Qu'est-ce que c'est?
Look what it is.
We've got customers to serve.
What are you doing?
Now go. Go away
and wash the dishes, you fool.
Bonjour.
How may I help you?
Do you recognize this?
Oh, mon Dieu.
Oh, that is vile.
That is--
it's practically inedible.
It came from this
restaurant.
Oh, then that makes sense,
doesn't it?
Maybe you'd like one?
This guy is loony.
Yeah, his head is full of grease.
Did anyone suspicious purchase
a croissant like this recently?
Suspicious?
No.
Nobody suspicious at all.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
Maybe you would like
a croissant.
I'm good, thanks.
Can we go shopping now?
Good day, monsieur.
Au revoir.
Who's next? Bye-bye.
Customers to serve.
Au revoir.
Have a nice day.
Now that's how
you behave under hypnosis.
Kylie here.
Anything to report?
It was a dead end
at the burger place.
What's the analysis
on the clues we sent you?
The paintbrush
is inconclusive-
gross, but inconclusive.
She's not kidding.
You might want to check out
the crime scene again.
- Maybe there's something you missed.
- Copy that.
Nothing. We're toast.
Better call Mr. Bobbins.
Man, my first mission out in the field
and I got nothing.
Okay, in the academy
they told us to start
from the beginning.
So what have we got?
- The croissant.
- The croissant. Good.
- Is there an echo in here?
- Yeah, and his name is Holden.
Oh, that's harsh.
The croissant only had
two bites taken out.
It appeared to be half-eaten.
It broke up on impact, yes.
After breaking into the museum,
Big Baby used mirrors
to bypass
the motion detectors.
And used GPS spectral analysis
to stay clear of the guards,
which allowed Beauregard
to come right through the door.
Of course.
He was wearing a beret
in an attempt to blend in
with the locals.
So Big Baby had to act fast.
He used his laser cutter
to cut the picture out of the frame.
Yeah!
So it all comes down
to the painting.
Yes!
He's got the what,
when, and where.
But why does he want it?
Mm! Why does he want it?
Why does he want it?
- Sir.
- Oui?
Did you happen to sketch
the painting that was stolen?
You mean the "Mona Larry"?
Actually, that one
was a commission.
Ah, from who?
A very strange man
with a very large baby.
- A large baby?
- He wanted me
to make the copy,
but to change the faces.
Wait.
I'll show you.
Ah, here it is.
Yeah. Can you remember
anything else?
He said to make
the picture work,
they needed berets.
Bingo.
Ha! Thank you.
What's up, dude?
Find something?
Maybe. Pull up the specs
on that beret we scanned.
The labels were all removed,
but chemical analysis suggests
the fibers originated in Vietnam.
So we need to find that vendor
who was selling those berets.
Good. I want to nail him
for crimes of fashion.
I'm already tracking
his movements.
He's taking a break
at Big Daddy Burgers.
Beret, monsieur? Non?
Bonjour.
A French beret?
Sir, did you sell this beret?
- Oui, I did.
- Do you remember who bought it?
Oh, how could I forget?
A crazy big man and a big baby
who smelled like hamburgers.
Good. Do you remember
which direction they came from?
Oui. From right under
the Tour d'Eiffel itself.
Good.
Gabi, contact Charlie.
Have him grab his dad
and the police
and get them over to Eiffel Tower
right away.
Let's go, team.
Good. Come on.
Hamburgers!
Get your hamburger right here!
Throwing the hamburgers on
right now.
The painting.
Big Baby,
the painting we stole
is ready for the artist
to put our faces on.
My portrait.
Taking over the world
just wouldn't be the same without it.
In a few minutes, we'll rendezvous
with the helicopter
at the top of the Eiffel Tower.
And then to our private jet
to fly to our next destination.
And what's my name?
O Magnificent One.
Very good.
Today I'm just a baby,
but tomorrow
everyone will look up to me.
Oh, no.
That Baby Squad is coming.
Stop them.
Big Baby
is making a big break for it.
Stop them.
Monsieur Holden, you will not believe
what I have just discovered.
- I have cracked the case.
- Oh, that's great.
But right now can you help us out
with the bionic busboy over here?
Not yet. This is fun.
Arrest him.
- Where is Big Baby?
- Escaping behind you.
Au revoir, Baby Squad.
Oh, man.
The Burgers got away again.
It doesn't matter.
We have the culprit.
He tried to stop you.
His fingerprints are on the tableau.
This case, she has been
shut and open.
You mean open and shut.
You are mistaken,
peanut breath.
Oil suis-je?
How did I get here?
The question is,
where are you going?
The answer-- prison.
Hey, rookie, not bad
for your first mission.
Yeah, you guys
weren't so bad yourselves.
All right. Good job.
- Now can we finally go shopping?
- Two down, one to go.
Well, we solved the crime
at the Louvre
and recovered
the stolen painting.
Unfortunately, the Burger boys
got away again.
With the scepter and the crown.
We only got two days left
to get that crown back
or it's going to be a disaster
for the queen of England.
I have a feeling Big Baby is up to
something much bigger than all this.
Shh.
Pay attention to the mission
and not your stomach.
Shh.
Grab an end and be careful.
Steady. Steady.
Ohh.
No, don't touch that.
You're so hungry under hypnosis.
Mamma mia!
The pizza di tutte pizze,
she's gone.
Trying to use
the NSA satellites
to find where Big Baby
hid the jewels.
NASA found some strange activities
in the vicinity of Centauri Alpha.
I'm using the satellite
to track hamburger grease
in the world's sewer systems.
I found deposits in Pisa, Italy.
Something's strange
about the rings around Saturn.
Those aren't rings.
That's where you spit up
on the blocks last week.
Oops. My bad.
Oh, listen, why don't you show them
the artwork, okay? Gracias.
Hmm.
What are my little darlings
doing now, hmm?
I'm sure it's something unusual,
especially for babies.
Mm-hmm.
You know, the Cosmonauter
can also be used
to search and contact
alien life.
Uh-oh, here comes trouble.
- Ugh, Mrs. Garcia.
- Time to foil Mrs. Garcia.
- ' Oh!
The blocks
got knocked down.
Oh, no, no, no.
Mrs. Garcia didn't mean
to knock over your blocks.
- Did you?
- No, no, no.
Listen, I came over here
and I saw something amazing.
- I'm sure you did.
No, I didn't do nothing.
I was looking-
- Oh, isn't it snack time?
It is snack time.
- Crazy, I know.
- No wonder they're crying.
No snacks, right?
Whew.
Let's move.
- Good morning, Uncle Bob.
- Morning, team.
We've got Pisa, Italy,
on the monitor.
Italy needs your help.
- What's wrong?
- The pizza di tutte pizze.
- The pizza of all pizzas?
- That's one sweet pizza.
My father Antonio Angelotti,
the greatest pizza chef
in all of Italy, created it.
It was his life's work.
And now it has been stolen.
It was created for the prime minister's
birthday celebration tomorrow.
Yes. You must find it before then
or my father's reputation is ruined.
Don't worry, Tony.
We're on the case.
Okay, team, get ready.
We're on mission to Italy.
A new Big Daddy Burger restaurant
opened in Pisa, too.
Smells like a Big Baby connection.
This is the case
of the Leaning Tower of Pizza.
Get it?
- Pisa, pizza.
- Not funny, dude.
- Is this on?
- Oh, grow up.
Kylie, you'll be taking Alfred
and Gabi on the away team.
Skip, Jordan, Holden, you'll be
manning the command center.
Energy fluctuation stabilized.
Vortex transmission positive.
Stand by
to be transported directly
into the lobby
of the Tower of Pisa.
Italy, here we come.
A taxicab? Again?
This is getting ridiculous.
Shh.
Here comes the drive-
Well, hello there.
I stopped for five minutes
for a cappuccino,
and suddenly
my car is full of babies, eh?
He looks familiar. Yes?
Yeah.
Isn't he the same--?
Nah.
Do you know a restaurant owned by
Antonio Angelotti-- Pisa Pizza?
Oh, sure I know Pisa Pizza.
I know Antonio Angelotti.
But to tell you the truth,
his pizza is not so good.
His pepperoni is not fresh.
He's been slicing
from the same pepperoni for 20 years.
Ooh, that is old.
All in all, we still need
to get to the Pisa Pizza.
Well, we could go to Rome, though,
you know.
You see, the Colosseum,
it bring you to tears.
It's so beautiful.
It's four hours away by cab, that's all.
Four hours in a cab?
He's trying to keep us
from getting there.
Thank you for the suggestion, sir,
but to Pisa Pizza, please.
Okay, sure. I go.
You are little smarty-pants babies.
That's where we're gonna go.
Ciao, bella.
-- I'm Sophia Loren.
- Pisa!
- Buongiorno!
Yay!
I love you.
It's quite the smooth drive,
considering that I'm the driver.
Okay, there it is-- Pisa Pizza.
But very upset, he,
because of the stolen giant pizza.
There's thieves among us, eh?
Finally we're here.
Now let's go investigate
the stolen pizza.
Sounds like a baby crying.
Signore Angelotti?
Hi. I'm Kylie Bobbins from the CCC--
Culinary Crisis Center.
In all of Italy,
I was the chef they chose
to make the prime minister's
birthday pizza,
and now
I'm a disgrace!
I spit on myself.
No, no, no, no. Don't do that.
We're gonna get it back for you.
You will?
- Yes. That's what we're here for.
- Ah.
My Papa.
he's very emotional.
No need for apologies.
May I say
you are working that hat?
Tell us about the stolen pizza.
Not a pizza-- a master pizza.
It was priceless.
Yeah, a lot of dough, right?
Get it?
It loses something
in translation.
Okay, kids, let's get to work.
The clues are the key.
Find ones
the grown-ups don't see.
Check out my new wheels.
I got something.
Looks like pepperoni.
Yes, it's a pepperoni.
Seriously, folks,
we're in a pizza shop
and this is the best clue
we can find?
Come on, what does that say
about us as detectives?
That we're hungry?
Believe it or not,
there was actually clues
on the clues you sent us.
Put it on the screen, Skip.
Who took a nap
and made you president?
The spectrum analysis indicates
large traces of mucosa rhinitis
on the pepperoni slices.
Mucosa what?
- Snot.
- Eww.
It was just enough to render
a positive DNA match.
Okay, here's how I see it.
Using an old-world
pizza cutter,
they broke in,
snuck by Antonio Angelotti...
-- Shh.
...and snagged
the prime minister's pizza.
The pepper in the pepperoni
caused an allergic reaction.
Ah-choo!
Without waking
Mr. Angelotti,
who was guarding the pizza,
they made their getaway.
Hold it.
You are wrong, wrong, wrong.
It did so not happen like that.
- Says who?
- This is what really happened.
Using a high-tech
laser pizza cutter-
a Swiss-made Urich 3000,
by the way--
they breached
the perimeter,
then bypassed the high-tech
security system-
the Angelotti 350--
and grabbed the pizza.
Pepper and pepperoni-
allergic reaction.
It was really Beauregard
that sneezed, not Big Baby.
Hold it. Totally wrong.
It was the Big Baby
who sneezed.
What are you drinking in that bottle?
It was Beauregard.
- Big Baby.
- You're a big baby.
Hold on, guys. Who cares
whose snot is on the pizza?
We've only got two hours
to find it
or the reputation
of Angelotti is finished.
It's raining pepperoni.
If we keep following
the trail of pepperonis,
it will lead us
to the stolen pizza.
There's cheese on it.
Gross.
There's another...
and another and--
oh, wait.
That's from a pigeon.
Great.
The pepperoni ends here.
- We hit a dead end.
- Hey, guys.
- I found it. I found it.
- Another clue?
No, the perfect outfit,
two shops down.
-- Maybe this guy knows something.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Oh, please,
this is a power station,
not a tourist attraction.
You must take the bambinos
away pronto.
Oh, no,
I just want to know
if you've noticed
anything unusual lately.
Oh, we've got big problems.
The electricity-- she's not going
where she's supposed to.
What do you mean?
Everybody in town--
they're having blackouts.
- Somebody's stealing our power...
...to run something big.
-- Oh, we got so many problems.
Luigi, I tell you,
you put that down!
So why is Big Baby
stealing electricity, and how?
I don't know why,
but I think I know how.
Oh, yes.
They're following my plan.
Somebody is using
this power cord.
Dad, you're being childish.
Wheel
Oh, sparkles.
This is so unbelievably shiny.
All right, Dad.
The scepter is not a toy.
We need it to focus the ray.
But I like it.
Grown-ups.
We follow the cord.
And we find
the evil pizza thieves.
It leads
all the way to the tower.
This cord is longer
than a million plates of spaghetti.
Can't we take the escalator?
They didn't have escalators
when the tower was built.
We have to climb up
all 296 steps.
296? Man, that's crazy.
I'm glad I didn't wear heels.
Are we there yet?
Alfred, you're driving
us both crazy.
No wonder your mom
hates long drives.
So are they there yet?
Holden, stop asking me that.
When I give the signal,
power up.
Yes, when you give me
the signal.
At last, we found you!
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the Baby Squad
and the babysitter.
Too late, as usual.
Now!
Why did you disintegrate
the prime minister's pizza?
Disintegrate?
Look again, closer.
-- You shrunk it?
Tell them, Father.
The genius that is Big Baby
condensed the molecules
of the pizza,
thereby miniaturizing
its atomic structure.
Right, so you shrunk
the pizza.
Okay, fine.
I shrank the pizza.
- But why?
- Because if I can make it smaller,
I can also make it bigger.
Get back!
- Now that's a pizza.
My prototype is a success.
Ready to move
to my master plan.
You're actually moving on to jail.
And here comes your ride.
Perhaps not.
- Transport.
- There they are.
They stole my pizza!
Sorry, we've got to fly.
Dad?
- Ciao, Baby Squad.
- Oh.
They're getting away again?
But look what they left behind.
You found my pizza.
But it's a bigger pizza.
It's enough for the prime minister
and the whole city.
Well, at least we got
the scepter and the pizza.
- Now we can shop.
- Yeah.
Ah, pizza.
Grazie.
Ancora? Grazie.
Ah, grazie.
Now that's
a pizza di tutte le pizze!
Good work, Baby Squad.
We've recovered
two of the crown jewels.
We just need to find the queen's crown
to make her Jubilee in time.
The Glockenspiel!
Polizei! Polizei!
The Glockenspiel has been stolen!
Come, come!
- Argh! They defaced the Glockenspiel!
- Polizei!
Those babies,
always up to something.
Here we go.
Time to test the upgrades
to my Cosmonauter.
What's it do?
Using two screens,
I can search
for the queen's jewels
and alien life forms.
Does it work?
Let's find out.
Imagine I want to send aliens
a friendly message
and find the jewels.
I got a bad feeling about this.
And behold!
Where did my cup go?
Don't worry.
Mrs. Garcia is my problem.
The Glockenspiel is kaput!
This is a crime that has struck
at the very heart of Germans
everywhere.
Hans, we understand completely
and we're on it.
Bobbins out.
- Okay, listen up.
I've got tofu waffles
and soy milk.
Everybody eat up.
Okay, team.
- Man, good stuff.
- Really?
That was Hans Bezelug,
the son of Germany's top police chief.
It looks like we're going
to Munich, Germany,
where one of the country's most
precious symbols-- the Glockenspiel--
has been defaced and brought
to a complete standstill.
That's awful.
The Glockenspiel
is one of the most beautiful
and intricate clocks ever made.
Fortunately, we do have
a suspect this time.
That is just so wrong.
Somebody needs a time-out.
Skip and Jordan,
you're on the away team.
Alfred, Gabi, and Kylie
will be backing you up from here.
And, Holden-
Where is Holden?
How do I look?
Like Hansel in search of Gretel.
Haven't you guys ever heard
the term "undercover"?
You should be
under the covers.
Guess what.
A new Big Daddy Burgers
has opened in Munich.
I smell a Big Baby.
Yeah.
Activating vortex.
Good luck, team.
And remember...
mein hiinden
ist nicht stubenrein.
Your dog is not housebroken?
Uh, maybe that didn't
come out right.
Oh, and you
watch over him, okay?
Don't worry, I'll take good care
of the babies.
I think she's saying the babies
should be looking after you.
Energy field at full power.
Normal activation 97, 93,
99%.
Wheel
- Whoa.
- I can't see. I can't see.
Let me get this.
There we go.
Whew, looks like there's still
a few kinks in the Z-35 Vortex.
Uh, sir?
You should not sneak up
on anybody like that.
Did you sneak
into the car anyways?
Finally, a tourist
with a sense of style.
You are a cool dude, man.
See? I told you I was cool.
Dream on, dude.
Such smart-looking babies, eh?
You know, I had a lot of
smart people in the cab.
Albert Einstein
drove in this cab.
This is when he was nothing.
He was just Albert.
And I couldn't roll up
the windows.
The wind, when we were driving,
made his hair all crazy.
That's-- that's great.
Can you take us to
the Big Daddy Burgers restaurant?
Oh, sure, I could take you
to Big Daddy Burgers.
If you like burgers that taste like
old socks, that's the place.
Look at that guy.
- Haven't we seen him before?
- Who, me?
Don't we know you
from somewhere?
Let's not talk about me.
I'll take you on a tour of Munich, ja?
Hans Bezelug,
chief of police.
Holden Hammer-smith,
with the World Clock Institute.
These are members from our
Junior Timekeepers League.
Interesting.
Makes about as much sense
as your outfit.
What do you have for us so far?
Only that we've been unable
to reset the Glockenspiel.
And that by leaving
this statue behind,
the thief is daring us
to catch him!
This guy's got anger issues.
He taunts us!
He needs to chill out.
Any other clues
from the crime scene?
Just this stone debris
from where the perpetrator
- entered the clock tower.
- Look at this stuff, guys.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
What do we have here?
Okay, team, listen up.
Run a digital
spectrum analysis.
Skip, see what else
you can find.
I'm on it.
Got something.
Oh, a ticket.
Oh, darn, it's in German.
Well, we are in Germany.
Guys, I found something.
Let me get it.
- Ugh!
- Oh.
- Let me help you.
- Here.
- I could have gotten it.
- Good work.
Find anything unusual,
besides your hat?
Did it take you all day
to think of that one?
Yeah. Pretty much.
I'm uploading the clues now.
Well, it's definitely a tool,
but not the kind that any modern
nut or bolt would fit.
Great. We now know what they used,
but the question is why.
Why would Big Baby
sabotage the Glockenspiel?
I don't know why, but now we know
where he's been.
Snickety-snack. A ticket stub.
Maybe they went to a movie.
This is a ticket for the tour
of Castle Neuschwanstein.
Pack your bags.
We're heading to Bavaria.
Walt Disney was so impressed
with the architecture,
he modeled the Sleeping Beauty
castle on it.
Help yourselves to a Red Delicious
poisoned apple...
...if you dare.
All right, guys,
we know Big Baby's here.
We just have to find out why.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Holden, watch out.
Checking heat signature levels.
Collecting rocks
and mortar samples.
Ultraviolet scan.
Holden here.
Transmitting clues
from Castle Neus--
Neuschwenber-- Neus--
the castle.
Any data
from the crime scene?
Okay, this is how the computer
breaks it down.
Someone breached internal security
through the ventilation shaft.
He used the wrench that you found
at Big Daddy Burgers
to remove the clock's
pinion cog.
What's a pinion cog do?
It runs the timing system. So in other
words, it makes the clock smart.
Alfred, maybe your brain needs
a pinion cog.
Oh, that hurt.
We have to get Big Baby fast.
We only have an hour left
before we have to get the stolen
crown back to the queen.
What about the clues we just
collected from the castle?
Checking that now.
Gabi, give me a spectrum comparison.
Bingo.
The stone samples
from the crime scene
match the same ones
Jordan just found at the castle.
That means whatever we're looking
for is right under our feet.
- That's a no-no.
- Ouch.
All right, the clock
is ticking, people.
Somewhere in this place
there's a secret passage.
We're gonna have to
find it quick
or there's gonna be
one very unhappy queen.
I'm picking up something.
This section is hollow.
Okay, they taught this
at the academy.
All secret hatches
must be activated
by a force-to-pressure ratio
mounted exactly
two feet from the base.
It's right here.
Oh.
Perfect.
Don't give up hope, Holden.
Something will
pop up soon.
Now we're never gonna get the crown
back to the queen.
Man!
- What's happening?
- Whatever it is, it's major.
Whoa, you guys
got to see this.
You're a little late to stop me.
What is that thing?
Say hello to my little friend.
While you've been playing
with blocks,
I've been building this.
Meet the Expander Ray.
Dad, sit down!
- After I finish entering the code...
...l'll step in front,
activate the beam,
and in seconds
grow to over 100 times my size!
That's one big baby.
That's one big diaper.
Whoa, what did you do
to your dad?
A little too much hypnosis.
Not to worry.
Soon I won't need hypnosis,
'cause he too will answer
to the new and improved
Bigger Baby!
He is one bad little boy.
All right, we can't let him
get away with this.
That's it. I'll wake up Beauregard
from his trance.
And I'll distract Big Baby.
And I'll shut down
the Expander Ray.
All right, Baby Squad on three.
One, two, three.
- Baby Squad!
- All right, let's go, guys.
Hey, Beauregard.
Wake up.
Nein!
Okay, burger man,
repeat after me.
Let go of my joust.
- Are you sure?
- Ja!
Yes!
I am in control.
I am not in control.
This isn't going to be easy.
So, Big Baby,
why the queen's crown?
It's a unique combination of rare
gold, silver, and diamonds.
It makes it
the perfect power source.
Why do you want to be so big?
You're a grown-up.
You don't know what it's like
to be a baby.
"Take a nap! Go to bed!
Eat your vegetables!"
Have you ever tried
mashed broccoli?
I know what he means.
Now I'm going to be
the size of 100 adults.
You're too late, Baby Squad.
Look out, world.
Here comes Bigger Baby!
Junior, what do you think
you're doing?
This is not the type of young man
I wanted you to be.
Want to be a good boy
or a naughty boy?
A naughty boy
- I did it!
- Touchdown!
Kids, come here, quick.
Cover your eyes. Hurry.
- Cover them.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Big Baby's pocket-sized.
BB, you're tiny.
Aww,
he's kind of cute now.
I don't want to be cute.
Officers, here's your man.
I mean, your Big Baby.
I mean, the Big Baby
who is now a small baby.
I don't think we have
a prison cell this size.
Perhaps a shoebox?
Mark my words, Baby Squad.
I'll be back!
And when I am, you'll regret it.
Hey, I'm kind of hungry.
Can we stop for a burger?
Auf wiedersehen, Baby Squad.
Come on, team.
Put your glasses on.
-- We need emergency Z-35 activation.
Take us to Buckingham Palace.
Get it right this time.
I've got your position
triangulated.
We'll meet you there.
Stand by.
The crown.
Grab hands.
Here we go.
Ahh!
I think this is for you,
Your Highness.
Indeed.
It's fit for a queen.
- Bye. Bye.
- Ta-ta.
- Bye.
- We did it!
Good-bye,
Your Royal Highness.
We received a tip that somebody smarter
and more devious than Big Baby
might be after
the Expander Ray techno-
Where is it?
The Expander Ray,
it's gone!
We must alert Interpol.
I agree with you, Inspector.
I am as smart as Big Baby
and more devious
than Big Baby.
They think I'm a cabdriver.
By the time they find out
I'm the great Moriarty,
I will have played them
like a piano.
They don't know
who they're dealing with.
I know..
Me.
Job well done, Bob.
You're now unofficially official.
Haiger out.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, Dad.
Aww.
And we love our little
spy baby
and the rest
of the Baby Squad, too.
we're official.
- Yay!
- That's what I'm talking about.
- We are the Baby Squad.
? Feeling good right now ?
? Take a look right now ?
? Once I was a little shy ?
? But now I'm gonna
catch your eye ?
? Oh, yeah, yeah ?
? Don't you know
I've got to show ?
? Just what I've been
keeping inside? ?
? Feeling good now, baby ?
? Take a look now, baby ?
? I know it takes a little while ?
? But now I see your smile ?
- .' I'm gonna let it shine .'
- .' Feeling good right now .'
- .' I've really got to shine .'
- .' Take a look right now .'
- .' I'm gonna let it shine .'
- .' Feeling good right now .'
- .' I'm really gonna shine .'
- .' Take a look right now .'
- .' I'm gonna let it shine, shine .'
- .' Feeling good right now .'
- .' Shine, shine, yeah .'
- .' Take a look right now .'
? Feeling good right now... ?
- We got a bogey in the air.
Switching to the Garcia cam.
Recon robot is active.
Activating beam
inside robot dog.
Bogey has eyes
on our robot alarm.
Switching to mobile
surveillance code for recon.
Setting velocity beam.
Stand by
for level-four distraction.
-- Argh!
Take it up to level nine.
Ahh!
Distraction contained. Yes!