Go, Katyl Go, Katyl Go, gol
Go, Katyl Go, Katyl Go, Katyl Go, gol
Marie, this is police business.
I oouldwa washed you.
It's just a water gun, you jerk.
This is Mad Dog. I can't wait
for backup. I'm going in alone.
You're dead meat, Mad Dog.
[door closes]
You feel lucky about yourself, Sanchez?
- Do you, punk'?
- Eat slime, cop.
You're mine.
Sanchez, come out
with your hands in the air.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, nol I thought you were on fire.
We're not finished, Mr Bufler.
You're lucky I got a class.
Damn civilians.
[door cruakfi]
OK, we'll do 'rt the hard way.
Freeze, dirlbagl
- Get outta here.
- I'm history.
Nice u! you t: drop 'm, Butler.
Well, I'm dropping out.
If you hurt mo,
my dad'll rip your head off.
Blood and guts and slime
will be coming out your ears.
That don't re Rio.
- My dad's doin' hard time.
- You must be very proud.
- I am.
- Whoa.
A dollar a day.
That's a bargain to come to this school.
- Ain't it?
- You smell like vomit.
Bufler thinks he's a real cop.
Put me duwnl
Crawl back in the hole you me froml
- Thanks for the money, dweeb.
- Give 'rt back to ma, you pus heads.
- Pus heads? That calls for payback.
- Put me downl Put me downl
- Guys, please.
- You little twerpl
- I meant it in the nicest my.
-Too badl
- [toilet flushes]
- Swifly.
Looks like you had a little accident
- Hope you have fun.
- Enjoy your recess, nerd.
- Let me inl Let me inl
- I love this school.
I've been looking for you, mister.
You been swimmin'?
No, he's been dunkin' for finds.
That's enoughl
Let's you and I take a walk.
- Give my regards to Mr Fleming.
- [children] Yeahl
Now, is“ ma, what have you
burned may'? Sit up straight.
That I can hold my breath
a lot longer than I thought I could.
Do I sense... a little insolenoe?
NO.
Devon. Devon, Devon, Devon.
Lies are not oxplanafions.
I'm not lying.
Every day these big jumbos
come and inks my money,
they put me in the toilet
and hold me upside down.
Always blaming 'rt on someone else.
You leave me no choice, Devon.
I have to call your grandmother.
Mr Fleming, please.
You don't have to ll her.
She can't take personal calls.
it makes her sick.
And she's on a very hard shift now.
SR dawn, Devon.
Devon, if I don't make this call,
you will never learn,
and I would have done you
a great injustice.
- 283, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Whit?
Yes, Mr Fleming.
Thank you.
Don't worry about Fleming.
Ho's just a dork.
Why doesn't my grandmother know that?
[siren wails]
Shop, listen.
- Fire tuck'?
- No, that's a cop.
It's a code three. Let's roll.
[tuck horn blaras]
[copon speaker] I'm notqetfinq
outoftfaiscanlhetetorun!
lbldyou
Pmnotgetfingoutofthiscar!
What are you, a nut?
L°°pllwamedyou_
- Do all oops do that?
- Only the best.
[cop] Quintana, who do you think
is gonna run out of gas first?
Chu, got inl
- [Devon] Here, hold these.
- Got 'em.
- Did you got the license?
- You but.
[cop] Quintaro, don? jump
over that fence. I hate to run.
Lookl We gotta go see thatl
Son of a... Son of a...
I hats in jump-
I really hate to jump.
Come on, Sanchezl Keep up.
We're gonna win first prize this year.
Oh, my goodnessl
Who do you think you are,
the Lone Ranger? Got out of my ynrdl
[cop] End of the linel
Hey, get your fitthy butt off my car.
I just had 'rt waxed.
All right,
we're gonna do it the hard my.
All right, stop whining.
Did you drop something?
Looks like drugs.
- That ain't mine.
- You know who I am?
You used to be Nick McKenna
before you lost a step.
Owl
I'm sorry. I broke the nose.
And I gotta fix 'rt I'm s...
Let mefixthis.
Hhinklnfixit
[Quintana screams]
Did you hear it? I should've been
a doctor. It's all right
Sony about the disturbance.
All right Put your hands out.
You know the drill.
Now I'm gonna fie you to the r.
I don't want you getlin' in my car.
Yeah.
You know my:
Bemuse you stink “ks garbage.
OK, you ready?
And we'll just take
this little evidence along.
You overweight mtl
You're a sore loserl
McKenna, come on, man.
Listen, this is not civilised.
He's makin' that 'fool
run all the way back to the station.
Damn you, MoKonnal You're not
gonna do ihisl Not the froevnyl
Let's get outta here.
- Bye.
- See you later.
[woman] Let's go. Come on.
You're late.
- Fresnel
- Devon?
You won't believe what me and Ray saw.
'What Ray and I saw."
- The school called again.
- VVhafd the school say'?
“WM- vw arm Sbp phyin'
5519'“! 90p games.
They're not stupid.
And just shit inking responsibility.
But if were a policeman,
I probably could take care of you
and get my own apartment someday.
I hke re of myself.
You learn to hke re of yourself.
Did you see my "W?
- You're going to work'?
- Yes, I'm going to work.
The keys are in the ashlny,
next to my handcuffs.
Yes, the hospital's short-handed.
I gotta sub again.
But tonight's the night
we vntch Miami Vice.
Don't you think I wish I could just
sit back and vntoh TV with you?
You're a nurse.
You could make up some great disease.
Aw.
You know I can't do that
[car horn beeps]
There's my ride. In bed by ninel
- But, Grandma, wit“
- Not a minute Mafl
- Do you hear ma, Devon?
- I can't do that 10.30.
Forgot it.
9.45. I'm in the fourth grade.
9.30. And you're in the third grade.
- Deal. You have your police whistle?
- Yes, Devon, I have 'rt.
Mrs Norris is gonna look in on you.
Make sure you leave your homework out
so I can check 'rt.
Leaving him alone again, I see.
Sfickin' your sweet hoe into
everybodys business again, I see.
Bye-
Your gmndmolher should be
reported to Social Services.
Oh, really? And you should be
reported to the Orkin Man.
$998M Spanish
You're under enssl.
[man] My client's ready to make a deal.
lwomenlFitstdeqreeraducedbaecorud,
withnomorathentenyeers.
- Make it five.
- Seven.
Bu! m want him
m may against Medford.
That's bonus inlbrmation.
Ever hear of quid pm qua?
- Onehendweshestheother?
-Quidproquo.
[women] Get me some soap.
Hey, Ray, wanna go for a ride?
Sony, I have b eat dinner
with my parents. Cell you Mar.
OK.
That black r againl
Wuhan“
Quintere, McKenna gave you
the third degree?
He asked about Bebe, the drugs
being delivered to Mr Fountain.
- I told him zippo.
- You did good.
Good enough to moot the boss,
you lucky sliff.
Ho's gonna thank you personally.
- What do you think'? Sit.
- I'm just bein' a shnd-up guy.
.R wen, hey!
J" I'm the type of guy
that likes toruam wound
tfmneverinoneplecqhey!
lroemfromhwntohwn
Hlovebmendlleevebm
uosyouknowthetfmtfsebest
Hhopinbmyoer
endldriveeroundthewofld
♪ They call me the wanderer
Yeah, the wanderer
J" {roam around and round
and round and round
♪ Round and round
and round and round I'
- Hey, boss, you kill me.
- You are my idol, Mr Fountain, my idol.
I'm so happyto moot you.
I lave your singing.
Do you have an album out?
You wouldn't just say that to butbar
me up? Because I detest hypocrisy.
NO W5'!-
ON Chu, there's a fish 'm have.
Get rid oi 'n.
- You got it.
- What are you doin'? Tum loose of mo.
In a fit of nostalgia,
I ms gonna shoot you myself,
but I hate being so hands-on,
but I hate shoolies even more.
Sbooliel I'm no stoolie.
I never said a word to McKenna.
Are you kidding me? You think I don't
knowwhymey lat you go sofast?
You got it all wrong.
What a waste of a good chicken leg.
Relax. You're gonna got indigestion.
This is gonna take you
all the way back to 1961 .
♪ Spli-sh, splash, I was hkin'a bath
♪ All about e Saturday night
♪ Bum, bum, bum, bum
♪ Rub-e-dub, I jumped beck in the tub I'
Bobo delivers the euphoria, 10.30
Thursday morning. That's 10o grand.
Did your cop friends got that,
Quintana, huh?
Was it loud enough for you, huh?
[mufflod yelling]
[Fountain] What? You can't swim?
Quintana, I hope
you got your flippers on.
I hope your suit is drip-dry.
- [splash]
- [clinging]
- Relax. Probably the pigeons.
- I'll take care of 'rt.
- Oh, no.
- I'm 00min', boss.
We'll take care of this, Mr Fountain.
- You really think that's gonna work'?
- No, boss. I'm stupid.
Just once I would likn to conduct
business in a hygienic environment
- [woman] McKenna, give me something.
- I just got here. Give me a break.
- Hey, found him for you.
- Quintana?
- So much for the "scum floats" 'theory.
- He was my only lead.
- Hey, relax. Got a witness.
- You got a witness?
- Yes, sir.
- Where is he?
Ho's right aver here.
Where?
- Nick.
- Yeah?
Over here.
He's been askin' for you all night
- Hi.
I'm Devon Butler.
You an lust m“ me Devon.
Ready for fingerpriniiflfl?
Let me hlkto you a minute.
Any idea what a sharp lawyer
will do to a kid on a witness stand?
He will rip him to shreds. He won't
know the killer from Captain Kangaroo.
- Nick, he's all we got
- What's up?
Lilfle boy.
If you sawihe bad man again,
would you recognise him?
Don't you think a formal intanogafion
downtown is in order?
And Captain Kangaroo
hasn't been on the air for nine years.
God hates mo. Got his parent.
Got him downtown.
- [Nick] Who are you?
- I'm Devon Bufler.
I just told you back there.
Short memory.
Look at that fat jumbo. [laughs]
Do you recognise anybody in the book'?
You have any pictures
of these guys from the back'?
I don't think I like that quesfion. Why'?
That's the my I saw 'em.
I'm gonna explain something to you,
all right?
Sea, my strong suit is not patience.
Sowhatlwantyoutodo
is lookatthe book
and find someone that you recognise.
Otherwise I'm going to rip
your little head off.
- I got a plate number.
- Why didn't you tell us before?
Anybody ever heard u! quid pro qua'?
One hand washes the other.
Thais bonus information.
- VVould you like a Popsicle?
- I don't want no Popsicle.
I wanna see your superior.
Hello, Devon. My name is Captain Rubio.
I understand that you wanted to see me.
You need me to testify and identify'?
Yes, Devon, that would be very helpful.
Ma'am, I'd like to cut a deal.
- Hevnn1stobeacop.
-What?
Shield, assignments,
squad car, the works.
He won't help us unless he gets it.
Bring the criminal back
when you anast him.
Don't go... Don't go let him eat
Just bring him to jail.
Bring him to jaill
Give me five minutes with him alone.
Hey, uh...
So, anybody want a sip?
Guess not
[Devon hums]
Devon, sweetie.
Why don't you just go ahead
and give us that plats number?
- And then we can all go home.
- OK. Make me a cop.
Why do you wanna be a cop?
Look at this guy.
Raggedy-ass clolhes, 20-year-old r,
bad back, bad marriage, bad attitude.
Does that sound like any kind of life?
But if you were a cop,
people don't sass you.
- Give us the plats numberl
- Nickl
I tall you what, I'll give you
a little taste of what I got
A taste? Where does he get this stufi'?
Prime-time.
There's a shipment
of euphoria coming in.
Tell us something we don't know.
Thursday, 10.30.
Min-hm.
- Where?
- Don't know, but I got a name.
Why is everyone galherin' around me?
- What's the name?
- I really vnnna give you this name.
You put me on duty, it's yours.
Hey, McPhaiL I'm from out! space.
- Listen, you've had ride-alongs before.
- No, I don't.
- Take him for eight hours.
- Other guys have ride-alongs.
Put a sock in it, Nickl
I vnnt you to drive him around
for eight hours,
let him hit ihe siren, humour him.
- What is the problem with this?
- I don't got along with kids.
- Nobody cares.
- You can't have any fun with a kid.
He has one drink,
he falls off his stool. What?
You gave me a wonderful present today:
two destroyed lawns...
- I gave you a perp.
- Reckless endangerment You awe me.
I don't awe you nolhin'l
When you got home,
check and see haw the blues fit.
A little snug under the bait?
- Hello, I'm
- Babyl
Oh. baby-
- I told them not to call.
- You had me scared to deathl
Mrs Baldwin, hi. I'm Captain Rubio.
We spoke before.
As I explained, young Devon
witnessed a murder eaflier.
- He wasn't harmed.
- They're gonna lat me be a cop.
We're gonna have one of our men
ride him around for a few hours,
sortofasarwnrd.
It's quid pro quo for helping them out.
My grandson has seen
all I want him to see of police work.
This is going to be nothing dangerous.
He's going to be riding
with our most decorated man.
Devon, you ride around
with me for eight hours.
If you so much as think
about getting in my way,
I'm gonna fie your little ass
to the axle
and drag you all aver the city, OK?
Nick, I'd like you to meat
Devon's grandmother.
- How do you do?
- Don't bother with introductions.
We're leaving.
You talk to my grandson again like that
and you'll be wearing that axle.
I'll be serving our community,
inking responsibility.
- Now wherdd you got that?
- From you.
- Well...
- Thank youl
- Now, I didn't say yes.
- But you said "well".
You alvnys say "well"
before you say "yes".
Well... We need to discuss
this some more.
That's sharp, Nick.
[Fountain] I' Remember when
I first met you
Wish me luck.
XTheheevenainmyheed
tLeapedinloyourflwf
- You're amazing.
- You really think so, huh?
This halter be good.
[Chu] Well, sir, they got a witness.
And what did this witness witness?
It's just some kid,
but we know where he lives.
How much could a little kid see?
[mocking laugh]
I ms a lilfle kid once myself
and I saw everylhing.
Thank you.
Chu, find out everything you n
about this kid.
[Devon] Nice pair of boots, Nick.
I'll have to get me a pair of those.
- So what kind of hardware do you carry'?
- I canya bazooka inmehunk.
Everyone, could I please
got your aflanfion?
You be careful out there.
- Don't talk to anybody, especially me.
- Take care of him. He's fading fast.
- I'm not a miracle worker.
- Get in the r.
My shield, my badge?
All right, here you are.
Now got in the r.
I always wanted one of these.
Got in the rl
Yes?
My cuffs. A cop's gofln have cuffs.
He's right, McKenna. Cufis are what
make this job worth doing.
Thank you.
Everybody. get in the rl
- Jawohl.
- Aye, aye, sir.
Let's get dawn to business.
We're gonna have fun.
- Right Buckle up.
- Wait a minute. I n't see.
Raise your butt up.
All right
Calling all can.
This is Detective Butler.
- What are you doing?I
- Wherever you
You give me no joy.
[Devon] What you got under the hood?
[McKnnna] I got an engine
and in a minute, you.
[Devon] When do we stop
for doughnuts and coffee?
Haven't you heard about secondary smoke?
Heard about minding your awn business?
At this very moment,
the pink, delicate tissues
of my still-forming lungs
may be shrivelling
into green chunks of mucus,
struggling for their last gasp
u! poison, brown air.
- Happy'?
- Now you're littering.
- What are we here for?
- Shknout It's your shift.
Do I look like a five-yaar-old to you?
I can't tall.
The lighfs nottoo good in here.
Dani's off. This is Dullsville.
Well, lesson number one:
police work is Dullsville.
- Whafd you have in mind?
- Cop sluff.
Shakedowns, shoot-outs,
busfing scumbags.
Right
LOOK. partner.
A code 27. Purse snatch.
Hey, come halal
Heyl Kidl
[Devon] Shop, thiafl
[hem blarus]
Hey, watch where you're drivingl
- I'm commandeering your vehicle.
- Hey, got back halal Are you nuls?
Whoal Whool
Dammitl
Police businessl Coming ihroughl
Look outl
Sorry-
[Devon] Slnpl I hatch mnl
- Makn it easy on yourself.
- Marlhal Marlhal
- Shop, ihiefl
- Bye, honey. Have a nice day.
- Thanks, honey.
- What are you doing?
- You're under anust Code 27.
[Pflfliiflil]
Boy, Nick, you don't look too great
I nabbed the purse snatcher.
My wife forgot her purse.
I ms flying to catch herl
- You're not a purse snatcher?
- No. I'm calling the oops.
I am a police offioer.
- What are you gonna do about this?
- This?
I'm gonna kill this.
Why do you think I spend
hours and hours at the range
shooting at silhouettes,
shooting the heads out of 'om?
Every single day.
I've been doin' that for years.
Why do you think I do that? I do that
because I don't wanna chase anybody.
I don't like to run.
So I want you to give me
the plate numberl
Hey, this is more likn it.
Pamela are supposed to fight
Part of the lava/hate rulafionship.
We don't have a lava/hate relafionshipl
We have a hula/hate rulafionship.
You must drive
your grandmother bonkersl
How do you know'?
You don't even live with us.
Give me the plats number.
Plats number: N6B72G.
- Hey, Nick.
- Go.
We got a make
on a '65 Lincoln Continent!
registered to a D DiMucci, 264 Bowman.
Let's get a warrant
and ransack the place.
- 10-4.
- Wail a minute, wail a minute.
264 Bowman is a public library.
I figure DiMuccik e phoney name also.
[McKenna] A public library. Will
you give me something that I can use?
Bobo.
- Bobo who?
- Bobo I don't know.
Haw many Babes an there be'?
You bother pray just one.
[as Poo-Woe Herman]
Bombing Bufler. Annhl
Come on, Jenkins.
You don't wanna be like him.
- [imitates elephant]
- What is this, a zoo?
- It's a partyl it's a Part!"
- [phone rings]
Grow upl
I'm listening to you.
Offioer Bufler here.
OK, lady, calm down. Calm down.
VVhafd the cat look like?
No, I'm eight Hello?
- [dialling lone]
- Hello?
Damn civilians.
What have we got?
We got three Bobos.
[cluckinfl]
[confinues clucking]
Detective Bufler here.
Detective McKanna would like
to ask you a few quesfions.
- Go ahead, Nick.
- [clucking]
Is your name Bobo?
Perfectl
- Are you Mr Bobo?
- In blue.
Listen, I don't think this is the guy.
I didn't know alt ms so dangerous.
How did you know he wasn't our Bobo?
Lesson number two:
you gofln bust your instincts.
When you were in school,
kids ever pick on you?
Yeah.
- Whafd you do?
- Well...
I handled it the best my I could.
Hey, Nick, it's a code 73.
- What's today, Bobo?
- Today? Feels like a Wednesday.
- I don't know.
- Tell mel
You shy in the r. Don't got out.
Yeah, yeah. yeah-
[man yells In Spanish]
- My mother gave us this.
- That's right
And you know whit?
She gave us this tool
- What the hell's goin' on here?
- Ask him, sir, Mr Bobo.
Ask him what day it is todayl
- ls your name Bobo?
- I forgot our anniversary.
[onlookers boo]
You forgot your anniversary?
- It's your anniversary?
- And I got a present for you, Bobo.
No, no, no. Not the Ids. No, no, no.
All... all of your old baseball Ids.
[husband] No, nol
[speaks Spanish]
Don't, ma'am.
Detective Bufler here.
What seems to be the problem?
- Get in the r.
- Domesfi require two police offioers.
You're not a police offioerl
Got in the rl
Can I hlkto you for a minute?
Never let civilians see us disagree.
it undermines my authority.
I'm disgusted. Really disgusted.
When you shop being mad at him,
you're gonna be mad at yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll never shop being mad at himl
Who are you, the Mickey Mouse pahol?
Get your skinny butt outta there
before she throws you outl
Nick, please, give me a second, OK?
You think it's bad he forgot
an anniversary? it's not so bad.
I have these big jumbos
who always throw me in the toilet
and, worse yet,
I have him for a partner.
You two at least have each dlher,
even though you don't have
any more plates.
Yeah, you may be right
I may be right
Bobo, shit up the shits.
She can start down.
You guys can meat hatfw-ay.
Thank you.
Instinct, right?
- He wasn't the Bobo.
- Right
You know whit?
You were very good back there.
What time you gonna pick me up tomorrow'?
- I'm not
- Why'? You said I did a great job.
You didn't kill ma, I didn't kill you.
But the deal was one shift.
- But there's another Bobo.
- Yeah. He pops up, I'll unite you.
I knew you would change your mind, Nick.
I knew it.
Give me your sluff.
You're a good kid.
So what happened? You shoot anybody?
- Nothing happened.
- Come on. Something musfve happened.
Naming happen“-
All right
Hey, Ray, they want us to keep
this stufi kind of hush-hush.
You know, police business.
Do you understand? Come on.
I.
- Sowhat do you want to do'?
- Leis grab a Ding Dong.
Hwy. Ray. Slnpl Lookl
The black Lincoln. Got aver halal
- They know our neighbourhood.
- Who does?
They want me, nut you.
Keep this 'm the evidence baker.
I'll take care of 'rt
Now mm around
and vnlk out of here naiumlly.
Nam rally.
- Hey, how you doin', fart head?
- Mr Big Shot with the oops, huh?
Don't you morons
have anything else to do?
- VVhafd you do that for?
- Cos you called me a moron.
Throwing yourjackat on the ground
makes you smarter?
This kid's making me nuts.
Hey, guys, I can't kid around any more.
I'm watching my grandma's car.
- So you're here with Grandma?
- Mm-hm.
So this is Gmndmommys r, huh?
Hey, guys, please.
Bust me up, but not the r. Please.
You mean don't do this?
- Thais exactly ma“ mean.
- Or this'?
Ah, ho bad.
My mm. This is your kiss goodbye.
Hey, what are you doin'?
I'll break your heel
Jflevercatch upwilhyoul
- We'll got you, you lilfle bmisl
Let's got back in the r.
Come on, let's go.
Ah, look at this. These punks got
no respect nowadays. Get in the r.
Hi, Grandma.
[slams phone]
- It finally caught up with you.
- What did?
The new school counsellofs
here to see you.
I hope you're happy.
Just answer euveryming, 'truthfully.
There you are. Hi, Devon.
Hi.
You recognise mo?
NO.
I'm Mr Goodman,
the new counsellor from school.
You haven't seen me around school, huh?
NO.
We“, his sit dawn.
you know why I'm here?
- Missing school today?
- Exncfly.
You've been helping the police
find a very dangerous man.
You won't believe
the dirlbags
Hello? Devon? You were saying?
I said I didn't see them.
I didn't see the bad guy's face.
That's good. I mean, that's bad.
- Probably the police are disappointed.
- Very disappointed.
Mad, too, because I wasted their time.
- Well...
- I'm afraid we're out of cream.
Gee. You know whit?
I'm gonna inks a min check on this
because I've got...
I think I'll take one of these.
lwegotafewstops I havebo make.
- Is euveryming all right?
- I'm very pleased with Devon.
Asamafiaruifachbeuoflsagombuy.
You have a good day.
Gmndmal
- Hey, hey, mister.
- Damn.
- Come here.
- What?
Excuse mo? Come here?
I overheard your oonversafion.
That woman n't control...
Got your arm off mo, madam,
or I'll put you in a home.
[Nick] I cannot do my job
with a kid aroundl I do not like kidsl
Why does he have to shy with mo?
Why not with somebody also?
Believe me, you wouldn't even be
my second choice.
But the kid is comfortable with you.
Come on, how long can 'rt last?
Give me a break here.
Besides, you have such
a lovely rapport with him.
Let's go.
You are going to listen
to Mr McKenna, right?
- Detective McKenna?
- Detective McKenna.
Look at mo. Devon, look at mo.
Now, you won't leave here
without him, right?
- Grandma, he's got a gun.
- I'm sure he has.
You won't leave him and go
and play cowboys and Indians?
Next time somebody breaks in,
why don't you ll the bunkhouse
and ask for a cowboy?
They'd come a lot faster than you.
I've been busfin' my chops
all my life...
- Anybody see Barnyard Cop?
- What?
He always asks his partner".
what comes afbar L?
- I don't know.
- Bow. Don't you got it?
- Elbowl
- [McKenna coughs]
You hit me one more time
with your L-bow
and I'm gonna rip 'rt off
and wave 'rt at you.
You keep pullin' that attitude
with my grandson.
I don't have an attitude, lady.
I'm just a police dlfioer.
Come here.
- Take re of yourself, Devon.
- I will.
Hey, Nick. ls 10o grand
the same as 10o thousand?
Yeah, my:?
The guy in the warehouse said 'rt
"1 (I) grand."
I heard 'rtwas more like
a hundred million.
- Wait.
- Hm?
- Swords.
- What swords?
Come on, it's fun.
My friend Raymond n piss eight fest.
Ho's my new hem.
Watch what you're doin'.
- Come on, this'll be
- [tickling]
Sorry-
Good night, kid.
- Hey, Nick'?
- Yeah?
Aren't you gonna read me a story'?
You gotta get your batteries recharged.
Besides, you're eight
I'm not gonna road to you.
Don't you know anylhing about kids?
It relaxes us.
Once upon a time... "Randy Milligan was
released from the Kansas City Hospital
and planned to join his team-mates
for a hip to New Yolk
on Thursday night"
"Milligan was knocked unconscious
If Iar he ran into second baseman
Billy Ripknn whi..."
Give me a break. It's a story.
"Milligan was knocked unconscious
afbar he ran into Billy Ripken
while chasing a ground ball
on Wednesday night"
"Milligan sustained minor concussion
and loft the field in an ambulance."
"Tests Thursday revealed
no major damage besides concussion."
"Milligan suffered a... a, uh...
bruised cheekbone and. . ."
Actually, the doctors
don't have much hope for him.
They're gonna cut off his testicles.
[Devon coughs]
Oh, boss, these are beautiful.
[hllms]
- VVhafd you find out, Chu?
- Sir, the kid's with McKenna.
- Why?
- Cos I'm boiling.
Are you gentlemen capable
of doing anything right?
Absolutely.
With McKenna, huh?
Erase 'em like a bad grade.
You got it, boss.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[claflarind]
I just wanted a glass of milk.
Incoming.
- So you're dumping the kid?
- I gave him to McPhail.
McPhail already has some kids.
- I'm not used to this sluff.
- What slufl'?
Look, I'm not a bodyguard.
I'm not a baby-sitter.
I have a routine.
I have a routine to do.
Uh-huh.
Well, I guess the kid
has gotten to you, huh?
Give file kid in McPhaill
He likes oornflakas in the morning.
[sighs]
38 in a 35 zone. What do you think,
Devon? Do we let him slide?
- I don't care.
- You gotta help me out here, Devon.
I was gonna lat him slide,
only you gotta be with me.
We're partners here.
And don't tell Rubio.
- OK, let him slide.
- Hey. Good decision.
- You'll make a good cop.
- Nick doesn't think so.
Hey, let me tall you
something about Nick.
Eight years ago, there was a drug bust
and his parlnerwas killed.
Nobodys fault, but Nick blamed himself.
You understand?
Aflar that he wouldn't let anyone close.
He wouldn't be friends
with anything that breathed.
But it vnsn't his fault.
I know that Try convincing Nick.
If he'd liSIBn, I'd by.
I know, I know. Come on, you're on duty.
- There's one we gotta nab.
- 38 in a 35 zone. Could lat him slide.
Please, we gotta nab this one. Pleasel
- Book 'em, Dan-O.
- Yesl
- You'll need this.
- Thanks.
You, pull aver.
Yes, Offioer?
Licence and rogishafion,
please, Mr Fleming.
What's gain' on have'? What are you...
I'm your worst nighlmare.
An eight-year-old with a badge.
I'm in a huny, Bufler, and I got
a nightmare for you in my dlfioe.
- You know when that is.
- Don't sass mo.
Oflioer Buiier
has full jurisdiction here.
Slap out of your r, please, sir.
- Is this for real?
- Out
Hands on the hood and spread 'em.
- Any concealed weapons?
- No.
In explain. I...
Herman, if I don't do this,
you will never loam
and I would be doing you
a great injustice.
- Fleming, right?
- Yes.
- Yes, what?
- Yes, sir.
Thanks.
Due by Tuesday.
[WIN SGIOOOh]
You see him?
Yeah.
[Chu] Our little problem
is about to go away.
Dena!“
Nol
HEM
- You OK?
- Yeah.
That ms just likn Miami Vice.
I- I- I-
I, I, I would go Iflar that Linoolnl
Let's go. I'm too old for this.
[siren wails]
- You sure you're all right?
- Yeah.
Except I couldn't see nolhin'.
Your arm ms in the my.
Sorry-
I found another Bobo.
Can I have my badge back'?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Let's go kick some ass.
[Devon] Do you need a tattoo
to get in this place?
All right
Take off that goddamn T-shilt
I don't want you 00min' inside.
You hang around in that bar,
you got hurt
- I n handle it.
- Yeah.
I thought this was a leather barl
Leave me alonel
Hey, don'tl Put that back duwnl
Come on. Hang around in the parking lot
and you'll got hurt
You n look that my in a few years.
If that's not a 48-year-old midget...
Here's his ID rd.
- You're a cop.
- I'm a cop?
And he's my assishntl
- Lookin' for a guy named Bobo.
- You lookin' for Bobo?
That's him atthe and of the bar.
- The guy with his shirt off?
- Yeah.
Dear God.
- You Mr Bobo?
- Ask your mother.
[Devon] Hey, pall
- You hlkin' to mo?
- I didn't catch your name.
I didn't throw 'rt.
Slave. Good name.
Give me a milk, Slave.
In a dirty glass.
I'm lookin' for a Mr Bobo
because I have some money
I wanna give him.
- Tell me about Bobo.
- I heard he was a famous hairdresser.
Maybe this will rufreshen your memory.
Thank you.
Apparently Mr Bobo
doesn't want this money.
Mr Bobol
You can't have the money
fill you tall me your name is Bobo.
- I'm Bobo.
- Good, cos I wanna talk to ya.
[DWWI] if I W!!! you, I'd play dead.
Thanks.
Well, I'm fine.
Don't hit her. She's a woman.
Didn't hit her.
All light, kill himl
- You're minel
- I don't think sol
Yesl
Got aver halal
[Wlling]
[gifgfl wails]
[Devon on PA] This is the SWAT teem
commander. We have you surrounded.
Thepolicearshers!
Was that a good place to h'rt a guy'?
[McKnnna] A guy that big,
that's the only place you hit himl
Whafd you ll for help for?
I ms doin' final
it didn't look like 'rt to me.
- Ho's headin' for the bridge.
- I n see that
- You're losing him.
- Shut upl
♪ Oh, say, canyon-see...
- What are you doing?
- When I'm rod, I sing. Do you mind?
♪ Oh, say, can you see
by the dawn': eefly light
♪ Whelaoproudly...
I could have made itl Maybe.
Now you n ll for backup.
- I don't think I can do that
- Why?
Cos I think I'm sick.
- [radio] What's your 10-20?
- We're perpendicular.
[distant a cappella singing]
Hey, um
IPIeaaedonHeaveme
♪ My life would be still
I
J" We}:
Dena!“
You guys seen a little kid around here?
IOoh-ooh
J" Web...
Hey, Nickl
- Where the hell have you been?
- I wanted to surprise you.
Glazed or chocolate?
Pwnle are flying m kill youl
Are you some kind of bonehead or whit?
I'm not, and you don't have to yelll
I can't handle this any moral
I cannot handle 'rt any more.
Pick a city. Cincinnati. Cleveland.
You and your grandmother,
you go there, I'll pay for 'rtl
You ll this being a father?
I'm not your father.
- I'm not your partner eitherl
- Final
I don't want you to be my father
or my parlnerl
I don't want you to be anylhingl
- I'm gonna handle things myselfl
- Ah, Devon.
Dena!“
Come back aver halal
Will you come... Devonl
I'm on official police business.
- Just come with us.
- Quietly.
Back offl I'm only gonna count to one.
- Shut up, man.
- Don't you wish?I
- Let me gol
- Another shrimp bites the dustl
- First we're gonna break your armsl
- Then your ugly little face.
- Fiay dawn, you “the on!“
- Hay, there's a fight over them
- It's Wedgie fimel
- Put me duwnl
Watch and learn, kiddiesl
- Let me downl
- Hey, how does that sand taste, huh?
- I love 'rtl
- Put me down, you jerkl
- 11me to kick your ass.
- I don't think sol
[all cheer]
You're dead, you little pukel
Got off mel
- Got off mo, manl
- Come onl Got himl
Got youl
- You're deadl
- You little pukel
- Let us go...
- Or you're dead, little creepl
if you can't do the time,
don't do the crime.
I'm Dskecfive Butler,
and you two it farms are under arrest
- Devon, come on.
- Be quiet
Hey, Deputy Sanchez,
does this happen to be yours?
- Thanks.
- That is so cool.
Remember, Katy, the law is on your side.
Oh, nol Got up here.
Listen up. I need a diversion.
- We could do that
- [all] Yeahl
- Shane, go close the gate.
- Yes, sir.
The rust of you split.
- Come on, talk to Devon. Oohl
- Gobchal
MON"
- These punks smashed the r.
- [boys] Oh, nol
Morning, boys. Haw do you feel?
- Dena!“
- Over herd
Waldo, aver there.
Gdnhil
Hey, mister. I likn your suit.
Come on, sucker. I'm fight here.
- Are you ready?
- Come onl
[children laugh]
You OK?
All right, everybodyl Sit duwnl
Where is Devon Bufler?
- I'm Devon Butler.
- I'm Devon Bufler.
- I'm Devon Buflerl
- I'm Devon Butler.
- M“ I'm Devon Buflefl
- FilUl
Let's not tall anybody
about this, all right?
- Not again.
- I'm not done with you yetl
Come on.
Have you got any idea where he might be?
Any place at all?
- He doesn't have many friends.
- I know.
- Ho's just a baby.
- I'm gonna find him.
I promise. I promise, Rachel.
Offioer, are you from Social Services?
Yes. I was giving Mrs Bufler
the Grandmother of the Year award.
By the way, we're keeping an eye on you.
[Fountain on cassette]
I' Memories to my surprise...
- This sucks.
- Well, you'd halter learn to lave ll.
[music shops]
[welkie-talkie] Devon, did you make it')
Are you in the our?
This is not a good place to ll mo.
- What the hell was that?
- Will you 111m off your radio?
You have the fight to remain silent
Anything you say...
- Shut up, fir“
- What's happening, Dev? Talk to me!
Imagine this little punkl
- You owe me 9.95.
- Get over here, you little...
[Chu] Sit duwnl Don't muvel
Wuhan“
What are you looking at?
Whats the matter with you?
Nice to see you again.
You remember me?
We had that nice little talk.
Pity you didn't listen.
- You're in trouble now.
- Uh-oh.
- You like music, Devon?
- That '50s crap they were dissin'?
I hoard you sing. A oat ohokin'
on a hairball sounds halter than you.
How would you know'?
Doyou haveanyideaastowholwas?
Lock him in the other dlfioe.
OK, boss.
Hey, put me down, piggyl
Do not move. You understand? Let's go.
Helpl
All right, now calm down.
What would Nick do?
911.
Could you get me Nick McKenna?
it's Devon.
Captain, it's Buflerl
Honey, when are you?
- Who's on the phone?
- The kid's on the phone.
The kid? The doorl
- Tell him 10o grand is not money.
- What does that mean?
Did I tall you not to touch anything?
Take him, Rudy.
- Get Nick.
- Nlbk, we heard fiam Devan.
He said tall Nick
that 10o grand isn't money.
- What the hell does that mean?
- We don't know.
10-4.
Put me down, you oink-oinkl
Rudy, what are you doin'? Over here.
The drug lab is over here.
I knew 'rt was drugs.
I'm sure that I said
to keep him in the dlfioe.
- He was a bad boy, boss.
- He called me piggy.
I like that Slick him in the comer
fill we're finished.
Slick him in the comerl
This is a good consistency.
Let's leave it at this.
[WIN SGIOOOh]
[McKenna] Hello, Bobo.
We got the drugs outta all of the horns.
Good.
Uh-oh.
[moon voice] Well, Devon,
it looks likn it's time to say goodbye.
- Take him tome boat
-You got it, boss.
- You're gonna
- Shut up.
See ya, Devon. Give my regards to Elvis.
I b6! you're peein'
in your pams by now, kid.
No wonder dinosaurs are extinct.
Big heads, small brains.
I'm fired of you calling me namesl
- Get outta the way, Chul
- Take 'rt easy, Rudy.
Hey, kid, you wanna say a prayer?
Go ahead.
Hey, Bobo, you're late.
- Everybodys vnifin' on ya, Bo.
- Hey, kidl
What comes sitar L'?
IAB,C,D,E,F,GI
Bowl
- Where's the gun?
- Under halal I n't reach it.
Dam!“
Come onl
Seal off the vnrahousel
There's no my out now, McKnnnal
[Screams]
Whoal
- You see anybody?
- No. Nobody.
Come on, Rudy.
Shy put.
Hey, Nick.
- Are you mad at mo?
- Nah.
- You OK, boss?
- Got the rl Come on, got upl
Got up. Got the boat
McKenna, you're minel
- Jumpl
- Now'?
NUWl
- Nick, you've been shotl
- Yeah.
There's Bobol
What are you looking at, weenie?
Ho's got my r doorl
Come onl
Go faster, Nickl Fastarl
Move out of the way I
- Get outta the way I
- What is your name?
I'm wolkin' here. All right
ha!“
We're out of gasl Gol Gol Gol
- it's awfully quiet Maybe we got 'em.
- Maybe not
- Shit diggin' under the bags.
- Yeah. Where are ya? Where are ya?
Nice and easy, will ya? Nice and easyl
They're not halal
Can you hot-wire this 'thing?
- We got keys.
- Bother idea.
Nick, you can't use your arm.
I gotta do 'rt.
They're in the boatl
There's McKnnna on the boatl Follow himl
Lgrs go, Rudy.
Follow mel Follow mo, you siupidml
Follow mel
Why'? All I wanna do is singl
Come onl Follow the bossl
There he is, up iherel See him?
[hlgboafs hootar blarus]
Nickl Tugboatl
- Oh, Nickl
- Keep 'rt steadyl
[hwtar blares]
Tum it aboutl Tum it aboutl
[Wlling]
Got back here, Chul
[hwtar blares]
Tum itl Tuml
Ah-hal
[YQIIs]
[Devon] Oh, nol It's a dead and, Nickl
All right, you gotta drive this boat
fight up those pipes.
- I can't do that, Nick.
- Yes, you canl
That's it. We got 'em now.
- I'm rod.
- I'm rad too, Devon.
But You're my parlnerl
LUIS hit itl
[both] I' Oh, say, can you see
By the dawn': eefly light
♪ What so pluudlywe hailed...
- They're gonna jump the pipel
- Nah. They're nuts.
♪ “Lest gleaming
And the rockets' rad glam
♪ Bombs bunting in air I'!
Yesl We did it, Nickl
Owl
- Follow himl
- Goin'l Goin'l
Yea!“ Oh, yea!“
Come on, balm You an do 'M
Rightl To the rightl To the rightl
[WWI scream]
Get me outta here ncrwl
Get me outta herel
I'm a little indisposed
at the moment, sir.
I can't even get mysetf
outta here, boss.
[Fountain] This is ridiculousl
Heyl Tum it offl
McKenna, I'm gonna kill youl
Uillqhs]
Big joke, huh, McKenna?
I'm gonna stick you 'm have.
Keep hughin'.
Waldo, there's fish here.
Hay, boss, shut up.
[belches]
[q gins]
- Hey, Nick.
- Uh-huh.
I wanna put my police business
on hold for a while...
and be a kid again.
You know something, Devon?
Me, too.
Great
Hey, partner, how you doin'?
Can we go a little faster?
I'm used to speed.
Heyl I was shot three montlns ago.
You want speed, give me some help.
Read!”
[Rachel] This is the life.
L' Why is my baby blue
♪ Canines the colours of a sunny day
Xstuckinhetpointofview
Xwhetoenldobtaksyowtseiaeway?
♪ Oh, I'm not delaying
Hfselhetimefnruying
♪ Just tell me why
you look so sad tonight
Hknowhuazy
♪ Livin' in the world these days bu'!
Hfyouteksmebyhehend
- J"
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
J" I'm positive of this, I tel! you
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
Xflggirlmleeaeletmehelpyouom
♪ HI pick you up so hi9"
♪ You'll start forgetting
you were everdown
♪ Guess who will dry youreyes
tThisisthewey
htumyowwofldaround
XWeellQBilOHBW
tBmifyoujuatholdme
twebotfucenqo
beyondtfsestersbnight
.I"Oh, wrceyouhaveit
I' Love works like magic
♪ Justopal, open up yowheart
IOh-oh-oh
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
J" I'm positive of this, I tel! you
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
I' Love is the glue the! binds us
Whenwegetlostilfindaumyeeh
♪ You'll lose your blues soon
IOh-oh-oh
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
J" I'm positive of this, I tel! you
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
I' Love is the glue the! binds us
Whenwegetlostilfindaumyeeh
♪ You'll lose your blues soon
I' Con, baby, my love is bus, break I'!
QIHNQWBQM!
♪ Oh, once you have it
I' Love works like magic
Juatopenllliwwheen
IOh-oh-oh
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
J" I'm positive of this, I tel! you
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
IOh-oh-oh
J" I'm positive of this, I tel! you
I' There's nothin' my love
can'! fix for you, baby
Ohyouknowifabue
J" Al! I goth: say is baby, baby
f?! love you in every way cos, lady
'Ywwflflqeieweywitfume
YOI-lqothgetaweywitfametoday
ttiosourlovehesqotboshottfumzqh
And, honeyyougothseeittoo
tThetwewersmeenLgirLmeendyou
I' Bu! lately you been ectin'
like I smell like e zoo
I' Philly Zoo lo be exact and Philly's
my origin as a metteroffact
J" Bu'! Jet's getbeck
to the subject at hand
♪ Baby, baby, baby
Oh, you is back in demand
twhenllooketyomqitl
Myheertgoesrightintoewhifl
I' And all I gotta say
ebouttfsesituafion
IOh-oh-oh
I' There's nothin' my love can'! fix I'