[ Man Praying
In Foreign Language ]
[ Praying Continues ]
[ Praying Continues, Fades ]
[ Man ]
We hereby commend
our brother to you, Lord.
And so it remains
that Matthew Cordell...
can now live on
in your eternal presence.
[ Praying Continues ]
We cannot sit in judgment
ofthis man...
any more than we might sit
in judgment ofthose responsible...
for his false imprisonment
and untimely demise.
[ Praying Continues ]
In your mercy and love,
please forgive whatever sins
he may have committed...
through human weakness.
[ Praying Continues ]
[ Praying Continues, Faint, Echoing ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Praying Continues ]
[ Nightstick Hitting Hand ]
[ Gunshots ]
Hey, Mac.
Aren't you supposed to be off
at some political bullshit function?
That's right.
I'm just warming up.
[ Laughs ]
So what's with the no headgear?
I love the sound of gunfire.
[ Chuckles ]
Why aren't you out celebrating?
Don't feel like it.
Go out, for Christ's sake.
It's your birthday.
Have some fun.
Go to a movie.
Anything but standing
around here and shooting
at anonymous bad guys all night.
Maybe they're
not so anonymous to me.
Anybody I know?
Yeah, maybe.
Hank Cooney
from the mayor's office.
What's the problem?
[ Tapping Gun On Table,
Cartridges Clicking ]
He's calling me into deposition
to answer another citizen complaint.
[ Gun Cocks ]
Excessive force?
Seems to be
the popular complaint these days.
Broke the bastard's cheekbone.
What was the charge?
Attempted rape.
Next time wait a little longer.
Then you can kill the bastard.
Hollow-points, huh?
Where accuracy
is never a problem.
Well, you know they are
calling me Maniac Kate.
I wouldn't consider that
a compliment.
Hey, Mac, I'll see you later.
[ Paper Crinkling ]
What?
Happy birthday, kid.
You crazy-
Hey, Mac, I love it.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Cat Yowls ]
[ Sirens Wailing ]
[ Man ]
Down at the end ofthe alley!
Get those bums
out ofthere!
[ Police Radio:
Dispatcher, Indistinct ]
[ Officer ]
We need some more
over here!
[ Police Radio:
Chatter Continues, Indistinct ]
Mac. Down here.
Hey, Lieutenant.
[ Officers Chattering, Indistinct ]
Watch your step.
Sorry I had to call you
out ofthe function.
You did me a favor, Leo.
Yeah, we'll see.
It's some gruesome shit.
At least he died
with a smile on his face.
[ Laughing ]
Very funny, Leo.
[ Officer ]
Lieutenant!
Newshounds are here.
Shit.
Yeah, it's McKinney.
Should be good with him here.
What is it?
What you got?
Homeless guy.
Well, how 'bout an angle,
McKinney?
You want an angle?
Yeah.
How about 1 80 degrees?
Come on, man.
Give me a break. Huh?
It's a routine O.D.
You wanna check it out, go ahead.
But ifyou were smart,
you'd go down to 29th and Park.
We got a jumper.
You're an angel.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Guns Cocking ]
[ Gasps, Groaning ]
See what you get? Huh?
Fucking McKinney.
That son ofa bitch.
He really gave us the shaft,
that prick.
I knew there was nojumper.
I knew it.
Couldn't you tell
he was trying to get rid of us?
What else we got?
Okay, let's see what we got.
[ Scanner: Dispatcher, Indistinct ]
We got a bomb scare.
Long Island City and Kennedy Airport.
- Maybe we could string
the both ofthem together.
- No, they always turn out to be duds.
What else?
Drug-related homicide, SoHo.
Nah, that's no good.
Wait a minute. Is it a kid?
Black male, 1 8 to 25.
Couldn't be
a fucking Irishman or a fucking Greek?
Don't they get high on drugs?
Next! Next!
Got a four-alarm fire
in Brooklyn.
Forget about it.
- Wait, wait. This is big.
- Come on.
The networks won't even consider it
unless there's at least three confirmed dead.
It's a warehouse.
A fucking mattress warehouse.
Forget it!
Fuckin' somethin' better happen.
- [ Mumbling ]
- What are you doing?
Praying to the news gods
to grant usjust one good misfortune.
So, Mac,
we gonna chalk this up
as a routine O.D., huh?
Well, let me ask you something.
What do you think?
Did they stuffthe chicken
down this guy's throat
before he O.D.'d or after?
It's Palo Mayombe.
You're not thinking
about food now, are you?
It's a spin-offofSanteria.
They use the heads for their rituals.
How do you know
about this occult shit?
Ever since Cordell,
it's been an interest of mine.
They whacked this poor bastard
for his head?
No, they probably
found him dead.
Theyjust got there
before we did.
So how does the bird play in this?
It's a courtesy to the stiff.
It allows the soul to take flight.
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
[ Sirens Wailing, Faint ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Sirens Wailing, Louder ]
[ Kate ]
This is Sullivan, 1 084. Arrived at scene.
Cannot determine extent ofactivity inside.
Are now entering to investigate.
Over and out.
- [ Screams ]
- God!
Come on! Next!
Son ofa bitch!
- We got us a shooter.
- [ Scanner: Chattering, Indistinct ]
Officer Kate Sullivan?
Oh, that's beautiful.
[ Tires Squealing ]
I'll kill you all.
I'll kill all you fucking bastards.
Come on! Come on!
Who's next? Huh?
How does it feel?
Does it hurt?
Come on! Who's next?
[ Cackling ]
Shoot me now, bitch!
Go ahead! I dare you!
You want to see her brains?
Huh?
Why don't you come back here
and give me a smooch?
[ Cackling ]
Get out of my way!
What the hell is wrong with you,
you stupid jerk?
The head...
carries the spirit.
The heart...
carries the soul.
A head with no heart...
is a spirit with no soul.
Did you see what went down here?
I see whatyou see.
I saw a symbol...
in the dirt.
Two triangles...
facing each other across a line.
You see...
the symbol ofanti-justice.
You can't touch me!
Stick with him.
I got him. I got him.
[ Shooter Hooting, Shouting, Faint ]
You can't touch me!
No fuckin' Valium?
Give me a fuckin' break!
[ Mumbling ]
[ Shooter ]
All right, where's the good stuff?
This is nothin'!
Just fuckin' glorified aspirin shit!
Oh, yeah.
[ Muttering ]
Oh, fuck! Dilaudid!
This filthy creep's
gonna make us rich.
Oh, man.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, look.
Hey, we're on TV.
Wave- Hi, Mom.
[ Woman Screaming ]
Drop the gun!
You look like
you could use some downers.
This'll be
on the world news tomorrow.
Go ahead.
Help yourself.
- Let the kid go.
- No.
I don't want to.
I'll give you a count of 1 0.
Oh, is that what
you're gonna do? Huh?
One.
Two.
Three.
Lady, you can't hurt me,
'cause I'm immortal.
- Look at this sick bastard.
- Four.
[ Hammer Cocks ]
But she's not.
[ Screams ]
[ Woman ]
You shot him.
Calm down.
Backup's on its way.
- [ Woman ]
You shot Frank.
- You buzzed him in.
I'm buying a new foreign car.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Siren Stops ]
She's got a pulse.
It's fading.
How bad is she?
You know her religion?
Catholic.
Get a priest.
I'm losing her.
Pulse is 32.
[ Chattering, Indistinct ]
Oh, Sean.
Mrs. Sullivan.
What's happening to my baby?
She was involved in a shooting.
The police brought me here.
They said something about a chest wound,
but nobody tells me how bad it is.
Well, they don't knowyet, Mrs. Sullivan.
You've always been her protector.
Please make sure
she gets the best ofcare.
Mrs. Sullivan,
I have some important papers
foryou to sign.
Ifthe Lord calls her,
make sure they let her go to him.
- I promise.
- [ Woman ]
Please, Mrs. Sullivan.
[ Exhales ]
[ Woman On P.A. ]
Mr.Jenner to Admitting.
[ Chattering, Indistinct ]
Lieutenant McKinney?
Yeah.
Would you like to wait upstairs?
I think you'd be more
comfortable up there.
Yeah. Thanks.
You are the first cop
to walk these streets in a long time.
These are dark days, my friend.
I need your very special
kind ofdarkness.
You want to kill me...
because I'm the one
responsible foryour resurrection.
But understand,
I could not have brought you back
unless you allowed it.
Even I cannot overcome
the will ofa spirit at rest.
And your spirit will never be at rest,
will it, Officer Cordell?
[ Radio: Voices, Indistinct ]
[ Radio: Voices Continue, Indistinct ]
[ Radio: Man ]
I ain't afraid ofthe gangsters out there.
It's the cops. I'm afraid ofthe cops.
They're psycho, man,
every last one ofthem.
Check this out.
Uh, that Kate Sullivan?
She kills the hostage
and the perpetrator lives.
I mean, what is this? Iraq?
[ TV: Man ]
City officials are concerned over recent-
Kate's lucky.
Myerson's on duty tonight.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
What makes her lucky?
He's top ofthe line in trauma.
Well, I hope so.
I oughta know.
I put him through med school.
[ TV: Man Continues ]
Please call the authorities.
Let's go live now-
I hope it wasn't
a correspondence course.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm standing outside LaRue's Pharmacy
at 1 25th Street and Lexington...
during an event which can only be
described as a black rainbow ofterror.
What began as a routine burglary call
ended in a gruesome tragedy earlier tonight...
as a 1 9-year-old pharmacist's assistant
was brutally shot dead by police.
News cameras were on the scene
with this shocking footage.
Get out of my way!
[ Reporter]
In what could be
the most chilling example of its kind,
Officer Kate Sullivan is seen here
shooting both hostage and suspect...
with no apparent regard
for innocent life.
That's bullshit.
[ Woman ]
Ifyou call 91 1 and Domino's,
we all know who's gonna get there first. Right?
I feel safer with a pizza.
You know what I mean?
[ Reporter ]
While the suspect, FrankJessup,
is recovering...
in the lockup ward
at Queen of Mercy Hospital,
at the center ofthe controversy,
and fighting for her own life,
is Officer Kate Sullivan,
a six-year veteran,
well known among her colleagues
as fearless, opinionated and brash.
In recent months she'd earned
the nickname Maniac Kate,
a nod to another cop
with a knack for overkill.
A police spokesman stated that
an Internal Affairs investigation has been initiated.
But for this young pharmacist,
the last prescription she filled...
was the bitter pill offate.
Son ofa bitches.
Where can I find Katie?
Seventh floor O.R.
Thanks.
[ TV: Woman ]
New "Buy American" plan
isjust the deal-
I'm at Customs in Mexico City.
This guy says to me,
"You got anything to declare?"
I said, "Yeah. I can't focus my eyes,
and it burns when I urinate."
Oh, man.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for
a Dr. Myerson.
Who are you?
Lieutenant McKinney.
Well, I'm Myerson.
Can you tell me the status
of Officer Sullivan?
She's alive.
Can you be
a little more specific?
Reticular formation's intact.
- She's got primary cerebral cortex-
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey. Hey.
I'm a cop, not a doctor.
She can respirate and eliminate.
You're telling me
she's brain-dead?
Yeah.
What's the prognosis?
Stick her in a rock garden.
I don't like your sense of humor.
Help these people.
?? [ Man Singing In Distance,
Indistinct ]
[ Gavel Rapping ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Screaming ]
Hey, that cop's up there, right?
You know,
the one that shot the hostage.
Kate, uh-
What's her name?
Ask me,
she had it coming.
About time you guys figured out
this ain't the Wild West, pal.
Bunch ofcowboys.
Yeah, that's it.Just a bunch offunny cowboys.
Hi-ho, Silver.
[ Gasps, Screaming ]
So, how bad is the stench
down at the halls ofjustice these days, William?
Oh, pretty bad.
Um, look, um, don't tell anybody
where you got this from.
I never do.
The city is gonna roll over
on this case, big time.
Scumbag, he's already got himselfa lawyer.
Now he's suing us.
So let him sue. He's a hopped-upjunkie.
Nobody's gonna take him seriously.
Somebody already has.
He's got himselfa case, Mac.
Your friend Kate,
she had herselfan automatic drop gun.
Hollow-points in a service revolver?
Come on.
For Christ's sake, Willie,
you've been on the streets.
Every hitter out there's got that and more.
What are we supposed to
fight them back with? Pop guns?
Don't matter.
Those are illegal weapons.
Cops can't use them.
You know that, I know that,
she knows that, scumbag knows that.
That's why he's suing the city for 1 0 mil
for each slug we pull out of his sorry ass.
Which, at this point,
I think it's up to three.
What kind ofdeal are they gonna cut him?
Six months, suspended sentence,
in exchange for him
dropping his suit against the city.
What's that do to Katie?
Just pray your friend doesn't wake up.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Alarm Beeping ]
Step back.
[ Beep ]
Thanks.
[ Door Buzzer Buzzes ]
Couple ofsquirts of morphine
in my I.V. drip there, huh, beautiful?
We wouldn't want to turn you into an addict,
now would we, Mr.Jessup?
Oh, my mind would be
a terrible thing to waste.
Excuse me. Dr. Fowler?
Hi.
- Can I help you with something?
- Yeah. I'd, uh- I'd like a minute.
I'm sorry.
I don't have the time right now.
[ Chuckles ] No,
I mean with the patient.
Oh.
Uh, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
I just need to ask him
a couple ofquestions.
- Can I have one minute?
- One minute?
Please.
[ Dr. Fowler ]
Okay.
Thankyou.
I told the story to your friends.
Well, you know what?
I don't want the story. I want the truth.
[ Chuckles ]
Then you can wait
for my memoirs.
- [ Laughing ]
- Shh.
I'd rather not wait that long.
Now...
I didn't know that girl Terry,
but I do know the officer,
and I know that when she puts a slug
between somebody's eyes,
it belongs there.
Now, I want you
to mull this over. Okay?
[ Gasping ]
I want you to think about it.
You don't have to answer me now.
But are you sure
there isn't anything else?
I want you to tell me. All right?
Maybe there's something else
you forgot to tell the other detectives.
- Think about that.
- [ Gasping, Panting ]
What's going on in here?
I didn't see nothin'.
It's terrible when you have
an itch you can't scratch.
[ Wheezing ]
[ Door Buzzer Buzzes ]
Lieutenant McKinney.
What went on in there?
We had a little chat.
I have a feeling if it had been a big chat,
he'd be dead right now.
Are you assigned to this case?
No, not officially.
Then I'm gonna have to askyou
to stay away from my patient.
Look, Dr. Fowler.
Take him in here.
Come on.
Maybe I stepped
out of line back there.
I don't know anymore.
But Katie is-
Well, she's like a kid sister to me.
Please try and understand that.
[ Monitor Beeping ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Monitor Beeping Rapidly ]
[ Beeping Accelerates ]
Nurse.
Nurse!
Nurse, there's some kind of reaction
from Kate Sullivan. Dr. Fowler.
[ Monitor Beeping:
Normal Rate ]
I don't see any change.
Her eyes were open.
- You sure?
- I know what I saw.
That monitor was going crazy.
Well, there's nothing there now.
She grabbed my hand, like this.
- I'll go tell Dr. Myerson.
- You can't do that.
If he knows it comes from me,
he won't lift a finger.
Then he won't know.
Can you page Dr. Myerson,
please?
Dr. Fowler.
So how come
you're so willing to believe me?
Because you don't strike me
as the kind of man with much imagination,
Lieutenant McKinney.
Thanks.
Close him up.
Count the sponges.
Hello, gorgeous.
I just came
from Kate Sullivan's room.
Mmm.
Chest wound.
Mm-hmm.
What are you doing
talking to one of my patients?
I thought I might find you there.
I love it when you pursue me.
You miss me, don't you?
Not as much
as you'd like to think.
Whoa.
[ Chuckles ]
Anyway, that's not what
I came here to talk about.
My loss.
There was alpha activity
on Kate's monitor.
Mm-hmm. And?
She actually opened her eyes.
Her monitor was going crazy.
"Going crazy." Would that be
your exact professional diagnosis?
Or could you be
any more specific?
No. I didn't stop
to analyze the readings.
Okay. How about "crazy"
as a simple neural seizure?
It's very common
in cases like this.
Take a nine-volt battery,
hook it up to a dead frog,
you get about the same result.
Peter, I want you to authorize
another brain scan.
[ Imitates Buzzer ]
I can't do it.
Why?
Because it is unwarranted.
It's a waste of money,
it's a waste oftime,
and as far as I'm concerned,
it's a waste ofa bed.
She's Gumby.
Peter!
Please, Susan, don't push me on this.
You know how I react
when you push me.
How about dinner?
[ Scoffs ]
You're unbelievable.
Ifyou change your mind, beep me.
I'm on vibrate.
[ Woman Moaning ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Moaning Continues ]
[ Electrical Zap ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Zap ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Zapping ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Groaning, Screaming ]
[ Loud Clank ]
- [ Gasps ]
- Dr. Fowler, what are you doing down here?
Did you see a police officer?
Nobody down here but us.
But you betterwatch your step.
It's dangerous down here with all these pipes.
Then I better get back.
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Police Radio, Indistinct ]
[ Helicopter Overhead ]
[ Siren Wailing In Distance ]
He's around the back.
I'll go get him.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
Hey, Mac, no smiley face
this time, huh?
Smiling on the inside, Leo.
What do we got here?
Looks like the doctor here
kissed something with a hell ofa jolt.
Fried his brains right down to the nubs.
Oh, Christ.
Friend ofyours?
Not in this life.
[ Leo ]
Round up the staff.
I want to talk to them.
Anybody- You know,
maintenance people who were working.
I never used to smoke around Peter.
I didn't want him to knowjust how much
he was worming his way under my skin.
So tell me, Detective McKinney,
how do you deal with pain?
Chocolate-chocolate mint ice cream.
About a pint with a ton ofwhipped cream.
Works every time.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thanks.
Do you have any idea who might have a motive
to use that thing on Myerson?
Practically everyone
who works at this hospital.
That's a hell ofa lineup.
Maybe I ought to
consider myselfa suspect.
Well, then you'd have to
get at the back ofthe line.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Is there a cop assigned to Kate's room?
No. Why do you ask?
Because I saw one
leaving there earlier.
I don't know-
I didn't get a good look at him,
but he was huge
and kind ofscary looking.
I don't know why, but I followed him
down to the tunnels under the hospital.
Where do they lead?
Well, they used to connect with
all the older buildings in the area,
but now I think
they mostly go nowhere.
[ Hammer Cocks ]
[ Wings Flapping ]
[ Man ]
I've been expecting you, McKinney.
I have a way ofattracting
certain restless souls...
who find no comfort
in conventional wisdom.
I am a houngan malfaiteur.
Raiser ofthe dead.
Does that happen to include
desecration ofcorpses and
stuffing them with dead chickens?
You are not here to...
nail a humble religious practitioner...
on a misdemeanor
corpse desecration charge.
I want to know about resurrection.
I am not a priest.
To some people you are.
Some people leave this world...
with an unanswered cry forjustice.
Sometimes the echo...
don't die away completely.
And when it does?
One might be compelled to return.
But the resurrection,
it's far more painful
and terrifying than death.
You cannot imagine the torment,
the sense of loss...
to walk alone among the living...
and not be alive.
That must be
the most cruel injustice ofall.
Then you'd know something
about that veryjustice,
wouldn't you, McKinney?
Where is he?
You'll find him.
What makes you so sure?
Because you both walk the same path.
Are we tied up
after work tonight or what?
God, I love the smell of
fresh plasma before breakfast.
Dr. Powell.
Ah, Mr. Cooney.
I'm hoping we might be able
to speak privately.
I've got my hands full this morning.
My top trauma guy didn't show up.
Whoa, sweetheart.
Tie offthat femoral there.
He could lose the leg.
He already has as far as I'm concerned.
What's on your mind?
Kate Sullivan.
I am familiarwith the case.
Mm-hmm.
Vegetative state, chronic.
Right.
And there is some legal precedent
to remove her from life support at this stage,
if I'm not mistaken.
Yes, you're correct,
in certain situations.
[ Monitor Beeping ]
How we doing?
B.P. dropping,
going into V-tach.
50 c.c.'s digitox.
Be prepared with those paddles.
Why do you ask?
Well, let'sjust say we can
save Kate a great deal of pain...
and save this city a great deal of pain
ifwe put an end to this episode.
We need permission
from next of kin.
[ Woman ]
Fifty over 25.
Pop another 50.
What's this?
That's a letter ofconsent.
Signed by the mother.
That's right.
We've been talking to her.
She's a very agreeable woman.
In fact, she's a terrific lady.
[ Woman ]
B.P. 1 1 0 over 69.
I think he's coming around.
[ Man Screaming ]
[ Muffled Screaming ]
Welcome back, son.
Nice to get down to the trenches
every once in a while. Keeps you fit.
I would hope
that we could accomplish this
in a timely fashion, Doctor.
I can handle this this afternoon.
Really?
Oh, that'd be terrific, sir.
I really thankyou very much.
And I know Kate would too
ifshe could.
I'm sure she would.
[ Man Shuddering ]
Ah, sewing up now, are we?
Yes, sir.
About time.
By the way, now that you're here.
Uh, I have family
coming in from out oftown.
These are real Knicks fans.
Now, I don't know whetheryou
can do anything about it, but, uh-
Well, I certainly can.
Center court, floor,
right next to Pat Riley.
How's that sound?
Perfect.
Hey, it's my pleasure.
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Glass Shatters ]
Who's in there?
I don't appreciate my staff using this hospital
like a goddamn Greek restaurant.
Come on out,
whoever's responsible for this.
Aah! No!
Aah!
No!
[ Muffled Screaming ]
[ Muffled Screaming Continues ]
[ Muffled Grunting ]
[ Whirring, Clicking ]
[ Whirring, Clicking Continue ]
[ Muffled Screaming, Faint ]
What the-
Oh, my God!
[ Whirring, Clicking ]
Where the heck are you driving?
Look at this neighborhood you're
driving through. What, are you crazy?
I wouldn't feel safe ifwe had
a police escort right now.
I swear to God.
- I hearyou, man.
- You need the fucking National Guard
to come through this place.
Hurry up. Come on.
Let's get out of here.
What do you suppose would happen
ifwe showed that cop shooting in full?
Like how?
I mean, like, don't cut out
the stuffthat we usually cut out.
You gotta look at it this way.
Cop brutality sells, okay?
Just ask Rodney.
Yeah, I know that.
But you don't understand-
You gotta find that one little twist
that you can sell it with.
Otherwise,
we don't make a nickel, man.
Drive-by shooting
five blocks from here.
Forget about it.
It's a child!
What?
That's it!
[ Dog Barking In Distance ]
[ Siren Wailing In Distance ]
Let's get this.
All right, I want you to go
get the body, shoot the body.
All right.
I'm gonna get some B-roll.
Okay.
I'll catch you back there.
All right?
Right.
Okay.
Hey, did you see who got shot?
Yeah.
You did?
Do you mind if I askyou
a few questions?
Great.
Uh, was it a kid?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Boy or a girl?
Girl.
Sh-Shot bad?
How bad?
Shotgun?
Did you know her?
She's my sister.
She-
Wow. Hey.
Well, life's a bitch, huh, man?
Where the hell is everybody?
Yo, Trib.
Trib!
I should just get a shot ofthis.
This could be it.
[ Screams, Sobbing ]
[ Groans ]
[ Blade Slices ]
[ Body Thuds On Ground ]
Where'd you get the tape?
Elvis.
The buzzer.
You buzzed him in. Why?
[ Gunshot ]
- [ Tape Rewinding ]
- We got something here.
What?
It was an insidejob.
Poor Katie.
You buzzed him in. Why?
This will clear her,
won't it?
I hope so.
[ Gunshot ]
Let's go.
[ Gunshots ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Clears Throat ]
[ Hammer Cocks ]
Huh?
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
I think my client will be
satisfied with the basic terms.
But along with
the suspended sentence,
I think we need to offer Mr.Jessup
the opportunity to benefit...
from standard commercial
exploitation of his story.
Literary rights, film rights,
TV appearances, that sort ofthing.
So what more do you need from us?
When you reduce his sentence,
just delete any reference to homicide
or manslaughter from the record.
Those distinctions would make it
difficult for him to benefit...
from collecting fees or royalties.
And you can understand how important
that would be to Mr.Jessup.
Well, I'll- I'll see what I can do.
Now have you, uh, presented
our offer to Mr.Jessup?
Oh, no.
As his attorney, I feel I should be satisfied
with the general parameters first.
No need in raising
false expectations.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
Oh, ofcourse not.
Then I can assume
we're in accordance.
Mr.Jessup will be very happy.
Oh, yeah. Hello, Harry.
- Listen, I don't see any reason
why I can't have access to those records.
- [ Door Buzzer Buzzes ]
And, uh, Ms. Lindsey.
Yes?
May I call you Gina?
Ofcourse, Hank.
Once this is resolved,
maybe you and I can have
a cocktail ofour own
and, uh, do a little celebrating.
Hmm.
I think we can agree on that.
Okay.
[ Gunshots ]
Save it!
Come on!
[ Alarm Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
Oh, great. I shot my lawyer.
Fuck 'em.
You can get another one.
They're free.
[ Alarm Continues Ringing ]
[ Monitor Beeping ]
[ Monitor: Sustained Tone ]
What's this?
Looks like a runaway stiff.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Click ]
[ Screams ]
- [ Groans ]
- [ Gunshot ]
[ Toilet Flushes ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Electricity Crackles ]
I thought I told you
not to mess with my patients.
Then don't leave their cages open.
I didn't.
I know.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Ifyou've got insurance,
maybe I should send you a bill.
How about, uh, dinner instead?
I don't know.
How long are you planning
to stick around?
In this place,
not long if I can help it.
Then I guess dinner
is out ofthe question.
[ Electricity Crackles ]
Jesus.
Mac, I'm sorry.
Oh, bad timing, Leo.
Katie's missing, Mac.
She's gone.
How long could she
stay off life support?
She can't.
Get me backup, Leo.
[ Lightbulb Shatters ]
[ Electricity Crackles ]
I'll take it from here.
I'm coming with you.
Stay here.
[ Lighter Clicking ]
Mac.
I think you need me.
Come on.
[ Water Dripping ]
Welcome back, McKinney.
Your path has reached its end.
What we do here is good-
to unite two tortured souls...
in holy matrimony.
That's bullshit.
There's nothing good
or holy about this.
[ Murmuring Prayer ]
Ashes to ashes-
Take that shit
away from her.
Dust to dust.
I can't imagine
the kind of pain you feel, Matt.
I'm not gonna pretend to.
But don't condemn her
to the same fate.
She deserves better.
You cleared her.
She's at peace.
Let her go, Matt.
Let her go.
Finish it!
[ Praying In Foreign Language ]
[ Praying Continues ]
I cannot recover this soul.
She will not allow it.
[ Shotgun Cocks ]
[ Dr. Fowler ]
Mac!
Mac! Mac!
Here! Come on!
Hurry up!
Come on!
[ Screams ]
[ Dr. Fowler ]
Mac!
Mac! Hurry! Hurry!
He's coming!
Mac, hurry up! Hurry!
He's coming! Mac!
Goddamn it!
Mac!
[ Screaming ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Gun Cocks ]
Oh, McKinney, it's you.
Get me an ambulance.
[ Chattering, Shouting ]
[ Siren Wailing In Distance ]
Let's go.
Queen of Mercy?
No, the other one.
Check.
[ Sirens Wailing ]
[ Fire Engine Horn Blaring ]
[ Explosion ]
[ Glass Shattering ]
Rest in peace, Katie.
Are you okay?
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Screams ]
Get down!
- [ Screams ]
- What's going on back there?
Get the hell out of here!
Jesus!
[ Grunts ]
I don't see him.
[ Screaming ]
Mac!
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Gasps, Screaming ]
[ Screams ]
Son ofa bitch!
[ Gasps ]
[ Horn Honking ]
Where is he?
[ Dr. Fowler ]
I hate this!
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Clanking ]
Take the wheel.
[ Grunts ]
Mac!
-Just keep away from him.
- I can't.
No!
- [ Dr. Fowler ]
What are you doing?
-Just step on the gas.
[ Screams ]
Oh!
Go on! Keep going!
[ Dr. Fowler ]
I'm trying. I'm trying.
- You son ofa bitch!
- I don't believe this!
[ Dr. Fowler Screaming ]
Mac! Mac!
Go! Go!
Get the fuck out of here!
- Go! Go! Get going!
- I can't!
Go!
I can't! I can't!
[ Screams ]
- Move over.
- Oh, my God!
Do something, Mac!
He's clamped on.
[ Dr. Fowler ]
It's gonna blow!
[ Screams ]
Get us out of here!
[ Tires Squealing ]
Mac!
Hang on.
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Mac ]
Hang on.
[ Grunting ]
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]