1
00:03:35,298 --> 00:03:38,711
(Man reciting)

2
00:04:26,975 --> 00:04:32,345
(Speaking French)

3
00:04:32,481 --> 00:04:34,722
- Want a hot dog?
- No, thanks.

4
00:04:34,858 --> 00:04:37,645
Just ketchup, please.

5
00:04:40,113 --> 00:04:41,193
Thanks.

6
00:04:41,323 --> 00:04:42,938
Listen, I've got an errand to run.

7
00:04:44,075 --> 00:04:45,531
(Chuckles)

8
00:04:46,077 --> 00:04:48,693
Kind of skimpy on the k etchup.

9
00:04:48,830 --> 00:04:51,742
Duncan, I've got to do this alone.

10
00:04:51,875 --> 00:04:53,365
What?
Wait, wait, wait.

11
00:04:54,127 --> 00:04:56,869
You called me in Paris,
and you said we have to meet.

12
00:04:57,339 --> 00:05:00,251
Now suddenly you've
got an errand to run?

13
00:05:00,383 --> 00:05:02,590
What's going on?

14
00:05:02,719 --> 00:05:04,584
I don't know.

15
00:05:04,721 --> 00:05:06,211
It's...

16
00:05:07,516 --> 00:05:09,507
...nothing.

17
00:05:09,643 --> 00:05:11,258
You OK?

18
00:05:12,687 --> 00:05:15,850
Yeah. I'm OK.

19
00:05:15,982 --> 00:05:17,472
Really.

20
00:05:17,609 --> 00:05:20,897
I know you better
than that, Connor.

21
00:05:21,029 --> 00:05:22,985
Haven't seen you lik e this.

22
00:05:24,491 --> 00:05:27,358
People change, Duncan.

23
00:05:27,494 --> 00:05:29,655
You'II learn that.

24
00:05:29,788 --> 00:05:31,324
Fine.

25
00:05:31,456 --> 00:05:33,617
You can tell me
all about it tonight.

26
00:05:33,750 --> 00:05:36,366
8:00 at the bar.

27
00:05:36,503 --> 00:05:38,915
And you're buying.

28
00:05:39,047 --> 00:05:40,628
Right.

29
00:05:40,757 --> 00:05:43,089
8:00, and I'm buying.

30
00:05:43,218 --> 00:05:44,549
Mm-hmm.

31
00:05:47,180 --> 00:05:49,262
You sure you
gonna be all right, Connor?

32
00:05:49,391 --> 00:05:51,882
Of course. Duncan...

33
00:05:56,356 --> 00:05:57,687
...watch your back.

34
00:06:21,298 --> 00:06:23,459
(Bell ringing)

35
00:06:25,218 --> 00:06:26,754
Connor?

36
00:06:29,264 --> 00:06:30,595
Connor?

37
00:06:59,711 --> 00:07:01,622
(Voices on TV)

38
00:07:12,766 --> 00:07:14,176
(Connor on TV) 'OK.'

39
00:07:16,561 --> 00:07:17,721
(Girl on TV) 'What is it, Connor? '

40
00:07:17,854 --> 00:07:18,843
(Connor) 'Open it.'

41
00:07:18,980 --> 00:07:20,265
(Girl) 'Oh, a ballerina.

42
00:07:21,942 --> 00:07:23,523
'Wow. She's beautiful.

43
00:07:23,652 --> 00:07:25,392
'Thank you.'

44
00:07:25,528 --> 00:07:27,268
'Mmm, my angel.'

45
00:07:27,405 --> 00:07:29,396
(Music playing)

46
00:07:33,036 --> 00:07:34,867
(Connor) 'Oh, my God,
I'm so proud of you.'

47
00:07:34,996 --> 00:07:35,985
'I love you, Connor.'

48
00:07:36,122 --> 00:07:37,282
'I love you, my Rachel.

49
00:07:37,415 --> 00:07:38,825
'Oh, God,
I'm proud of you.'

50
00:07:38,959 --> 00:07:40,039
(Rachel) 'Thank you.'

51
00:07:40,168 --> 00:07:42,159
(Telephone rings)

52
00:07:50,553 --> 00:07:54,922
(Telephone continues ringing)

53
00:08:03,483 --> 00:08:08,523
(Telephone continues ringing)

54
00:08:08,655 --> 00:08:09,861
(Beeping)

55
00:08:09,990 --> 00:08:10,775
Hello?

56
00:08:10,907 --> 00:08:12,022
(Beeping)

57
00:08:18,748 --> 00:08:20,579
Rachel!

58
00:08:26,423 --> 00:08:28,334
(Connor) 'Rachel.

59
00:08:28,466 --> 00:08:30,502
'My beloved Rachel.

60
00:08:34,681 --> 00:08:37,468
'How long has it been
since she died?

61
00:08:37,600 --> 00:08:41,513
'A year?
A century? More?

62
00:08:41,646 --> 00:08:43,511
'My mind k eeps slipping,

63
00:08:43,648 --> 00:08:46,890
'but some things I know.

64
00:08:47,027 --> 00:08:49,894
'I am Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod,

65
00:08:50,030 --> 00:08:54,945
'and once,
a very long time ago,

66
00:08:55,076 --> 00:08:57,442
'I was a Highlander.

67
00:09:09,632 --> 00:09:11,213
'Born of this land,

68
00:09:11,342 --> 00:09:14,425
'and lik e this land, immortal.'

69
00:09:23,855 --> 00:09:24,719
(Dogs barking)

70
00:09:24,856 --> 00:09:26,266
(Man) Witch!

71
00:09:26,399 --> 00:09:29,232
You brought
this plague on us.

72
00:09:29,360 --> 00:09:31,692
You damned us all,
Connor MacLeod.

73
00:09:31,821 --> 00:09:33,186
You sold your soul!

74
00:09:34,365 --> 00:09:36,526
(Man) You're a witch!
You child of Satan!

75
00:09:36,659 --> 00:09:40,322
They drove you from your home,
cut you off from your own people.

76
00:09:40,455 --> 00:09:42,241
What else do they want?

77
00:09:42,373 --> 00:09:43,579
Someone to blame.

78
00:09:43,708 --> 00:09:45,539
Your mother will burn!

79
00:09:45,668 --> 00:09:47,033
Connor.

80
00:09:47,170 --> 00:09:50,503
Your mother will burn!
Rot in hell!

81
00:09:50,632 --> 00:09:52,372
Get in the house.

82
00:09:53,259 --> 00:09:54,920
(Connor) Get off my land!

83
00:09:55,053 --> 00:09:56,634
Leave us in peace!

84
00:09:56,763 --> 00:09:58,253
Get off my land!

85
00:10:03,853 --> 00:10:05,218
(Heather) Connor, please.

86
00:10:05,355 --> 00:10:07,391
You're not going back to Glenfinnan.

87
00:10:07,524 --> 00:10:09,435
I have no choice.

88
00:10:09,567 --> 00:10:11,228
Connor, please.

89
00:10:11,361 --> 00:10:13,647
They can't hurt me,
and they know it,

90
00:10:13,780 --> 00:10:16,442
but they can still
hurt the ones I love.

91
00:10:17,367 --> 00:10:18,857
I'm afraid.

92
00:10:20,286 --> 00:10:22,277
I love you, Heather.

93
00:10:22,413 --> 00:10:24,278
More than anything in this world.

94
00:10:24,415 --> 00:10:26,497
Do you believe me?

95
00:10:26,626 --> 00:10:27,661
Yes.

96
00:10:27,794 --> 00:10:29,455
Then don't be afraid.

97
00:10:29,587 --> 00:10:31,873
Nothing can keep me from you.

98
00:10:35,885 --> 00:10:37,796
(Horse whinnies)

99
00:10:37,929 --> 00:10:39,009
Nothing.

100
00:10:40,974 --> 00:10:42,134
(Horse neighs)

101
00:11:31,024 --> 00:11:32,935
Connor.

102
00:11:34,527 --> 00:11:36,483
I thought you might be
the water horse...

103
00:11:36,613 --> 00:11:40,322
come to tak e me on his back
and drown me in the loch.

104
00:11:49,375 --> 00:11:50,785
No one comes
to take care of you?

105
00:11:50,919 --> 00:11:52,329
(Mother) Not in years.

106
00:11:52,462 --> 00:11:54,327
They think I bedevil
their children

107
00:11:54,464 --> 00:11:57,797
because my own was banished.

108
00:11:59,844 --> 00:12:01,880
I'm sorry.

109
00:12:02,013 --> 00:12:03,469
I'm so sorry.

110
00:12:05,850 --> 00:12:10,560
Tiny mites
and soured dispositions.

111
00:12:12,690 --> 00:12:16,023
I've no need of them, Connor,
any of them.

112
00:12:21,241 --> 00:12:24,233
Then it's settled.
You're coming with me.

113
00:12:29,332 --> 00:12:30,913
(Wind blows)

114
00:12:31,042 --> 00:12:32,031
Aah!

115
00:12:32,168 --> 00:12:33,624
Connor!

116
00:12:33,753 --> 00:12:35,289
Connor, what is it?

117
00:12:35,421 --> 00:12:36,831
I'm not sure.

118
00:12:36,965 --> 00:12:38,250
It happened once before.

119
00:12:38,383 --> 00:12:39,463
Aah!

120
00:12:39,592 --> 00:12:41,833
Aah! Connor!

121
00:12:46,349 --> 00:12:50,843
(Priest) In the name of the Holy See
and the rule of law...

122
00:12:50,979 --> 00:12:51,968
Jacob?

123
00:12:52,105 --> 00:12:56,439
...you are hereby charged,
Connor MacLeod, with heresy

124
00:12:56,567 --> 00:12:59,434
and the practise of black magic.

125
00:12:59,570 --> 00:13:02,152
We were friends, remember, Jacob?

126
00:13:02,282 --> 00:13:03,863
I stood at your ordination.

127
00:13:03,992 --> 00:13:05,323
I vouched for you.

128
00:13:05,451 --> 00:13:07,157
You shouldn't have
come back, Connor.

129
00:13:07,287 --> 00:13:08,618
(Priest) Tak e him.

130
00:13:09,998 --> 00:13:11,078
Aah!

131
00:13:12,792 --> 00:13:14,657
(Priest speaking indistinctly)

132
00:13:19,007 --> 00:13:25,469
(Priest) The ties of blood
cannot be severed by word or deed.

133
00:13:31,728 --> 00:13:32,683
(Gasps)

134
00:13:32,812 --> 00:13:34,177
(Connor) Mother.

135
00:13:34,314 --> 00:13:38,432
(Jacob) Due to the infinite compassion

136
00:13:39,527 --> 00:13:43,236
you are entitled
to one final opportunity

137
00:13:43,364 --> 00:13:45,195
to renounce all that is unholy,

138
00:13:45,325 --> 00:13:49,739
and declare Connor MacLeod
not of your loins.

139
00:13:51,372 --> 00:13:53,158
How say you,
Caiolin MacLeod?

140
00:13:55,543 --> 00:13:57,909
If your God

141
00:13:58,046 --> 00:14:02,130
should persecute me
into the next world,

142
00:14:02,258 --> 00:14:05,000
then I shall simply have
to find myself another.

143
00:14:05,136 --> 00:14:06,216
(Gasps)

144
00:14:06,346 --> 00:14:07,677
(Crowd muttering)

145
00:14:07,805 --> 00:14:09,045
(Woman) Burn her!

146
00:14:09,182 --> 00:14:12,049
No! No! No!

147
00:14:13,227 --> 00:14:15,764
(Jacob) He is your son.

148
00:14:15,897 --> 00:14:17,853
I am silent for you.

149
00:14:21,069 --> 00:14:23,355
(Connor grunting)

150
00:14:25,573 --> 00:14:26,938
(Man) Black powder.

151
00:14:27,075 --> 00:14:28,485
It will ease your suffering.

152
00:14:32,747 --> 00:14:34,362
(Connor) Mother!

153
00:14:38,169 --> 00:14:40,251
No!

154
00:14:42,757 --> 00:14:44,372
No!

155
00:14:49,389 --> 00:14:50,674
(Grunting)

156
00:14:57,563 --> 00:14:59,474
(Caiolin weeping)

157
00:15:01,692 --> 00:15:03,398
(Screaming)

158
00:15:11,828 --> 00:15:13,614
(Grunts)

159
00:15:13,746 --> 00:15:16,032
(Man) You're next, you demon!

160
00:15:25,383 --> 00:15:26,668
Aah!

161
00:15:28,553 --> 00:15:29,759
(Growling)

162
00:15:36,310 --> 00:15:37,720
(Horse neighs)

163
00:15:48,322 --> 00:15:49,607
Aah!

164
00:15:52,034 --> 00:15:54,241
My water horse.

165
00:16:12,555 --> 00:16:14,341
Uh!

166
00:16:17,810 --> 00:16:19,846
(Man) The Devil's come back to life!

167
00:16:28,863 --> 00:16:30,979
(Priest) Let her be, Connor.

168
00:16:32,116 --> 00:16:33,606
Aah!

169
00:16:37,538 --> 00:16:38,744
Father?

170
00:16:39,624 --> 00:16:40,784
(Jacob) Father?

171
00:16:42,418 --> 00:16:44,158
Please.

172
00:16:44,295 --> 00:16:45,956
Do not leave me.

173
00:16:47,173 --> 00:16:48,788
Father.

174
00:17:00,978 --> 00:17:02,058
Aah!

175
00:17:02,188 --> 00:17:03,894
(Jacob grunts)

176
00:17:09,278 --> 00:17:10,688
Connor...

177
00:17:50,486 --> 00:17:55,526
(Connor) 'My endless days
are filled with memories of the past

178
00:17:55,658 --> 00:17:59,242
'and the death of my mother
by Jacob Kell.'

179
00:18:19,181 --> 00:18:21,593
(Engine revs)

180
00:18:35,156 --> 00:18:38,523
(Man) Boy, you people are
extremely difficult to find.

181
00:18:38,659 --> 00:18:40,149
We like it that way.

182
00:18:48,961 --> 00:18:51,748
Go ahead, man.
Tak e your pick.

183
00:18:53,591 --> 00:18:54,797
Uh!

184
00:19:03,142 --> 00:19:04,222
Uh!

185
00:19:06,520 --> 00:19:08,010
Aah!

186
00:19:17,490 --> 00:19:19,230
(Engine revs)

187
00:19:41,138 --> 00:19:42,594
(Gun cocks)

188
00:19:45,893 --> 00:19:47,224
(Fires gun)

189
00:20:10,876 --> 00:20:12,992
Aah.

190
00:20:18,509 --> 00:20:20,921
Tak e their heads.

191
00:20:21,053 --> 00:20:22,543
They might be Immortals.

192
00:20:22,680 --> 00:20:24,170
Yes, they might be.

193
00:20:39,488 --> 00:20:41,194
Aah!

194
00:20:51,584 --> 00:20:53,040
Don't be long.

195
00:20:53,169 --> 00:20:54,659
(Coughs)

196
00:21:09,977 --> 00:21:12,059
The Sanctuary.

197
00:21:13,022 --> 00:21:14,887
So it's true.

198
00:21:23,324 --> 00:21:27,067
What sacrifices
they have made of you,

199
00:21:27,203 --> 00:21:30,912
warehoused lik e
rotting pieces of meat.

200
00:21:36,378 --> 00:21:40,747
Tell me,
is this the better way?

201
00:21:40,883 --> 00:21:45,377
(Kell) I'm sure you've had
time to reflect upon it.

202
00:21:46,597 --> 00:21:48,963
What you need to understand

203
00:21:49,099 --> 00:21:51,841
is that I don't care
about the game.

204
00:21:52,686 --> 00:21:54,426
I don't care about the rules.

205
00:21:54,563 --> 00:21:58,647
I don't even care about
these pathetic souls

206
00:21:58,776 --> 00:22:03,236
you k eep lock ed away
as a barrier to the prize.

207
00:22:03,823 --> 00:22:07,782
Which one is Connor MacLeod?

208
00:22:18,504 --> 00:22:20,870
(Whistling)

209
00:22:31,976 --> 00:22:33,466
(Grunts)

210
00:22:38,399 --> 00:22:40,014
(Strained breathing)

211
00:23:11,724 --> 00:23:13,214
Well, what do we do now?

212
00:23:13,976 --> 00:23:15,682
What we always do.

213
00:23:15,811 --> 00:23:17,802
We're Watchers, not cops.

214
00:23:17,938 --> 00:23:20,099
(Man) We'll find another volunteer.

215
00:23:23,611 --> 00:23:25,522
(Bell tolling)

216
00:23:30,451 --> 00:23:33,193
(Telephone rings)

217
00:23:39,501 --> 00:23:42,163
(Telephone continues ringing)

218
00:23:54,183 --> 00:23:56,799
(Ring continues)

219
00:24:04,735 --> 00:24:08,648
(Woman) 'Whatever you fear
about Connor MacLeod,

220
00:24:08,781 --> 00:24:10,396
'fear the worst.'

221
00:24:12,451 --> 00:24:13,611
Who is this?

222
00:24:13,744 --> 00:24:15,109
A friend.

223
00:24:16,664 --> 00:24:18,495
'Don't bother looking for me, Duncan.'

224
00:24:20,501 --> 00:24:22,913
(Dial tone)

225
00:24:29,218 --> 00:24:31,049
He's on the move.

226
00:24:40,604 --> 00:24:43,846
Duncan MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.

227
00:24:44,650 --> 00:24:46,311
Hello, Methos.

228
00:24:46,443 --> 00:24:49,901
What brings you
to my humble abode?

229
00:24:50,030 --> 00:24:51,270
Need your help.

230
00:24:52,282 --> 00:24:53,488
Why me?

231
00:24:53,617 --> 00:24:55,448
(Duncan) You've been around
for 5,000 years.

232
00:24:56,829 --> 00:25:00,162
I want the benefit of your experience.

233
00:25:00,290 --> 00:25:03,407
And I thought it was a social call.

234
00:25:04,920 --> 00:25:06,626
You ever had nightmares?

235
00:25:07,172 --> 00:25:08,412
What kind of nightmares?

236
00:25:09,133 --> 00:25:11,044
Bloody images

237
00:25:11,176 --> 00:25:13,292
powerful enough to even
break your meditation.

238
00:25:14,513 --> 00:25:17,505
We live violent lives, MacLeod.

239
00:25:17,641 --> 00:25:19,222
Some of that's
bound to stay with us.

240
00:25:20,686 --> 00:25:23,849
These ones came 10 years to the day
that Connor MacLeod disappeared.

241
00:25:25,441 --> 00:25:27,181
Connor had good reason to go.

242
00:25:27,317 --> 00:25:29,558
He told me how much
Rachel meant to him.

243
00:25:29,695 --> 00:25:33,108
There was more to it than that.
I was with him that day.

244
00:25:33,240 --> 00:25:35,071
The day Rachel was killed?

245
00:25:35,200 --> 00:25:37,191
Something wasn't right.

246
00:25:37,327 --> 00:25:38,817
'Connor, you OK? '

247
00:25:38,954 --> 00:25:42,822
'Yeah. I'm OK.
Really.'

248
00:25:42,958 --> 00:25:45,370
'I know you better
than that, Connor.

249
00:25:45,502 --> 00:25:48,744
'I've never seen you lik e this.'

250
00:25:48,881 --> 00:25:51,839
'People change, Duncan.

251
00:25:51,967 --> 00:25:53,548
'You'll learn that.'

252
00:25:55,679 --> 00:25:57,761
I need to know
if he's still alive, Methos.

253
00:25:59,349 --> 00:26:01,465
You know a little
about Buddhist monks.

254
00:26:01,602 --> 00:26:03,638
Some of them come
to cherish life so much

255
00:26:03,771 --> 00:26:07,764
that to step on an insect
or harm a blade of grass

256
00:26:07,900 --> 00:26:09,765
becomes a violation
of their creed,

257
00:26:09,902 --> 00:26:14,145
so they place themselves under
an extreme form of protective custody...

258
00:26:15,074 --> 00:26:16,405
A Sanctuary of sorts.

259
00:26:17,743 --> 00:26:20,485
Well, for an lmmortal
who comes to abhor the bloodshed,

260
00:26:20,621 --> 00:26:22,361
there's a similar solution...

261
00:26:22,498 --> 00:26:24,955
A way to be removed
from the game forever.

262
00:26:25,084 --> 00:26:27,621
The price is unimaginably high,

263
00:26:27,753 --> 00:26:33,669
but you are, for all practical purposes,
protected from the violence within you.

264
00:26:33,801 --> 00:26:35,883
And it's called The Sanctuary.

265
00:26:36,428 --> 00:26:37,838
Connor would never do that.

266
00:26:37,971 --> 00:26:41,213
Are you sure? It's been around
since before you were born.

267
00:26:41,975 --> 00:26:43,511
At least until last night.

268
00:26:43,644 --> 00:26:45,350
What happened last night?

269
00:26:46,563 --> 00:26:48,224
It was annihilated.

270
00:27:04,289 --> 00:27:06,996
(Connor) 'Hey, Duncan,
what's the matter? '

271
00:27:07,126 --> 00:27:09,333
(Duncan) 'The British
destroyed the clans, Connor.

272
00:27:10,254 --> 00:27:11,414
'Scotland's finished.'

273
00:27:11,547 --> 00:27:14,254
(Connor) 'Scotland will always
be Scotland,'

274
00:27:14,383 --> 00:27:16,248
and someday you'll go back.

275
00:27:16,385 --> 00:27:17,875
You can bet on it.

276
00:27:18,011 --> 00:27:20,127
- How much?
- Aw, come on.

277
00:27:20,264 --> 00:27:22,926
Does everything have
to be a wager with you?

278
00:27:23,058 --> 00:27:24,923
Well, you're the one
that keeps telling me

279
00:27:25,060 --> 00:27:27,221
our lives are nothing
but a boundless game.

280
00:27:27,354 --> 00:27:29,185
(Chuckles)

281
00:27:29,731 --> 00:27:31,562
(Duncan) Good morning, gentlemen.

282
00:27:31,692 --> 00:27:33,228
What seems to be
the problem here?

283
00:27:33,360 --> 00:27:36,022
(Man) They refuses to pay her toll, sir.

284
00:27:36,155 --> 00:27:37,986
(Duncan) Really? How dare they?

285
00:27:38,115 --> 00:27:39,355
These men are rogues.

286
00:27:39,491 --> 00:27:41,732
(Faith) These men are
liars and scoundrels, sir.

287
00:27:41,869 --> 00:27:44,702
They've done nothing but prey upon us
three years running,

288
00:27:44,830 --> 00:27:46,741
right at this very spot.

289
00:27:46,874 --> 00:27:49,160
And by whose authority
do you act?

290
00:27:49,293 --> 00:27:51,454
By Deed of the King.

291
00:27:53,130 --> 00:27:55,371
(Connor)
There is a little 'X' down here.

292
00:27:56,091 --> 00:27:58,503
Does the King always
sign his name with an 'X'?

293
00:27:58,635 --> 00:28:00,000
Excuse me. Sorry.

294
00:28:00,137 --> 00:28:01,627
I think these gentlemen
should be paid.

295
00:28:01,763 --> 00:28:03,219
That deed is a fak e.

296
00:28:03,348 --> 00:28:04,588
That's a matter of opinion.

297
00:28:04,725 --> 00:28:06,761
You, sir,
are no better than they.

298
00:28:07,227 --> 00:28:09,263
That is also a matter of opinion.

299
00:28:09,396 --> 00:28:10,932
Here you go.

300
00:28:12,566 --> 00:28:13,555
Ladies.

301
00:28:14,401 --> 00:28:15,436
It's gold!

302
00:28:15,569 --> 00:28:17,651
Why not... It's gold.

303
00:28:17,779 --> 00:28:18,894
(First man laughs)

304
00:28:19,031 --> 00:28:20,396
Hey, wait a minute.
They took my money!

305
00:28:20,532 --> 00:28:21,863
Oh, it's here.

306
00:28:21,992 --> 00:28:23,402
They took my money!

307
00:28:23,535 --> 00:28:24,741
(Man) Let's go get 'em!

308
00:28:25,329 --> 00:28:26,318
Shall we?

309
00:28:26,455 --> 00:28:27,661
(Yelling)

310
00:28:27,789 --> 00:28:28,995
Aye.

311
00:28:30,667 --> 00:28:32,328
(Man) Ah!

312
00:28:35,214 --> 00:28:36,545
- Ooh.
- Ooh.

313
00:28:45,641 --> 00:28:46,721
Heh heh.

314
00:28:46,850 --> 00:28:49,011
(Connor) Not bad.
Uh-oh.

315
00:28:50,771 --> 00:28:51,851
Mmm.

316
00:28:53,357 --> 00:28:55,564
All right boys, time to go.
Let's go!

317
00:28:56,276 --> 00:28:57,937
Come on!

318
00:28:59,029 --> 00:29:00,940
(Duncan) Oh. Cuckoo.

319
00:29:01,073 --> 00:29:03,610
Oh, looks heavy, huh?

320
00:29:03,742 --> 00:29:05,152
(Duncan) Looks lik e
you lost your edge, lad.

321
00:29:05,285 --> 00:29:06,365
(Connor) Really heavy.

322
00:29:06,495 --> 00:29:08,827
- Or could he be lass?
- Could be.

323
00:29:08,956 --> 00:29:10,617
Could be.

324
00:29:10,749 --> 00:29:12,330
(Groaning)

325
00:29:13,377 --> 00:29:14,492
Hyah!

326
00:29:16,004 --> 00:29:17,414
(Driver) Come on!

327
00:29:17,547 --> 00:29:19,708
Hyah! Hyah!

328
00:29:21,635 --> 00:29:23,125
Hyah!

329
00:31:13,747 --> 00:31:14,862
(Bombs exploding)

330
00:31:14,998 --> 00:31:16,909
(Duncan) 'Corporal Duncan MacLeod,
sir.

331
00:31:17,709 --> 00:31:20,371
'I've come to pick up
the wounded.'

332
00:31:48,990 --> 00:31:50,946
(Indistinct chatter)

333
00:31:57,582 --> 00:31:58,992
You've improved greatly.

334
00:31:59,126 --> 00:32:01,208
Ah, you really think so?

335
00:32:05,590 --> 00:32:07,421
No.

336
00:32:07,551 --> 00:32:09,007
I'm just being gracious.

337
00:32:09,136 --> 00:32:10,717
Hmm.

338
00:32:11,847 --> 00:32:13,553
Now, remember.

339
00:32:13,682 --> 00:32:17,925
You are only immortal as long
as you can k eep your head

340
00:32:18,061 --> 00:32:19,301
on your shoulders.

341
00:32:22,899 --> 00:32:24,309
Argh!

342
00:32:24,443 --> 00:32:29,688
Duncan, what you give up
to your adversary in defeat...

343
00:32:29,823 --> 00:32:30,903
...is everything.

344
00:32:31,575 --> 00:32:36,035
I know. And at that point,
I'm very, very dead. Come on!

345
00:32:36,163 --> 00:32:39,655
Not just dead, Duncan.
Empty!

346
00:32:42,419 --> 00:32:44,626
Aye, Connor, I know.
It's called the Quick ening.

347
00:32:44,754 --> 00:32:46,870
Our strength and knowledge,
our life essence,

348
00:32:47,007 --> 00:32:50,124
flows into the victor, feeds him,
and mak es him stronger, yes?

349
00:32:50,719 --> 00:32:53,381
It's what drives the other Immortals
to kill us,

350
00:32:53,513 --> 00:32:56,676
and what forces us to be smarter,
better than the rest.

351
00:32:56,808 --> 00:32:58,890
(Groans) I understand.

352
00:32:59,936 --> 00:33:01,221
Oh.

353
00:33:04,232 --> 00:33:05,813
You do?

354
00:33:06,443 --> 00:33:07,853
Oh.

355
00:33:07,986 --> 00:33:09,476
(Connor) Good.

356
00:33:10,489 --> 00:33:12,320
(Groans) I slipped.

357
00:33:12,449 --> 00:33:14,735
Listen, soon you
and I will have to part.

358
00:33:15,869 --> 00:33:19,032
There is one more thing
I want to give to you.

359
00:33:20,540 --> 00:33:21,575
(Grunts)

360
00:33:21,708 --> 00:33:22,868
<i>Va via. Va via!</i>

361
00:33:23,001 --> 00:33:25,333
(Laughing) Oh, aye!

362
00:33:25,462 --> 00:33:28,545
Oh, aye.
This is much more to my liking.

363
00:33:28,673 --> 00:33:30,038
Good.

364
00:33:30,175 --> 00:33:31,665
Bah!

365
00:33:33,595 --> 00:33:34,835
Attack me.

366
00:33:36,515 --> 00:33:37,971
But you've got your back to me.

367
00:33:39,267 --> 00:33:42,009
It's not always
about strength, Duncan.

368
00:33:42,145 --> 00:33:43,510
Attack me!

369
00:33:49,778 --> 00:33:51,234
Aah!

370
00:33:51,363 --> 00:33:53,979
It's about manipulation of the mind...

371
00:33:57,911 --> 00:33:59,367
...as well as the body.

372
00:33:59,496 --> 00:34:02,203
Aye, but now I'm in control.

373
00:34:02,999 --> 00:34:04,535
Are you?

374
00:34:08,380 --> 00:34:09,870
(Grunts)

375
00:34:11,800 --> 00:34:14,963
Remember well, my friend.

376
00:34:15,095 --> 00:34:18,462
Properly executed,
this move is unstoppable.

377
00:34:20,058 --> 00:34:23,141
Properly executed,
we'll now have this talk again.

378
00:34:36,700 --> 00:34:38,907
(Wind blows)

379
00:34:46,710 --> 00:34:48,371
Who are you?

380
00:34:48,503 --> 00:34:51,165
A friend or a lover.

381
00:34:51,756 --> 00:34:53,246
Or a wife.

382
00:34:53,383 --> 00:34:55,419
- Kate?
- Atta boy.

383
00:34:56,219 --> 00:34:58,380
Except I'm Faith now.

384
00:34:59,472 --> 00:35:01,929
Part of the mak eover.

385
00:35:02,058 --> 00:35:03,298
What are you doing here?

386
00:35:04,436 --> 00:35:06,176
Remember our wedding day,
Duncan?

387
00:35:07,188 --> 00:35:09,179
I do.

388
00:35:09,316 --> 00:35:11,898
(Sighs) The way we danced.

389
00:35:12,027 --> 00:35:13,358
(Scottish music playing)

390
00:35:13,486 --> 00:35:15,226
I felt lik e we were flying.

391
00:35:23,997 --> 00:35:27,660
Of course, we did come down,
didn't we?

392
00:35:31,004 --> 00:35:32,540
Crashing.

393
00:35:35,008 --> 00:35:36,498
(Motorcycle engines revving)

394
00:35:36,635 --> 00:35:37,841
Oh, shit.

395
00:35:47,854 --> 00:35:52,644
(Man) It's time to show
our lmmortal brother a thing or two.

396
00:36:02,702 --> 00:36:04,488
Somebody order a club sandwich?

397
00:36:04,621 --> 00:36:06,987
He's funny.
Nice outfit, too.

398
00:36:07,123 --> 00:36:09,830
Faith, I told you
I look like a fuckin' orange!

399
00:36:09,959 --> 00:36:12,416
I'm not dressing you black, Bob.
Trust me.

400
00:36:12,545 --> 00:36:14,536
- Who are they?
- Friends.

401
00:36:16,299 --> 00:36:18,085
What, it's a team sport now?

402
00:36:18,218 --> 00:36:19,503
What, you didn't know?

403
00:36:19,636 --> 00:36:21,251
It's a whole new ball game.

404
00:36:23,390 --> 00:36:24,721
Aah!

405
00:36:43,618 --> 00:36:44,858
Hey!

406
00:36:45,787 --> 00:36:47,368
Nice bat.

407
00:36:59,384 --> 00:37:00,464
Argh!

408
00:37:00,593 --> 00:37:01,833
Told you I was gonna cut you.

409
00:37:12,147 --> 00:37:14,138
(Growling)

410
00:37:20,572 --> 00:37:22,483
Let my man Jin Ke
deal with him.

411
00:37:25,118 --> 00:37:27,279
Jin Ke...

412
00:37:27,412 --> 00:37:29,152
...who served
with the Emperor Chin.

413
00:37:29,914 --> 00:37:31,495
The same man.

414
00:37:31,624 --> 00:37:33,580
Some people say
you're a man of honour.

415
00:37:33,710 --> 00:37:35,666
What do you know about honour?

416
00:37:37,547 --> 00:37:39,083
Oh, great.

417
00:37:40,675 --> 00:37:41,710
Yah!

418
00:38:25,929 --> 00:38:28,466
Honour's not in a weapon.

419
00:38:28,598 --> 00:38:29,929
It's in the man.

420
00:38:58,086 --> 00:38:59,667
(Kell) Enough!

421
00:39:03,258 --> 00:39:05,465
Boys, boys.

422
00:39:06,636 --> 00:39:08,217
(Kell) I do apologise.

423
00:39:08,805 --> 00:39:10,761
When it comes to discipline,

424
00:39:10,890 --> 00:39:14,803
the first hundred years
are the hardest.

425
00:39:18,189 --> 00:39:19,304
Oh!

426
00:39:20,733 --> 00:39:22,564
Oh!

427
00:39:23,987 --> 00:39:25,818
Guess I'm not much
of a swords guy.

428
00:39:25,947 --> 00:39:30,441
I thought I told you to stop.

429
00:39:31,452 --> 00:39:34,615
Yeah, well, I stopped.

430
00:39:34,747 --> 00:39:35,782
Tell me, Carlos.

431
00:39:35,915 --> 00:39:38,327
How much is your life worth?

432
00:39:38,459 --> 00:39:40,871
Don't start this bullshit, man.

433
00:39:41,004 --> 00:39:43,620
(Kell) 'Cause the only way
to win your freedom

434
00:39:43,756 --> 00:39:45,371
is to kill me.

435
00:39:45,508 --> 00:39:48,045
- You're crazy.
- Am I?

436
00:39:48,177 --> 00:39:49,633
Then go ahead.

437
00:39:49,762 --> 00:39:52,595
Stop the madness.

438
00:39:52,724 --> 00:39:54,260
(Tyres squealing)

439
00:39:54,392 --> 00:39:57,555
Can you live with the fear?

440
00:39:57,687 --> 00:40:00,474
Can you live
with the weakness?

441
00:40:03,109 --> 00:40:05,270
(Saw buzzes)

442
00:40:05,403 --> 00:40:07,064
Weakness, Carlos.

443
00:40:11,826 --> 00:40:13,487
I call this

444
00:40:13,620 --> 00:40:16,202
decap with a twist...

445
00:40:16,331 --> 00:40:17,662
No sugar.

446
00:41:00,375 --> 00:41:02,832
(Gasping)

447
00:41:05,254 --> 00:41:07,245
- Watchers?
- Huh?

448
00:41:10,093 --> 00:41:11,924
Watchers observe Immortals.

449
00:41:12,053 --> 00:41:13,918
They're not supposed to interfere.

450
00:41:14,055 --> 00:41:16,717
Unfortunately, our role
has changed somewhat.

451
00:41:16,849 --> 00:41:18,259
Why?

452
00:41:18,393 --> 00:41:20,099
Because the rules have been broken.

453
00:41:20,228 --> 00:41:24,471
One of your kind has gone renegade.

454
00:41:27,110 --> 00:41:29,522
In doing so, he's gained
himself a sizable advantage.

455
00:41:29,654 --> 00:41:31,986
One that'll be
impossible to overcome.

456
00:41:32,115 --> 00:41:33,571
Nobody's unbeatable.

457
00:41:33,700 --> 00:41:36,692
Oh, yes, Duncan.
He is.

458
00:41:39,998 --> 00:41:41,488
Unbeatable.

459
00:41:46,087 --> 00:41:47,497
No.

460
00:41:48,756 --> 00:41:50,712
(Grunting)

461
00:41:56,264 --> 00:41:57,549
Ah.

462
00:41:57,682 --> 00:41:58,762
(Grunts)

463
00:41:58,891 --> 00:42:01,303
Sorry about that.

464
00:42:01,436 --> 00:42:04,018
There must always
be two of your kind.

465
00:42:04,147 --> 00:42:07,480
As long as there are two,
and you're kept from fighting,

466
00:42:07,608 --> 00:42:09,473
then the prize is safe.

467
00:42:09,610 --> 00:42:12,226
The Sanctuary must not fail again.

468
00:42:12,363 --> 00:42:13,694
You're insane.

469
00:42:13,823 --> 00:42:16,189
(Duncan) Get yourself another volunteer.

470
00:42:16,325 --> 00:42:20,318
We had a number of volunteers!

471
00:42:20,455 --> 00:42:23,868
Sadly, that's no longer the case.

472
00:42:24,000 --> 00:42:26,582
You'll be warehoused, hidden away.

473
00:42:26,711 --> 00:42:28,201
Go to hell.

474
00:42:28,671 --> 00:42:30,502
Don't worry.

475
00:42:30,631 --> 00:42:33,623
(Distorted) The drugs
will kick in momentarily.

476
00:42:38,931 --> 00:42:42,844
(Heavy breathing)

477
00:42:46,064 --> 00:42:48,601
(Woman screaming)

478
00:42:52,820 --> 00:42:54,230
(Gasps)

479
00:42:56,365 --> 00:42:58,947
(Horse neighing)

480
00:42:59,077 --> 00:43:00,942
(Swords clanging)

481
00:43:01,829 --> 00:43:04,241
(Gasps)

482
00:43:11,964 --> 00:43:13,795
(Connor) Get up.

483
00:43:14,926 --> 00:43:16,791
Get up!

484
00:43:23,810 --> 00:43:26,597
You have better things to do
than lie there on your ass.

485
00:43:27,814 --> 00:43:29,350
Who are you?

486
00:43:29,482 --> 00:43:33,521
Someone who knows more about you
than you know about yourself.

487
00:43:33,653 --> 00:43:35,518
Are you a demon?

488
00:43:35,655 --> 00:43:40,149
(Laughing) I've been called that
and worse.

489
00:43:41,702 --> 00:43:43,818
I'm Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.

490
00:43:43,955 --> 00:43:45,661
Connor MacLeod?

491
00:43:46,707 --> 00:43:50,996
And lik e you, my friend,
I have a hard time dying.

492
00:43:59,887 --> 00:44:02,469
(Metal tools rattling)

493
00:44:07,270 --> 00:44:08,305
Dawson?

494
00:44:09,689 --> 00:44:11,054
You look lik e shit.

495
00:44:11,190 --> 00:44:12,270
Thanks.

496
00:44:12,942 --> 00:44:13,931
How long have I...

497
00:44:14,068 --> 00:44:15,774
We'II talk about it later.
We gotta get outta here.

498
00:44:15,903 --> 00:44:18,440
Come on, can you walk?

499
00:44:18,573 --> 00:44:19,858
Yeah.

500
00:44:19,991 --> 00:44:21,197
Uh.

501
00:44:37,842 --> 00:44:40,800
(Duncan) Go. Go!
What are you doing here?

502
00:44:40,928 --> 00:44:42,384
(Methos) Keeping tabs on you.

503
00:44:42,972 --> 00:44:44,132
(Duncan) Yeah?

504
00:44:44,265 --> 00:44:48,383
Well, someone should k eep tabs
on that psychotic asshole back there.

505
00:44:48,519 --> 00:44:50,055
Didn't you get it back in London?

506
00:44:50,188 --> 00:44:52,429
(Methos)
These guys don't play by the rules.

507
00:44:52,565 --> 00:44:54,226
You don't know what
you're up against, Mac.

508
00:44:54,358 --> 00:44:55,598
So people k eep telling me.

509
00:44:55,735 --> 00:44:57,066
Stop the car.

510
00:44:57,195 --> 00:44:59,481
I managed to liberate
that from their lost and found.

511
00:45:00,323 --> 00:45:01,403
There's blood on it.

512
00:45:01,532 --> 00:45:03,397
I didn't say it was easy.

513
00:45:04,493 --> 00:45:06,358
- Pull over.
- (Methos) What?

514
00:45:06,495 --> 00:45:07,860
Pull over.

515
00:45:07,997 --> 00:45:10,613
(Dawson) MacLeod, tell me something.

516
00:45:10,750 --> 00:45:11,739
Mac, hear him out!

517
00:45:12,376 --> 00:45:14,332
Mac! Will you tell me something?

518
00:45:14,462 --> 00:45:17,044
Now, how many Quick enings
have you had?

519
00:45:19,467 --> 00:45:20,957
How many heads have you tak en?

520
00:45:21,093 --> 00:45:23,584
I don't k eep score.

521
00:45:23,721 --> 00:45:25,302
Well, we do.

522
00:45:32,813 --> 00:45:35,054
(Computer) 'MacLeod, Connor.'

523
00:45:35,191 --> 00:45:36,522
What's that?

524
00:45:36,651 --> 00:45:38,232
The Watchers' version of a résumé.

525
00:45:38,361 --> 00:45:41,774
'262 confirmed Immortal kills.'

526
00:45:42,657 --> 00:45:45,774
It's a bit lik e handicapping horses,
but it's part of the gig, all right?

527
00:45:45,910 --> 00:45:47,901
'MacLeod, Duncan.

528
00:45:48,037 --> 00:45:51,529
'174 confirmed Immortal kills.

529
00:45:51,666 --> 00:45:54,624
'174 confirmed Immortal kills.'

530
00:45:54,752 --> 00:45:56,413
Sound about right?

531
00:45:56,545 --> 00:45:58,706
So, what's your point?

532
00:45:58,839 --> 00:46:01,421
(Sighs) Here's the gentleman
you met in Connor's loft.

533
00:46:02,510 --> 00:46:08,756
'Kell, Jacob.
661 confirmed lmmortal kills.

534
00:46:08,891 --> 00:46:12,679
'661 confirmed Immortal kills.'

535
00:46:12,812 --> 00:46:15,269
Welcome to your worst nightmare.

536
00:46:15,398 --> 00:46:17,605
Sanctuary wasn't shit, pal.

537
00:46:17,733 --> 00:46:20,315
This guy is way out of your league.

538
00:46:26,075 --> 00:46:28,657
I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body.

539
00:46:28,786 --> 00:46:30,196
Why?

540
00:46:30,329 --> 00:46:32,866
Something doesn't mak e sense.

541
00:46:32,999 --> 00:46:34,910
What are you saying?

542
00:46:35,042 --> 00:46:38,409
I think he's saying
he wants to see the body.

543
00:46:38,546 --> 00:46:40,082
Well, it's gonna be a rough I. D.

544
00:46:40,214 --> 00:46:42,705
They're all missing their heads!

545
00:46:54,228 --> 00:46:57,265
(* Harmonica)

546
00:47:23,299 --> 00:47:25,335
We gave 'em
a Christian burial, MacLeod.

547
00:47:25,468 --> 00:47:28,426
It was decent, you know.
Said all the right words.

548
00:47:28,554 --> 00:47:31,011
Can't begin to tell you
how reassuring that is.

549
00:47:31,140 --> 00:47:33,222
(Dawson) With all these
unexplained corpses,

550
00:47:33,351 --> 00:47:36,468
well, we had to tak e it
off the beaten track.

551
00:47:36,604 --> 00:47:38,435
End of the road, Joe.

552
00:47:40,649 --> 00:47:41,638
Thanks.

553
00:47:43,694 --> 00:47:46,276
You watch your ass, MacLeod.

554
00:47:46,405 --> 00:47:48,862
It's not my ass
I'm worried about.

555
00:47:52,328 --> 00:47:54,910
Did I happen to mention
about all this coming to a bad end?

556
00:47:55,915 --> 00:47:58,907
No, Methos.
I don't believe you did.

557
00:48:04,715 --> 00:48:06,205
You were gonna stay and dig.

558
00:48:06,342 --> 00:48:08,958
Dig? Oh, yeah!

559
00:48:09,095 --> 00:48:10,960
(Car door closes)

560
00:48:27,613 --> 00:48:29,444
(Thunder)

561
00:48:33,994 --> 00:48:37,486
(Duncan) 'I need to know
if he's still alive, Professor.

562
00:48:37,623 --> 00:48:40,660
'I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body.'

563
00:48:41,460 --> 00:48:45,373
(Methos) 'One of your kind
has gone renegade.'

564
00:48:50,344 --> 00:48:52,926
(Connor) 'People change, Duncan.

565
00:48:53,055 --> 00:48:54,886
'You'll learn that.'

566
00:48:58,894 --> 00:49:00,759
(Wind blows)

567
00:49:14,452 --> 00:49:16,158
(Connor speaking native language)

568
00:49:21,750 --> 00:49:22,910
No.

569
00:49:30,759 --> 00:49:32,295
What are you doing here?

570
00:49:33,846 --> 00:49:36,462
You walk ed out
on your life, Connor.

571
00:49:36,599 --> 00:49:37,634
Why?

572
00:49:40,728 --> 00:49:42,389
I had my reasons.

573
00:49:43,022 --> 00:49:44,102
Reasons?

574
00:49:47,109 --> 00:49:49,691
Every life I touch ends...

575
00:49:50,738 --> 00:49:54,105
...brutally and for no reason.

576
00:49:55,326 --> 00:49:58,238
It's a curse that's followed me
for centuries.

577
00:49:58,370 --> 00:49:59,780
(Chuckles)

578
00:49:59,914 --> 00:50:03,657
I can't outrun it,
and I can't outlive it.

579
00:50:05,753 --> 00:50:08,085
Rachel's death made you
the last soul on this planet

580
00:50:08,214 --> 00:50:09,545
that means a damn to me.

581
00:50:10,549 --> 00:50:12,380
I thought there was a way out.

582
00:50:12,510 --> 00:50:13,545
The Sanctuary?

583
00:50:15,221 --> 00:50:16,336
Yes.

584
00:50:19,058 --> 00:50:20,594
The Sanctuary.

585
00:50:21,810 --> 00:50:23,050
So, how did you escape?

586
00:50:24,855 --> 00:50:26,345
I didn't escape.

587
00:50:28,400 --> 00:50:29,515
I was let go.

588
00:50:33,197 --> 00:50:35,358
I couldn't see the slaughter...

589
00:50:36,200 --> 00:50:37,440
...only heard it...

590
00:50:38,744 --> 00:50:39,824
...and felt it.

591
00:50:42,206 --> 00:50:43,867
(Wind blows)

592
00:51:07,314 --> 00:51:09,270
(People yell)

593
00:51:12,528 --> 00:51:13,938
Jacob Kell.

594
00:51:25,374 --> 00:51:26,955
So, here we are.

595
00:51:27,501 --> 00:51:29,207
Both Immortal.

596
00:51:30,004 --> 00:51:33,747
Missed the signs,
didn't we?

597
00:51:33,882 --> 00:51:37,420
But we were both
so new at the game.

598
00:51:37,553 --> 00:51:39,544
(Thunder)

599
00:51:40,431 --> 00:51:41,841
(Duncan) Connor.

600
00:51:43,183 --> 00:51:46,391
What a glorious sight.

601
00:51:48,230 --> 00:51:50,562
Just look, Connor.

602
00:51:52,234 --> 00:51:55,726
Look back at the endless
travesties of your life,

603
00:51:55,863 --> 00:52:00,027
and you'll see me, always there
waiting in the shadows.

604
00:52:00,743 --> 00:52:03,610
When friends and lovers
are wiped from your sight...

605
00:52:04,663 --> 00:52:05,743
...I'm there.

606
00:52:06,498 --> 00:52:10,662
When those you cherish
die abruptly and for no reason

607
00:52:10,794 --> 00:52:12,785
I'm there for you.

608
00:52:13,922 --> 00:52:17,961
And when your cellmates
in their so-called Sanctuary

609
00:52:18,093 --> 00:52:21,210
are left twitching
lik e headless chick ens...

610
00:52:22,640 --> 00:52:23,675
Guess who?

611
00:52:28,604 --> 00:52:29,844
(Duncan) Connor.

612
00:52:29,980 --> 00:52:32,266
(Connor) Stay out of it, Duncan.

613
00:52:37,112 --> 00:52:40,400
Would you kill
an unarmed man again, Connor?

614
00:52:41,533 --> 00:52:42,613
Oh!

615
00:52:43,369 --> 00:52:45,485
You didn't know, Duncan?

616
00:52:47,373 --> 00:52:49,409
Because you didn't tell him.

617
00:52:49,541 --> 00:52:54,035
Would that finally put the agony
in your soul to rest?

618
00:52:54,963 --> 00:52:56,874
Then go ahead.

619
00:52:57,007 --> 00:53:00,750
Send me home.

620
00:53:00,886 --> 00:53:02,342
What's stopping you?

621
00:53:02,971 --> 00:53:04,461
Honour?

622
00:53:04,932 --> 00:53:06,672
Guilt?

623
00:53:06,809 --> 00:53:10,472
The nagging sense that maybe you,
more than I, deserve to die?

624
00:53:11,772 --> 00:53:13,637
Or somewhere along the way

625
00:53:13,774 --> 00:53:16,686
did you just lose your nerve?

626
00:53:17,528 --> 00:53:18,768
It's holy ground, Connor.

627
00:53:18,904 --> 00:53:20,769
Hmm.

628
00:53:20,906 --> 00:53:22,442
Yes.

629
00:53:22,574 --> 00:53:25,316
Tak e your shot.

630
00:53:26,370 --> 00:53:27,951
What better chance than now?

631
00:53:28,997 --> 00:53:30,157
Do it.

632
00:53:30,958 --> 00:53:34,371
Do it for your sweet mother.

633
00:53:35,212 --> 00:53:36,452
'Aah! '

634
00:53:38,006 --> 00:53:40,372
Or the sweet little war orphan

635
00:53:40,509 --> 00:53:43,467
Rachel Ellenstein...

636
00:53:47,474 --> 00:53:48,839
...who, if I'm not mistak en,

637
00:53:48,976 --> 00:53:51,558
you raised
as your own daughter.

638
00:53:51,687 --> 00:53:53,769
Tell me, do they even begin

639
00:53:53,897 --> 00:53:56,229
to equal for the murder
of a man of God

640
00:53:56,358 --> 00:53:58,474
who raised me as his own son?

641
00:53:58,610 --> 00:54:00,851
'Aah! '

642
00:54:02,614 --> 00:54:03,979
Slow...

643
00:54:04,116 --> 00:54:05,856
...close...

644
00:54:06,744 --> 00:54:08,905
Feels good, doesn't it?

645
00:54:09,663 --> 00:54:11,494
But look at you.

646
00:54:12,249 --> 00:54:15,241
Even now, you're afraid,

647
00:54:15,377 --> 00:54:17,117
afraid you'II lose.

648
00:54:17,254 --> 00:54:19,119
That's your true fear, isn't it?

649
00:54:19,256 --> 00:54:21,793
The thought of giving up
your essence to me,

650
00:54:21,925 --> 00:54:25,634
making me
even stronger by it.

651
00:54:27,514 --> 00:54:29,345
What's wrong?

652
00:54:29,475 --> 00:54:32,967
Don't you want
to be inside me?

653
00:54:59,171 --> 00:55:02,208
I want you to think back
to this moment, Connor!

654
00:55:08,597 --> 00:55:10,633
In the endless nights ahead!

655
00:55:10,766 --> 00:55:12,256
(Connor) Aah!

656
00:55:25,364 --> 00:55:27,275
And know...

657
00:55:27,783 --> 00:55:30,775
...that every time
you close your eyes

658
00:55:30,911 --> 00:55:35,371
from now to eternity,
I'll be there!

659
00:55:37,000 --> 00:55:40,584
Ripping apart the ones
you care about most!

660
00:55:40,712 --> 00:55:42,077
Aah!

661
00:55:50,764 --> 00:55:54,507
It's never over,
Connor MacLeod.

662
00:55:54,643 --> 00:55:57,385
Living is what matters.

663
00:55:57,521 --> 00:56:01,605
And you will live with this.
Count on it.

664
00:56:02,317 --> 00:56:05,980
One far-off day, you and I
will be the only two remaining.

665
00:56:06,113 --> 00:56:07,944
You will look back on this

666
00:56:08,073 --> 00:56:11,736
and know you had
one chance to stop me.

667
00:56:11,869 --> 00:56:13,029
You failed.

668
00:56:13,620 --> 00:56:15,030
But until that day,

669
00:56:15,163 --> 00:56:17,950
I will tak e my vengeance
on those you love.

670
00:56:19,501 --> 00:56:23,460
Your living has been my prize.

671
00:56:24,339 --> 00:56:25,829
For old times' sak e.

672
00:56:27,676 --> 00:56:29,587
(Jacob) 'He is your son.'

673
00:56:32,180 --> 00:56:34,922
You, on the other hand...

674
00:56:39,229 --> 00:56:42,642
...are on borrowed time.

675
00:56:42,774 --> 00:56:44,014
Call you.

676
00:56:49,573 --> 00:56:51,313
Is what he said true?

677
00:56:55,203 --> 00:56:56,192
Is it?

678
00:56:57,205 --> 00:57:01,539
Believe only what your heart
and conscience tell you.

679
00:57:02,461 --> 00:57:06,329
Connor, with time,
anything can be forgiven.

680
00:57:06,465 --> 00:57:08,296
You taught me that.

681
00:57:13,555 --> 00:57:15,136
Did I?

682
00:57:30,739 --> 00:57:33,651
(Clapping, laughing,
music playing)

683
00:57:44,127 --> 00:57:46,083
Oh, look at Dave. Dave!

684
00:57:46,213 --> 00:57:47,623
(Kate) Behave yourself, Duncan!

685
00:57:47,756 --> 00:57:49,542
(Man) No more talking!

686
00:57:49,675 --> 00:57:53,543
May all your hardships fade away.

687
00:57:53,679 --> 00:57:55,886
(Man) Till night becomes morn,

688
00:57:56,014 --> 00:57:59,131
let love remain
to guide your way.

689
00:57:59,267 --> 00:58:01,098
Till the day we are reborn.

690
00:58:02,604 --> 00:58:04,219
Till the day we are reborn.

691
00:58:04,356 --> 00:58:05,641
Kiss her, won't you?

692
00:58:05,774 --> 00:58:08,186
(Cheering and clapping)

693
00:58:14,574 --> 00:58:15,654
(Duncan) Connor?

694
00:58:19,413 --> 00:58:21,028
(Laughing)
I thought you'd never get here.

695
00:58:21,164 --> 00:58:22,654
Connor!

696
00:58:26,378 --> 00:58:29,415
(Connor) You know
Kate is lik e us, Immortal.

697
00:58:29,548 --> 00:58:31,880
Aye. I sensed something
the day we met,

698
00:58:32,009 --> 00:58:33,419
but I wasn't sure.

699
00:58:33,552 --> 00:58:35,383
Well, now you know.

700
00:58:36,596 --> 00:58:41,966
And you know as well as I do
that her immortality

701
00:58:42,102 --> 00:58:45,515
can only be triggered
by the shock of a violent death.

702
00:58:46,440 --> 00:58:48,396
Yes, I do.

703
00:58:48,525 --> 00:58:51,016
And without such a death,
she will simply grow old and die.

704
00:58:51,153 --> 00:58:52,859
Yes, I know, Connor.

705
00:58:52,988 --> 00:58:55,354
Is that what you came
to tell me on my wedding day?

706
00:58:55,490 --> 00:58:58,027
Come on.
Drink up, man.

707
00:58:58,160 --> 00:59:00,902
(Sets down mug) No.

708
00:59:01,580 --> 00:59:02,820
I was wondering.

709
00:59:05,500 --> 00:59:07,365
Does she know?

710
00:59:09,379 --> 00:59:10,459
Why?

711
00:59:17,012 --> 00:59:19,845
Many years
after I was married...

712
00:59:21,433 --> 00:59:22,923
...one night...

713
00:59:24,227 --> 00:59:27,469
...I found Heather
in front of the house.

714
00:59:27,606 --> 00:59:31,315
She had a knife in one hand
and her hair in the other.

715
00:59:31,443 --> 00:59:35,027
When I ask ed her why she
had done such a thing to herself,

716
00:59:35,155 --> 00:59:37,646
she said it was
the one part of her

717
00:59:37,783 --> 00:59:39,819
that would never age.

718
00:59:39,951 --> 00:59:41,782
It would forever
remain the same

719
00:59:41,912 --> 00:59:44,870
as when I first
fell in love with her.

720
00:59:46,083 --> 00:59:48,790
That's how she wanted me
to remember her.

721
00:59:49,544 --> 00:59:51,580
Why are you telling me this?

722
00:59:51,713 --> 00:59:55,922
Because I once loved a woman
more than life itself...

723
00:59:59,846 --> 01:00:01,802
...and I watched her die.

724
01:00:03,433 --> 01:00:06,596
Unlik e me, you have a choice.

725
01:00:23,078 --> 01:00:25,319
What would you have me tell her?

726
01:00:25,455 --> 01:00:28,822
I'd tell her nothing.
She wouldn't believe you anyway.

727
01:00:28,959 --> 01:00:30,369
Then I can do nothing.

728
01:00:30,502 --> 01:00:33,665
She's in the flower of her youth.

729
01:00:33,797 --> 01:00:36,504
Enjoy the moment,
and let it pass.

730
01:00:36,633 --> 01:00:38,043
And if it were you in my place?

731
01:00:38,176 --> 01:00:40,041
I was in your place!

732
01:00:42,139 --> 01:00:44,676
But I thank God
I never had the choice.

733
01:00:44,808 --> 01:00:46,924
I love Kate,

734
01:00:47,060 --> 01:00:50,052
and I will hold on to her
as long as I can.

735
01:00:50,188 --> 01:00:52,179
And that is all I can do!

736
01:00:56,611 --> 01:00:59,193
(Duncan) 'Forever, my love.'

737
01:01:00,615 --> 01:01:02,355
'Until the day we are reborn.'

738
01:01:03,827 --> 01:01:05,408
'Until the day we are reborn.'

739
01:01:51,291 --> 01:01:53,373
(Wind blows)

740
01:02:01,760 --> 01:02:04,923
- You haven't lost your touch.
- What do you want?

741
01:02:05,055 --> 01:02:07,137
- To talk.
- Oh, that's a first.

742
01:02:07,265 --> 01:02:09,051
I've tried to talk to you
a thousand times...

743
01:02:09,184 --> 01:02:10,515
Get to the point.

744
01:02:10,644 --> 01:02:13,226
- I was wrong.
- Oh, no, no.

745
01:02:13,355 --> 01:02:14,845
Stealing is wrong.

746
01:02:14,981 --> 01:02:16,972
Lying is wrong.
Killing's wrong.

747
01:02:17,108 --> 01:02:19,019
What you did
goes well beyond wrong.

748
01:02:19,152 --> 01:02:22,144
Fine. I deserve that,

749
01:02:22,280 --> 01:02:23,861
but I want a chance
to make it right.

750
01:02:23,990 --> 01:02:25,855
You want to mak e it right?

751
01:02:25,992 --> 01:02:28,859
Then give me back the ability
to have children,

752
01:02:28,995 --> 01:02:31,236
to grow old
with the man I love.

753
01:02:31,373 --> 01:02:33,614
How about anything that
resembles a normal life?

754
01:02:33,750 --> 01:02:35,911
And you took it all
away from me.

755
01:02:36,044 --> 01:02:37,784
Those things I can't give you.

756
01:02:37,921 --> 01:02:40,333
Oh, something else
you forgot to tell me.

757
01:02:41,716 --> 01:02:42,796
Goodbye, Duncan.

758
01:02:42,926 --> 01:02:47,590
Kell can't give you those things, either,
so tell me, Kate, why him?

759
01:02:48,682 --> 01:02:52,721
Because I've never known anybody
with such a capacity for hate

760
01:02:52,852 --> 01:02:54,183
except me.

761
01:02:54,312 --> 01:02:57,475
That's what's k ept you
going all these years?

762
01:02:57,607 --> 01:02:59,097
Hmm?

763
01:03:01,152 --> 01:03:02,642
Fine.

764
01:03:04,322 --> 01:03:05,653
Go home, Faith.

765
01:03:07,450 --> 01:03:09,987
Tak e care of what's important.

766
01:03:41,776 --> 01:03:44,017
(Wind blows)

767
01:04:15,894 --> 01:04:18,727
(Thunderclap)

768
01:04:32,827 --> 01:04:35,159
You were with him.

769
01:04:37,582 --> 01:04:39,868
A woman is a temple

770
01:04:40,001 --> 01:04:42,663
built on a sewer.

771
01:04:43,463 --> 01:04:45,749
(Thunder rumbling)

772
01:04:45,882 --> 01:04:49,340
Remember what you were
when I first found you.

773
01:04:51,096 --> 01:04:53,087
A whore.

774
01:04:54,849 --> 01:04:56,840
Now, look at you.

775
01:04:57,852 --> 01:04:59,968
A liberated whore.

776
01:05:00,105 --> 01:05:01,436
Fuck you.

777
01:05:01,564 --> 01:05:05,148
Oh, we'll get to that, blossom.

778
01:05:05,276 --> 01:05:10,987
But in the interim, be grateful
I don't take your pretty little face off.

779
01:05:12,158 --> 01:05:14,820
Hurts, doesn't it...

780
01:05:16,204 --> 01:05:19,321
...that there is something
you actually can't have?

781
01:05:20,834 --> 01:05:26,079
Hmm. I can have
anything I want.

782
01:05:27,757 --> 01:05:29,668
Except me.

783
01:05:30,385 --> 01:05:32,216
(Sighs)

784
01:05:32,929 --> 01:05:35,841
I've already had you.

785
01:05:38,143 --> 01:05:40,805
(Thunder crashing)

786
01:05:40,937 --> 01:05:42,598
(Softly) Not really.

787
01:05:46,985 --> 01:05:48,976
Close enough.

788
01:06:13,928 --> 01:06:16,340
(Door opening)

789
01:06:37,952 --> 01:06:42,491
(Woman vocalizing)

790
01:06:45,793 --> 01:06:51,538
(* Woman singing)

791
01:08:07,166 --> 01:08:08,997
Forever.

792
01:08:44,203 --> 01:08:46,945
May love remain
to guide our way

793
01:08:47,081 --> 01:08:48,821
till the day we are reborn.

794
01:08:54,130 --> 01:08:56,086
Forgive me.

795
01:08:58,051 --> 01:09:00,542
(Screams)

796
01:09:14,317 --> 01:09:15,557
I'm sorry.

797
01:09:17,403 --> 01:09:19,314
You had no right.

798
01:09:36,798 --> 01:09:37,787
(Wind blows)

799
01:09:37,924 --> 01:09:38,913
(Gasps)

800
01:09:39,050 --> 01:09:40,881
(Thunder)

801
01:09:42,720 --> 01:09:43,835
(Duncan) Kate?

802
01:09:43,971 --> 01:09:46,758
No. Don't be frightened.
You're lmmortal, we both are.

803
01:09:46,891 --> 01:09:48,882
Aah!

804
01:09:51,312 --> 01:09:53,143
I did it for you...

805
01:09:53,856 --> 01:09:55,346
...for us.

806
01:09:55,483 --> 01:09:57,849
- Aah!
- Kate.

807
01:09:57,985 --> 01:10:01,853
- Oh, no!
- Oh, my God! What have I done?

808
01:10:01,989 --> 01:10:03,479
Kate!

809
01:10:03,616 --> 01:10:05,857
(Faith) 'You wanted this.'

810
01:10:05,993 --> 01:10:08,609
You forced it on me.

811
01:10:09,414 --> 01:10:11,325
I never ask ed for eternity.

812
01:10:11,457 --> 01:10:12,947
(Crying)

813
01:10:13,084 --> 01:10:15,951
(Duncan) 'I never wanted us to be apart.'

814
01:10:20,133 --> 01:10:22,795
- Would you have really understood?
- Which part?

815
01:10:22,927 --> 01:10:26,340
The endless, numbing
sameness of it all?

816
01:10:26,472 --> 01:10:28,679
Or never bothering
to love someone

817
01:10:29,600 --> 01:10:33,388
because whole lifetimes tick by so fast
they don't even count any more?

818
01:10:33,521 --> 01:10:35,637
(Opens door)

819
01:10:36,149 --> 01:10:37,559
Then why did you come?

820
01:10:39,110 --> 01:10:41,772
To see if I could feel again...

821
01:10:42,613 --> 01:10:44,274
...anything.

822
01:10:45,032 --> 01:10:46,863
(Door closes)

823
01:10:56,627 --> 01:10:58,618
(Elevator bell dings)

824
01:11:02,717 --> 01:11:04,708
You're missing the point, Kate.

825
01:11:04,844 --> 01:11:07,176
The difference
between Connor and I

826
01:11:07,305 --> 01:11:08,966
is that as long
as you're still alive,

827
01:11:09,098 --> 01:11:11,589
there's a chance that one day
I might be forgiven.

828
01:11:12,477 --> 01:11:13,683
It may tak e years...

829
01:11:15,021 --> 01:11:16,761
...centuries, even.

830
01:11:17,899 --> 01:11:19,855
But at least I can carry
that hope inside me.

831
01:11:20,860 --> 01:11:23,272
That's one blessing
of immortality...

832
01:11:25,323 --> 01:11:27,314
...there's always tomorrow.

833
01:11:28,951 --> 01:11:30,191
Even for us.

834
01:11:36,918 --> 01:11:38,829
(Bell tolling)

835
01:11:48,763 --> 01:11:51,175
What are you doing, Jin?

836
01:11:52,141 --> 01:11:53,506
Just thinking.

837
01:11:55,102 --> 01:11:58,435
(Jin) Men, for the most part,
can mend their ways

838
01:11:58,564 --> 01:12:01,271
only after they have made
a mistak e.

839
01:12:03,194 --> 01:12:04,525
One day soon,

840
01:12:05,571 --> 01:12:10,907
we will all serve very little purpose
to Kell, except dead.

841
01:12:26,592 --> 01:12:27,957
(Kell) A toast.

842
01:12:30,263 --> 01:12:32,254
I see tonight...

843
01:12:33,432 --> 01:12:36,265
...as a celebration of the spirit.

844
01:12:37,770 --> 01:12:39,556
To all of you

845
01:12:39,689 --> 01:12:43,978
who continue to stand by me
even those who might waver

846
01:12:44,110 --> 01:12:45,941
at times...

847
01:12:47,238 --> 01:12:50,605
You are my flock.

848
01:12:52,076 --> 01:12:52,940
You

849
01:12:53,536 --> 01:12:55,572
nourish my soul.

850
01:12:59,292 --> 01:13:03,331
You are all a part
of a great journey,

851
01:13:03,838 --> 01:13:06,671
a 400-year quest...

852
01:13:08,384 --> 01:13:10,215
...for justice.

853
01:13:12,221 --> 01:13:15,679
(Kell) And here, my friends,

854
01:13:15,808 --> 01:13:19,346
is the instrument of that justice.

855
01:13:20,897 --> 01:13:24,560
The giver and taker
of creation...

856
01:13:27,236 --> 01:13:29,773
...baptised in blood.

857
01:13:32,825 --> 01:13:37,410
It is the living
that matters after all.

858
01:13:42,335 --> 01:13:44,496
It sings lik e an angel.

859
01:13:45,963 --> 01:13:47,578
Just listen.

860
01:13:50,343 --> 01:13:51,924
(Faith gasps)

861
01:13:56,182 --> 01:13:57,046
(Jin) Uh!

862
01:14:03,940 --> 01:14:05,225
(Man) Uh!

863
01:14:13,366 --> 01:14:14,856
(Carlos) Uh!

864
01:14:14,992 --> 01:14:16,402
(Gasps)

865
01:14:28,172 --> 01:14:30,163
Till the day we are reborn.

866
01:14:31,384 --> 01:14:32,715
(Faith gasps)

867
01:14:41,644 --> 01:14:42,884
Uh!

868
01:14:50,861 --> 01:14:52,192
Aah!

869
01:14:53,614 --> 01:14:55,525
Aah!

870
01:15:11,716 --> 01:15:13,957
(Wind blows)

871
01:15:27,356 --> 01:15:28,641
Kell.

872
01:15:30,109 --> 01:15:31,315
Jacob Kell.

873
01:15:40,161 --> 01:15:41,992
Connor?

874
01:15:51,672 --> 01:15:53,879
(Sighs)

875
01:15:54,008 --> 01:15:57,375
We've lived many lives,
you and I.

876
01:15:57,511 --> 01:16:02,881
We've seen things that most people
could never understand.

877
01:16:03,017 --> 01:16:05,759
But now what do you see?

878
01:16:05,895 --> 01:16:08,602
I see someone who would
never kill an unarmed man.

879
01:16:10,191 --> 01:16:14,560
I also see someone
who has lost hope.

880
01:16:14,695 --> 01:16:17,402
Life brings hope and pain...

881
01:16:19,784 --> 01:16:22,491
...but revenge
never brings redemption.

882
01:16:22,620 --> 01:16:25,612
The path and choice are ours.

883
01:16:32,713 --> 01:16:34,294
Connor, what the hell's going on?

884
01:16:35,132 --> 01:16:36,622
I have chosen mine.

885
01:16:36,759 --> 01:16:37,794
Aah!

886
01:16:37,927 --> 01:16:39,337
What are you doing?

887
01:16:39,470 --> 01:16:42,633
Kell's too strong,
and he's getting stronger.

888
01:16:42,765 --> 01:16:45,222
Neither one of us can beat him alone.

889
01:16:47,186 --> 01:16:48,301
Are you out of your mind?

890
01:16:50,481 --> 01:16:53,348
If we let him win,
it could mean the end.

891
01:16:59,240 --> 01:17:00,946
Connor, no!

892
01:17:03,494 --> 01:17:07,282
Kell is going to kill you, Duncan,
just to torment me,

893
01:17:07,414 --> 01:17:10,156
and there is nothing
you can do about it, nothing!

894
01:17:10,292 --> 01:17:12,123
I don't believe that, Connor.
Neither should you.

895
01:17:12,253 --> 01:17:14,915
Alone, neither one of us
can beat him.

896
01:17:15,047 --> 01:17:16,253
Together, we can.

897
01:17:16,382 --> 01:17:18,589
You know the rules.

898
01:17:18,717 --> 01:17:20,708
Only one lmmortal
can challenge another.

899
01:17:21,720 --> 01:17:23,176
And only one will.

900
01:17:24,181 --> 01:17:25,261
This isn't the answer.

901
01:17:26,058 --> 01:17:27,264
Listen to me.

902
01:17:27,393 --> 01:17:28,803
In the end,

903
01:17:28,936 --> 01:17:33,225
there can be only one,
and that has to be you.

904
01:17:35,651 --> 01:17:37,141
No.

905
01:17:37,945 --> 01:17:39,185
We can beat him together.

906
01:17:39,321 --> 01:17:41,778
Then we are in agreement.

907
01:17:52,877 --> 01:17:54,868
Enough, Connor!

908
01:17:55,004 --> 01:17:59,088
I won't fight you.
I will never fight you, Connor.

909
01:17:59,592 --> 01:18:01,628
Then you die!

910
01:18:28,120 --> 01:18:30,577
No!
You're not doing this, Connor.

911
01:18:31,624 --> 01:18:33,990
Oh, yes, we're doing this.

912
01:18:34,126 --> 01:18:39,211
Every day, every breath we took
was for this end.

913
01:18:42,635 --> 01:18:45,968
Look inside
and tell me I'm wrong.

914
01:19:05,950 --> 01:19:07,486
Aah!

915
01:19:09,453 --> 01:19:11,660
Aah! Aah!

916
01:19:17,002 --> 01:19:18,993
Do it!

917
01:19:22,341 --> 01:19:24,332
I can't.

918
01:19:27,054 --> 01:19:29,215
Remember how
you first found me?

919
01:19:29,348 --> 01:19:33,682
Sitting in that bloody bog,
scared out of my mind?

920
01:19:33,811 --> 01:19:37,019
You taught me how to live, Connor.
You taught me why we live.

921
01:19:38,148 --> 01:19:40,605
Have you forgotten all of that?

922
01:19:42,528 --> 01:19:44,018
No.

923
01:19:46,615 --> 01:19:50,107
Our bonds are all
that hold us in this world.

924
01:19:52,162 --> 01:19:54,153
Don't break this one.

925
01:19:58,752 --> 01:20:02,665
Please, Connor.
I'm begging you.

926
01:20:06,427 --> 01:20:08,418
It's too late.

927
01:20:15,269 --> 01:20:17,726
This has to be done.

928
01:20:17,855 --> 01:20:19,265
Aah!

929
01:20:22,318 --> 01:20:23,683
No, Connor!
Not lik e this!

930
01:20:23,819 --> 01:20:25,184
Come on, stop!

931
01:20:25,321 --> 01:20:27,903
- Connor, stop!
- Duncan!

932
01:20:32,494 --> 01:20:35,156
One of us has to die now,
old friend.

933
01:20:37,124 --> 01:20:38,614
No.

934
01:20:41,003 --> 01:20:42,789
And you know it.

935
01:20:44,882 --> 01:20:46,372
No.

936
01:20:49,678 --> 01:20:51,669
Goodbye, Duncan...

937
01:20:52,765 --> 01:20:54,926
...my true brother.

938
01:20:57,603 --> 01:20:59,844
I love you, Connor.

939
01:21:09,114 --> 01:21:10,820
Aah!

940
01:21:13,410 --> 01:21:14,900
No!

941
01:21:23,837 --> 01:21:25,452
Aah!

942
01:22:13,554 --> 01:22:16,091
(Screaming)

943
01:23:40,599 --> 01:23:44,183
(Hands clapping)

944
01:23:50,984 --> 01:23:52,474
Duncan.

945
01:23:53,278 --> 01:23:55,269
Well done.

946
01:23:59,284 --> 01:24:02,742
I ever thought
you had him in you.

947
01:24:04,748 --> 01:24:08,411
What does it feel lik e
to kill a brother?

948
01:24:09,336 --> 01:24:12,920
Feels good,
doesn't it?

949
01:24:14,049 --> 01:24:16,415
You'll never know, will you?

950
01:24:18,804 --> 01:24:22,217
Now you'II never have
Connor MacLeod's head.

951
01:24:23,433 --> 01:24:26,345
Are you going to run?

952
01:24:26,478 --> 01:24:29,311
Are you going to hide?

953
01:24:31,900 --> 01:24:33,436
Run?

954
01:24:33,569 --> 01:24:35,935
(Grunts)

955
01:24:36,071 --> 01:24:38,278
Brother, come on!

956
01:24:38,407 --> 01:24:40,614
Aah!

957
01:24:40,742 --> 01:24:42,073
(Grunts)

958
01:24:42,202 --> 01:24:44,443
Aah!

959
01:24:48,166 --> 01:24:51,408
(Both screaming)

960
01:25:16,612 --> 01:25:18,728
How bad do you want it,
Duncan?

961
01:25:21,742 --> 01:25:23,152
You'll pay!

962
01:25:48,226 --> 01:25:50,342
Aah!

963
01:26:08,205 --> 01:26:10,287
(Screams)

964
01:26:21,468 --> 01:26:22,674
Duncan!

965
01:27:43,341 --> 01:27:45,172
(Grunts)

966
01:27:45,302 --> 01:27:48,965
OK, Kell. Come on.
Let's do this.

967
01:27:54,936 --> 01:27:56,346
(Camera winding)

968
01:28:00,108 --> 01:28:01,644
Just watch.

969
01:28:25,509 --> 01:28:28,171
Merry Christmas.

970
01:28:49,783 --> 01:28:51,648
A valiant effort, Duncan.

971
01:28:52,661 --> 01:28:54,617
Too bad.

972
01:28:54,746 --> 01:28:57,032
And this is just the beginning.

973
01:28:57,165 --> 01:29:02,285
You see, when you absorbed
Connor's spirit, you inherited his curse.

974
01:29:02,420 --> 01:29:05,708
Revenge is so sweet.

975
01:29:05,841 --> 01:29:08,457
I wonder who we'll start with?

976
01:29:14,474 --> 01:29:16,010
Oh, Kate.

977
01:29:17,269 --> 01:29:19,009
(Thunder)

978
01:29:19,145 --> 01:29:20,305
(Whispering) 'Forever.'

979
01:29:21,940 --> 01:29:23,771
Oh, God.

980
01:29:25,110 --> 01:29:26,190
Kell!

981
01:29:28,154 --> 01:29:30,440
Jacob Kell!

982
01:29:32,742 --> 01:29:37,406
Revenge will never
bring you redemption,

983
01:29:37,539 --> 01:29:40,121
so I'm going to do it for you.

984
01:29:41,459 --> 01:29:43,199
Aah!

985
01:29:46,006 --> 01:29:47,997
Is that all you've got?

986
01:29:57,058 --> 01:30:00,516
(Kell) Duncan, I'd thought
I'd be home for dinner an hour ago,

987
01:30:00,645 --> 01:30:02,556
but this is very impressive.

988
01:30:04,316 --> 01:30:07,729
Come on.
What are you waiting for?

989
01:30:07,861 --> 01:30:09,601
I'd be delighted.
Yah!

990
01:30:22,083 --> 01:30:25,371
Impressive... isn't it?

991
01:30:25,503 --> 01:30:26,993
Uh!

992
01:30:27,130 --> 01:30:28,040
Duncan!

993
01:30:28,173 --> 01:30:30,255
(Drops sword)

994
01:30:34,054 --> 01:30:36,716
You see at last your fate!

995
01:30:37,641 --> 01:30:40,758
Yes!
Because this game is done!

996
01:30:44,814 --> 01:30:46,475
Uh!

997
01:30:49,235 --> 01:30:50,941
Well, look on the bright side.

998
01:30:51,071 --> 01:30:53,403
At least
you went down swinging.

999
01:30:53,531 --> 01:30:55,021
(Connor's voice) 'Jacob Kell.

1000
01:30:56,910 --> 01:30:59,652
'Time for redemption.

1001
01:31:02,415 --> 01:31:05,077
'The game isn't over yet.

1002
01:31:06,169 --> 01:31:07,579
'What's the matter?

1003
01:31:08,254 --> 01:31:10,666
'Don't you want to be inside me?

1004
01:31:14,094 --> 01:31:15,174
'ln the end... '

1005
01:31:15,887 --> 01:31:18,003
...there can be only one.

1006
01:31:29,150 --> 01:31:31,436
(Connor's voice) 'And you're not it.'

1007
01:31:33,363 --> 01:31:34,853
Call ya.

1008
01:31:56,594 --> 01:31:58,585
No!

1009
01:32:00,557 --> 01:32:02,468
(Screaming)

1010
01:32:04,811 --> 01:32:06,472
Aah!

1011
01:32:44,476 --> 01:32:46,467
(Wind blows)

1012
01:33:10,335 --> 01:33:13,668
Hope you found peace,
my friend.

1013
01:33:13,797 --> 01:33:16,288
(* LOREENA MCKEN N ITT:
"Bonny Portmore")

1014
01:33:16,424 --> 01:33:21,009
* Oh Bonny Portmore

1015
01:33:21,137 --> 01:33:24,971
* I am sorry to see

1016
01:33:25,809 --> 01:33:31,099
* Such a woeful destruction

1017
01:33:31,231 --> 01:33:35,691
* Of your ornament tree

1018
01:33:35,819 --> 01:33:40,483
* For it stood on your shore

1019
01:33:40,615 --> 01:33:45,234
* For many's the long day

1020
01:33:45,370 --> 01:33:51,787
* 'Til the long boats from Antrim

1021
01:33:51,918 --> 01:33:58,255
* Came to float it away...

1022
01:33:59,509 --> 01:34:01,921
(Wind blowing)

1023
01:34:48,808 --> 01:34:52,141
So, why are you here?
You hoping you'd find me?

1024
01:34:55,523 --> 01:34:57,855
For whatever reason,
Kell made his choice.

1025
01:35:02,363 --> 01:35:03,853
So...

1026
01:35:04,741 --> 01:35:06,322
...what now?

1027
01:35:09,412 --> 01:35:11,448
Trust.

1028
01:35:11,581 --> 01:35:13,071
You can always trust me, Faith.

1029
01:35:14,083 --> 01:35:15,914
Faith is dead.

1030
01:35:16,878 --> 01:35:20,712
I thought we'd give
Kate another chance.

1031
01:35:31,601 --> 01:35:33,557
Not yet.

1032
01:35:33,686 --> 01:35:35,392
(Kate whispers)
'Till the day we are reborn.'

1033
01:35:35,521 --> 01:35:37,136
You hold onto it for me.

1034
01:35:38,524 --> 01:35:39,980
We've got plenty of time.

1035
01:35:40,109 --> 01:35:41,144
(* "Bonny Portmore" continues)

1036
01:35:41,277 --> 01:35:45,862
* Oh Bonny Portmore

1037
01:35:45,990 --> 01:35:50,734
* I am sorry to see

1038
01:35:50,870 --> 01:35:55,910
* Such a woeful destruction

1039
01:35:56,042 --> 01:36:00,456
* Of your ornament tree

1040
01:36:00,588 --> 01:36:05,298
* For it stood on your shore

1041
01:36:06,386 --> 01:36:10,049
* For many's the long day

1042
01:36:10,181 --> 01:36:16,723
* 'Til the long boats from Antrim

1043
01:36:16,854 --> 01:36:23,191
* Came to float it away

1044
01:36:24,737 --> 01:36:29,572
* Oh Bonny Portmore

1045
01:36:29,701 --> 01:36:34,445
* You shine where you stand

1046
01:36:34,580 --> 01:36:39,791
* And the more I think on you

1047
01:36:39,919 --> 01:36:44,162
* The more I think long

1048
01:36:44,299 --> 01:36:48,542
* If I had you now

1049
01:36:48,678 --> 01:36:53,763
* As I had once before

1050
01:36:53,891 --> 01:37:00,262
* All the Lords in Old England

1051
01:37:00,398 --> 01:37:07,236
* Would not purchase Portmore

1052
01:37:08,614 --> 01:37:13,779
* All the birds in the forest

1053
01:37:13,911 --> 01:37:17,950
* They bitterly weep

1054
01:37:18,082 --> 01:37:23,372
* Saying, "Where shall we shelter?

1055
01:37:23,504 --> 01:37:27,918
* "Where shall we sleep?"

1056
01:37:28,051 --> 01:37:32,010
* For the oak and the ash

1057
01:37:32,138 --> 01:37:37,804
* They are all cutten down

1058
01:37:37,935 --> 01:37:44,306
* And the walls of Bonny Portmore

1059
01:37:44,442 --> 01:37:51,189
* Are all down to the ground

1060
01:37:52,241 --> 01:37:56,985
* Oh Bonny Portmore

1061
01:37:57,121 --> 01:38:01,785
* You shine where you stand

1062
01:38:01,918 --> 01:38:07,038
* And the more I think on you

1063
01:38:07,173 --> 01:38:11,542
* The more I think long

1064
01:38:11,677 --> 01:38:15,545
* If I had you now

1065
01:38:15,681 --> 01:38:21,017
* As I had once before

1066
01:38:21,145 --> 01:38:27,766
* All the Lords of Old England

1067
01:38:27,902 --> 01:38:35,320
* Would not purchase Portmore *

