"Narita International Airport"
On its way from Hong Kong to Tokyo,
First Airline flight 816
was hijacked before landing in Narita Airport.
No demand except for a ramp
has been made by the hijackers...
They may be armed with guns.
The passengers' safety is of the greatest concern.
What's their demand?
20 million dollars and a getaway plane.
We won't accept.
Should we send in the SWAT team?
Not yet. We'll use them as our last resort.
They're taking too long.
We'll wait 5 more minutes.
Stop screwing with us!
Our vacation abroad...
It was a bad idea.
At any rate...
How can she stay asleep?
I slept so well.
Are we landing soon?
Keep your voice down.
Quiet!
Yes.
Hijack?
When did this happen?
Can I have some water?
Shut your mouth, hag!
Hag?
What's that look?
Sit still and behave, geezer.
Unforgivable.
You all behave.
Miss Yamaguchi!
They're people who deserve respect
for their decades of hard work.
How dare you dis them.
What'd you say?
Whatever it is you want,
face the sun and
say it with pride and dignity.
Stop blabbering!
Move in!
There was a gunshot.
The hijackers did have guns.
Forgive us!
Huh?
Miss Yamaguchi?
- What?
- Look!
You're kidding!
Miss Yamaguchi?!
Yankumi...
My Lady...
Kumiko...
My Lady's in trouble!
You guys, let's go!
We're going.
It's over.
No... I'm not the criminal.
I'm straight.
Straight?
I'm Kumiko Yamaguchi.
A teacher at Akado High School.
I teach math.
My nickname is Yankumi.
By the way, I'm single.
GOKUSEN THE MOVIE
"The Oedo Family"
I'm glad you're okay.
It was reckless of you.
I'm sorry to worry you.
But we were impressed.
Guts and honor befitting
the 4th generation head.
You can take over any day.
My Lady!
No..."Lady Boss"!
Sounds nice.
You guys, follow my lead.
"The Oedo Family"
No way. I'm not taking over.
I bought souvenirs for you.
You didn't have to do that.
Oops... They're at the airport.
Sorry.
I'm Kumiko Yamaguchi,
a high school teacher.
I lost my parents at age 7
and was raised by my grandfather,
Ryuichiro Kuroda,
the 3rd generation head of the Oedo Family.
I've been a teacher for 7 years.
My students always happen
to be so-called delinquents.
But they taught me things.
Face them squarely and they'll do the same.
You can see eye to eye.
In 7 years, I've grown thanks to my students.
Good morning, Yankumi.
Good morning, Kuma.
I saw you on the news yesterday.
No big deal. I wasn't afraid of them.
You were cool.
No compliments.
It's embarrassing.
See ya.
"Hijackers surrender themselves"
"Hijackers arrested"
I didn't know this was your flight.
I was shocked when I saw the news.
Thank goodness you're safe.
It was terrifying.
Miss Ayukawa is still in shock.
I'm gonna die...
A hijack...
Help me.
So why did the hijackers surrender themselves?
Well, Miss Yamaguchi...
They knew they couldn't get away.
Miss Yamaguchi.
Good morning, Vice Principal.
Principal.
Oh... sorry.
May I?
"Passenger scolds hijackers?"
Was it you?
No.
Good.
Nobody must find out
about your family business.
Don't forget.
I've told you many times.
We'll both be fired.
Don't attract attention to yourself.
A trainee teacher starts today, right?
He's not here yet.
Late from day one.
He needs to be disciplined.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I apologize.
Odagiri!
Yankumi...
Baba...
You're...
That Odagiri?
Vice Principal Monkey Brain.
Principal Sawatari.
Seriously?
You know him, Miss Yamaguchi?
He was my student at Kurogin.
I'm Ryu Odagiri, the trainee teacher.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go.
Good luck.
Welcome.
Give him proper guidance.
Yes, sir.
It's been a while.
You were such a handful back then.
But look at you now.
This was my dream.
A student admiring me
choosing to become a teacher.
What?
So, Odagiri...
You and me and the students united
with passion and sweat!
Follow my lead.
You're even more gung-ho.
You don't want to be a teacher?
I don't know yet.
I just took the teacher-training course.
You're not here because I'm here?
Of course not.
Oh...
How're you doing with
your new troublemakers?
Not that well.
I'm taking it slowly.
Teachers have to be patient
with their students.
Join me.
You still do that?
Yes.
Good morning.
Quiet, please.
Quiet down.
I told you to be quiet!
"Teachers have to be patient," right?
What're you babbling about?
You can't boss us around!
Who put out a cigarette here?
So that's why.
She was just lucky.
You have to use an ashtray.
That's not the point.
Who was smoking?!
- I dunno
- We wouldn't tell you anyway.
We don't sell out our friends.
We take good care of each other.
What's funny?
Nothing.
Smoking by minors is verboten.
Verboten?
What's that word?
Not being caught doesn't make things okay.
The sun's watching you.
The sun?
What does that mean?
Let me introduce him.
Mr. Ryu Odagiri, a trainee teacher.
To get acquainted with Mr. Odagiri,
let's play Kick the Can.
Change into your jerseys
and come to the field.
At least we can get acquainted.
No thanks.
Dammit!
Uh-oh. Run!
Whoa...
That trainee teacher was
Yamaguchi's student.
A delinquent at Kurogin.
A delinquent-turned-teacher?
No way.
Big news!
Unbelievable!
What's going on?!
Listen to this!
What's up?
Why are you so amped up?
You see!
Stop talking at once.
Yankumi was walking with a guy.
- You guys saw them too?
- Yeah.
He was even good-looking.
- No way.
- Probably an illusion.
- It was really her!
- It'll snow tomorrow!
Table for two, please.
Sit. I recommend...
I know.
Guys! Long time no see.
How're you doing?
Why are you gaping at me?
Odagiri, it's you!
Hello.
Ryu Odagiri, Yankumi's student
from Kurogin High.
Student?!
Now I understand.
So that's why...
They were worked up
because they saw you with a guy.
They thought it was an illusion.
Yankumi could never find
a good-looking boyfriend.
Never.
We were such idiots.
Totally.
I told you "no way."
No way?
You guys, outside!
Right now!
What do you mean...
Calm down.
Two ramen noodles, please.
"Kumai Noodle Shop"
Yummy!
I'm impressed.
You're going to school regularly.
We try.
You've matured since high school.
How's work going for you guys?
Just great.
Kura's always getting in trouble.
Don't tell.
I get in trouble with my dad at our tofu shop.
Work is tough, no matter what it is.
I wish they'd pay me more.
Yeah. That's why I'm getting a night job.
A night job?
You idiot! A delivery job.
Oh.
I thought the shady type.
Of course not.
What shady type?
You still having a hard time with your class?
Sort of.
We rejected her at first too.
Yeah, her lectures were awful.
So annoying at first.
We bet on when she'd quit.
We did too.
Really? How about you?
Probably.
Everyone's the same.
Yep.
Are you crying?
No, you idiot.
I'm happy.
My students from
different schools are here...
Laughing together...
Real happy.
I'm glad I became a teacher.
Wipe them.
Eat as much as you want.
Order anything. It's my treat.
Roasted pork noodles!
Dumplings, large portion!
Sounds good.
Large fried rice!
Kuma, bring them all.
It's before payday, isn't it?
No large portions. No roasted pork.
Cancel the dumplings.
Just more noodles, okay?
More noodles for six.
No way!
Reita's late.
He'll be here soon.
Yo, can I borrow some money?
Don't have any.
Shut up and hand it over.
Reita!
Keep your hands off my friends.
Who are you?!
Reita Takasugi of Akado.
Got a problem?
It was my dream to drink
with a student of mine.
Don't be shy, brother.
Brother?
He means "friend."
Wonderful, isn't it?
A student, now a responsible adult.
It means you taught him well.
That's not true.
I know.
What'd you say?
Tetsu, sit.
Certainly.
Scary.
You had the brains, Odagiri.
- Minoru.
- Sorry.
Be prepared.
Drink 'til you drop.
That's My Lady.
"Be prepared" huh...
She must've been so happy.
Her student finding his own path.
I haven't found mine yet.
Gonna be a teacher, right?
No...
I thought I could
find my path in college but I couldn't.
So I started to panic.
Then I remembered what she said.
"Don't give up."
"It's okay to fail."
She was sort of annoying
but taught me many things.
She puts her heart and soul into everything.
I want to find my own path like her.
My head hurts.
I'm gonna throw up.
- Excuse me.
- Me too.
Yankumi!
Takeda! Hyuga!
Long time no see.
How're you doing?
You two working hard?
Of course. Dumb question.
Look at me, a businessman.
What are you doing here?
Listening to his speech.
Thank you for your time.
I've decided to run for
a seat in the Lower House.
My name is Kentaro Kurose.
Who is he?
You don't know? The president of
Dream Associates, an IT giant.
He's amazing.
A former delinquent like us
who succeeded in business.
Now he'll be in the election.
Impressive.
Yeah, he is.
Today I'm a success in the IT industry
but I used to be a troublemaker.
I was reformed thanks to
many people's support.
I want to repay this society for accepting me.
Wonderful.
You have my support.
Thank you.
You look like my old flame.
I bet you are kind and earnest
and honest like him.
Good luck.
Let's go.
You're troubling him.
I'm rooting for you.
My name's Yamaguchi.
"Akado High School"
Those guys yesterday pissed me off.
Whoever they were, Reita showed them.
They talked big but they were pussies.
You're awesome, Reita.
Not really.
- Another fight?
- Is that a problem?
Don't pop out of nowhere!
Fighting isn't necessarily bad but...
Then leave us alone.
Reita Takasugi, come out here!
I heard you and my buddies
got friendly yesterday.
The guys from yesterday...
They're the Black Skull.
Black Skull?
A bad motorcycle gang.
A motorcycle gang is outside.
Please hurry!
Let's go.
We're not done with you!
Why on earth did you get involved
with that sort?!
Principal, they seem to be
a very violent group.
Extortions, assaults...
Many run-ins with the police.
Scary.
A fight with guys like that of all people...
It wasn't a fight.
Reita stopped them from
extorting money from us.
You're saying it wasn't some foolish reason?
If you don't believe us, then forget it.
We can't forget it.
Is it true what you told us?
Yeah.
- Vice Principal.
- Principal.
They're not lying.
You believe them?
I do.
If they're lying,
I'll see it in their eyes.
Are you sure?
I'll hold you responsible.
The next time your students cause trouble,
you're fired.
Fine.
I'm not afraid to lose my job for them.
- See it in our eyes?!
- She's trying to act tough.
She doesn't mean it.
Teachers are all the same.
You okay, Reita?
They're real bad asses.
Been arrested a lot.
Serious?
They'll be back.
We'll be in deep shit.
The next time your students cause trouble,
you're fired.
I'm not afraid to lose my job for them.
Where're you going?
To settle the matter.
- That's crazy.
- They'll kill you.
I don't wanna owe her.
Let's start. Take your seats.
What happened?
Takasugi took off.
To settle things with the bikers.
He's gonna get his ass kicked.
You guys, why'd you let him go?
Why let him go alone?
Because...
Those guys are seriously bad...
Aren't you his friends?!
Yankumi...
Her ideas on friends and loyalty...
They're meaningless and annoying at first.
We thought so too.
But now we understand.
The things she taught us...
Calling yourselves friends is easy
but that's just talk.
If you're friends for real,
you stick together no matter what happens.
Right?
What now?
What should we do?
You have balls coming here alone.
Fight me 1-on-1.
1-on-1?
If I win, stay away from us and our school.
Did you hear that?
Stop laughing!
Too bad. I don't fight 1-on-1.
Let him go... my precious student.
Who the hell are you?!
I'm his homeroom teacher.
A teacher?
You really messed him up.
You're pathetic.
All of you ganging up on
one high school kid.
We're teaching him a lesson.
He gets this for being a cocky asshole.
Common sense, right?
Don't make me laugh.
Common sense?
Don't pretend like you know
what you're talking about!
Watch it.
If words aren't enough, I'll fight you.
Let me warn you.
I don't hold anything back
to protect my students.
Odagiri.
Fighting is done with bare hands.
Haven't had enough?!
Odagiri... thanks.
Whatever.
Reita!
You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry you had to come alone.
We're so sorry.
Forget about it.
You guys...
Now you're real friends.
So reckless, you...
No, you... What teacher fights?
This one.
You fight to protect the things you cherish.
Things you cherish?
Yeah.
I cherish you guys.
Teachers have to protect their students.
All right! Let's run into the sunset!
Follow my lead!
You guys, follow me!
What a weird teacher.
She is.
But no one else tries so annoyingly hard to
relate to us.
What sunset?
Stop!
Good morning.
G'morning.
Morning.
Mochizuki, Matsushita, Igarashi, Muto...
What?
Did you just say that to me?
Who else is there?
You complaining?
Finally...
You guys are opening up to me.
From now, the mornings will be...
Good morning.
Good morning, Yankumi!
Good morning!
Good morning, class.
My beloved students.
I knew it would come!
A lovely morning like this!
You'll be late for the faculty meeting.
Oops.
Don't be late, you guys!
Look who's talking.
Now that I am the principal
I want you teachers to be
strict with your pupils.
The first semester is almost over.
The final exams start
next week so classes will be
shortened starting today.
Many students take advantage of the situation
and use the extra time to
play around and get in trouble.
Please make sure you prevent that.
Yesterday, a student in Ara High
was arrested for drug possession.
For drugs?
Miss Yamaguchi!
Idiot.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Drug possession by a student
is a serious problem.
A teacher being late...
Nowadays, even college students
and ordinary housewives are doing drugs.
Is that true?
They don't understand
the terrible consequences.
Drugs destroy the body and soul.
It's frightening.
I hear a big drug ring is
running the operation.
That's unforgivable.
Getting rich by selling drugs...
Where's their sense of duty and justice?
- Duty?
- Justice?
Miss Yamaguchi!
Such no-good rotten scumbags
need a serious beatdown!
You're talking like a yakuza.
Excuse us.
Who are you?
We're in a meeting.
- We're the police.
- Police?
"Faculty Room"
Kazama dealing drugs?
It can't be true.
He's not that kind of guy.
It must be a mistake.
We were informed about
a drug deal in a warehouse.
When we arrived there...
The dealers were gone.
But we found evidence and a wallet.
Look.
It belongs to
Ren Kazama.
That doesn't prove he's the culprit.
That's right.
But he's been missing since last night.
You guys, listen!
The cops are after our
upperclassman Kazama.
What did he do?
They said he sold drugs.
You're kidding.
A former student, a criminal...
It's not for certain.
I suppose so but...
I think it's true though.
Me too.
He's 19, still just a kid.
Perhaps he wanted to make
some easy money.
He'd never do anything like that.
"My child would never..."
is an unsafe thought.
And if he's innocent,
why would he be in hiding?
I'm sure there's a reason.
Odagiri, take care of the class.
You're not going
to go look for him, are you?
He's not your student anymore.
You're wrong.
He is my student.
Miss Yamaguchi...
Your call cannot be connected.
Kazama...
You guys...
Kura told me about Ren.
The cops came to the office this morning.
Ren might get fired.
Oh no...
He'll never do anything illegal.
There must be a reason
why he's running.
- Yeah.
- There's gotta be.
We believe in Ren.
He's our friend.
Let's find him.
You guys...
Let's go find him!
That way.
You go that way.
Let's split up.
Takasugi...
Have you seen Kazama?
No.
He's in trouble, right?
He's done nothing wrong.
If you see him, let me know.
Thanks.
=====
Let's split up.
"Yankumi"
Your call cannot be...
Where is he?
She never came back.
I don't know what happened
but you should tell Yankumi.
I don't wanna trouble her.
She's not my...
Teacher anymore?
She's not like that.
Do you have a place to go?
This was the only place, huh?
Kazama!
Ren!
Thank God.
Why are you running around
without telling us anything?
We were worried.
You should've called.
We're your friends, aren't we?
You're not alone, you know.
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
Kazama...
Why didn't you come to me?
Why?
Say something.
He didn't want to trouble you.
You'll go out of your way to help him.
That's why he didn't tell you.
Right?
Kazama...
In high school...
I caused you so much trouble.
Even now, after I graduated...
I was ashamed.
Listen... A teacher
welcomes trouble from her students.
But I'm not your student.
You...
are my precious student.
Right now, I'm in charge of this class.
But you guys who graduated
and students from other schools...
Are all my precious students.
And you're not alone.
Not just them.
Everyone else from 3D
was looking for you.
Sorry.
You guys...
I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
So sorry...
I...
found this sweet job through a friend.
All I had to do was
make a delivery as instructed.
But something was odd.
Over here.
Open it.
Yes.
Open the box.
Put it in the car.
I'm sorry.
You klutz!
This is something bad, isn't it?
I'm quitting.
I didn't realize
what I was delivering.
You want money, right?
You gotta do "something bad"
to make 30,000 yen a night.
It's too late.
You abetted a crime.
Just do as you're told.
Mr. Terada.
All right.
The cops are coming.
I was scared and ashamed.
I didn't know what to do.
Why did you accept the job?
I wanted money.
Money?
Once I started working,
I thought I could support my sister.
But my salary's so low...
That's why
I jumped at the opportunity.
I was an idiot.
Listen, Kazama.
Trying to make money isn't bad.
But don't be fooled by quick easy money.
Money is important.
But it's not everything.
Don't ever forget that.
You guys too.
Okay.
You can stay at my house for a while.
Yankumi is amazing.
I've never known a teacher like her.
She hasn't changed.
Still no sex appeal.
Yankumi is...
still Yankumi.
Sorry to get you involved.
Whatever.
I'll see you.
Odagiri.
You seem troubled too.
Everything's cool...
Okay.
My Lady, this guy Terada...
You were right.
He's a drug dealer.
So it's true.
He avoids getting caught
by making the greenhorns deliver the dope.
The bastard.
Enticing innocent guys with money
and involving them in crime...
But Kumiko...
There's a ringleader.
Ringleader?
Him.
Kentaro Kurose.
He uses his success
and legit company as a front
for his drug business.
He wants power and position
to make more money.
A crook trying to become a politician...
"From failure to success"
Unforgivable.
Where're you off to alone?
I don't want to interfere with
what you do for your students
but this time is different.
You're risking your job as a teacher.
You sure about this?
I can't ignore these bastards
who tried to take advantage
of my precious student.
Kumiko!
I taught my students a few things.
Don't lie.
Live with pride and dignity.
That's why
I can't pretend not to know
what Kurose truly is.
I see.
We have a problem.
Those guys are gone.
This is it.
It's huge.
We should find some evidence here.
Yeah, let's nail those jerks.
How do we get inside?
The security looks tough.
What's that?
"Kurose Campaign Rally"
Campaign rally?
Let's go to the back.
Ogata, what are you doing?
Where are you?
At the ringleader's.
What?
Kentaro Kurose, right?
You idiot! Come back!
That car!
Now.
Hello?
Those reckless fools.
Odagiri...
Hop on.
"Math class today: Study period"
Weird... Yamaguchi took the day off.
Odagiri too. Strange huh.
Do you think something
happened with Kazama?
Kurose is running for office...
We're at Kurose's campaign rally.
Yankumi...
Ryu!
Tsucchi...
Tsuchiya, what are you doing here?
Working. Assistant cameraman.
Yeah?
I still have a lot to learn.
We'll fill you in later.
Let's go.
Kurose's campaign rally is about to begin.
Many supporters have gathered here.
Was that?
Why is she there?
Wasn't that Miss Yamaguchi and Odagiri?
I saw them too.
That's not possible.
They're both sick today.
The principal's right.
It wasn't them.
Odagiri's late.
You are late.
No drugs anywhere.
Maybe he keeps them somewhere else.
Where are we?
We're lost.
Is Kurose really the ringleader?
Hide!
That's him.
Kentaro Kurose's campaign
rally is about to begin.
The IT giant is running for
a seat in the Lower House.
This is a live broadcast.
Kurose! Kurose!
Where did they go?
It's starting.
There's nothing.
It's the box.
Open the box.
Ren!
What is it?
There it is.
Then all these boxes?
Now we have proof.
What're you doing there?!
Kazama!
You shouldn't be here.
Now I can't let you leave.
I'm happy to see you all here today.
Thank you for coming.
I stepped off the path
during high school and
was even arrested by the police.
But now, thanks to your
and many people's support,
I've found my place in society.
Kids should keep their noses out.
Yankumi!
You guys okay?
This was stupid of you.
Sorry.
We almost died.
I almost peed in my pants.
A society where youth can dream.
Catch the dream.
Kurose... You're unforgivable.
I'll handle things from here.
What're you talking about?!
I can't put you guys in any more danger.
But...
Odagiri, take care of them.
Yankumi!
Why'd you let her go?!
We can't just leave her!
We'll do the things we can do.
I know what it feels like
to be labeled a delinquent.
I can reform the education system.
In this unjust world,
education is most important.
To foster compassion,
parents, teachers, and
the people of the country
must be united in the heart.
Don't make me laugh!
Compassion huh?
Who are you?
Me?
Just a high school teacher.
A crooked money monger
pretending to be a do-gooder
have no right preaching
about education and compassion.
Is there something you'd like to say?
Miss Yamaguchi...
You're kidding...
Look.
It's Yamaguchi.
Yamaguchi!
What is she doing?
She's gonna get it.
My Lady...
Katayama!
Matsukata!
Let's go!
How dare you use my precious student
for your dirty money-making scheme.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop the act!
What you are is the leader of a drug ring.
I think you should stop now.
You're troubling everyone here.
Escort her outside.
I'm here with a major scoop.
We found something in the
Dream Associates' basement.
Look at this.
They're all drugs.
This place is the hub of a drug trade.
Drugs everywhere!
Thanks, Tsucchi.
Continue the broadcast.
Tsuchiya, good job.
Those reckless fools.
Why?
There's something else over here.
These men work for Mr. Kurose.
Look at what they have.
Guns!
Very dangerous.
You all should be careful.
Those men are probably armed too.
Please calm down, folks!
This is a mistake!
Let's get in there!
How could this happen?
You bitch...
Don't screw with me.
Showing your true colors now?
Get her.
Watch out!
Odagiri, why are you here?
I can't let you fight alone.
Odagiri!
This brat's gonna die!
Don't worry about me! Just get them!
Yankumi!
Crush them!
Stop it!
Stop!
Get your hands off our teacher!
You guys...
Who are you?
We're...
her students.
Teacher-pupil love, is it?
I don't want to hurt you.
Get out of here.
No frickin' way!
We're not gonna desert her!
She's our precious teacher!
We owe her everything!
You're up against all of us!
Yankumi taught us to fight
to protect what we cherish.
That's why
we'll fight you to protect her!
Stay away!
Stay away from these scum.
You're my precious students.
I'm not putting you in any more danger.
We can't just sit and watch you get beat up!
I said, stay away!
I'm not gonna let you
ruin your futures
for dirty lowlifes like them.
You guys are my dream.
Still want more?
Wait! Hey!
Come back!
Now, Mr. Kurose...
it's just you.
Kurose had a gun!
The police cannot move in.
Yamaguchi...
Move! Our teacher's inside!
Yankumi...
Yankumi?!
Miss Yamaguchi!
Everything I built
you just destroyed.
Everything you built was worthless anyway.
Did you say worthless?
Money means nothing when
you step on people to get it.
Stop acting like a saint!
Money is money.
Is it that important to you?
Society only trusts
those who have money.
Look at me.
The more money I made,
the more supporters I had.
With money,
I can have anything.
Nowadays, you sure can buy
most things with money.
But...
you can't move people's hearts.
Hearts?
Your henchmen left you, didn't they?
But not these guys.
Even with you and your gun,
they won't budge.
You're right.
Money is important.
But some things are more important.
Friends, family...
Working hard for them
and spending time with them.
That's happiness.
Such small happiness.
There's no difference!
Happiness is
being proud with the sun shining on your face.
Money can't buy it.
There're times you don't feel like laughing.
But don't give up.
Hang in there.
If you mess up, regret it.
Have the courage to start over.
Then you'll find happiness.
That's what my students do.
They were all like you before.
Hopeless outcasts...
They still get in trouble,
get fired from work and have money problems.
But they live with pride and dignity.
You know why?
They have something they cherish.
Friends that are connected in the heart.
Freeze!
Don't shoot!
Give him a chance.
To pay for his crime and start over.
Yankumi!
You guys...
You know...
You guys are lucky.
To have teacher like her...
Yankumi!
I'm okay.
Yamaguchi!
Takasugi...
You guys came?
Stop acting like a nut case.
You're a teacher.
Tsuchiya...
Thanks.
You guys are all...
my wonderful students.
That's my high school teacher.
Yankumi...
I have big shoes to fill.
I bet the director and principal are so mad.
I can't make excuses.
I'll have to apologize.
Hey...
Hi, Yankumi.
Minami! How are you?!
Okay.
I saw you on TV.
I'm glad you haven't changed.
Come on...
I remembered high school.
You made me feel like working harder.
Good for you.
I have to get to work. See ya.
Bye! Good luck!
Minami hasn't changed.
I know.
Noda!
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Probably the same as Minami.
I hit a wall at my job
but I saw you on TV yesterday.
I felt encouraged.
I wanted you to know.
Noda...
See ya.
You really are
a teacher we're proud of.
Bye! Good luck!
Uchiyama!
Minami and Noda came too?
Yeah.
You peas in a pod...
We're your students.
Your words cut straight to the gut.
I still think about them.
You do, huh...
You stay the you we know.
Uchiyama...
Off to another day at work.
You be cool.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's go.
Bye, Uchiyama!
Thanks!
Good morning.
Miss Yamaguchi!
I'm very sorry!
You're...
the pride of our school.
A teacher like you
so dedicated to her students
is a principal's joy.
Thank you.
What's happening?
The phones are ringing nonstop.
There're tons of email too.
The whole country was moved by you.
Our school achieved national fame.
We'll have more applicants next year.
All thanks to Miss Yamaguchi.
Bravo.
You're being too kind.
She's right.
Director.
For whatever reason,
putting students in such danger
shows your inexperience as a teacher.
Yes, ma'am.
You must do better from now.
It really was reckless of you.
One moment.
Timely magazine wants to do an article on you.
An article?
I wanna be in it too.
You can introduce your colleagues.
Wait a minute. Don't get so excited.
But it's a magazine article.
Miss Yamaguchi.
Don't get carried away.
Nobody must find out
about your family business.
I know.
Do you really?
Yes, I do.
I've had to repeat myself.
You're so persistent, Vice Principal.
- Principal.
- I know.
- You don't.
- I do.
It's your last day here.
Yes, thank you.
I heard you specifically requested
to be assigned here at Akado.
Did you find something?
Being a teacher isn't too bad.
I see.
Thank you.
Today is Mr. Odagiri's last day.
So...
we'll play Kick the Can to make memories.
Let's go!
To the field!
Where're you going?
Why not?!
Gotcha!
Where are they?
Miss Yamaguchi!
Gotcha!
Yankumi.
Thanks.
What?
Nothing.
Odagiri.
If anything's troubling you,
come back anytime.
I'm your teacher until I die.
Watch out, Yankumi!
"Yankumi"?
Did you call me Yankumi?
Let's run into the sunset!
So, what sunset?
Go for it!
The glory days of youth.
You guys, follow my lead!
Yukie Nakama
Kazuya Kamenashi
Katsuhisa Namase
Yuya Takaki (Hey! Say! JUMP)
Haruma Miura
Hideo Ishiguro
Junta Nakama (Kansai Johnny's Jr.)
Akito Kiriyama (Kansai Johnny's Jr.)
Shohei Miura
Yuta Tamamori (Johnny's Jr.)
Kento Kaku
Jingi Irie
Win Morisaki
Motoki Ochiai
Aya Hirayama
Aki Hoshino
Shinji Uchiyama
Tomohiro Waki
Ken Kaneko
Shun Oguri
Yuma Ishigaki
Hiroki Narimiya
Mocomichi Hayami
Teppei Koike
Keisuke Koide
Ikki Sawamura
Yoshihiko Hakamada
Riki Takeuchi
Mikihisa Azuma
Kyoko Enami
Ken Utsui
Original Story "Gokusen"
by Kozueko Morimoto,
published by SHUEISHA YOU comics
Screenplay by
Michiru Egashira, Yuko Matsuda
Music by Michiru Oshima
Theme Song by
Aqua Timez (EPIC Records)
Produced by Masatoshi Kato
Production Company: AX-ON Inc.
Planning & Managing Production: NTV
Directed by Toya Sato
2009 NTV, SHUEISHA, TOHO, Production Ogi,
J Storm, Yomiuri Shimbun, VAP, 28 NTVAffiliates