Let's split up.
"Yankumi"
Your call cannot be...
Where is he?
She never came back.
I don't know what happened
but you should tell Yankumi.
I don't wanna trouble her.
She's not my...
Teacher anymore?
She's not like that.
Do you have a place to go?
This was the only place, huh?
Kazama!
Ren!
Thank God.
Why are you running around
without telling us anything?
We were worried.
You should've called.
We're your friends, aren't we?
You're not alone, you know.
You're hurt.
I'm fine.
Kazama...
Why didn't you come to me?
Why?
Say something.
He didn't want to trouble you.
You'll go out of your way to help him.
That's why he didn't tell you.
Right?
Kazama...
In high school...
I caused you so much trouble.
Even now, after I graduated...
I was ashamed.
Listen... A teacher
welcomes trouble from her students.
But I'm not your student.
You...
are my precious student.
Right now, I'm in charge of this class.
But you guys who graduated
and students from other schools...
Are all my precious students.
And you're not alone.
Not just them.
Everyone else from 3D
was looking for you.
Sorry.
You guys...
I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
So sorry...
I...
found this sweet job through a friend.
All I had to do was
make a delivery as instructed.
But something was odd.
Over here.
Open it.
Yes.
Open the box.
Put it in the car.
I'm sorry.
You klutz!
This is something bad, isn't it?
I'm quitting.
I didn't realize
what I was delivering.
You want money, right?
You gotta do "something bad"
to make 30,000 yen a night.
It's too late.
You abetted a crime.
Just do as you're told.
Mr. Terada.
All right.
The cops are coming.
I was scared and ashamed.
I didn't know what to do.
Why did you accept the job?
I wanted money.
Money?
Once I started working,
I thought I could support my sister.
But my salary's so low...
That's why
I jumped at the opportunity.
I was an idiot.
Listen, Kazama.
Trying to make money isn't bad.
But don't be fooled by quick easy money.
Money is important.
But it's not everything.
Don't ever forget that.
You guys too.
Okay.
You can stay at my house for a while.
Yankumi is amazing.
I've never known a teacher like her.
She hasn't changed.
Still no sex appeal.
Yankumi is...
still Yankumi.
Sorry to get you involved.
Whatever.
I'll see you.
Odagiri.
You seem troubled too.
Everything's cool...
Okay.
My Lady, this guy Terada...
You were right.
He's a drug dealer.
So it's true.
He avoids getting caught
by making the greenhorns deliver the dope.
The bastard.
Enticing innocent guys with money
and involving them in crime...
But Kumiko...
There's a ringleader.
Ringleader?
Him.
Kentaro Kurose.
He uses his success
and legit company as a front
for his drug business.
He wants power and position
to make more money.
A crook trying to become a politician...
"From failure to success"
Unforgivable.
Where're you off to alone?
I don't want to interfere with
what you do for your students
but this time is different.
You're risking your job as a teacher.
You sure about this?
I can't ignore these bastards
who tried to take advantage
of my precious student.
Kumiko!
I taught my students a few things.
Don't lie.
Live with pride and dignity.
That's why
I can't pretend not to know
what Kurose truly is.
I see.
We have a problem.
Those guys are gone.
This is it.
It's huge.
We should find some evidence here.
Yeah, let's nail those jerks.
How do we get inside?
The security looks tough.
What's that?
"Kurose Campaign Rally"
Campaign rally?
Let's go to the back.
Ogata, what are you doing?
Where are you?
At the ringleader's.
What?
Kentaro Kurose, right?
You idiot! Come back!
That car!
Now.
Hello?
Those reckless fools.
Odagiri...
Hop on.
"Math class today: Study period"
Weird... Yamaguchi took the day off.
Odagiri too. Strange huh.
Do you think something
happened with Kazama?
Kurose is running for office...
We're at Kurose's campaign rally.
Yankumi...
Ryu!
Tsucchi...
Tsuchiya, what are you doing here?
Working. Assistant cameraman.
Yeah?
I still have a lot to learn.
We'll fill you in later.
Let's go.
Kurose's campaign rally is about to begin.
Many supporters have gathered here.
Was that?
Why is she there?
Wasn't that Miss Yamaguchi and Odagiri?
I saw them too.
That's not possible.
They're both sick today.
The principal's right.
It wasn't them.
Odagiri's late.
You are late.
No drugs anywhere.
Maybe he keeps them somewhere else.
Where are we?
We're lost.
Is Kurose really the ringleader?
Hide!
That's him.
Kentaro Kurose's campaign
rally is about to begin.
The IT giant is running for
a seat in the Lower House.
This is a live broadcast.
Kurose! Kurose!
Where did they go?
It's starting.
There's nothing.
It's the box.
Open the box.
Ren!
What is it?
There it is.
Then all these boxes?
Now we have proof.
What're you doing there?!
Kazama!
You shouldn't be here.
Now I can't let you leave.
I'm happy to see you all here today.
Thank you for coming.
I stepped off the path
during high school and
was even arrested by the police.
But now, thanks to your
and many people's support,
I've found my place in society.
Kids should keep their noses out.
Yankumi!
You guys okay?
This was stupid of you.
Sorry.
We almost died.
I almost peed in my pants.
A society where youth can dream.
Catch the dream.
Kurose... You're unforgivable.
I'll handle things from here.
What're you talking about?!
I can't put you guys in any more danger.
But...
Odagiri, take care of them.
Yankumi!
Why'd you let her go?!
We can't just leave her!
We'll do the things we can do.
I know what it feels like
to be labeled a delinquent.
I can reform the education system.
In this unjust world,
education is most important.
To foster compassion,
parents, teachers, and
the people of the country
must be united in the heart.
Don't make me laugh!
Compassion huh?
Who are you?
Me?
Just a high school teacher.
A crooked money monger
pretending to be a do-gooder
have no right preaching
about education and compassion.
Is there something you'd like to say?
Miss Yamaguchi...
You're kidding...
Look.
It's Yamaguchi.
Yamaguchi!
What is she doing?
She's gonna get it.
My Lady...
Katayama!
Matsukata!
Let's go!
How dare you use my precious student
for your dirty money-making scheme.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop the act!
What you are is the leader of a drug ring.
I think you should stop now.
You're troubling everyone here.
Escort her outside.
I'm here with a major scoop.
We found something in the
Dream Associates' basement.
Look at this.
They're all drugs.
This place is the hub of a drug trade.
Drugs everywhere!
Thanks, Tsucchi.
Continue the broadcast.
Tsuchiya, good job.
Those reckless fools.
Why?
There's something else over here.
These men work for Mr. Kurose.
Look at what they have.
Guns!
Very dangerous.
You all should be careful.
Those men are probably armed too.
Please calm down, folks!
This is a mistake!
Let's get in there!
How could this happen?
You bitch...
Don't screw with me.
Showing your true colors now?
Get her.
Watch out!
Odagiri, why are you here?
I can't let you fight alone.
Odagiri!
This brat's gonna die!
Don't worry about me! Just get them!
Yankumi!
Crush them!
Stop it!
Stop!
Get your hands off our teacher!
You guys...
Who are you?
We're...
her students.
Teacher-pupil love, is it?
I don't want to hurt you.
Get out of here.
No frickin' way!
We're not gonna desert her!
She's our precious teacher!
We owe her everything!
You're up against all of us!
Yankumi taught us to fight
to protect what we cherish.
That's why
we'll fight you to protect her!
Stay away!
Stay away from these scum.
You're my precious students.
I'm not putting you in any more danger.
We can't just sit and watch you get beat up!
I said, stay away!
I'm not gonna let you
ruin your futures
for dirty lowlifes like them.
You guys are my dream.
Still want more?
Wait! Hey!
Come back!
Now, Mr. Kurose...
it's just you.
Kurose had a gun!
The police cannot move in.
Yamaguchi...
Move! Our teacher's inside!
Yankumi...
Yankumi?!
Miss Yamaguchi!
Everything I built
you just destroyed.
Everything you built was worthless anyway.
Did you say worthless?
Money means nothing when
you step on people to get it.
Stop acting like a saint!
Money is money.
Is it that important to you?
Society only trusts
those who have money.
Look at me.
The more money I made,
the more supporters I had.
With money,
I can have anything.
Nowadays, you sure can buy
most things with money.
But...
you can't move people's hearts.
Hearts?
Your henchmen left you, didn't they?
But not these guys.
Even with you and your gun,
they won't budge.
You're right.
Money is important.
But some things are more important.
Friends, family...
Working hard for them
and spending time with them.
That's happiness.
Such small happiness.
There's no difference!
Happiness is
being proud with the sun shining on your face.
Money can't buy it.
There're times you don't feel like laughing.
But don't give up.
Hang in there.
If you mess up, regret it.
Have the courage to start over.
Then you'll find happiness.
That's what my students do.
They were all like you before.
Hopeless outcasts...
They still get in trouble,
get fired from work and have money problems.
But they live with pride and dignity.
You know why?
They have something they cherish.
Friends that are connected in the heart.
Freeze!
Don't shoot!
Give him a chance.
To pay for his crime and start over.
Yankumi!
You guys...
You know...
You guys are lucky.
To have teacher like her...
Yankumi!
I'm okay.
Yamaguchi!
Takasugi...
You guys came?
Stop acting like a nut case.
You're a teacher.
Tsuchiya...
Thanks.
You guys are all...
my wonderful students.
That's my high school teacher.
Yankumi...
I have big shoes to fill.
I bet the director and principal are so mad.
I can't make excuses.
I'll have to apologize.
Hey...
Hi, Yankumi.
Minami! How are you?!
Okay.
I saw you on TV.
I'm glad you haven't changed.
Come on...
I remembered high school.
You made me feel like working harder.
Good for you.
I have to get to work. See ya.
Bye! Good luck!
Minami hasn't changed.
I know.
Noda!
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Probably the same as Minami.
I hit a wall at my job
but I saw you on TV yesterday.
I felt encouraged.
I wanted you to know.
Noda...
See ya.
You really are
a teacher we're proud of.
Bye! Good luck!
Uchiyama!
Minami and Noda came too?
Yeah.
You peas in a pod...
We're your students.
Your words cut straight to the gut.
I still think about them.
You do, huh...
You stay the you we know.
Uchiyama...
Off to another day at work.
You be cool.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's go.
Bye, Uchiyama!
Thanks!
Good morning.
Miss Yamaguchi!
I'm very sorry!
You're...
the pride of our school.
A teacher like you
so dedicated to her students
is a principal's joy.
Thank you.
What's happening?
The phones are ringing nonstop.
There're tons of email too.
The whole country was moved by you.
Our school achieved national fame.
We'll have more applicants next year.
All thanks to Miss Yamaguchi.
Bravo.
You're being too kind.
She's right.
Director.
For whatever reason,
putting students in such danger
shows your inexperience as a teacher.
Yes, ma'am.
You must do better from now.
It really was reckless of you.
One moment.
Timely magazine wants to do an article on you.
An article?
I wanna be in it too.
You can introduce your colleagues.
Wait a minute. Don't get so excited.
But it's a magazine article.
Miss Yamaguchi.
Don't get carried away.
Nobody must find out
about your family business.
I know.
Do you really?
Yes, I do.
I've had to repeat myself.
You're so persistent, Vice Principal.
- Principal.
- I know.
- You don't.
- I do.
It's your last day here.
Yes, thank you.
I heard you specifically requested
to be assigned here at Akado.
Did you find something?
Being a teacher isn't too bad.
I see.
Thank you.
Today is Mr. Odagiri's last day.
So...
we'll play Kick the Can to make memories.
Let's go!
To the field!
Where're you going?
Why not?!
Gotcha!
Where are they?
Miss Yamaguchi!
Gotcha!
Yankumi.
Thanks.
What?
Nothing.
Odagiri.
If anything's troubling you,
come back anytime.
I'm your teacher until I die.
Watch out, Yankumi!
"Yankumi"?
Did you call me Yankumi?
Let's run into the sunset!
So, what sunset?
Go for it!
The glory days of youth.
You guys, follow my lead!
Yukie Nakama
Kazuya Kamenashi
Katsuhisa Namase
Yuya Takaki (Hey! Say! JUMP)
Haruma Miura
Hideo Ishiguro
Junta Nakama (Kansai Johnny's Jr.)
Akito Kiriyama (Kansai Johnny's Jr.)
Shohei Miura
Yuta Tamamori (Johnny's Jr.)
Kento Kaku
Jingi Irie
Win Morisaki
Motoki Ochiai
Aya Hirayama
Aki Hoshino
Shinji Uchiyama
Tomohiro Waki
Ken Kaneko
Shun Oguri
Yuma Ishigaki
Hiroki Narimiya
Mocomichi Hayami
Teppei Koike
Keisuke Koide
Ikki Sawamura
Yoshihiko Hakamada
Riki Takeuchi
Mikihisa Azuma
Kyoko Enami
Ken Utsui
Original Story "Gokusen"
by Kozueko Morimoto,
published by SHUEISHA YOU comics
Screenplay by
Michiru Egashira, Yuko Matsuda
Music by Michiru Oshima
Theme Song by
Aqua Timez (EPIC Records)
Produced by Masatoshi Kato
Production Company: AX-ON Inc.
Planning & Managing Production: NTV
Directed by Toya Sato
2009 NTV, SHUEISHA, TOHO, Production Ogi,
J Storm, Yomiuri Shimbun, VAP, 28 NTVAffiliates