I want to be a good
wife and mother when I grow up.
I don't have a mom.
She passed away when I was 5.
That's why I don't have a mom
waiting for me when I come home.
When I grow up, I want to be a mom
who waits for her kids at home.
I want to be a good mom
and a good wife.
I want my help my husband and kids
to become leaders of Korea!
- Episode 1 -
Men nowadays...
...have a different definition of what
a good wife and mother is.
What kind of a wife and mother
do Korean men want now?
First of all, men want women
who are financially settled.
Because of the rising prices and housing costs, men want a double-income family.
Second of all...
...men want women who can increase assets through smart investments.
They also wanted
women to be up to date...
...on information regarding childrearing.
Thank you!
Moreover, they expect women to carry out the traditional role of a housewife.
They want women to be
a professional at home as well.
Don't watch it.
It's not that good.
I can't believe it's on the news now.
I know you're happy!
You got the scoop of the month with that modern good wife and mother article.
Here.
Maybe your wife is
a modern good wife and mother.
Maybe that's why you thought of
such a fine idea like that.
That's right.
Modern good wife and mother?
My wife?
Gosh, this is giving me a headache.
You can leave that here
and take this instead.
Okay.
Damn knockoff...
Get off, Eun-Suk.
Listen to your teacher
and don't talk during class.
Okay.
Guk-hee.
Hi.
Are you going to Gi-Suk's
kindergarten registration?
Of course!
A lot of people stand in line
since the day before.
Are you coming?
I'm going to send my housekeeper.
Call me if she does something wrong.
Sure, I will.
Hello.
Hi. Bye.
Because of this...
Mom cannot sleeping well, you know?
You're embarrassing me.
You have a horrible accent.
No, that's wrong.
Because...
Since we can't afford American tutors, you need to practice with me.
Go.
Where's my homework?
What do you think?
I'm good, aren't I?
The other kids told me that
their afterschool art teacher...
...made their projects for them.
Mine looks the worst.
But mine's much better than
the ones other moms made.
During art class...
Hello?
What?
Mom!
Uh-huh!
- I'll be there to pick up Gi-Suk.
- Gosh...
What are you going to do?
I'm going to be graded on this!
I have to pick up Gi-Suk...
I'll make sure it's ready for art class.
I promise!
Oh, my legs.
Today's the last payment, right?
You're finally going to be a homeowner.
Congratulations.
I've been losing sleep
because I'm excited.
Good job.
I heard that they're going to
open another market chain!
We're just a local market!
They're driving me out of business!
Can't you do something about that hair?
Let's make this work!
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll be there.
Now?
When he's acting like that?
Child Center
Hop on, Gi-Suk.
Where are we going?
Today's your kindergarten
registration day.
Why is everyone running?
Why?
Why are you running?
Hold on.
Gi-Suk, get off.
I have to run.
Watch my bike until I get back.
Stop it!
Get in a line!
Whew...I got a number!
Excuse me, but...
What's this?
3 bowls of jajangmyeon,
5 bowls of champon?
That's our lunch order.
I've been waiting for years
to get my kid in this kindergarten.
Help me!
Are you a double income household?
Yes, I make money too.
We have another slot for
double income households.
I need proof of employment
from you and your husband.
I work part-time,
so I don't have anything like that.
We'll post a notice if someone opts out.
These women and I got here
around the same time.
This isn't fair for me.
I know, but we don't have
any empty slots.
I can't just leave like this!
This isn't fair!
Public kindergartens
aren't supposed to do this!
I'm going to file a complaint!
What do you want me to do?
We didn't break any rules.
Do whatever you want.
I'm sorry!
Don't go!
Please, hear me out.
We don't have any money.
The kids are getting older,
but we don't even own a home.
I don't even have time
to take my wisdom tooth out...
...because I'm always working
or taking care of the house.
I really need my kid to go to
a public kindergarten.
I'm begging you.
But I can't help you.
Put me on the top of the list
if someone opts out.
I'll keep this cell phone if you don't.
I won't even go home.
Please? I'm begging you.
We don't have any money.
Gi-Suk!
Mom!
Let's go!
Why isn't she back from the restroom?
I have constipation.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little sensitive because of
the real estate contract.
It takes me forever in the restroom.
But this won't happen again.
I'm buying a house today.
This is all thanks to you.
My constipation will be gone
after I buy that house.
I'll work harder from now on.
Do you know how long
you've been gone?
I'm sorry,
I'll never leave my station again.
Mom!
M-M-Mom?
Did you lose your mom?
How?
In this market?
I'll help you find your mom.
Excuse me!
Has anyone lost their son?
Cut it out!
He looks exactly like you!
It's almost time for Eun-Suk's art class.
- Why is he still here?
- I don't know.
Jung-Chul!
Where is he?
I need him to make deliveries.
Jung-Chul!
I'll do it!
Huh?
I'm a cashier,
but I can make deliveries too.
I should help out when the
market needs help, right?
I'll do it.
Hold tight, Gi-Suk.
Eun-Suk!
Class is over!
I couldn't turn my homework in!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Eun-Suk.
I'll make sure that I finish your
science homework ahead of time.
Don't get mad.
Come on, Eun-Suk!
That's a good boy.
I love you!
I'm sorry.
You're on.
We're only going to play poker, okay?
Okay.
Myung-Pil, are you sure your wife's
okay with unexpected visitors?
She's always ready
when her husband needs her.
This is when a housewife
comes in handy.
We can go anytime we want.
Hello, Honey.
My co-workers and I are going to play poker at our house today...
...to congratulate me
for getting a reporter's reward.
There are going to be 4 people,
including me.
What?
Now?
No way!
I have to stay and clean the floor because the market owner's mad at me.
What?
You already have the food ready?
I have to pay the rest of
the payment for the house.
The house is a mess,
and we don't have anything to eat.
Honey, just do it
in someone else's house.
Not today, okay?
I'm begging you.
Okay, I'll be there in 30~40 minutes.
She says she'll be waiting.
Myung-Pil!
She's a good wife!
Are you making fun of me?
Mr. Yeom lives with a good wife.
His wife is an acupuncturist.
Don't you see that smile on his face?
I'm going to win all your money
if you make fun of me.
But you always lose!
Kyung Guk-Hee!
You're going to be a homeowner today!
I think I'll be about 20 minutes late.
Can you wait for me?
I'll be there as soon as we can!
Take your time!
What?
The homeowner wants
to see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow at 6?
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Stop goofing around, Eun-Suk!
Take the trash out with Gi-Suk!
Make sure you throw it away
in the trash bag!
Hurry! Take your brother with you!
Where are you?
Near the district office.
I'll be there soon.
What?
Good evening!
Honey!
Hi!
I'm so sorry about making you nosebleed while cooking for us.
Look at all the food!
I feel bad making you cook all these.
I told you to serve the leftovers!
Enjoy your meal!
Thank you!
Enjoy!
Are you expecting more guests?
No.
Hold on.
The door's unlocked.
The rib soup and
the clam soup costs $60.
You gave me a $1 instead of a $10 bill.
You owe me $9.
Okay, okay!
These ribs are good!
Let's eat!
I'll raise you by $10.
I fold.
Sorry, I won.
This is boring.
Let's go.
Already?
Would you like some beer?
No, I should go home.
Why, you should stay longer!
You're not going anywhere.
My secret weapon is coming.
Start dealing!
Unless it's a pretty woman or a rich man who's bad at gambling.
Why should we wait?
We'll see about that.
Start dealing!
It's here!
Long time no see, Guk-Hee.
I think it's been 4 months
since I last saw you.
Didn't you miss me?
Here you go.
She's my wife's friend,
and my best school friend.
Her name is Im Tae-Ran,
and she's a writer.
The three of us are from the
United University Singers.
You two are the same age?
Yes.
Same age?
Friend? Yeah right!
I never hung out with a loser like you.
Why? We don't look the same age?
Do I look that old?
Well, my job requires me
to pull a lot of all-nighters.
No, no!
I hate you!
I really hate you!
You mean Guk-Hee?
She's pretty.
She was Miss Myeongdong
when she was younger.
Here we go again.
Why are you a writer?
You should be a model!
Not everyone can become a model.
Barf!
Have a seat!
Okay.
You make me sick.
Would you like something to drink?
Sure.
Go away!
Take it easy.
This doesn't happen too often.
You can't help it.
I'll clean it up.
You can't help it?
Our apartment is the first one
to be designated...
...as earth-friendly by the district office!
You know how much
the real estate went up after that, right?
That's all thanks to me.
I tried my best to keep this place
clean because I had that in mind.
Yes, I know.
How can someone do this before
our real estate values go up again?
I'm sure it's the renters who did this!
The renters!
How embarrassing.
Wow!!
You actually made this?
In that short notice?
But you must be busy with work!
No, I just brought
what I had in my workroom.
That means you're always ready to cook.
You're perfect.
You write well, make good money,
are pretty and also smart.
On top of that, you can cook!
Wait, that means she's the modern good wife and mother in your article!
She can do everything!
Her? Yeah right.
What's this world coming to?
No, I'm not.
Look at Guk-Hee.
She wanted to be a good mother
and wife ever since she was little.
What about now?
She's a good wife and mother too...
...but the wife Myung-Pil wrote about needs to make a lot of money.
Just like you, a lot of money!
Drop dead, will you?
Honey, bring us some wineglasses.
Tae-Ran brought us expensive wine.
Guk-Hee, can you bring us some plates and chopsticks?
Okay.
I fold.
It's just Mr. Yeom and Tae-Ran now.
I'm torn.
I think he has a good hand.
What should I do?
Ten.
Ten more!
Is it a made hand?
A full house?
Okay, I fold.
Enjoy.
Yes! Tae-Ran won with a pair of 3!
You were bluffing?
You're such a good liar.
I won, thanks to you.
Don't you think Myung-Pil
is an alpha male?
He's very competitive.
There are single men here.
Don't favor the married man.
She's my fan!
Leave her alone!
A lot of girls liked me in college.
She was one of them.
Really?
Yes, for a short while.
But Myung-Pil wasn't interested in me.
He only wanted Guk-Hee.
Im Tae-Ran!
Why are you rubbing it in for?
What are you trying to say?
That you're better than me?
Do you want to show off?
Yes, you're better than me!
So don't come to my house anymore!
Don't ever show up in front of
me and my husband!
She's going to kill her!
I'm sorry.
Please stop hitting me.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I deserve this.
I'll never come here again.
Guk-Hee.
Guk-Hee!
Do you have anything else?
Wine needs to be served in wineglass.
Do you have any wineglass, Guk-Hee?
This is all we have in our house.
Okay, we'll use this for today.
I'll treat you with a wineglass next time.
Why don't we meet up
at her place next time?
She has a huge house she works in.
She's already a homeowner?
Myung-Pil, you must be jealous.
He's going to buy a house too.
Oh, yeah.
Did you sign the contract?
You can say that since we already signed the contract!
Tomorrow's the last payment.
Must've been tough.
No.
Unmarried people don't know...
...how great it is to move to a
bigger place with your family.
Good for you.
Remember, you were supposed to buy me a drink after you buy a house.
Ji-Young and I are waiting.
Sure! Come over tomorrow.
I'll show you the deed while we drink.
Attention everyone.
Some shameless residents have
disposed of their trash illegally.
These trashers pollute the earth.
They're murdering indirectly by polluting the earth our children grow up in...
...shortening their lives.
I'm going to dig through the trash
to find any receipt or picture...
...to see which house it is.
Eun-Suk, wake up.
Why?
Did you use the trash bag
when you took out the trash?
No, I didn't.
3 and 5.
That's 8 total.
I fold.
I'll raise you by 8 more.
He's going to fold
if someone bluffs again.
Whatever.
What are you doing?
Oh, my back itches.
Honey!
Yes?
Why don't we eat ramen?
Sure!
Five ramen!
I'll go and buy ramen.
No, it wasn't me!
What's going on?
Gotcha!
It's not me, it's not me!
It was the renters, all right.
They really did come, like you said.
It's like catching mice.
All you need to do is to wait
after setting the mousetrap.
What are we going to do with them?
Let's hand them to the Police.
Let's kick them out of the apartment.
We need to embarrass them in public.
This is driving me crazy.
How embarrassing.
I hate this!
Wait! It wasn't me!
Su-Duk doesn't belong here.
Who's Su-Duk?
Me.
You don't belong here?
I recognize you guys.
I heard that you beat your kids.
You tried to steal someone else's delivered package, right?
But...
You've been flirting with every man
you see after you got divorce.
You're too busy working in that
market to take care of your family.
I'm not surprised to see you here.
What?
I never flirted with men!
You don't know anything!
You can't talk to me that way!
Who do you think you are?
What do you mean,
I don't take care of my family?
You're wrong!
I didn't try to steal it!
I only took a look!
Guk-Hee!
Honey!
What are you doing here?
Did you enjoy your dinner?
You embarrassed me
in front of my friends!
You can't even take out the trash?
Why did you do that for?
I told Eun-Suk to do it,
but he didn't do it right.
Why did you make Eun-Suk do it?
You have a lot of free time in the house!
Why did you make him do it?
What do you mean,
I have a lot of free time?
This is all because you brought unexpected visitors!
Do you know how busy I was today?
I get scared every morning
because I have so much to do!
Don't tell me you have a lot to do!
You just can't handle it
because you're incompetent.
Do you know
what the Pareto principle is?
Do you?
Answer me.
It's the law of the vital few.
As long as you take care
of the important 20%...
...the rest won't be a problem.
If you're busy, prioritize your tasks and start with the most important ones.
Then you wouldn't have to
make your kid take out the trash!
If you want that to happen,
you need to use your brain!
You're always messing up
because you don't think!
Don't you have any
wrinkles on your brain?
Why can't you think?
Did you get botox on your brain?
Botox? On the brain?
How can you say that?
See?
You can't take constructive criticism!
You get offended after
taking words at their face value!
That's why I'm telling you that
you got botox on your brain!
Where's my propecia?
The hormone I take to prevent hair loss.
I know I left it here somewhere.
I know it was somewhere here.
You really don't know where it is?
It's right here.
Where?
Right in front of you.
I don't see it.
Here.
So there it was!
Thanks.
What are you doing?
I don't remember because
I got botox on my brain.
Are those the papers for the house?
You have them all, right?
I don't know.
Come on...
You make it sound as though you're buying this house on your own.
I get the chills whenever I think about how many fights I had with you...
...about buying the house.
You told me that we should buy a house, but you didn't let me do anything!
Here we go again.
Is it because I didn't let you
become a nutritionist?
I can't get a full-time job.
We needed to buy a house,
but we didn't have enough money.
It took longer because I had
to take so many part-time jobs.
You don't need to cremate me
after I die...
...because I've already been
shattered to pieces inside.
Oops!
Here we go again.
Hey Guk-Hee.
Why don't you take a shower?
Aren't you going to bed?
Go ahead without me.
Why?
You told me to take a shower.
Because you smelled like sweat.
It's been more than 8 months.
I better go to bed.
Hi!
We're going to buy a house!
It's a big house!
Let's go.
Gi-Suk! Be quiet!
I'm sorry.
It's okay, he's just being a kid.
Did you complete all the documents?
Hi!
Let's call this deal off.
I'll give you $1,000 fine
to terminate the contract.
Take this and let's call this deal off.
What?
Hold on.
What's wrong?
There are talks about developing
this neighborhood.
It's a rumor.
The government announced that there won't be any developments for now.
No one's going to believe that.
I have my resources.
I want $20,000 more
if you want the house.
$20,000?
Why won't we cover a wife
who became a star by blogging?
I think people will be interested
if we cover a celebrity.
Actress Choi Hye-Ran has a blog...
Sorry, it's for me.
Honey, I'm in a meeting.
I'll talk to you later.
I'll take my battery out.
We can't sit here and wait forever.
What do you want to do?
Just take this money.
Let's call the deal off.
I'm going to rip this contract.
Wait! Wait!
Then, I'll give you $20,000 more.
Hello?
What?
Okay.
I need more than $20,000.
If you want to buy, I want $60,000 more.
What?
Someone sold her house for $60,000 more than market value today.
I don't see any reason
not to do the same.
Hold on.
The government's sudden announcement for development...
...is bringing excitement to the
real estate market in Gyeonggi-do.
The apartment prices went up by thousands of dollars today.
Almost no one is selling.
Whoa!
Myung-Pil!
You've hit the jackpot!
Thank you.
Your wife's buying the house
today, right?
Someone from our office
just made bank.
Some places are worth $100,000
more than they used to be.
Your wife bought out
the best spot out there.
Wow, lucky you.
Guk-Hee!
Guk-hee!
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Show me the contract.
Let me look at it.
We just made bank!
We finally got lucky!
Why the long face?
What's wrong?
I couldn't buy it.
I didn't buy the house.
What?
Why didn't you buy it?
We already signed the contract.
All we need to do was
make the last payment.
She wanted $60,000 more on the spot.
$60,000? That's nothing!
The value went up
by $100,000 more in one day!
You should've bought it!
There you were!
I ran here as soon as I saw the news.
You're rich now.
It was perfect timing.
We're all set now.
Why the long faces?
What's wrong?
Did you do that because
you didn't want to live with me?
Is it because we decided to live
together after you buy a house?
She said the woman wanted
$60,000 more on the spot.
$60,000?
She should've given it to her!
Everything was all set for you?
Why is it so difficult for you to buy something that...
...everyone else seems to have?
Now that the rent deposit went up
by tens of thousands of dollars...
...the money you saved up
will only cover the rent.
When and how are you
going to buy a house now?
My son's been working hard
for 10 years...
...after graduating from
Seoul National University Law School.
Yet he doesn't even have a house.
Who would believe that?
My poor son has
nothing to show for himself.
Hello?
I just turned in my final draft.
You bought the house, right?
I'll see you and Guk-Hee at the
cart bar in front of your house.
Okay, Tae-Ran.
Was that Tae-Ran?
Yes.
I heard that she already
owns two houses.
She's so lucky.
I didn't know that this
was going to happen.
I was just unlucky.
Guess what?
Luck comes to those who deserve them.
Hello?
What?
Someone wants you to clean
the trash bin as punishment.
What is she talking about?
But Su-Duk didn't do it.
Why did you kick that for?
Who do you think is going to clean that?
I hate people who do that!
No wonder you steal
other people's things.
What did you just say?
Su-Duk only took a look!
You're right.
We don't have to work this hard.
Let's take a break.
It's a dead end.
I want to go to the beach.
Sounds nice.
It's the full moon.
I didn't know you can see
the moon from here.
It's been such a long time
since I last saw the moon.
I think it's been years.
I wonder why I never got
a chance to see the moon.
I don't have time to see the moon.
I'm too busy worrying about
what's for dinner...
...and how I'm going to
pay for my kids' tuitions.
I don't even time to take
a break during the day.
I guess that's life.
How about you?
Do you see the moon?
No...
I want to die.
Die? Why?
Is your husband cheating on you?
Maybe she's divorced.
Did your husband leave you?
I get it.
He left home because
he cheated on you.
Is he with another woman now?
I hate men like him.
Don't just sit here.
Go and drag him home.
You should do something about it.
Where are you going?
To my husband.
We have some problems in the house.
I'll go and check if my husband's okay.
Do you know what
Jubel said on marriage?
Marry a woman you should take
as a friend if she was a man?
If Guk-hee was a man,
I would never be friends with her.
Why? Because she's too dumb for me.
According to Jubel,
I married the wrong woman.
I thought it'd be okay because
she's pretty and easy to get along with.
But she's been such a
stumbling block to my life!
You're only saying that
because you're mad.
You're so lucky, Tae-Ran.
You have everything.
I should've married you instead!
Cheers!
Did you meet your husband?
You wanted to go to the beach, right?
Let's go to the beach.
Right now.
Let's go.
Let's go somewhere. Anywhere.
I'll go nuts if I don't.
At this hour?
Then I'll just go by myself.
Shall we?
Shall we go?
I can go, but you guys are...
Aren't you going to make
breakfast tomorrow?
I don't want to get kicked out.
We can come back before morning.
I'm leaving right now.
Anyone want to join me?
Me! I'll drive.
Let's go to Sokcho.
I want to go there.
Where did they go?
They left without working!
I, Gyung Guk-Hee, is at the beach!
I'm here!
Su-Duk is here too!
I came when I should be cooking!
Hello, beach.
I haven't seen you in 7 years.
The stars look so pretty.
Lying here makes me feel
as though I'm back in the good 'ol days.
When?
My good 'ol days.
When was that?
Hmm....I wonder when that was.
Probably when I was seventeen.
Why seventeen?
Because I had a dream back then.
I wanted to be a charity worker.
I wanted to help people.
I wanted to adopt, and help orphanages.
You can help me.
Help me be skinny like you
even after eating a lot.
I can't even visit my family
because I'm divorced.
The neighbors don't want to
hang out with me either.
It's been 4 years
since I lived like a hermit.
I don't think I can help anyone.
I wanted to become a stewardess.
If I became a stewardess...
...I could be taking my family
on a plane trip right now.
You can still get on a plane.
I can't afford it.
Then go somewhere in Korea
with your family.
My husband doesn't want
to go anywhere with me.
He says he's embarrassed
because I'm fat.
You don't look too bad.
How about you?
What did you want to be?
I wanted to become a good wife.
You can still do that.
Just do it.
You're right.
It's hard to be a good wife.
That's the hardest thing you can be.
Take me for an example.
I can't believe I'm beating my kid now.
Why is everyone so depressed?
I don't want to go home.
Help!
What was that?
Jang-Mi!
Isn't that Jang-Mi?
Hey...let her go...
If you don't....if you don't....
What?
Are you telling me that
the real pervert got away?
Yes, he looked scary.
He saved me.
You were overreacting.
How scary.
He's here.
You're going to protect us, right?
Sure!
You're very polite.
You don't have to use honorifics.
We're not that much older than you.
What?
I think you guys are much...
Yongteurim?
That's a singing club!
Are you in college?
Yes, I'm in college.
No way...
She really is in college.
Me too.
These two aren't.
I see.
Since we're all in college,
I'll just drop the honorifics.
Okay, except for these two.
Hold on.
What language is that?
Are you a stewardess?
My father is an ambassador in Germany.
You must've lived all over the world.
I lived overseas with my parents
until I was in 7th grade...
...but I've lived in Korea even since then.
Why were you in Korea?
Because I like my friend.
Lucky you.
You got to travel all over the world.
You must've been lonely living
by yourself at such a young age.
Why?
Do I have something on my face?
No one has ever said that to me before.
Let's drink.
Cheers!
Nice to meet you all.
I need to use the restroom.
I, I had a dream.
Although it had been
tattered and torn into rags
I treasured my dream inside my heart
At times, I had to withstand
The smirks they took behind my back.
I can take it because
I'm waiting for another day.
One of these days,
I will leap over that wall
And fly over the sky.
Even this heavy world
is not strong enough to bind me.
Join me and smile
with me on that last day.
Keep it up!
Keep it up! Keep it up!
Next, is Gyung Guk-Hee!
Gyung Guk-Hee!
One, two, three, four!
I know you've got
someone else on your mind
And I know it.
- Keep it up!
-  My intuitions are never wrong.
Do you know how worried I am?
If you know how I feel, then you
better not mess with me anymore.
I sometimes get tempted
from other fine men out there.
If you keep trying to lie to me,
Pretending as if you're the
only one capable of pulling this off,
Then I don't feel the need
to be loyal to you anymore.
I'll just leave you.
I didn't know when we were
taking out the trash.
You must've been pretty
rowdy in your heydays.
What?
Do you want me to bring more firewood?
Yes.
Hold on.
It's almost time to go home.
I don't want to go home.
I guess we have to.
I have to go and make breakfast.
Nothing will change.
Everyone will expect me to do everything, but no one will give us credit.
I won't have a day of rest in that house.
I guess I'll grow old like this.
My life's not going to change.
Why isn't the other girl back
from the restroom yet?
Right, she's been gone for a long time.
Maybe...
Maybe what?
Maybe she met that pervert again!
Yun-Shil, are you inside?
Yun-Shil...
I don't think she's here.
Let's look for her somewhere else.
Okay.
Yun-Shil!
Where are you?
Answer me!
Yun-Shil!
Where are you?
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil!
Answer me!
Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil...
Yun-shil!
What are we going to do?
We can't find her.
It's almost morning.
Su-Duk needs to go and make breakfast.
Oh, no...
Call her.
I don't know her number.
Do you?
No.
Wait, she called her cell phone with my phone because she couldn't find hers.
Really?
I found it!
It is me?
No.
I think it's from the restroom.
But we were here before.
I'm scared.
What if something goes wrong?
My husband will kill me if he finds out.
Who wanted to come here
in the first place?
Be quiet!
Maybe she fell asleep.
Let's go.
I'll take the lead.
I'll call her again.
I'm too scared.
Hurry. Come on.
Yun-Shil.
Yun-Shil!
Are you still here?
Are you sleeping?
Hey Yun-Shil.
Yun-Shil... Yun-Shil...