I can't live with you like this anymore.
Please grant me a divorce.
Honey, Honey, Honey...
Honey, please don't
ask me for a divorce.
Anything but that! No!
I'll try harder!
Please?
Where are you going?
Please don't go!
Nothing will change if I stay!
I'll try harder.
We'll soon buy a house,
and I'll be nicer to the kids.
I'll be nicer to you too.
I'll be nicer to your mom too.
Honey!
How? With what?
Can you be an acupuncturist
like Mr. Yeom's wife?
We don't love each other anymore,
and there's no way out!
We have nothing to look forward to!
Let me go!
Honey...
Acupuncturist? You?
An acupuncturist?
Yeah, do you know
anything about it?
Do you have any acupuncturist friends?
I heard it's easier to
become one overseas.
I heard there's a program shorter
than 6-years at an institute.
Tell me if you know anything about it.
Stop it, Guk-Hee!
Is becoming an acupuncturist
what you really want?
Would that change your life?
Why do you take your friend's side
when you don't side with yourself?
Have you ever thought
about what you want?
Is this what you really want?
- Episode 5 -
I already said everything
I wanted to say last night.
Then just hear me out this time.
Now I know why...
I don't have time to take
my wisdom tooth out...
Why I don't have time
to get a surgery for varix...
Why it's my fault that
we couldn't buy a house...
Why I'm devoted to my in-laws when I don't even attend my mom's memorial...
Why I'm trying to be an acupuncturist...
...when you're the one
who cheated on me.
Now I know where
everything went wrong.
The problem is, I'm always
the one who's doing something.
I can't take it anymore.
I won't do it.
If this keeps up...
...I'll work myself to death
to make more money...
...even after I become an acupuncturist.
One of these days,
I might have a third child.
If our kids don't get into
a top-notch university...
...then it'll be my fault as well.
I won't get to take my wisdom
teeth out even when I turn fifty.
Gyung Guk-Hee won't be around anymore...only a staggering woman.
The kind of a woman you mistreat
and Tae-Ran looks down on.
So?
Now it's your turn to put some effort.
I worked to build this family, and
you're the one who's tearing it apart.
You're the one who should
apologize and try harder.
No more cheating in my house.
If you do, you can't live
in our house anymore.
Our house? My house?
You're wrong.
It's my house.
We're living in that house
with the money I earned.
The kids?
We raised them with my money.
What did you do for us?
I think the money you
earned from the market...
...is enough to cover a refrigerator.
If you put it this way, you don't
own anything in that house.
I'm the one who worked
like a dog to earn money.
Stop trying to corner me.
I want a divorce.
I don't have anything else to say.
Do you think you'll be
happy with Tae-Ran?
Fine then.
Be my guest.
I'll get out.
I'll get out of that house...
since I only paid for a refrigerator.
Do whatever you want.
Let's go inside.
What's with the bag and the kids?
What happened?
I want to live here.
Please let me live here.
Mom...
Let's stay here for now.
Here? You want to live here?
I never stopped Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk from doing anything they wanted to do.
If you stop people from doing
what they want to do...
...it'll only make them
want to do it more.
So I told him to do
whatever he wants.
So you told him to live with her?
If that's what he wants,
then that's what I'll let him do.
And?
I'll have to wait.
After that, I'll put
everything back to its place.
I'll get my place back.
What if you don't get it back?
What if it doesn't work out?
Then I won't have any choice.
But things aren't much
different now either.
My husband wants a divorce.
What else can I do?
Nothing...except letting
him step all over you.
My last chance
is to let him live with her.
Even if we separate,
I'll decide when that'll be.
Even if we get a divorce,
I'll give it to him when I want to.
Hide and seek?
Who's it?
Dad.
We're going to give Dad
a hard time until he gives up.
I'm going to hide from Dad.
Can you hide with me?
Yes!
I'm good at playing hide and seek.
I won't let Dad find us.
When Dad says, 'I give up!'
that's when we go home!
Until then...
Fight on!
Kids!
I made ddukboki for you guys!
Thank you!
Enjoy.
Your kids are so lucky.
My mom beat my dad up
in front of my eyes.
Okay.
Remember the place
we had sushi last time?
It's next to the Sokcho beach.
See you there by nine.
Dress up.
I miss you.
I have to use the restroom.
Is this the woman?
Is this the best you can do?
You never told me about your debt.
You're having an affair.
You didn't run a construction
company like you told me you did.
There wasn't an ounce of
truth in anything you said!
What?
Why, I ought to...
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Are you crazy?
Yun-Shil...
What's wrong?
What's bothering you?
The man who attacked me that night...
I don't know who...why...
or what happened.
My dad thought his life was over when my mom passed away when I was five.
But as I grew up, he told me...
'Life begins right when you
think everything's over.'
That's what he believed in.
Let's take this one step
at a time...together.
'Go ahead.'
'I'll stay out of your life. Go ahead.'
What was that about?
She's challenging me.
She doesn't think I can pull through.
She thinks we'll put an end
to this one of these days.
And?
Tae-Ran, I better go home
and hear what she wants to do.
Let's go.
Eun-Suk! Gi-Suk!
So? Where are you right now?
And the kids?
They're with me.
Don't worry, they're doing fine.
Let's get a divorce.
That'll take care of everything.
I'm not getting a divorce.
Then what?
I'll think about it if you still
like her after you live with her.
When will that be?
I don't know.
We'll see.
Hello? Hello?
Why are you outside?
I was on the phone.
What about you?
I was on the phone with my parents.
They were going to move
back to Korea this month...
...but they have to stay
longer in Germany.
I already put my place up for rent...
...so I can move in with my parents
when they come back.
What are you going to do?
Mom!
Yes? What's wrong?
Why are you guys up?
They got up in the middle of the night.
They were looking for you.
These two princes can't sleep
because they woke up.
This big man can't sleep
because he's lonely.
And now you're up too.
Three men and two women
will be up tonight.
Go to that side.
You too.
I'll show you an exercise
you can do to go to sleep.
Repeat after me.
Wow, this is fun!
Guk-Hee!
Guk-hee! Why didn't you wake me up?
My socks...
They're all wet!
Why are my socks all wet?
I'm sure we had another hair dryer.
Where's the hair dryer?
Close this broken valve
before you go to bed.
If you don't, the bathroom
will be flooded in the morning.
Why won't you listen to me?
Hello?
Hey you!
None of the socks
and towels are dry!
Where's the hair dryer?
It's in the master bedroom.
No, the other one!
Keep looking.
Where is it?
Don't yell at me.
Oh, I left it in the multi-purpose room.
I put it in the container behind the door.
Gyung Guk-Hee!
Th...Thief!
Good morning.
Oh, hi.
Off to work?
Yes.
Be careful.
Is this all the money I have?
All your accounts are in your husband's name except for this one.
Oh, well.
I'll take $180.
Okay.
Fill this out, please.
Do you know who he is?
Yes, I know him very well.
What's that smell?
My husband doesn't like the smell
of fish, so I'm drying them here.
I'll give you some after they're dried.
I hate the smell of fish!
What now?
Hey!
Oh, no!
I was going to tell you
to be careful of the water gun.
Too late.
This is my house!
I enjoyed the peace
and tranquility here!
What the heck is going on?
Are you guys trying
to make me go postal?
I hate it! I hate it!
What do you take me for?
I'm Sniff!
I told you that I'll be standing
in front of your house.
Get your butt over here!
How much is this?
That'll be $1.
Bottoms up.
Cheer up!
This won't make me feel better.
I need chicken soup.
I'll buy you that later.
Thanks.
Oh yeah, I heard something
strange at the bank.
Let me go!
I don't have anything to talk about!
Fine, we'll talk on the way!
I'll just plop on the floor.
Wait! Why won't you trust me?
Why would I trust you?
How can anyone trust someone
who wants to kill his wife?
I'm not stupid.
No, just hear me out.
There's nothing to hear.
You were trying to run off with
your wife's life insurance, right?
Out of my way.
White pants got $1 million
from the insurance company.
$1 mil? Why him?
He signed up for an insurance policy Yun-Shil's name two months ago.
The man who tried to kill me
is with my husband.
My husband tried to kill me.
Let's report white pants to the police.
Everything will be taken care of...
...once you show up
and tell them what happened.
What if they don't believe us
like they did last time?
Yun-Shil's alive right now.
We don't have any proof.
All we have is her testimony.
What are we supposed to do then?
We need undeniable evidence.
Oh, I know!
A security camera!
I'm sure he has something in the safe.
He never told me his password.
Still, give these numbers a try.
3258... 7564...
What happened?
It wasn't Su-Duk!
The only thing I did was touch that...
What are we going to do?
The kids are coming!
The kids?
What are we going to do?
The veranda! The veranda!
What are you doing right now?
I'm Min Seung-Gi,
a promising young officer.
I have great, shocking news for you!
What? They broke in where?
Tell me what happened!
I'm going to ask you this one more time.
Why did you go inside that house?
Geez...
Hello?
Hey, it's me!
What now?
Excuse me, I have a call.
I'm in front of your house right now.
I'm going to plop down here
until you pay me for killing your wife!
What? Now?
Hey! Hey!
Mr. Kim Jo-Han?
Yes?
Let's go to your house.
What? Why?
To check if anything's missing.
No need to do that.
My kids called and told me
that they invited these people over.
They wanted to give them
a few pictures of their mother...
...because they're her friends.
My kids asked you to come, right?
Yes, that's right.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Good morning.
Tae-Ran?
What happened?
When did you get here?
You must really be tired nowadays.
I don't think you were
that drunk last night.
I brought you home last night.
Come on.
Enjoy your breakfast
before you go to work.
Try it.
Okay...
Is it good?
It's good!
Can I get a cup of water?
I've always dreamed of picking my husband's necktie as he's off to work.
Do you know what
I've always dreamed of?
To have a great woman
like you take care of me.
This is my dream come true.
When I first started going out with you,
I never knew we'd end up here.
At first, I wanted someone
I couldn't have a long time ago.
But now I know what I really want.
I'm tired of dating younger men, teaching them how to date...
...and then break up right
before getting married.
I know that it'll be hard and painful
for you to break your family...
I'm sure of this.
I won't quit in the middle
like Guk-Hee thinks.
I want to be your wife, officially.
Guk-Hee!
Good morning.
Tae-Ran?
Why were you in that room?
Where's Guk-Hee?
Mother, let me explain.
Guk-Hee?
Come in.
The door's unlocked.
Good morning.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night because I was afraid of burglars.
But then again,
the people in this family...
...are the husband and
mother-in-law of the burglar.
What?
I can't live with your family anymore.
Please move out.
What?
We need to talk.
Follow me.
These are the divorce papers.
I already stamped my seal on it.
It's your turn now.
Why would I give you a divorce for?
Guess what?
Things are turning out
the way you wanted it to.
It's driving me crazy.
My life is a mess, both
at work and at home.
That's probably what you wanted,
but one thing's sure now.
I can't live with you.
You can live with the women
with botox on their brains.
I'll live with Tae-Ran.
You can be robbers or burglars
with them if you want.
Let's live with the people
we want to live with.
Fine! Live with her!
I don't have a problem with that.
Did you get botox
on your brains again?
I can't live with another woman
without getting divorced!
You know how much
I hate being wishy-washy!
Let's put an end to this
and get on with our lives.
Thanks, I needed some paper towel.
Hey!
I have to go.
Bye.
Hello?
Hello.
I brought Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk home.
What?
Don't you know that it's the women
who drive men to do what they're doing?
Can't you do anything right?
No wonder Myung-Pil
finds peace elsewhere.
Do I have to do everything for you?
Anyways, don't ever get a divorce.
The kids are here.
Just do as I say, okay?
Mom, don't let him find you!
I see.
Okay, Mom.
What did your mom say?
She brought the kids home.
She's uncomfortable with
a situation like this.
She's an old woman.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of everything.
Why don't we eat at home?
I doubt your mom
had a good dinner.
Let's get food to go and eat home
with your mom and the kids.
Are you thinking about your kids?
They're nearby.
They'll be fine.
I'm worried.
I feel as though things
will get worse.
I believed that
I won't lose everything...
...but I feel as though
I might lose everything.
Grandma...Grandma...
Eun-Suk!
Why are you up?
Gi-Suk is acting weird.
Why?
What's wrong, Gi-Suk?
Gi-Suk! Do you have indigestion?
I'm home.
What's wrong with him?
Do you have a stomachache?
Let me take a look?
Are you okay?
Look how much he's sweating!
I better take him to the hospital!
Wait, the director of
Yeonil Hospital lives nearby.
He's a good friend of mine.
Do something! Now!
Hello? This is Tae-Ran.
He has mesenteric lymphadenitis.
You can say that his intestine
came down with a cold.
- What?
- I gave him medications.
Just rub his stomach.
He'll be fine in the morning.
Does that mean he doesn't
have to go to the hospital?
He'll be fine once
the fever goes down.
What a relief!
Gi-Suk is okay now!
By the way, he has hernia.
Hernia?
Gi-Suk has hernia?
Since it only shows up
when he's breathing...
...his parents might've overlooked it.
It's a very simple procedure
at an early stage.
Come to the hospital tomorrow.
We wouldn't have known
if it wasn't for you.
If you find it at an early stage,
we can treat it before it starts hurting.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
You should thank Tae-Ran instead.
Call me up if you need more help.
Thanks.
I still owe you a big one for
helping me write my paper last time.
I better get going now.
Goodbye.
Stay a little longer.
This scared you too.
It's too late in the night,
and I'm sure you're both tired.
You should rest.
I'll take you home.
Your mother's by herself.
I can go with the doctor.
Goodnight.
See you later.
So...what are you trying to do?
Are you going to marry Tae-Ran?
That's what I want to do.
What?
How can you think about
leaving your wife?
No way!
A lot of people get divorced nowadays.
Things have changed.
It's okay to meet new partners
after getting a divorce...
...unlike like your generation.
Even if I live to be my father's age,
I still have 40 more years left.
Remember how unhappy
your marriage was?
Do you want me to be unhappy
for the next 40 years too?
But still...what about the kids?
The kids need their mother!
You saw how great Tae-Ran is.
The kids will be brought up differently than they would be under Guk-Hee.
But I think it's for the best.
I put your school supplies in this bag.
Color your board nice and pretty, okay?
- Dad didn't find you yet, right?
- Okay.
Gi-Suk, did you ever see me lose in your preschool parent-child competition?
I never lose!
You can come over to see me whenever you want after telling Grandma.
What about Dad?
Not Dad.
Where's Grandma?
There she is!
Hi...
Hello?
It's me.
My mom decided to go along
with my decision.
Things aren't going the way
you want them to be.
I want a divorce.
Stamp that seal.
Just because your mother changed her mind doesn't mean I changed mine.
I see how it is.
Fine then.
I don't know what you want to find out...
...but let's do it until you
find out what you need to.
You won't regret it, right?
No.
Here.
You want a divorce?
No, Honey!
Don't leave Su-Duk!
Take a look at it!
A dieting trip?
Do you know how much
weight you gained...
...from hanging out
in that woman's house?
I told you to stay at home
and go on a diet!
Now that the kids are in a boarding school, you should go on a dieting trip.
No, Honey.
Anything but that.
You know how I hate seeing
women flock together in groups!
Stop going to that house!
And stop eating!
This dieting trip is your only option!
I think it's him!
Yes, it's him!
He's the one who attacked me!
Are you sure?
Yes! We got him in the camera!
Let me see.
Can we zoom in?
Can you please be quiet?
Come on, we found the man
who attacked Yun-Shil.
See?
He's the man who knocked
Yun-Shil unconscious.
We got the two of them on tape.
We did it!
You're right.
He's the white pants, and...
It's Sniff!
Sniff?
He's my husband...
Husband?
The man you divorced?
No, I didn't get a divorce.
I couldn't.
What am I going to do?
Does that mean Jang-Mi's
husband attacked Yun-Shil?
What's going on?
Do you know what I went through
to stay away from my husband?
Why is he here?
This is all your fault!
You brought him here!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
What are you doing?
Jang-Mi...
Get out! Get out!
I know where you're coming from, but...
Jang-Mi, let's talk.
Where's Yun-Shil?
Yun-Shil!
Yun-shil! Yun-Shil, where are you?
Where is she?
- Yun-Shil, where are you?
- Yun-shil, where are you?
Yun-Shil!
Did you find her?
No.
She's not up there either.
- Let's go this way.
- Okay.
Yun-Shil!
No, that's dangerous!
I have to move out of here.
I need to get out of here
as soon as I can.
What seems to be the matter?
That's none of your business.
I need to get out of here, fast.
I can tell you're in an emergency.
Look at your face!
You're sweating.
I don't know what the matter is,
but you can talk to me about it.
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it!
Honey!
Nam Jang-Mi!
Why, you...
I knew it would be you!
Why, I ought to...
The both of you! Get over here!
Come here!
No, it's not what you think it is...
Are you okay?
Yes...
Be strong, Yun-Shil.
We're here for you.
Let's drive out Nam Jang-Mi,
the evil divorcee!
Hang on.
It's a misunderstanding.
Everyone!
Stop it!
You've gone too far!
They're going to get it!
What's that noise?
Calm down!
Hey! Stop right here!
Who do they think they are?
Just because we're not homeowners doesn't mean they can look down on us!
Oh, no...
You have a scar
on your pretty face.
I'll get more if Sniff finds me.
We're all good people...
...but how can they do this to us
just because we're different.
You're right.
Why do they judge us
and treat us like weirdoes...
...without getting the facts straight?
Jang-Mi is not boy crazy.
If a man touches her, she'd say,
'I hate it when a stranger touches me!
The same goes for you.
You're too timid to steal from anyone.
This makes me mad. Really mad.
They're so selfish!
Why are you laughing?
What's so funny?
Take a look at yourselves.
Look at your hair!
How about me?
Especially you.
You were awesome when you slammed that megaphone on the floor.
That felt great.
What about me?
Su-duk...You were really cute, especially when you threw that shoe at her.
You're praising yourselves.
Maybe I won't move out.
What about your husband?
I'm scared of him,
but I'm not alone.
As long as you're here with me.
Me too. I'll stay too.
I'll be here with you too.
My husband never listens to me.
He placed our kids
in the boarding house...
...even though my kids
and I were against it.
My kids aren't even home anymore.
I'll stay with you guys.
What about the dieting trip?
Why would I want to do that for?
He can go instead
if he wants to be skinny.
Ow, ow...I'm aching all over.
Really?
Looks sexy..
Maybe I should start
putting my hair up too.
Ouch...
I think you overstrained yourself.
Maybe you really need
that chicken soup.
Yes, I think so too.
You should address me with honorifics.
I'm five years older than you.
Once a friend, always a friend.
That's my motto.
Why do you want to be my friend?
Do you like this chaos?
Yes, I do.
Where else can I experience
something so spectacular at my age?
I think I'll be bored
if I stop coming here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hello?
It's me, Tae-Ran.
Do you want to meet up today?
Welcome.
A woman is expecting me.
She said she'll be here waiting.
We don't have any tables
with just one female guest.
Can you get me a seat?
Sure, right his way.
You should have some too.
Okay.
This is so good.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Yes, but I wish this was spicier.
I'll get some hot sauce.
Excuse me!
Oh, my gosh!
No, stay seated.
Guk-Hee!
Was this your plan?
You told me not to regret it.
Is this what you were thinking?
It was supposed to be just
you, me, and Tae-Ran.
The kids and my mother
somehow ended up coming.
See?
This hurts.
Everyone will get hurt.
We know where this is leading to.
Why are you making
it hard on everyone?
Stamp your seal.
Do it!
Stamp your seal!
Let's not hurt ourselves anymore.
I see.
Is that what you really want?
Fine, I'll do it!
I'll do whatever you ask me to.
Have fun!