- Episode 9 -
Did you bring all the paperwork?
And your ID?
- I brought them.
- Let's go.
Hey...
What?
Guk-Hee?
She has a million dollars
in her bank account?
Are you 100% positive?
Okay, bye.
Yun-Shil couldn't have opened a bank account because she's officially dead.
One million dollars, here I come.
Wait a minute...
Do you consent to the divorce,
Ms. Gyung Guk-Hee?
Yes.
Do you consent to the divorce,
Mr. Hur Myung-Pil?
Huh?
- What are you doing?
- Do you consent to divorce?
Do you?
I'm not sure.
What?
You don't want a divorce?
I'm...not sure!
Are you out of your mind?
I can't help it.
I'm not sure!
I'm not sure about what I want either.
Let me think about it.
Hey! Hur Myung-Pil!
Are you joking?
This is ridiculous!
You're the one who wanted a divorce.
Yeah, I know... but I want
more time to think about it.
Don't you agree, sir?
You should've thought about it at home.
See? You're nuts.
- I couldn't think at home...
- Both of you, get out! Now!
You're crazy.
1 million dollars...
Guk-Hee...
- Guk-Hee...
- Let go.
- I had my reasons.
- Reasons?
Guk-Hee!
The reason is...
Gugi-dong, please.
Haven't you heard that saying?
Even a foolish man can come up with one good thought after 1,000 thoughts.
- So we should...
- Stop quibbling! Save it for Tae-Ran!
Hey, we're going the wrong way.
Hey, mister.
This is a taser.
Don't do anything stupid.
- Where are we going?
- You'll find out.
Ms. Guk-Hee.
- $ 1 million...
- What?
That's how much you have.
Guk-Hee, you need to wire the money.
- I don't know my PIN.
- Did you forget?
You can change it
with a photo ID and seal.
I don't have my seal with me.
- Aim it at me.
- Whatever.
Aim it at me.
Don't be stubborn.
Forget it. Don't think I'll be grateful.
Just aim it at me.
Are you crazy?
Aim it at me, or else!
I don't need your help!
Let go.
Aim it at me.
Hey...let go.
- Let's get the seal.
- Aim it at me.
- Hurry.
- Fine, I will.
- Sir?
- Yes?
May I see your hand?
Sorry, you can go now.
- Where should we go?
- This way!
Hey!
What's going on?
Wait a minute!
- Hurry up!
- I think it's this way!
Hang on...
They're fast as lightning.
Where did they go?
Sheesh...
- He should be gone by now, right?
- Probably.
Why do you have so much money?
- None of your business.
- Tell me.
- Huh?
- Huh? What's going on?
Oh, no!
- Excuse me!
- Excuse me, open up.
- Oh, no! Excuse me...
- Oh, no...
I can't see.
- Ow!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. What's going on?
- Excuse me...
- Ow!
I knew it was you as soon as
I accessed my bank account.
White Pants must be going bonkers.
Tell me how I can help you.
Oh, that supermarket? Okay.
Okay, bye.
Do you like me?
Are you crazy?
Isn't that why you wanted
to be tasered instead of me?
Weren't you trying to protect me?
I know you liked it
when I was hugging you tight.
What's with you?
Do you want to see go mad?
It's freezing...
Aren't we getting a divorce?
I want to look back on our marriage.
Don't. We have nothing
but bad memories.
What kind of a husband was I?
You were demanding, got mad
when I made a mistake...
...and always criticized me.
So cold...
Let's be honest.
You weren't perfect.
I can't help but compare you to other top-notched career women.
No, I was just average.
I wasn't lacking anything.
- Don't say that to me.
- It's so cold.
Keep this in mind.
I...so cold...
I would've given my husband courage even if he wasn't the best.
I would've loved my husband
even if he were handicapped.
This is how we're different.
I have no intentions of getting
back together with you...
...so let's get it over with.
Oh my...
You scared me!
I'm sorry, mister.
This guy has a lot of money,
so ask him for the fare.
I'm freezing.
Where are we?
How could he say
he doesn't know in court?
Has he suddenly realized
how dear you are?
How could he be so selfish?
Should I tell that sly fox?
What about you?
Do you regret your decision?
What in the world are you talking about?
Guk-Hee, don't back out
on your decision!
We can't criticize her for
having second-thoughts.
They're married.
You never know what'll happen.
Do you want Guk-Hee
to get back with him?
- How absurd!
- Stop it!
That's easy for you to say.
Please calm down.
I'm not going to get back with him.
I talked to Yun-Shil,
and I think she has a plan.
Just the thought of it makes me happy.
White Pants is going to be arrested soon.
Yun-Shil's plan is...
What is it?
- Ta-dah!
- Oh my eyes...
Wow!
This is...
It's a gift for you now that
you're officially mine.
Um...Tae-Ran.
This is...
This is nothing compared
to what you've done for me.
I forgot about all the difficult times.
Should we go somewhere to celebrate?
Tae-Ran...what about
having dinner at home?
But I'll cook for you.
There's nothing to eat at home.
Let's go grocery shopping.
Okay.
Yun-Shil's going to take
the money herself.
I wish we could see her.
She wants to come when the coast is clear. I'll tell her the locker number.
Hey, Yun-Shil. We put the money
in locker number 79.
Bye. Let's go.
Do you know how long
I've waited for this moment?
What moment?
You look happy.
- I guess it hasn't sunken in yet.
- What?
Will it hit you once the divorce papers have been processed?
You're completely clueless, aren't you?
- About what?
- Let's go grocery shopping.
We're hungry.
Let's go home and make dinner.
Hold on.
What do you mean, I'm clueless?
Uh..I think you should tell her, Myung-Pil.
I already told you!
I'm not going to write anymore!
Can you help me out?
Tae-Ran doesn't know we're not officially divorced. I'm dead if she finds out.
Please save me.
Then why didn't you divorce me?
Give me just one more week.
I won't ask for more.
Please don't say anything for a week.
Didn't you tell me a camel stores
water to cross the desert?
Why do I have to be
the water for your survival?
Why am I the one
always helping you out?
Okay, I'm the camel.
I'm sorry.
Can you please keep it
a secret for just one week?
Here comes Tae-Ran.
What do I have to know?
Beats me.
Take a guess.
- Let's go, Suk-Doo.
- Okay.
Myung-Pil, what don't I know?
How would I know
what she's talking about?
Her brain is injected with Botox.
I divorced her because
we couldn't carry on a conversation.
Tae-Ran, pick out a bottle of wine
while I go to the restroom.
- Guk-Hee.
- Yeah?
- I need to go to the restroom.
- Okay.
Go ahead.
What a close call.
Jeez...
I feel sorry for you.
Why are you so shameless?
- What?
- Why are you so wishy-washy?
I can't stand seeing you.
Why don't you act your age?
What the heck?
Keep your promise and
finalize the divorce in a week.
If you don't, I'll make sure you pay.
Hey!
Don't tell me what to do!
Are you going to hit me again?
In front of Tae-Ran?
What a jerk!
You're dead meat if I see you again!
You don't scare me.
Why that...
Bye!
Those bastards!
They already withdrew all that money?
How could they be so sneaky?
Those slimeballs...
Why I should...
Hello?
It's me, Yun-Shil.
Y-y-yeah...
- Why aren't you here?
- I'm here.
Where's the money? Did you make Guk-Hee withdraw the money?
Let's negotiate.
Get me a valid passport, and I'll give
you half of my life insurance policy.
- Deal?
- Fine.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Checking out your homepage?
- Yup.
- Wow, You have a lot of replies.
- I know.
- That's a nice picture.
- This one?
Yup.
- Guk-Hee.
- Yeah?
I have something to show you.
Okay.
Ta-dah!
- Turn your face.
- Lipstick...
Su-Duk!
How does she look?
I made some alterations.
You look so pretty!
You mean, this belonged to Su-Duk?
You look so pretty in fitted clothing.
- She's pretty.
- Really?
We should take pictures of her
and upload it online.
Who says everyone
has to be a size 0 or 2?
Let's show everyone that
sizes 6 or 8 can be beautiful too!
Let me make you more elegant
and fantastic. Let me see.
Turn this way. Look up!
What a nutcase! Did you really
say that in front of the judge?
I couldn't say I wanted
a divorce at that moment.
I wonder why?
I was on the hot seat.
Answer it.
Hello, Tae-Ran.
Did you finally submit your draft?
P-p-party?
O-o-of course we should
definitely celebrate.
Okay...bye, Tae-Ran.
Didn't you say you found
the perfect wife...
...after contemplating it
more than 1,000 times?
I'm going to give you some advice.
Snap out of it.
Don't be a two-timer.
Yummy.
What a relief.
Did you test-drive the car?
Why? You don't like it?
No...I'm just saving it.
Don't.
I should do something for you too.
Manage my paycheck. You can take allowance and pay the bills with it.
Use it as your allowance.
What?
I don't like it when wives
take the husbands' money.
One should spend one's
hard-earned money.
Spend your paycheck however you want.
Okay...
Myung-Pil... Myung-Pil...
- What?
- I'm...bored.
I see...should we go watch a movie?
Oh, I see...
Oh, that...of course, I know.
Myung-Pil!
Come here!
Wait a minute...Wait a sec, Tae-ran!
- What's wrong with you?
- Hang on.
- I'm tired.
- As if!
Tae-Ran!
Stay put. Come on!
Take it off.
What's wrong?
Do you have a problem?
Is there something you're not telling me?
Tomorrow, I'll find out
the ruling of the house.
I wonder if I can get the house...
Hey! We're going to go
buy a house right now!
It's a big house!
Let's go.
I need more than $20,000.
I want $60,000 more.
Why is it so hard to buy a house?
You take out the trash now?
Did you and Tae-Ran fight?
- Tomorrow's the ruling, right?
- Yup.
I wonder why I don't have a house
when I'm surrounded by houses.
I'm finally going to get
that house tomorrow.
Don't be disappointed if you can't.
- I'm going to appeal.
- Do you like going to court?
I'm just doing it my way.
No compromises.
I'm not going to
compromise with you either.
You have one week
to make up your mind.
Court
Gyung Guk-Hee
According to Article 565
Clause 1 of the Civil Code...
...when the buyer hands over money...
...in the name of contract fee
or security deposit...
...the seller has the right
to forfeit the contract...
...until it is carried out by paying a penalty of double the contract fee.
But in this case, Gyung Guk-Hee, the buyer, already paid the part payment...
...and brought the
remaining balance with her.
That means the buyer has
carried out the contract...
...which means the seller
cannot forfeit the contract.
Which means Cho Gyung-Soon, the seller, must carry out the contract.
Guk-Hee will cry if things don't work out.
What the heck am I doing here?
Should I just go?
I shouldn't be a two-timer.
Stop thinking... Guk-Hee...
Guk-Hee!
I can't believe it! I did it!
- That's great!
- You're so smart.
- Thanks, Suk-Doo.
- Guk-Hee, you're awesome.
Su-Duk...
You can smile again
It's happy days
You should forget
all the bad and never cry
It'll be sunny days
I wish you the best
My friends are all gone
Why did you leave me?
Why do you have to leave me too?
There were...
- Why?
- That's depressing!
Come out everyone!
Myung-Pil! Cheer up.
I'm not happy even though I have a trophy wife, imported car, golf clubs...
And I can use my
paycheck as an allowance.
- I don't want to go home.
- Have a drink and forget everything.
This is what you wanted.
She's going to kill me if I drink.
Fine then, you just worry.
I'll drink it.
I want to cry. I so want to cry...
Nice breeze and a full moon...
a perfect night for a date.
You're right.
Guk-Hee.
Um...here.
If you want, I can get the stars
and the moon for you.
This is all I can do for you right now,
but I'll eventually give you the world.
Suk-Doo, this is...
Guk-Hee...
Don't take it.
Just hold on to it.
Get off.
Let me park the car.
Why that!
Why that little...
I came here first.
Park somewhere else!
No, I'm going to park here.
I normally park here!
Why are you always so stubborn?
Don't give me advice!
Then don't pester Guk-Hee.
- That's between me and my wife.
- She's not your wife anymore.
You're unbelievable.
- Get out.
- Make me.
Fine, you want a piece of me?
Okay, you're dead meat!
- You...
- What the...
You... are...dead meat!
Why did you get into a car accident?
Were you trying to shoot a movie?
It seems like you're older...
Leave me alone,
I'm about to go bonkers!
Anyone who annoys me will pay!
- Myung-Pil.
- What?
I am young, so I don't have much.
You may not think I'm unreliable.
But I have a bright future
that I want to spend with Guk-Hee.
You may think it's corny, but I even want to get the stars and the moon for her.
I want to succeed and
give everything to Guk-Hee.
That's how much she means to me.
I love Guk-Hee.
Please let her go.
I heard your car got messed up.
Why are you both so immature?
He made you upset, so I...
I'm sorry.
I don't want you two to mingle.
Don't come here until
things settle down for me.
Hello?
This is Guk-Hee speaking.
The press?
Come to the Dongjak Bridge
on the 25th by 2:30 PM.
- Do you have plans?
- Yup.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yeah.
- I have an important engagement.
- Really?
I'm going to head off.
Get Sniff off your trail and
I'll see you at 3pm on the 25th...
...at the place you proposed to me.
Yun-Shil, I'll finally going to meet you.
Why isn't she coming?
Yun-Shil...
You're looking good.
- Passport first.
- No way. Show me the money.
Should I call the cops?
Fine, fine.
Were you trying to pull
a fast one without me?
My money!
It's my money!
- It's my money!
- It's mine!
Where is she?
Wait, why did she tell us
both to meet her here?
She wanted us to fight each other and...
We're the police.
We need your cooperation.
Everyone, here's the money
for your drinks!
You need to win, sir.
I can't believe they conned me.
Fine, we'll see who wins.
Your article didn't get selected again?
Do you want to make a deal with me?
Deal?
Find me a candidate to be a good wife.
Can you introduce me to Tae-Ran?
I'll leak a good story to you in return.
This is actually for the Financial department, but we can write it too.
Think about it.
Ms. Gyung Guk-Hee?
Hello, my name is Han Chang-Sup
from the Financial Department.
Oh, hi.
I wanted to help other people
get their home back but...
Can you blur me out because
I'm just a common housewife?
I know someone who works here too...
Ms. Gyung Guk-Hee's here with Mr. Han.
Your case was a hot topic.
Thanks to you,
there won't be any more victims.
Weren't you afraid to sue?
I was under a lot of pressure to buy
a house for the past 10 years.
I was steaming mad.
A lawsuit didn't intimidate me.
How did you prepare for the lawsuit?
I didn't have enough
money to buy a house.
I had to use my brain.
That's right, Botox on your brain.
Isn't that your wife?
What?
I looked up your website.
You wrote that you're not qualified
to be a good wife. Why not?
People have new expectations
for a good wife.
They want a woman who can
make money, buy a house...
...get green cards for their kids
and send them abroad.
Some even manage to stay in shape.
I can't do that.
Do you think it takes
money to be a good wife?
No, I don't think so.
Then what do you think
makes a good wife?
I'm still trying to find the answer.
I'll let you know once I find out.
Thanks.
Thanks for the interview.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
I didn't know you'd be here.
You seemed like the smart
Guk-Hee I once knew.
I thought I didn't change...
...but I don't know what happened
with my marriage life.
I may have become like you too.
I wouldn't have been able
to handle all that.
You're supposed to make
your final decision today.
If you're not ready, I'll wait until tonight.
I read an essay that had
a paragraph about marriage.
A woman asked who'll
make a better husband.
There were two men
who wanted to marry her.
One man said he'll get the
stars and the moon for her...
...and the other said
he'll do his best to love her.
The man who said he'll get the stars
and the moon was an immature idealist.
The man who said
he'll do his best was a realist.
Guess which one the writer chose?
The idealist who'll do everything.
No one can get the stars or the moon, but he'll do his best to keep his promise.
If he can't, he'd at least be sorry.
That's the kind of a husband
a woman needs.
I think Suk-Doo's like that.
I'm a realist who always
tries to find a way out.
I'm sorry I hesitated at court.
I'll let you go.
This week, we want to get
the housewives' opinion on...
...what a wise mother and good wife is.
Women should...
Let's rank what conditions
need to be met.
I can't believe you're here to see me.
You gave me coffee before.
Study hard after drinking this.
This isn't energizing.
It's no chicken soup.
You're not immature.
I'm sorry for what I said yesterday.
I know that you're being sincere.
You should come by the house.
I'll make you dinner.
I need to stretch.
I'll make you something good.
Thanks.
Thank you. Good-bye.
Bye.
Seoul Family Court
Attendance Date?
Weren't they divorced?
What's going on?
You're completely clueless, aren't you?
Let's go grocery shopping. We're hungry. Let's go home and make dinner.
What is this?
They didn't divorce?
Tae-Ran
You won't answer my call? Fine.
Please leave a message after the beep...
Wake up.
Wake up!
Fatso! Are you nuts?
Why I should!
Here, read this.
These are what I need you
to do to make me happy.
- What is it?
- Read it.
- Call me Cutie instead of Fatso?
- Yup.
Thank me when I make you
something to eat.
Do I have to thank you whenever I eat?
Of course.
- Get rid of the reflection chair?
- Yup.
Oh, that's right.
I already smashed the chair.
- Fatso, are you out of your mind?
- Why I ought to!
It's Cutie! Cutie!
- Can you hurry?
- Sure.
Hello?
What?
You didn't catch Kim Jo-Han?
No one was there.
Yes. Ma'am...
- Are you sure?
- Then suite 103 is in danger.
Why should I believe you?
They're after that house.
You need to go immediately!
Can you tell me who you are?
Don't do this to me.
I don't know anything!
Fine, fine, fine.
Then bring someone who does.
Guk-Hee!
Open up, Guk-Hee!
Open up! Now!
Where are you?
Hey sly fox!
Why are you here?
Where's Guk-Hee?
Why should I tell you?
- Tell me!
- Hey, be quiet!
Why are you always fighting?
You're so weird.
If you lay a finger on me,
you're going to pay for it!
- Whatever.
- Be quiet, shorty.
Hey!
Don't do that to her.
She's my wife!
Tie them up!
Tie me up separately!
Jang-Mi, my interview was great.
So there you are, Guk-Hee.
What are you doing?
Let go!
Why are you here?
You didn't get a divorce, right?
- What happened at court?
- Why are you asking me?
Is this what a married couple's like?
- You make me sick!
- What?
I don't believe this.
What do you think you're doing?
Hey, hey, hey! Be quiet!
- You always fight!
- You guys are so weird!
Why do you keep on bickering
whenever you meet?
Tape their mouths shut!
Guess what I did to my husband?
Hey, hey, hey! Come here.
How could you miss her?
Don't come near me!
Grab her!
Come here.
Get her!
Jang-Mi!
Hang on, why I ought to...
Why are you giving me a headache?
Jang-Mi!
Oh my... oh my!
My eye...
Jang-Mi!
What's the matter?
A hostage situation
took place at suite103.
What?
Myung-Pil...there's a murderer
at your wife's place!
- What?
- I heard someone died.
- Who died?
- Pardon me?
- Your wife...
- Guk-Hee?
Guk-Hee!
- Myung-Pil...
- Guk-Hee!
Guk-Hee, don't die!
I love you, Guk-Hee...
You were my one and only love!
I don't want to divorce you,
but I didn't have the nerve to tell you...
I can't live without you...
I'll die with you!
What are you doing?
Guk-Hee!
Guk-Hee! You're alive!
Tae-Ran?