Just hear me out!
Listen to me for once, will you?
Let me explain why I'm doing this.
Something horrible is going on!
Be quiet!
Ouch...
Come on...
Guk-Hee, are you okay?
Who is he?
You and your friends...
...always get stuck with scoundrels
like him whenever you go.
I got a phone call to come
in for the missing girl.
Honey, are you okay?
Honey?
You have a husband?
Who are you?
Oh...
I'm Guk-Hee's friend.
Friend?
What the heck?
Whose friend? Since when?
Honey, he's not a friend.
I don't have friends.
I met him at the beach,
but there's nothing between us.
You don't know anything!
Why did you punch him?
Tell him that you're sorry!
You were so rude to her.
I never would've guessed
that you're her husband.
What? Why, I ought to...
Guk-Hee! They want you inside!
Honey, are you okay?
Let me help you get up.
Don't get mad, Honey.
Stay calm, will you?
Apologize! Tell him that you're sorry.
I'm sorry!
Do it sincerely!
Forget it!
If I ever see you again,
you're going to get it!
Got that?
You tiny little prick!
Let go!
Honey! Honey...
Honey...
Guk-Hee! Come inside...
- Episode 3 -
Why didn't you call earlier?
The officers and the neighbors
were all worried about you.
Someone even accused me.
Anyways, I'm glad you're safe.
I love you.
It's my wife.
- Lee Yun-Shil?
- Yes.
I'm calling from the police station.
I have a few questions to ask
about your missing case.
You're Lee Yun-Shil, right?
Can I get your resident
ID number and your address?
Good, thank you.
Bye. Thank you for your cooperation.
I've always been an honest man.
Don't treat me like a criminal.
I'll go home and think hard about how you should be reprimanded for this.
Bye.
Honey, it's me.
Are you home?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
You're not in college, right?
Why did you lie to me?
Huh? I'm sorry,
but I have to go home.
Hey! Gyung Guk-Hee!
I'm sorry I did that.
Still, you shouldn't have punched
him without checking who he is.
I'm really sorry for lying, though.
Honey!
Get out!
I'm sorry.
Get out! Now!
Honey! Honey!
Open the door.
This isn't right.
Eun-Suk! Ki-Suk!
Honey! Honey!
Honey! You only need milk
from the store, right?
Okay.
Honey! I'm sorry!
Eun-Suk! Ki-Suk!
Can you hear me?
Ki-Suk! Eun-Suk!
Don't open the door
without my permission.
Go to your room.
Honey! This isn't right!
Honey, please open the door.
Why, I ought to...
I'm Myung-Hoon.
Is Eun-Suk home?
Hey! It's Myung-Hoon!
Is he your friend?
I'm here to return Eun-Suk's book!
He brought your book.
Hold on.
Mom!
I helped you because you helped me
get my cat out of the gutter.
Don't ask me for favors
like this anymore!
I won't. Thanks, Myung-Hoon.
Goodnight, Eun-Suk.
Bye.
I know that you're angry, but you shouldn't kick me out like this.
Where do you expect me
to go this late at night?
You're going too far.
The four of us went to the beach,
but one disappeared.
It was crazy, and I couldn't
even tell you about it.
I was scared to death.
Anyways, we got in touch with her.
She's okay.
It's all over now.
I think that man's so weird.
I can't believe he punched you.
Since you're the better man,
just let him go.
I'll tell him off, although I doubt
I'll ever see him again.
Are you okay?
Stop it!
What are we going to do?
Leave me alone!
Honey! Kids!
Wake up! Let's eat.
Honey...I'll pick out your tie.
You look great!
Do you want that instead?
Well, you look good in anything.
People will think you're
Eun-Suk's uncle...
...if you wear that for Eun-Suk's camp.
Honey, I know I picked this out,
but doesn't it look really good?
You can't tell that it's fake!
This knockoff looks like the real thing.
Let's have breakfast.
I made your favorite seaweed soup
and stir-fried potatoes.
Seaweed soup and stir-fried potatoes?
Do you think you can be
a good wife by good cooking?
I'm worn out and don't have
anything to look forward to in life.
I'm about to go postal because I can never get any rest from work or home!
I don't need stir-fried potatoes.
Just don't drive me crazy!
Who knows what I'll do
if you stoop any lower?
Understand?
Su-Duk!
You dodged!
Su-Duk will get a time-out.
I'll sit here for my time-out.
I'll never go to the police
station again, I promise!
What a shame!
Not only those women
didn't come home for the night...
...they had to go to the police station.
The other people will think
we're just like them.
I wonder why the tenants
won't stop making trouble.
Yes, but our biggest problem
is the divorcee!
I'll tell the homeowners not to give
rent to families with problems.
Good idea!
They'll ruin our neighborhood!
Keep an eye on your husband.
Make sure he doesn't
get bitten by a crazy dog.
Eun-Suk!
What happened to your face?
Did you fight with your friend?
Myung-Hoon's mom said that I can't
run for class president because of you!
Because of me?
Because you went to the police station!
Myung-Hoon's mom!
Is it true that Eun-Suk
can't run for class president?
It's a decision made by the PTA.
Let me explain.
The reason why I went to the police station is not because I broke the law.
Besides, Eun-Suk shouldn't be
punished for what I've done.
Let's go.
Hello?
Suk-Doo?
Park Suk-Doo?
Dead? Who's dead?
A dead body?
She's dead?
Oh, my Gosh...
They found her body about 3km
away from the beach we were in.
Oh, no...
This is a dream, right?
Honey!
Mom...
We need the kids to stay outside.
This can be too much
for them to handle.
I'll take them outside.
Kids, come with me.
Honey!
How can this happen?
Honey...
Ms. Lee Yun-Shil doesn't have any contacts on her paternal family.
She's an orphan.
I'm the only family she has.
Honey...
You were legally married 4 years ago.
What about the kids?
They're from my previous marriage.
I was always worried about her
because she's very emotional...
...but I never imagined
she'd really do this...
What do you mean?
She tried to commit suicide
in the past out of depression.
Suicide? Suicide?
Don't mind them.
They don't know my wife very well.
They're just neighbors.
Excuse me.
This is so dirty...
How can you be so nonchalant
all of a sudden when your wife's dead?
Aren't you sad?
Are you sure you didn't kill her?
What? How can you say that?
Calm down.
We can't be sure yet, so calm down.
Yun-Shil needs someone on her side.
Why does she need you on her side?
I'm her husband!
Get out.
Get out, please.
Get out! Get out!
No! You're acting weird!
Why, I ought to...
You're acting weird.
Get out of my way!
Did you just hit Su-Duk? Why?
Why I ought to...
Stop it!
What are you guys doing?
Do you think the white pants killed her?
Does that mean I was with a murderer?
Let's tell the police.
What are we going to tell them?
About the so-called phone call
with Yun-Shil, the bloody scarf...
...and that he was cheating on her.
The policemen here don't know that.
To be honest with you,
I won't want to take a part in this.
It's scary, and I already
have enough problems as it is.
I'm sure the police will help her.
Uh...the same goes for Su-Duk.
Su-Duk is just a housewife.
Su-Duk's job is to cook and
do the laundry. That's it.
Oh, it's time to make dinner.
Su-Duk needs to go and make dinner.
I better go before there's traffic.
I wish I had a friend like you.
Cheer up.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
If you need help,
I'll help you...as a friend.
I'm scared...
Su-Duk...
Oh, my gosh!
I'm sorry, Yun-Shil!
Hello?
Are you sleeping?
No.
Hold on.
Hello?
Are you sleeping?
I saw a ghost.
I'm scared.
Su-Duk can't sleep tonight.
I tried to let it slide, but I can't.
Now that I want to do something
about it, there's nothing I can do!
I hate it!
We need more information.
What should we do?
I don't know.
We're not the police or detectives.
There's nothing we can do.
We can't get someone
on white pants' trail!
We can't even dig through his house.
There's nothing we can do!
Dig though his house?
No wonder you couldn't reach me!
Come on, I came here during my lunch break because I was worried about you.
You go to your wife
when I need you the most.
I guess it's because you're married.
Tae-Ran...
...you can distinguish the difference between my obligations for my wife...
...and what I do voluntarily
for the person I love, right?
You're like a ray of light to me.
I haven't been this happy in a long time.
What happened?
Oh, no!
If I lose my work, I'll be dead!
Let me take a look.
I think it's the G worm virus.
What's that? What am I
supposed to do?
You'll have to call the repairman.
It'll take a while.
Do you need it right away?
But I need to turn this in by today!
The presentation is tomorrow!
As long as the platter is okay...
...I can recover the data
with the equipment I have.
Do it for me! Where's the equipment?
In my house.
What if I get hurt? I don't want to do it!
Su-Duk can't do it!
Don't ask Su-Duk!
Su-Duk will die if she falls.
I asked Suk-Doo for help.
I'm sure he'll find a way.
I took a break from tutoring.
Is that the house?
Someone can get on my back.
Who wants to get on?
You're going to give a piggy back ride?
I'm probably the lightest person here.
But you're wearing a skirt, remember?
Then...
What about Su-Duk?
I injured my seventh
cervical vertebra in the past.
Come over here.
Get on.
Hurry! Before someone gets here!
Come on, you're not making a movie!
Hurry up and get on!
We don't have much time.
We can recover the data, right?
I can't write 60,000 words all over again!
You know that too!
Remember what people
called me in college?
Brad Pitt?
The other one.
Hur the McGuyver?
Okay, come in!
Guk-Hee! Good luck!
Thanks.
Bye.
He's so cute.
I thought she worked at a bank.
How did she find the time
to decorate the house like this?
It must've been tough for her.
Look! This is hand-made!
This too!
This is the master bedroom.
It's the white pants' clothes.
Wow, they're all expensive clothes.
Really?
How come the women's
clothes all look cheap?
This used to be mine.
Do you think all the clothes
in this world are yours?
I threw this away!
I sewed the cuffs with
a purple thread. See?
You're right.
This used to me mine too.
That means she wore
clothes from the recycle bin.
I'll check if anyone's coming.
I'll go to the other room.
How nice!
3 pairs of white dress shoes?
Oh, my...
Why didn't she get herself
a new pair of shoes?
What's that?
It's Yun-Shil's diary.
She had an abortion.
Abortion? Why did she get an abortion?
Although she didn't give
birth to white pants' kids...
...she wanted to be
a good mother to them.
Yet he cheated on her!
I hate men like him!
We have trouble!
What's wrong?
T-T-The white pants is here!
Oh, no!
I'm getting out of here!
Hurry up!
Are you kidding me?
I'm going to leave you behind.
What's wrong?
You can't retrieve my file?
Remember what my nickname is?
Hur the McGuyver!
Thank you so much!
Do you want me to give you a massage?
Oh, my gosh...
Guk-Hee!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Guk-Hee! You have a delivery.
A delivery?
Yes, a delivery!
I see....thank you.
Bye.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh, no.
I've fallen head over heals for you,
and I'm happy about it.
How am I ever going to get over you?
You don't have to get over me.
You won't ever have to.
Honey...
What are you doing here at this hour?
I'm here to fix my computer.
Don't you have work?
I work morning shifts to
accommodate Eun-Suk's schedule.
I told you that three times already.
Oh yeah...
I'm here with my friends...
do you remember them?
I have work to do.
I need to concentrate.
Then...Let's go.
Let's go to my house.
You went to Seoul National
University Law School, right?
Tell us what you think
about this drawing.
Give us a call.
Bye.
Honey!
Yes?
I got you a new $1 phone.
It's really nice.
All we need to do is call them and
tell them that we're switching services.
Here you go.
Take care.
Did all three of you get
botox on your brains?
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Tae-Ran?
You must've been scared!
I'm sorry for laughing.
They were so funny.
Are all married women like that?
Guk-Hee fits in with them.
They look serious, but their
stories are all over the place.
I was worried about you.
Hur the McGuyver, Brad Pitt...
What am I going to do with you?
I now understand what you
were talking about at that bar cart.
Here you go.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Oh, my husband's acting strange.
I've never seen him at
our place at this hour.
Maybe he got fired.
In dramas, some men don't
tell their families they got fired.
He's a competent employee.
He's respected at work.
Yes, he looks like one.
Why?
Nothing.
What is it?
It's nothing serious, but
it was the way he looked at us.
I felt like he was
dissing his wife's friends.
Why?
We tried hard to explain what happened!
Don't you get it?
He wasn't even listening.
Am I wrong?
He seemed to be dissing you too.
Why would my husband
look down on me?
I think he's tired today.
He's not usually like this.
What did he mean by
getting botox on the brain?
He was talking about us, right?
Get botox on our brains? How?
It's just an inside joke.
Don't worry about it.
If there's wrong, then that's good news.
A divorcee like me can sense problems in other couples too.
Even if he looks down on you...
...you'll be fine as long as
he doesn't cheat on you.
He's not cheating on you, right?
He was with another woman
when we went to the beach, right?
You're right...
Is that what's going on?
No.
Do you guys do it at night?
Well...we have to work...
we're tired at night.
Let's read her diary.
You really do have
a problem with your husband!
If men don't do it at home,
then they do it elsewhere!
That's not true!
My husband will never do that!
Why are you getting mad at us?
He will never do that to me!
He doesn't look down on me,
and he doesn't cheat on me!
I know my husband,
and he'll never do that!
Thank you.
There aren't that many people
here because it's members-only.
I got you a membership card.
Come and get yourself
a drink anytime you want.
You need a break and some privacy.
And during that break, you can call me with this brand new cell phone.
When did you buy this?
I'm sorry, my number's already
on speed dial number one.
Do you know what comes to my mind whenever I look at you?
So this is what femme fatale is.
A woman who reads me
and understand me.
She's irresistible.
She's so seductive, I can't
draw myself away from her.
Femme fatale.
Do you know what comes to mind whenever I look at you?
So this is what homme fatale is.
He's nice, yet tough.
But he seems incomplete
without my tough.
He's so seductive, I can't
draw myself away from him.
Homme fatale.
I want to do whatever I can for you.
I've always had a crush on you,
and now you're with me.
I want to fill you up so
I won't have any regrets.
Mom!
Look at this!
This is a $180 eraser.
I got it from Dad.
Mom! Look at this pencil case!
Remember Jung-Guk?
His family owns a golf course.
He has one just like this!
What?
Honey, did you buy those for the kids?
What's this?
That's not what I got you!
Did you buy a new cell phone?
Why did you buy
something so expensive?
We don't have any money.
You don't even know what luxury is.
Beautiful luxuries can
touch the hearts of people.
You don't even have that notion.
You're so dry.
Luxury?
I know what luxury is.
I want designer's brands too,
but we don't have the money.
That's why I don't even
dream about getting one.
I didn't buy it with my own money.
I got it as a gift from an interviewee.
You should've told me!
From who?
You wouldn't know even if I told you.
Just wipe that flour off your face.
Satisfied?
I said, wipe that flour off your face!
It's still on?
Just go and wash your face! You're getting it on the cellphone...
I'm so sleepy...
You're having a tough time
nowadays, aren't you?
I was so sad when
I read Yun-Shil's diary.
Why would such a
hard-working person die?
Why didn't her husband
know about this?
Why is everyone having
such a tough time?
I guess that's life.
It's so sad.
To be honest with you,
it's been tough for me too.
At least I'm much
better off than Yun-Shil.
At least I have you.
You're such a good husband.
What was that about?
I only gave you a nudge.
You're overreacting.
I'm too busy with work.
I want to sleep.
How can you do this to me?
You've never done this to me before!
You're acting strange.
Let's just sleep. I'm tired.
Are you cheating on me?
Cheating on you?
Why are you accusing
me all of a sudden?
Did those women with botox on their brains tell you that I'm cheating?
Is that what you guys talk about?
Why do you want to hang out
with those losers?
Don't you have anything better to do?
What's wrong with you?
You don't know anything about them.
Why are you dissing them
without a good reason?
Without a good reason?
Do you want me to tell you why they're losers?
Why are the three women with botox on their brains hanging out together?
There's a woman who
wears used clothes...
...and refused to give birth in order
to raise someone else's kids.
Yet her husband cheated on her.
There must be another reason
why a poor woman like that is dead.
Do you just feel sorry for her?
Did it ever occur to you
that she may be incompetent?
Why wear used clothes when
you have money to buy new ones?
Why get an abortion when
you can be a good mother?
Why would her husband
cheat on her if she's attractive?
Sacrifice? No, she's just incompetent!
We have wrinkles on our
brains so we can think!
Not to drive ourselves into fantasy!
Understand?
They can't make progress
because they think that's sacrifice!
They're losers because
they think like that!
How...how can you say that?
Stop!
That's enough.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Good night!
I'm tired.
I never knew that's what
you thought about them.
What are you talking about?
Is that what you think about me too?
I bring used clothes and
used furniture home too.
I don't even think about
having a third child.
Is that because I'm incompetent?
If you cheat on me, does that mean
it's because I'm unattractive?
If that scares you,
then you should try harder.
Try harder! Make some progress!
You're wrong!
If we keep this up...
...you'll look down on me and cheat on me like Yun-Shil's husband did.
Then you'll blame it on me!
No way!
I won't let that happen!
You should change the way you think!
Don't laugh at me.
I'm Gyung Guk-Hee.
What about Gyung Guk-Hee?
I'm Gyung Guk-Hee,
the woman you wanted to marry.
I'm working hard to
make it through this life.
You don't have a reason to diss me.
The same goes for Yun-Shil.
It's the white pants
who's wrong, not Yun-Shil.
If she has been wronged,
then I will help her.
I'll do whatever I can to bring justice.
Mind your own business.
Don't look down on me!
Don't yell at me!
- Are you on drugs or something?
- Stop!
That's enough.
I don't want to talk
about it anymore. Let's eat.
Make sure you do that
camping exercise with Eun-Suk.
He's been looking forward
to this for a long time.
Come home by 4.
Good morning.
I'm here to bother you on a
peaceful Saturday morning.
The thing is, they're verified my alibi.
It was my friend, not I,
who went to Sokcho that night.
I proved that I have
nothing to do with Sokcho.
That is the reason why
I'd like to sue you for slandering.
I hope you're loaded.
Bye.
Did you see that?
Do you still think I'm looking
down on you for no reason?
Go and beg him.
Beg him, and make sure he changes
his mind by the end of the week.
Mom...
Let's go.
Hold on.
Can we talk? Are you by yourself?
I'm Yun-Shil.
Hello?
Yun-Shil?
Are you really Yun-Shil?
I don't believe you.
I'm Yun-Shil, the one said...
...being a good wife is
the hardest thing you can be.
It's hard to be a good wife.
That's the hardest thing you can be.
Yun-Shil?
Are you really Yun-Shil?
Are you alive?
Can you come over?
Don't tell anyone.
I'm in Sokcho.
Tae-Ran, do you know what you
can never hide in this world?
Sneezing, poverty,
ticklish, and....love?
My friends tell me that
I look happy nowadays.
My assistant asked me
if I won the lottery.
Let's go somewhere for the weekend.
One night two days.
How about it?
Aren't you tired?
Don't you need a break
for the weekend?
The best part about dating is
that you always feel rejuvenated.
I'm energized to the max.
Then, do you want to go to Sokcho instead of Yangpyeong?
There are mountains and the beach.
Okay! Sure thing!
You don't have to prepare anything!
I'll arrange everything
from the car to the place.
That's great!
I needed a man like you.
See you soon.
If Suk-Doo can drive, that'll be great.
You didn't tell anyone that
we're going to meet Yun-Shil, right?
Of course not.
Okay, my husband will be home soon.
I'll leave as soon as he gets here.
Bye.
Honey, the kids are waiting.
Where are you?
A workshop?
Mr. Yeom's wife is sick from a cold.
I have to go as his replacement.
Take care of Eun-Suk for me.
He's supposed to do a
camping exercise with his dad.
I can't replace you.
Don't mind other people's business,
and do it right.
That's your job!
My boss is coming! Bye!
Tae-Ran!
Myung-Pil!
Did you wait long?
Nope!
Shall we?
Let's go!
Eun-Suk...
Mom...Dad's not coming?
Why don't we do something
besides camping?
Why don't we make a sand castle
at the beach with Ki-Suk?
Yes!
Okay!
Good? Good!
I'll make a nice sand castle for you.
Hi!
Workshop?
Men who leave during weekends
usually have something to hide.
Hi.
We have more guests with us.
If Yun-Shil is alive,
then whose corpse was that?
I have a headache.
I hate this!
You didn't get a call from a ghost, right?
I'm glad she's alive.
I'm so glad.
Mom, I want ice cream.
Okay, let's go.
Myung-Pil!
There aren't any guests
named Lee Yun-Shil.
She should be here by now,
but she hasn't even called.
Maybe it was from a wrong number.
Are you sure we're supposed to
see her at the condo coffee shop?
This is the place.
Mom, I want to build a sand castle!
Me too!
Do you want to build one with me?
Yes!
We're at the beach.
Of course they should go see the beach.
I'll be with the kids. Call me.
Let's go.
Did I fall asleep?
Was I asleep for a long time?
Did your arms hurt?
Not at all!
I was happy to see you sleep like a baby.
I must feel relaxed when I'm with you.
I've been taking melatonin
for 3 years because of insomnia.
I haven't slept so soundly in a long time.
Do you want to go to our room?
I'll be your human melatonin.
Sure.
I haven't walked side by side
with a woman in a long time.
Then what about all those times
you walked with Guk-Hee?
What kind of a husband will want
to hold his wife by the shoulder?
We walk front and back.
The other men who are
watching us will say...
'How did he get a woman like her?'
You can say you're a trophy.
Trophy?
Does that mean I'm a trophy wife?
I thought you said
I'm the new good wife?
You'll be a new good wife...
...if someone takes that trophy
and gets a marriage license.
You're such a smooth talker.
Shall we get some beer?
Hey! Hey!
Finish what you're eating first.
I was just in a hurry!
The clerk told me that there's another coffee shop on the 7th floor too.
Maybe that's where Yun-Shil
might be right now.
Go upstairs.
I'll check on the kids first.
Hurry.
Tae-Ran!
Let's get out of here!
Why?
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Get in!
G-G-Guk-Hee is here?
Yes, it was Guk-Hee!
What do we do?
Excuse me. Sorry...
Did you find her?
It's 8th floor.
We need to go up one more floor.
It's okay! It's okay!
She didn't see us!