You should have some too.
Okay.
- Episode 6 -
This is so good.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Yes, but I wish this was spicier.
I'll get some hot sauce.
Excuse me!
Oh, my gosh!
No, stay seated.
Guk-Hee!
Was this your plan?
You told me not to regret it.
Is this what you were thinking?
It was supposed to be just
you, me, and Tae-Ran.
The kids and my mother
somehow ended up coming.
See? This hurts.
Everyone will get hurt.
We know where this is leading to.
Why are you making it
hard on everyone?
Stamp your seal. Do it!
Stamp your seal!
Don't hurt yourself anymore.
I see. Is that what you really want?
Fine, I'll do it!
I'll do whatever you ask me to.
Have fun!
So you stamped it for him? Why?
You're only doing your husband
and his lover a favor!
I was fuming when I saw them
eating affectionately...
...with my mother-in-law and kids.
I was definitely pissed off.
You should've tormented them instead!
Stop. You're not officially divorced yet...
...until you go to
family court with your husband.
- Just don't go.
- Yes, you have time to reverse it.
No, I don't want to be with those people who don't know what's important in life.
Really?
I'll be fine.
Su-Duk, do you have any bibimbab left?
I'm hungry.
Huh? I'll make it for you right now.
Do you know why
I wanted us to drink tequila?
It used to be a regular drink...
...but with the
Spanish distillation techniques...
...it was reborn into this awesome taste.
The same goes for me.
Through you, I feel like I'm a new man.
I was touched to see you pull through.
I know it was tough. Thanks.
I know it was difficult for you,
and I know that I hurt Guk-Hee.
Knowing the pain I've caused everyone, I'll value our life together even more.
I'll never let you regret
or fail ever again.
Cheers.
What's all this?
Have breakfast. I made it myself!
When did you make all this?
I can do so much now that I don't have to worry about my husband and kids.
You should take a break from all this.
That's not easy to do if you've
never taken a break before.
Hi! Everyone's already up!
- Wow, this looks good.
- Come follow me for a sec.
How annoying...
There were quite a few
second-hand items at the thrift shop.
Let's have tea and chat.
Tea? Just like when we were single?
That sounds great!
Should we all have coffee right now?
You're so excited, aren't you?
Do you think Guk-Hee
is enjoying herself?
Guk-Hee, are you really okay?
Of course she's not doing well.
She stamped her divorce papers yesterday.
I'm okay. Now that I'm single,
I'm going to live my life.
Why not? Don't you agree, Su-Duk?
Huh? Well...um...I'm with you!
Okay then, let's all eat. I'm hungry.
Okay.
We're late. We need to hurry.
Mom!
Hi.
How are you doing?
Eun-Suk, I got your broken
rollerblades fixed.
From now on, don't put on
your wrist guards backwards.
I don't do that anymore, Mom.
Did you have a nice dinner yesterday?
How can I eat in a situation like that?
I can't believe this.
How did this happen?
You have no one to blame but yourself.
Don't come to see the kids for awhile.
I'll take care of them until
everything settles down.
I think it's best for you.
Let's go.
Hang on.
I need to tell the kids what's
happening between their mom and dad.
Okay, listen to your mom.
Come here.
Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk, do you remember
the 'The Prince and the Pauper' story?
Yeah, the Prince and
the pauper trade places.
The Prince becomes the beggar,
and the beggar becomes the Prince.
I'm going to play that game with Tae-Ran.
We're going to trade places.
Tae-Ran's going to be your mom,
and I'm going to have fun.
You're so lucky, mom!
Even though I'm at a different house,
don't worry about a thing.
I'm just playing a fun game.
I'm going to have fun,
so I hope you have fun watching.
Just think of it as a fun game, okay?
Okay!
Who's the pauper?
Tae-ran, of course.
Wow, you're the Prince!
A good wife?
What did the sly fox do
to be a good wife?
Just because she makes a lot of money?
Just because she's tall
and has a nice body?
Those people emphasize measurable
things rather than sincerity.
Then what about us housewives?
It's not like we don't
want to earn money.
Honestly, we don't have the time.
Besides, what did
Guk-Hee do wrong?
It's not her fault
she couldn't buy a house.
No, it's because real estate
prices skyrocketed.
It was because she was unlucky.
I heard that luck comes
to those who deserve them.
I guess I don't.
My husband told me that I'm not
qualified to be a good wife.
He said we're all disqualified.
What? Disqualified?
Why? What are we disqualified?
Do you know how much
misery we have to put up with?
What more do they possibly want?
They expect a lot from us. They keep
on demanding and wanting more.
What do they want us to do?
We work day and night to take care
of our family, but all we get are criticisms!
We have feelings too!
We're always being hit left and right.
We have attitude.
I want to show them that!
I really want to show them what we got.
Girls, we have a problem!
He's looking at it, right?
Oh, no! He found it!
He's coming! We're busted!
My heart's shriveling away! Help!
We're busted. What should we do?
Do you think White Pants knows it's us?
Maybe.
Then what should we do?
We don't have much time
since he found out.
Let's file a police report.
Would you be okay?
Even though we have a footage
of White Pants and Sniff together...
...you need to go in person
to find hard evidence.
I'll go to the police station.
Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil, let's go to the police station
after I come back from the market.
Don't back down, okay?
Okay, see you later.
It's okay, Tae-Ran.
I have time later this afternoon.
Let's have lunch together.
Hey, I'll talk to you later.
How are you?
Good. And you?
Good, since you stamped
the divorce papers.
Are you happy?
Thanks to you.
Good for you.
Honey!
You better not change your mind.
We still have to go to court before
our divorce becomes official.
We have to talk about
alimony and the kids.
Don't change your mind, okay?
Oh, and by the way!
You should move.
It'll be uncomfortable to keep running
into each other if you live here.
You need to move.
Why do I have to move?
I have to live here because
of the kids' school!
You're going to start a new life anyway.
It's better to move on with your
life instead of lingering around.
It's best for you.
It's all for your best!
Hey!
What the?
Ouch! Ouch!
You were always like this to me!
You always demanded me
to do things for you!
I painstakingly did
everything for you!
You wanted a divorce after cheating
on me! Now you want me to move?!
Are you...are you nuts?
What are you looking at?
Do you want me to hit you again?
Don't mistreat me.
You're no longer my husband,
so stop bossing me around!
My heads going to fly
all the way to Jeju Island...
...if I let out the stress I endured
for the past 10 years from you!
I better not catch you again.
You'll be dead meat, got that?!
What the...what the...
sheesh...
I bet they're behind this.
It's over for you if I get caught.
You do know you killed my wife, right?
Bring the surveillance footage
from that house.
Do it!
Is anyone home?
Of course not.
I'll check this room first.
Ta-dah!
How interesting.
There's a kimchi fridge in the room...
Nothing here.
Where could it be?
Nothing here either.
I found it!
It's snowing in Tahiti.
Awkward, isn't it?
You're tumultuous, and I'm sensitive.
This is just like us.
I'm scared of you.
It's snowing in Tahiti.
Awkward things shouldn't be together.
Nam Jang-Mi!
He already sent Yun-Shil's
kids abroad to study.
Yeah, White Pants is meticulous.
Yun-Shil!
- Sheesh!
- Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil...Yun-Shil!
Where are you?
Yun-Shil!
Who was it? Who did this to you?
Tell me!
Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil!
Are you positive it was Sniff?
I had more than 10 missed calls.
I didn't answer because I didn't
recognize the number, but it was Sniff.
He knows that this is my house.
He used to be a detective.
He finds addresses and
phone numbers in no time.
He found criminals just by
sniffing around!
I'm busted.
I can't get away from him!
What should we do?
Her husband's going to drag her
back, and we lost our evidence.
We need the laptop back.
I'll go...
I'm going to settle things
with my husband.
I'll go.
Why's the bulb already out?
White Pants fainted?
Yes, he must've thought
I was a ghost.
It makes sense since he had her
killed and cremated.
You do look like a ghost, all pale.
She's right.
Then you didn't settle anything
with your husband, huh?
I was so shocked, I ran away.
Should I go back?
No, I have a better plan.
Honey...
(Turn Yourself In)
Honey...I'm sorry...I'm so sorry!
Honey...I'm sorry...I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry, honey!
Let go of me!
What? Turn yourself in?
Yeah! I have to turn myself in!
You're doing this to take all the
life insurance policy for yourself, huh?
No!
I saw a ghost.
My wife came back to haunt me!
Whatever.
Hey, I'm Sniff, you hear?
If you lie to me,
I'm going to kill you.
Hand me the money, got that?
Wait! Are you leaving?
- Don't go.
- I'm coming back tomorrow.
Don't go!
? March along, sing our song,
with the Army of the free. ?
(Police Station)
Wow, we did it!
Su-Duk made a difference.
We did it!
My husband won't even
believe what Su-Duk did.
This is great!
Why did I have to touch him, huh?
Are you okay, Yun-Shil?
It's complicated.
After all, he was your husband.
I wonder what happened to us.
You were probably
only married on paper.
Sniff was my husband, but I never imagined him doing such a thing.
We don't know each other.
How can we be a married?
I married out of love.
My husband told me that I'm the most beautiful person in the whole world.
He keeps making fun of
my weight after having kids.
Hey...thanks to what
happened today, I think I can...
I think I have courage now!
That's great. Let's go.
Oh Bong-Goo. Wake up.
I told you to wake up!
Hey fatso! I'm glad you're here.
I told you not to go to her house!
Fatso, you're...
I'm not a fatso!
Hey fatso, did you just yell at me?
Yes, I did. So?
How dare you!
I'm going to kill you!
Get up. Get up!
I'm not going to cook for you anymore!
Not until you apologize!
And once again, I'm not fatso.
I'm Kim Su-Duk!
Shove it.
Bong-Goo, I'm watching you!
Hello?
It's me, Jang-Mi.
Jang-Mi...long time no see.
You showed up on your own will.
Have a seat.
Yun-Shil's husband came clean.
What?
I never knew you'd do
such a horrendous thing.
I'm not going to hide anymore.
I'm not going to hide and
ruin my life over you anymore.
Keep this in mind.
You don't scare me anymore.
Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk!
Did you guys brush your teeth?
No.
You should brush your teeth
if you don't want your teeth to rot.
How was the science class presentation?
Did you keep your promise?
Yes, I was the first one to raise my hand.
Good.
Come in.
Have some coffee.
Why don't we live somewhere
like this for about a year?
It's a private school in England.
I think it'll be a good experience
for Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk.
Sounds great!
But I'll be fired if I take a year off.
Do you want to work there
for the rest of your life?
How can you be an office worker for the rest of your life? That sounds horrible.
They say that your last chance
to change jobs is at age forty.
You can start a business or do something more creative.
Take control of your life.
Doesn't that sound cool?
Yes...
I like this school.
The facilities are nice,
and it's not too far from the city.
That'll be good for the kids.
?Repeat after me.
Repeat after me. ?
?Repeat after me. This is great! ?
Tae-Ran, go inside.
Gi-Suk! Eun-Suk! It's time for bed.
Go brush your teeth.
Eun-Suk! Gi-Suk!
Eun-Suk...
Look what you're doing?
This is the reason why
I asked you to move!
What will the neighbors think?
I don't care what my neighbors think.
No wonder you're shameless.
I'm not the one who's shameless.
You're the one who's shameless
for making me see my kids like this.
There's no point in blaming me.
Face it. You're a loser.
You're just holding on because
you don't want to face the facts.
I'm asking you to move because
you're being pathetic.
Now that I'm out of that house,
I can be objective with you.
I can see who you really are.
You're a quibbler.
You think you're all that.
You disrespect other people.
Yet I defended you and cared for you...
...because you're my husband
and my children's father.
I'm not pathetic.
I'm living my life without you.
Do whatever you want.
Just remember that you don't
belong here anymore!
Mom, are you in pain?
Do you need a kiss?
Do you feel empty?
I...now see what I've lost.
I'm pretending to be strong,
but I know what's irreversible.
This is where everything started...
like a midsummer night's dream.
My husband and my mother-in-law always pointed out my mistakes.
I had tons of things to do at home.
I saved every penny I can,
but I couldn't buy that house.
So many things happened
to me since then.
It all started here with that moon.
Do you want to go back to
how things used to be?
No.
I lost something,
but I gained something else.
I'm Gyung Guk-Hee now.
I have hope.
And as long as I have hope,
I can gain back what I've lost.
I'm sure I can start over.
Of course you can!
Guess what I just did?
I told my husband not to
call me fatso anymore!
You did?
Yes! I feel great!
Thanks, everyone.
I thought about what
I want to do from now on.
You'll see me change.
I'll be a good elder sister.
I talked to my ex-husband.
I'm not going to hide anymore.
What's wrong with you guys?
I bought some chicken soup
to cheer you up...
...because I thought
you guys were feeling down.
No one here is in regret?
Doesn't anyone want to
go back to how things were?
Go back? No way!
She's right.
Why would I want to go back?
Su-Duk yelled at her husband!
You know what?
I think you guys deserve a reward.
I feel nauseous.
I haven't been at a place
like this in 4 years.
Wow, everyone here is young!
They're still up at this hour!
What do you want us to do here?
We don't need anything.
Yes, you do!
Look at your clothes!
I can't afford clothes from a mall,
but I can get you clothes from here.
Prince Park Suk-Doo is willing
to shell out his pay!
Are you serious?
Well, I can't say no to that.
I'll start first.
Let's go!
Are you serious?
Tae-Ran, you're a great writer.
Do you like it?
It's a great read!
I think this will be an even bigger hit than your last work, Deja vu!
I love this scene!
I'm so proud of you.
Come over here.
No, I have to go.
I have a meeting tomorrow.
Stay a little longer...
just for 30 more minutes, please?
The kids are outside.
So?
It's Mr. Yeom.
Hello? What's up?
To my house? Now?
I love you, Gyung Guk-Hee!
What?
I love you!
Park Suk-Doo!
Stop making fun of me!
Hi, Myung...
Hi.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I would've have come if
I knew that you had a guest.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Mr. Yeom.
Let's talk outside.
Have fun.
See you next time. Bye.
I'm sorry...
Goodnight.
Where's Guk-Hee?
Is she sleeping?
She's not here?
No.
Was that...was that your new mistress?
You mean Tae-Ran and you are...
I'm hungry...
The food looks great!
I want everything on the menu!
Okay?
Okay!
Where's the restroom?
Around the corner.
Me too!
Stop messing with me.
You're going to get in trouble
if you do that again.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I feel great.
Me too.
It's tough, but I'm glad
I'm with good people.
I'm proud of myself
for pulling through.
Guess what?
I don't think I can hang out with college students anymore. I think it'll be boring.
Thanks, Suk-Doo.
You're much younger than me,
but I think of you as a good friend.
Now you think I'm a friend?
But I don't want to be
your friend anymore.
I thought you said once a friend,
always a friend.
You don't want to be
friends anymore?
I feel happy!
Hello, night time!
I haven't been outside
at night in a long time!
Same here.
I haven't felt this great in a long time.
By the way, Suk-Doo, you spent
your hard-earned money on us.
You should start saving up now if
you want to be a good husband later.
You need practice in order
to be a good husband.
Practice? What kind of practice?
Do you want to know?
I want to know how
I can be a good husband.
First, you to be kind.
Everyone grows old.
Families are people
who watch you change.
Love will turn into affection, and affection will make an everlasting bond.
If you want to be a good husband...
...you need to be kind-hearted
and unchanging.
You to practice how to
make conversation.
If you don't have conversations,
you'll end up like me and Sniff.
A man of hatred
instead of conversations.
Some men will think
your wife is pretty too.
Instead of lusting over other women, remember how pretty your wife is.
I want sincerity.
As long as he's sincere,
his family can accept him...
...no matter what the
world thinks of him.
I'll keep that in mind!
Cheers for a good husband!
Cheers!
Nothing's stopping you, isn't it?
I don't know what to say to you.
I can't you believe
you're getting a divorce.
It wasn't easy for me either.
Are you sure about this?
I thought this over millions of times.
I'm confident.
A modern good wife?
Is that what you want?
I just want a woman
who's suitable for me.
What brings you to my place tonight?
What happened to your eye?
Who did this to you?
Who is he?
It's a she.
My wife did this to me.
She's a good puncher.
Why?
She gets a little sensitive
when she's writing her thesis.
I came home drunk.
There's nothing wrong with drinking!
I'm supposed to go home early
and sober when she's writing.
That's not a reason to hit you!
How can you let a woman hit you!
Don't talk too loud!
There are people here.
If you're so ashamed,
then why did you let her do that to you?
Be a man!
Lose your ego.
Lose your ego?
Everyone's envious of
my acupuncturist wife.
A man should bust out
his wallet faster than a bullet.
That's how I life my life.
I bust my wallet out
and buy everyone drinks and food.
People think I'm great.
Life is like a coin with two sides.
If you choose this, you'll lose that.
If you choose that, you'll lose this.
I think we're going to have a lot of things to talk about in the future.
Let's call it a day.
Take your time.
Oh, my eye hurts.
Let's drink.
Hello? This is Tae-Ran.
Are you home?
I left my laptop at your place.
I'll go and pick it up right now.
Is Mr. Yeom still with you?
No, you can come over.
Thanks, Suk-Doo.
Although you lost money, you heard a lecture about how to be a good husband.
Just think of it as tuition.
That's right.
Be a good husband and a good man!
Park Suk-Doo!
Me too!
I'm going to go and
try my new underwear on!
Goodnight!
Guk-Hee! Can you help me?
Stop it!
I feel so much better after a drink.
I'll walk you to the taxi.
No, I can go by myself.
Hey, let go of my hand!
No, my hand's asleep!
Stop it!
Don't tell anyone that
my wife punched me!
My lips are sealed.
Those young people are lucky.
I hope you stay happy!
Are you jealous?
There's a taxi! Taxi!
No, that's an expensive taxi.
I can afford it.
I bust out my wallet faster than a bullet.
Goodnight.
Goodnight!
Stop it!
You're acting strange today.
What do you mean?
You've been acting strange since we were at the shopping center!
You said something like
'I love you' and all.
Do you think that's strange?
Of course it is.
Don't say things like that
in front of other people.
You're a good friend, but...
Stop it!
I love you. I mean it.
Gyung Guk-Hee!
Are you okay?
Why did you punch him?
What?
Subtitles provided by MBC America