Did you find her?
It's 8th floor.
We need to go up one more floor.
It's okay! It's okay!
She didn't see us!
Wasn't that your husband?
Do you know who the woman is?
9th floor!
They went to 9th floor!
- Episode 4 -
Guk-Hee! Guk-Hee!
Hold on.
No...
Guk-Hee!
Honey! Honey!
Honey...Honey! Honey!
Guk-Hee! Are you okay?
Why is Guk-Hee here?
What happened?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Get dressed.
You might catch a cold.
I'll make coffee for you.
I don't feel like coffee right now.
Let's go.
No, don't worry about me.
Let's stay here and have fun.
I don't feel like having fun.
I'll take a shower.
You should start packing.
How did she find out?
Mom!
Look what Suk-Doo made for me!
He made this for me!
Mom, did you get hurt?
Do you need a kiss?
No, I'm fine.
Mommy's fine.
Workshop? My team?
Oh! Yes, we have a workshop.
I forgot.
Yes, there's a workshop.
Where's the workshop at?
I don't know.
Mr. Choi, where's the workshop at?
You don't know?
Why not?
No one here knows.
Only the ones who are going know.
You don't sound like you have a cold.
A cold? Yes, I do.
I'm coughing a lot.
According to my husband,
it was your wife who has a cold.
No one's at the coffee shop
on 8th floor either.
Maybe it wasn't Yun-Shil who called.
Who called then? A ghost?
Stop it! You're scaring me!
Maybe it's just a prank call.
This is killing Su-Duk.
Something's always going wrong.
I can't take it anymore.
First, a person's missing, then she dies, and now her husband's cheating on her.
Why are you hitting me?
Do you want to wait here?
It's been more than 3 hours.
What? 3 hours?
No, Su-Duk needs to go home and cook!
Let me go home and cook!
Cook! Cook! Cook!
All you do is cook!
Let's go home.
I want to go home.
My wife?
I got caught!
What's wrong with you?
You should've just
weaseled your way out of it!
Why are you blaming me!
Don't worry, Myung-Pil.
There's always a way out.
Even if you get bitten by a tiger, you'll
be safe as long as you stay focused.
Even if you get caught by your wife,
you'll be safe as long as you play dumb.
What are you talking about?
Do you know what I had
to go through to learn all this?
I can't tell you for free.
Tell me! Now!
What do I need to do? Tell me.
Are you okay?
Okay with what?
We saw everything.
Don't act dumb.
Thanks for driving.
You're welcome.
I only did what I was supposed to do.
Goodnight.
I'll call you guys later.
Let's go, Eun-Suk.
Goodbye.
Wash your hands and brush your teeth.
Okay.
Who's here?
It's you.
Where were you?
I was waiting for you.
Don't stay out too late.
Just act dumb.
Even if she catches you red-handed...
...she might not say anything
if you pretend nothing happened.
There's no point in fighting, and
it's not that easy to demand a divorce.
You scared me!
What are you doing there?
I brought some kimchi.
It's a Sunday! You should've slept in. Why are you up already?
Good.
Come to church with me.
I want to serve everyone coffee
since I'm the new senior deaconess.
How many coffee pots do you have?
Give me everything you have.
Guk-Hee, are you sick?
No.
I think we have about 3 coffee pots.
Would you like some tea?
No, I just need water.
Congratulations on becoming
a senior deaconess.
Thank you. Hi.
Come to the evening meeting.
Sure, see you then.
Have some coffee.
- Thank you.
- Hi. Welcome.
Guess what?
She divorced her husband because
her husband cheated on her.
She's not even young.
She's more than 60 years old.
It doesn't matter how old you are.
It's shocking to hear that
your husband cheated on you.
She probably couldn't stand it.
Still, that's wrong.
I've come to realize that you'll be
better off if you just forgive your spouse.
I thought you didn't forgive him either.
That's why I'm living
the rest of my life in regret.
I threw a fit and threatened
to kill myself and my husband...
...when he cheated on me.
I guess he got sick of me since then.
We barely talked
to each other after that.
Marriage is mandated by heaven.
You need to care for each other,
instead of thinking of ways to break up.
That's the wise thing to do.
Good morning.
What's for breakfast?
Fish stew.
Come home for dinner.
It's a Sunday.
Of course I will.
I'll go and wash up.
Guk-Hee invited you too?
And?
It'll be stranger if I refuse to go.
I should go.
How can the three of us eat together?
No! I think that's wrong.
Just tell her that you're too sick to come.
Are you scared of Guk-Hee?
I'm not scared of her.
I just can't stand her.
Besides, I don't even know
what she's thinking about.
Then let's go and find out.
I don't want to run away.
I'm okay.
Okay then.
Whatever Guk-Hee does, just stay put.
I'll protect you whenever you need me.
Understand?
The door's opened.
Come in.
Am I late?
It's for Eun-Suk's homework.
He needs to do a camping exercise
with his dad and turn the picture in.
They're doing it today because
they didn't get to do it yesterday.
Hi! Hold on.
- Hold on!
- Ki-Suk, Daddy's getting tired!
Why isn't this working?
Honey, you're supposed to put this in.
Try again.
Let's put this up here.
That looks good.
Doesn't this look good?
Yes!
Now it's time to flip this over.
- Hot! Hot! Hot!
- Be careful!
Eun-Suk, take a picture
to turn it in as homework.
Then what about me?
I need the whole family in the picture.
Tae-Ran!
Can you take a picture for us?
Tae-Ran, can you take a picture for us?
Okay...
Come over here.
You too, Eun-Suk.
Everyone smile and look excited.
Cheese!
Can I take another one for myself?
Sure.
Tae-Ran wants to take a picture too.
Say kimchi this time!
Let me see.
Let's eat what we made.
- Sit down.
- How did it turn out?
That looks hot. Be careful!
Everyone came out looking nice.
Thanks, Tae-Ran.
Eun-Suk, you're done
with your homework now!
Dad! Next time you have
to go on a real camp with me.
Don't back out like you did yesterday.
Okay, okay. How many times
do I have to promise you?
Your dinner will be ready soon.
Honey, answer that.
Eat it slowly. It's hot.
Hello?
Yes, Mom.
A church get-together?
Oh yeah! I'm sorry, I forgot!
I'll be right there.
Bye.
You forgot Mom's church get-together!
We were supposed to eat
with her church people!
Hurry up. Let's go.
What about Tae-Ran?
I'm sorry, Tae-Ran.
It's for my mom's church,
but only the family is invited.
Oh...You should go then.
Go inside and get dressed.
Okay!
Just go with the kids.
I'll stay here and eat with Tae-Ran.
I need you with me!
Tae-Ran, I'm sorry.
Bye.
Grow up, will you?
Everybody is with their family
on a Sunday evening.
Look what you're doing here
in someone else's home.
Don't you feel sorry for yourself?
It's about time you settle down
and live like an adult.
I feel sorry for you because
you're wandering like a tramper.
Tramper? What do you mean?
I know more about life than you do.
You become an adult after getting married and having kids in due time.
You don't know what it means
to have your own family.
You lust over what's not yours
because you don't know life.
Find your own and cherish it.
Then one of these days, you'll
realize how patient I'm being right now.
Bye.
She invited your girlfriend to your place?
Your wife really is something.
Why do you think she did that for?
She's marking her territory.
This is my boundary, so keep off.
If you don't, you'll get hurt.
It's a warning.
Most women cry and fight
with their husband.
Guk-Hee really is something.
Darn, I had fun until now.
Nothing's free in life.
Ever since then, she won't
pick up the phone.
What's wrong with her?
Are you going to continue
seeing your mistress?
I'm not scared of my wife.
She'll give it up one of these days.
Myung-Pil, I have a bad
feeling about this.
I can smell it.
Smell what?
The smell of a dynamite wick burning.
The smell of a huge explosion on its way.
Guk-Hee!
Why did you buy so much food?
Do you want to feed good food
to that husband of yours?
I'm only doing my job.
You're too nice.
You'll rot away one of these days.
One of these days?
I've already rotted away.
Same here.
- That looks heavy. Let me help you.
- I'm okay. I'll put it here.
Now that everyone's here, tell us.
What did the police say?
They're going to cremate
Yun-Shil tomorrow.
Cremate her?
They found her ID and a suicide note
in Sokcho, where the body was found.
Does that mean Yun-Shil didn't call me?
I guess it was a prank call.
Now that I think about it, she did
seem like the type to commit suicide.
Remember how she jumped
into the ocean in Sokcho?
That looked odd.
Do you want to go see her get cremated?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
My whole life is in a mess now.
Hello?
I called earlier.
Is Tae-Ran back?
When do you think she'll be back?
It's already been more than 2 hours.
She usually doesn't answer her
phone when she has writer's block.
I see.
She's not sick or
anything like that, right?
I don't think so.
I see. Bye.
Did you two get in a fight?
No, I just want him now...as my own.
I now know what exactly
what I envied and wanted.
Tae-Ran, I want to hear your voice.
Call me after you
get this message, okay?
Mr. Choi! Just leave a message
like I told you to.
She'll call.
Okay, bye.
Did I wake you?
I came outside to answer the phone because I didn't want to wake you up.
You're so mean.
Are you sure you're my husband?
What?
I thought my husband will stay loyal.
I'm barely holding on.
If you aggravate me any further,
I don't know what I will do.
What?
Honey! Honey!
What a lonely way to leave this world.
I wonder what drove her to death.
Life is tough for everyone.
She should've gone through with it.
She should've asked us for comfort...
...even if she feels
betrayed by her husband.
Do you think she would've
been happier if she was alive?
At least she'll have hope.
Honey!
Is your husband back?
Did you eat?
You look pale.
You should eat something.
Try this rice cake. It's good.
Thanks.
Who...
It's a ghost!
It's me.
It's me, Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil?
Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil!
What's going on?
Where were you?
Whose corpse did we
cremate yesterday?
I think my head is about to explode.
I hate it when this happens!
She probably needs glucose.
Let her drink here.
Here, drink this.
Should we call white pants?
No, we don't know what happened.
Let's ask her what happened
when she wakes up.
Let's not call him until
we're sure that she's safe.
Are you okay?
Can you recognize us?
Yun-Shil.
Everything's going to be okay now.
Let's go outside.
What happened?
Let's wait until she gets better.
Wait until she gets better? Where?
Here?
Just the two of us?
No! I'm scared!
I'll visit often.
You can't stay with us 24 hours a day.
I'll come by whenever I can.
I'm glad Yun-Shil's still alive.
Where is she going to sleep?
I can't sleep when
someone's next to me.
There's nothing to eat in this house.
Something to eat?
Su-Duk has a lot of things
to eat in her house!
I can't eat them at home because
my husband gave me mean stares.
I can eat them here with you! Yes!
Mom, where are we going?
- To the beach!
- Yay!
- Let's have fun.
- Okay!
Go and get your bags.
Okay!
Do we have to leave on a holiday?
We have to come back in a day.
Yes, we have to go.
We need a family trip
and some time to talk.
Take this icebox downstairs.
Sheesh...
Tae-Ran, call me if you can.
Hello?
Hello? Tae-Ran!
Myung-Pil, I'm sorry.
I tired not to call...
I know I shouldn't, but...
Where are you?
Where are you, Tae-Ran?
At the bar we drank together...
Let's have fun.
Okay!
Honey! Open the door!
Mr. Yeom's father just passed away!
It was a car accident!
I have to go! Stay home.
Tae-Ran...
Myung-Pil...
You should eat at home, not here!
This is so good.
Jang-Mi, come and eat with me.
What's wrong with everyone?
She won't stop eating,
Yun-Shil is like a living corpse...
...and Guk-Hee looks like
she's about to join her!
Everything is in chaos!
I hate it when things are in chaos!
Is this what marriage is like?
I couldn't have imagined...
Awesome.
There's a golf group for
people in the media.
The VP from your company
is a member there too.
You should start playing golf with me.
This place is nice.
Here you go.
Cheers.
This is for you.
I was going to use this house as
a work area, but I rarely come here.
You can come over to rest
whenever you want.
You look tired.
You need a place to rest.
I'm begging you, Tae-Ran.
Please don't disappear like you did.
I don't think I can live without you.
Please, Tae-Ran.
Honey...were you with Tae-Ran?
How can you say that?
Don't you have any
emotions in your brain?
Mr. Yeom's husband passed away!
Aren't you sad for him?
Honey!
Why do you keep lying to me?
Tell me the truth.
You met Tae-Ran, right?
Stop it!
Honey!
Did you hide the golf clubs?
Can you hear me?
It's me, Guk-Hee.
Tae-Ran called to tell you
to hide your golf clubs.
You're my husband and our kid's father.
We're a family.
We should stay loyal to each other.
What are you trying to do?
I waited patiently.
You should get over her by now.
What are you trying to do?
I don't know either.
Tell me what to do.
We should just pretend
nothing ever happened.
But I can't.
Now what should I do?
Tell me what to do.
Why are you so cheeky?
Don't you feel bad for me?
I'm being honest because I feel bad.
Since when?
I heard you tell Tae-Ran at the bar cart that you should've married her instead.
Was it before that?
Ever since that day!
I still don't have a house.
I was lonely and desolate.
I lost all courage and hope for tomorrow.
I wanted someone to make me feel better, and Tae-Ran was with me.
Lonely and desolate?
Same here!
I was afraid and depressed too.
We were in the same situation.
Why did you have to cheat?
Because this is your fault!
I can't stand you, Guk-Hee.
I feel like breaking down.
We're not going anywhere!
Is it my fault that
we don't have a future?
I did my best.
I worked as hard as others.
Then whose fault is it?
We don't have a way out.
Our home, our family, and
our future is getting nowhere.
I have to do anything for you!
I can't stand it!
Life is tough.
There's nothing to look forward to.
I only have responsibilities.
Can't you understand me?
Just leave me alone.
How can I leave you alone?
You're cheating on me!
That's exactly the reason
why I can't stand you!
Where are you going?
Honey!
Honey! Honey! Honey!
Myung-Pil!
What are we going to do?
What's wrong with my life, Tae-Ran?
I feel like going crazy
whenever I'm home.
I don't feel relaxed even
when I'm away from home.
Everything seems to be in a chaos.
Everything's a mess.
I'm so confused.
I feel as though I can't get a moment's rest anywhere in this world.
Is this what life's is, Tae-Ran?
Honey!
Good morning!
Myung-Pil, you're...
Leave me alone.
I'm tired.
- Mr. Hur Myung-Pil?
- Yes?
I have a package for you.
Here you go.
This is a...
This is expensive!
Myung-Pil, what does your
girlfriend do for a living?
I'll go and change myself
into my new clothes.
Did your article get turned down?
You must be too busy dating
to think of a new article.
Do you have any good ideas for me?
I don't have anything.
Myung-Pil, if you're in a hurry...
what about this?
The average life span
of Koreans is rising.
Marrying twice is a good idea?
Living the rest of your
life with a spouse...
...you found when you were
in your 20's is too long.
People make a lot of mistakes
with their first marriage...
...because they were
too young at the time.
The spouse you found in your 30's
or 40's is suitable to grow old with.
And to back up that trend...
...the divorce rate of couples
in their 30's and 40's is exploding.
There's also a huge market
for second marriages.
This makes sense.
That's a hot topic.
Let's work on it before
we submit it for an evaluation.
- Thanks.
- Your welcome.
The spouse you found in
your midlife is the right one for you.
Right, you know better now.
Living the rest of your life
with one spouse is boring.
That's why people cheat
on their spouses.
You're right!
People don't know
better in their 20's.
You need more time to
know who's right for you.
If I can pick a second spouse,
I want someone really young.
Myung-Pil, I think you sympathizing
too much with the need to marry twice.
(Guk-Hee)
I brought this here so people won't know you didn't come home last night.
You already changed into new clothes.
I haven't seen that before.
Did you get it from Tae-Ran?
You're Hur Myung-Pil.
I thought you placed your pride
above everything else.
Why are you letting her control you?
Take it back.
I'm busy!
Do you think she's controlling me?
Can't you tell that she's
helping me get my pride back?
It's me.
Come outside. Now!
Why are you doing this?
What did I ever do to you?
Why are you thinking of this
in terms of a dichotomy?
Don't think of it in terms of
an offender and a victim.
It's just that both Myung-Pil
and I were unhappy.
We were happy when we were together, and I wasn't lonely anymore.
That's it.
No one here is the
offender nor the victim.
You don't think I'm the victim?
If love found you...
...someone may be asking you the same question you're asking me right now.
It's not wrong to want
love and happiness.
No.
Do you think it's wrong for Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt to be in love?
They only fell in love a little late in life.
Are you saying that
you're Angelina Jolie?
I'm just saying.
I'm just telling you that we get along
and that we're happy together.
You can seek happiness
with a single man.
Why with a married man?
I thought you're the
new perfect wife men want.
True love has no boundaries.
I can see my young,
innocent self in his eyes.
He sees his young,
energetic self in my eyes.
Don't you know what pure love is?
Are you happy?
Shut up!
I'm too busy making a living
to think about happiness!
I'm too busy with raising my kids
and saving up for a house...
...to listen to your crap,
you immature child!
Stop calling me immature!
Do you think you're mature?
Just because you're married?
I can do a much better job taking
care of the house than you do!
You don't know anything!
Why, you...
What?
You don't have a right to do this to me!
Stop it!
Calm down! Calm down!
I won't ask you to pay for the
damages if you two calm down.
Stop it! Stop it, you two!
Tae-Ran, are you okay?
Let me take a look at you.
Myung-Pil...
I can't believe she did this to you!
- She's going to get it!
- Don't go!
Stay with me.
I'm scared.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
You didn't do anything wrong.
The only thing you did was to love me.
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
Look at me.
I'm okay.
No, you're not!
It's you I'm worried about.
Can you live with Guk-Hee
for the rest of your life?
Remember when you told me
that you can't live without me?
Same here.
I can't live without you either.
Tae-Ran.
Tae-Ran!
We can talk at home.
I want a divorce.
I can't live with you anymore.
Even if we get through this crisis...
...how are we going to make it
though the years to come?
What'll happen when I'm forty or fifty?
I'll eventually ask for a divorce again.
Let's get divorced.
Honey!
I'm not happy when I'm with you.
I always thought something was missing, but I didn't exactly know what it was.
I told myself to just
get by and grow older.
But things are different now.
I now know there's another
way to be happy.
I can't live with you after knowing
that I can take that road.
I can't go on like this anymore.
Let's get a divorce.
I mean it.
Honey, is it because Tae-Ran got hurt?
It wasn't me.
She scratched herself
with her own bracelet.
She pulled my hair.
I got hurt too, Honey.
You misunderstood.
Guk-Hee, please try to understand me.
I want to live with Tae-Ran.
I mean it.
She can give me the life
and the future I want.
I don't feel powerless
when I'm with Tae-Ran.
I feel like I can conquer this world.
I feel like I'm back to my young self.
I can't like with you like this anymore.
Please grant me a divorce.
Honey, Honey, Honey...
Honey, please don't ask
me for a divorce.
Anything but that! No!
I'll try harder!
Please?
Where are you going?
Please don't go!
Nothing will change if I stay!
Do you want to live with me like this?
We won't get anywhere together.
I'll try harder.
We'll soon buy a house, and
I'll be nicer to the kids.
I'll be nicer to you too.
I'll be nicer to your mom too.
Honey!
How? With what?
Can you be an acupuncturist
like Mr. Yeom's wife?
We don't love each other anymore,
and there's no way out!
We have nothing to look forward to!
Let me go!
What am I going to do?
Subtitles provided by MBC America