Stop it! Let me go!
Jang-Mi! What are you doing to her?
Hello, Tae-Ran, I'm almost here.
You're already outside?
Come to the roadside.
Stop it!
Officer!
What the heck?
Myung-Pil!
I'm going to go crazy!
Follow that car!
What's the matter?
It's an emergency! Go after that car!
- Episode 8 -
Someone has been kidnapped!
Oh! Suk-Doo!
It's an emergency!
I have to go!
Su-Duk!
Go faster! We have to follow that car!
What's going on?
Faster!
Where are you, Guk-Hee?
I just passed the Bukak Tunnel.
The Bukak Tunnel?
They're passing
the Bukak Tunnel! Hurry!
They're passing the
Bukak Tunnel right now.
The Bukak Tunnel!
Jang-Mi!
What the heck?
What's going on?
Let me go!
Jang-Mi, stay still.
Jang-Mi, I'm really sorry,
but where's Lee Yun-Shil?
We have to find her.
Are you crazy? Let me go!
Shut up! Where's Lee Yun-Shil?
You killed her! You had her cremated!
I know that she's still alive!
If you don't bring her back,
I'll kill you too!
Stay still.
Heck no! Let me go! I want out!
Be quiet!!
This is your fault. You undermined me.
Let me go!
Hey Jang-Mi, are you okay?
Take it easy.
Shut up!
This wouldn't have happened
if you kept an eye on Lee Yun-Shil!
I'm going to ask you one last time.
Where's Yun-Shil?
Jang-Mi! Are you okay?
Oh! Guk-Hee! There you are!
What are you doing here?
I can't let you get beaten up
in the middle of the street!
Don't make me mind your business!
Mind your own business!
That's what we agreed on!
Yes, so could you please move out?
I told you that I'm going
to get the house back.
The house? After a million years?
Do you think you have
magic powers or something?
There you go again.
You're all talk!
Stop it! Why are you guys fighting?
If you want to fight, then fight at home!
You're making it sound like
I'm doing this because I want to!
What?
Freeze!
Put your hands up!
These two...
Come out! Come out!
Uh...
Guk-Hee! Jang-Mi! Are you guys okay?
Yes, I'm okay. How about you?
Why, that...
You mean he's White Pants...
and he tried to kill his wife?
That's crazy!
And they kidnapped her?
Yes.
We've been living in the same neighborhood with him!
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Did you get botox on your brain?
I already told you that.
But they're...
Are you leaving?
- We can handle this ourselves!
- No! I don't want to!
According to
Criminal Code 276 Article 1...
...anyone who arrests
and confines another person...
...will serve either 5 years or less in prison or fined with $7,000 or less.
Kidnapping is a crime.
Did you hear that?
How many times do I have to tell you?
She's my wife! I didn't kidnap her!
Do you consent?
No, I don't.
Apologize for calling me 'Fatso'
and give me my money back.
If you don't...
Don't point your finger at me!
Why, I ought to...
Injury and violence. Code 257.
Anyone who exercises violence upon...
...his/her family or
his/her spouse's family...
...will either serve 10 years or less in prison or fined with $15,000 or less.
That's a serious offense. Understand?
We lost Kim Jo-Han again.
He left his car.
License plate number 02DA8025.
Run the plate and
don't tell the Chief. Bye.
Please leave a message after the tone.
I'll promise you that
I'll never talk to Guk-Hee again.
I'll never go see Guk-Hee on my own will.
Satisfied?
I'm too scared to go home.
I'll stay with you and protect you for now.
Are you sure?
Yes.
What am I going to tell her?
Tae-Ran, I was at a workshop...
Just play dumb!
She might let you off the hook
if you act as if nothing happened.
Oh, my gosh!
Tae-Ran?
You were home?
You must've been worried about me.
Gosh, it's hard to be working man.
Are you trying to play dumb?
I saw you follow Guk-Hee.
You have a lot of explaining to do.
White Pants tried to kill someone.
He hired Sniff, who happens
to be Jang-Mi's husband.
He kidnapped her because
someone took his insurance money.
Guk-Hee somehow got
herself into the mess.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you think you're making any sense?
Huh? Yes...
I didn't believe her at first either, but she was telling the truth.
You're acting just like Guk-Hee.
What you're trying to tell me is that
you don't have any feelings...
...and that you're just
reacting to the situation.
This too hard for me to handle.
You promised me that you're
not going to talk to her again.
I was just reacting to the situation.
What are you going to do
if there's another situation?
This is too hard for me to handle.
My editor wants me to re-do my work.
I'm getting stressed out
because of Guk-Hee.
This is got to stop.
If you don't, I'll be disappointed in you.
Hello, I'm disqualified to be a good wife.
Tomorrow's my first oral proceeding.
I never coveted
someone else's property.
I only wanted to keep what's mine.
Why is that so difficult a task?
Are you guys going
through the same thing?
Why do we need to fight to live in peace?
What are you doing?
I've never fought with anyone in my life.
Now that I'm taking it to the civil court,
I feel nervous.
Guk-Hee, let's go outside.
Tae-Ran, we've been talking
too much in all this commotion.
Why don't we use our
body language instead?
Uh-huh.
What did you say?
We've been talking too much...
Let's use our body language...
How am I supposed to emphasize
the romantic part here?
Do you have a lot of editing to do?
I thought you'll be done soon.
Don't wait for me. Go to sleep.
One, two, three...
At ease.
Next, we breathe in the moonlight.
Repeat after me.
Muzeap Sepire Cartage.
What?
Muzeap what?
Come on...
Muzeap Sepire Cartage!
Muzeap Sepire Carta...
What's that? It sounds weird.
You smiled!
You told me that you're
nervous about the lawsuit.
Are you relaxed now?
Yes, but what does that mean?
What does that mean?
Are you sure it's a yoga term?
I...like...you.
If you keep messing around,
I'm going to sue you too.
At least you're relaxed.
Why don't we chant the spell again?
Muzeap Sepire Cartage...
The deposit?
Why do you look so surprised?
The homeowner has
a right to break the contract.
She's going to give you $40,000, double the deposit you gave her, as penalty.
I'll pay you $40,000.
I don't want to sell that house.
What happened?
The homeowner paid the penalty.
She wants to fight until the end.
Guk-Hee, come over here.
Look at all these replies to your post.
Look!
Cheer up, Gyung Guk-Hee!
'I hope you get your house back!'
Everyone's cheering you on.
Someone here wrote,
'I hate that homeowner!'
All the other married
women are talking about...
...how much trouble
they're going through.
All the other housewives didn't have anyone to complain to, just like us.
How sad.
Life's tough.
They work all day, but get no recognition.
You're right.
But then again, we've been
through the same thing.
Why don't we get
ourselves a homepage?
A homepage?
Sounds great!
Are you going to call it 'Good Wife'?
No, it'll be 'Good Wife...'
Good Wife....Disqualification Club?
Good Wife Disqualification Club!
Great!
One, two, three!
I like this one.
Much better.
I'm off to work.
Did you pull an all-nighter?
Did you have breakfast?
The bread's in the oven.
I'll be home early.
Let's rest together.
I didn't take a shower yet.
It happens when I have
a deadline to meet.
Thanks for the gift, Yun-Shil.
I wanted to see you again,
but I didn't know how to contact you.
I'm sorry I didn't visit you until now.
I'll bring an even better gift
for you guys later.
Did you really live in our orphanage?
Why?
Do you think I can grow up
to be a great person like you?
I'm not a great person.
I'm sure you'll be an even
greater person when you grow up.
It's an unlisted number.
Hello?
It's me, Yun-Shil.
Yun-Shil?
Where are you?
We've been worried about you!
Is she alive?
Where is she?
Uh-huh. White Pants
knows that you're alive.
Guk-hee, is Jang-Mi okay?
That's a relief.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I have more work to do.
I'll go back after I'm done.
Bye.
- How is she doing?
- Where did she say she was?
She sounds like she's doing fine.
Uh...I have something to say.
What is it?
When I was living with you...The fact that I didn't listen to what you had to say...
Can we talk privately?
We can talk here.
Just pretend I'm a tree.
Just pretend I'm a bird up on that tree.
Guk-Hee!
Hi, Suk-Doo!
Hey! Why are you here?
Go home!
I'm living with them.
What?
Is that true?
Are you living with this kid?
First, the other women, and now him?
What am I going to do with you?
Hello, Tae-Ran.
What am I going to do?
The house is on fire!
Come home!
What?
Did you pull an all-nighter?
Yes, I was getting prepared for the lawsuit.
All I have left now is the trial.
You're working too hard.
We should go...to the sauna!
What am I going to do?
Myung-Pil!
Oh, no...Tae-Ran!
I was going to splash water in the oven, but it got on you too.
I'm so sorry!
What's wrong with me?
Everything's going wrong!
All I wanted was a piece of bread!
Look at me!
Tae-Ran, calm down.
I'll make you feel better.
This is just a happening.
I'll take today off from work.
Let's take a break together.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'll let you off the hook
because you're pretty.
Married women are strong.
You'll be dead meat if you mess with us.
Su-Duk knows how to head butt.
My husband fainted.
Look who we have here.
I hate this.
Looks like we have trouble.
Why do they keep following us?
Tae-ran, do you want to leave?
Why? We didn't do anything wrong.
You're right. We should
stay and have fun.
I'm thirsty. I want something to drink.
Do you want rice punch?
Wait for me over there.
Thank you.
Are you getting her something to eat? I'm impressed.
Please don't prowl around me anymore.
Prowl around?
You prowled around me this morning because you had something to say.
We were here first.
Maybe you're following me.
Do you think I prowled around?
Do you think I'm following you?
I really had something
to say this morning...
...and this is the only sauna
in the neighborhood.
So you really are following me.
I really had something to say!
What is it?
When I was with you...
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Guk-Hee!
The furnace is on.
The furnace?
Let's go.
If you keep nagging me,
I'm going to quit writing!
Gosh, you look so happy together?
Are you really going to live with him?
Whatever.
She's a complete stranger now.
You're asking for too much!
What are you trying to say?
That felt good.
What are you doing?
You scared me!
Let me ask you one question.
Do you like that kid?
Yes.
You like that kid?
Yes, he's a great guy.
Yes? Yes?
Yes? Did you say, 'yes'? Did you?
Tae-Ran!
Hey!
I had to use the restroom.
Let's go.
Why? What about the rice punch?
Now I'm sure.
You're still attached to him.
Attached?
I was a little bothered by you,
but I don't feel the need anymore.
You're prowling around Myung-Pil because you want him to notice you.
How foolish.
Getting a man's heart back
after he left you...
...is harder than bringing an audience
to a crappy movie.
You can't win this game.
Just shake if off, will you?
What are you doing?
You wanted me to shake it off.
Hi.
What? Aren't you going to get dressed?
Aren't you going to take your pants off?
These are my pants! Why do you care?
Sorry.
Hey kid, do you like hanging out
with older women?
Do your parents know about this?
I've been living away from them
since junior high.
They don't know the details.
What?
Let me get straight to the point.
Get out of that house.
Maybe Guk-Hee's hanging out
with you because she's out of it.
Both you and Guk-Hee need to grow up.
You're the one who needs to grow up.
What?
Everyone knows that.
Hey kid!
I was a little offended because
you kept on calling me a kid.
But then again, your body tells me
that we have a good age gap.
What?
Why, you...
Ouch!
Stop it!
You dork!
When I count to three,
let each other go, okay?
One, two, three!
- What are you doing?
- Myung-pil!
Tae-Ran!
Oh-no! Suk-Doo!
Too bad.
I'm not the fool who's still attached.
You should keep an eye on him.
What?
Let's go.
Tae-Ran, let's go.
Tae-Ran!
If we take Guk-Hee's kids, she'll have
no choice but to give us Yun-Shil.
Stop staring at the picture, will you?
Hello?
It's me.
You better not do anything to Guk-Hee, Jang-Mi, and Su-Duk.
Why shouldn't I?
Because you want money.
You married a banker like me
so you can get that loan.
So?
If you want the insurance money, get Sniff off your trail and come by yourself.
I'll see you at 3pm on the 25th.
Come to the place you proposed to me.
- What's wrong?
- Huh?
Oh, it was a loan shark.
He's nagging me to pay him back.
Money! Money! Money!
We have to change our plan.
Why? We're almost there.
I have to take care of him first.
Let's get back to her after I'm done.
Kill some time before I'm back.
You can go meet your wife.
Are you a pervert?
You've been smacked.
- Why are you smiling?
- Yeah.
Oh no, do you have head injury?
Do you feel nauseous?
No, I'm smiling because...
When fighting for love,
whoever punches first loses.
Wow! Pretty impressive.
Looks like Guk-Hee's husband
has met his match.
You're right.
Too bad you ended up
fighting at the sauna.
Why don't hold a pork belly party
to make ourselves feel better?
- Okay!
Guk-Hee! Do you want pork belly?
Sounds good.
Let's go grocery shopping together!
Shopping? Sounds good!
Oh, I'll bring some
snake wine from home.
I'll get the place ready.
You two should go
shopping by yourselves.
Jang-mi!
Let's go.
Shall we?
Tae-Ran!
Myung-Pil
Please leave a message...
Gyung Guk-Hee!
The door's unlocked. Come in.
Jang-Mi.
Go away!
Stay away from me!
No, not today.
Go away!
Guk-Hee, this is a dead end.
It's do or die!
Come on...
Jang-Mi! Jang-Mi!
I have something to tell you!
Why are you running away?
Guk-Hee!
Su-Duk!
- I brought snake wine.
- Su-duk!
Why so little? It's too little!
It's for you.
You never know when
you'll get in another fight.
What happened?
Who is it?
Honey! Honey, wake up!
What are you doing here? Honey!
Honey, get up! What's wrong with him?
Honey, get up! Wake up!
What happened?
Uh...I don't know why you left me.
What did I do wrong?
After you quit your detective job, you locked me up in that house for 3 years.
You disconnected our phone
and internet service.
You still don't know what you did wrong?
That's because you were
cheating on me!
Why did you open a bar?
Why do you think I opened a bar?
To meet men.
I hate dealing with people.
I wanted you to become a cop again.
I was willing to make money
if you can go back to preserving justice.
That's why I willingly did
something that I hate.
Why didn't you tell me that?
Nothing would've happened
if you told me that.
I prayed every night
for you to go back to your old self.
But you drank everyday
and battered me day after day...
After a thousand days, I left you.
Myung-Pil! Myung-Pil!
Where am I?
Jang-Mi's house.
I thought you were
knocked unconscious.
Then you snored.
Why do you keep getting
yourself into trouble?
Trouble? Me?
Right, I can't believe this either.
I'm scared of getting out of bed.
Not a day goes by in peace.
That's exactly what I told you
while I was living with you.
I didn't know how things went wrong.
I had too much to do,
and didn't know how to do them.
It happens.
You try to explain, but you'll feel
agitated if no one listens to you.
You should go home.
Guk-Hee.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you
this morning that I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not listening to you,
and embarrassing you.
I thought I should apologize.
'I'm sorry...'?
I can't believe you just said that.
It just happened.
It just happened?
I see.
But you're being irresponsible.
I think I've taken you for granted.
I never took time to
appreciate what I have.
I took you for granted.
I want to say something too.
I don't know if I fully explained to you who I am and what makes me happy.
Someone persevered and
explained for 1,000 days.
I don't think I've tried that hard.
I think I should apologize for that.
Our life was too dry.
We've been too busy
making money, having kids...
...and buying a house that we didn't talk.
It's too late now.
But I'm glad we got to tell each other that we're sorry and got it off our chest.
The Sly Fox is here.
Tae-Ran?
Guk-Hee, tell her that I'm not here.
I made that commotion at the sauna.
I can't let her know that I'm here.
Please tell her that I'm not here!
That means I'm hiding you!
Just this once! Please tell her
that I'm not here.
I'll do anything you say!
I'm sorry for intruding.
What is it?
I just...
Shouldn't you tell us why you're here?
I was wondering if Eun-Suk
and Gi-Suk are here.
They're with their grandmother.
You know that too.
Right.
Myung-Pil's here, right?
Answer me.
You can call his name out
if you want to find out.
Tae-Ran...
Hey.
You told me that Tae-Ran
boosts your ego, right?
Where's your ego now?
Bye.
Tae-Ran, listen to me.
Guk-Hee
Hello?
It's me, Guk-Hee.
What did you want to see me about?
Let's not make this
harder on each other.
What do you mean?
I know how it feels to see your man
get tangled up with another woman.
I experienced first-hand, thanks to you.
What happened today was
just a coincidence.
You don't have to fight with Myung-Pil.
Are you taking his side?
No, I'm doing this because it's over.
We're going to court tomorrow,
and everything will be over.
You told me that it's hard to
get a man's heart back, right?
I don't want it back.
My heart left him already.
You don't need to fight with Myung-Pil.
Why are you telling me this?
It was tough for me when I had
a feud with Myung-Pil over you.
Maybe it would've been easier
to handle if I had money like you do.
My family was my everything.
I was scared and in pain.
I would've sold my soul if anyone offered to save me from that mess.
I don't want anyone to go
through that pain anymore...
...including you and Myung-Pil.
I'm not perfect, but I loved him with all my heart and gave him everything I had.
I gave my all to my family...
...so I don't have any regrets.
Anyways, we were on the wrong track, and this is where we ended up.
We can't go back,
and I don't want to go back.
I won't get in your way.
I hope you're happy with him.
You'll be very busy tomorrow.
I never thought it would end like this.
Do you want me to go with you?
No.
Thanks, Suk-Doo.
I owe what I am to you.
After you get everything settled, I want you to say something besides thank you.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
It's okay for me to wait, right?
Sure, you can wait.
But I get to decide
what I'm going to say to you.
Did you bring all the paperwork?
And your ID?
I brought them.
Let's go.
Hey...
Uh...well...
- ...nothing.
- Let's go.
Do you consent to the divorce,
Ms. Gyung Guk-Hee?
Yes.
Do you consent to the divorce, Mr. Hur Myung-Pil?
Mr. Hur Myung-Pil?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Do you consent to the divorce? Do you?
I'm not sure.
What?
You don't want a divorce?
I'm...not sure!
Are you out of your mind?
I can't help it. I'm not sure!
I'm not sure about what I want either.
Let me think about it.
Hey! Hur Myung-Pil!!
Subtitles Provided by MBC America