- Episode 7 -
Stop it!
I love you. I mean it.
Gyung Guk-Hee!
Why I ought to...
Are you okay?
Why did you punch him?
What?
- Are you nuts?
- Aren't you nuts?
Why did you punch him?
Of course, I...
You're...you're with him...
late at night...
- How can you do this?
- Mind your own business.
We're divorced now.
Apologize.
What?
Apologize for punching him!
You want me to apologize to him?
Apologize. Now!
Forget it, Guk-Hee.
I'm okay. You may go now.
What?
Let's go.
Why I ought to...
I'm older than you,
and I'm a married woman.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you laughing?
You defended me.
Don't ever do that again.
I'm okay with it.
It's me. Come out!
Come out!
You wanted me to apologize to that kid?
What are you trying to do,
make me jealous?
Maybe you're using too many brain cells.
You're supposed to apologize
after punching someone.
That's what I taught Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk.
Fine. Let me ask you one question.
What's that kid to you?
Are you guys dating?
I don't have to answer that.
You're really going to go out with him?!
What the...
What's wrong with you?
I've protected you until now, but you need to have your head on straight.
You hang out with women with botox
on their brains and now that kid?
Stop! That's enough.
Listen, you didn't protect me.
You made me into a fool.
I accommodated you, but you
always complained. I lost my identity.
Didn't you say Tae-Ran boosts your ego?
I'm regaining my confidence
now that you left me.
I found the Gyung Guk-Hee
who was talented and confident.
The people you belittle
have given me strength.
Mind your own business. Don't call me
late at night and lecture me.
It's up to me to date a kid or an old man.
Stay out of my life.
Fine, is that what you want?
I'm never going to help you
when you're in need.
Got that?
I'll never ask you for your help.
Yun-Shil, time for lunch.
I have a great plan. I'll be back.
I'll be a changed woman
when you see me again.
From, Yun-Shil.
Why are you laughing? Do you think
it's funny that Guk-Hee punched me?
I can't help it.
Speak for yourself.
I'm mad at myself.
I can't believe I punched that kid
when Guk-Hee and I am divorced.
I think I have a lot to look forward to.
Hello?
Tae-Ran, why didn't you come
pick up your laptop?
I waited for you.
You didn't answer my calls.
What's wrong?
- What is it?
- You have a cut on your face.
Oh, I scratched myself while playing
with Eun-Suk last night.
Isn't it uncomfortable for you to live in the same neighborhood as Guk-Hee?
Well...
It is.
What's that?
Wait, I've seen this before.
This is mine.
Is this his way of telling you
that he's mad?
You deserve half of what he has!
Why did he only give you your clothes?
You're right. You need to
fight for your right.
Who is it?
Go in.
Saw your stuff? I put it there
because I moved in.
I was going to wait until the wedding,
but why wait?
Shouldn't you move on
with your life too?
I thought you'd need your stuff.
Excuse me. I need to
make snacks for the kids.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
You don't want your stuff back?
No, I'm so glad you moved in.
Mother took care of Eun-Suk
and Gi-Suk for too long.
I'm glad you moved in.
Here are the things you should know.
Memorial on March 6th and July 7th.
Mother's birthday on June 7th.
HOA meeting every first
Monday of the month.
Volunteer at Eun-Suk's school
every Wednesday.
You need to clean and cross students.
Mother's bible study is here on Wednesdays. It's tiring even to read it.
You can check the rest yourself.
HOA rules. It's annoying but
has to be abided by. Listen carefully.
Electricity bill is due on the 10th, water 15th, gas 20th, and HOA fees 18th.
Don't be late on your bills.
No running water on Wednesdays.
There's more.
Recycling times are Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays from 7-9AM.
Be sure to separate chicken bones,
crab shells, and eggshells.
Stay home during disinfection time
every second week of the month.
Or else all the roaches will be
all over this place.
Bye. Let's go.
Did you see the look on her face
when we talked about the roaches?
Why is she scared of roaches?
They're so tiny.
She's so fake.
She's never done housework.
Are you okay?
Yes. We should lead a planned life.
We ought to put it into action.
Plan? Okay!
I'm going to pull out my wisdom tooth, and give my dad some allowance.
I want to sleep in too.
Sleep in? I like that idea.
I'll sleep in once a week
and read comic books.
Maybe we should go rent some now.
Get me some romance novels.
There was something else
I wanted to read...
I should've done this earlier.
If I didn't go to the beach that day,
I would've never had time for myself.
We should learn to enjoy our life.
Tuesdays, snacks for Gi-Suk's child care center...
Wednesdays, Mother's bible study group...
Electricity bill is due on the 10th, water 15th, gas 20th...
These are the household chores?
- Is that what Guk-Hee told you?- Yes.
She wrote these to give you a hard time.
It's impossible to do
everything on the list!
You never helped her, right?
Of course I did...
She only wrote what's necessary.
How can you do all these by yourself? Let's ask my mom to come.
The hardest thing to do in life
is to earn money from writing.
Household chores are a piece of cake.
Then let's do it. I'll help you.
Sir, there are 4 crazy
female ghosts at my house.
Just go home.
I can't go home!
I reported it, but there's
no such thing as ghosts!
Are you shocked that
your wife passed way?
Go home, we already closed
your wife's suicide case.
No, I can't go home!
Officer, can you interrogate me?
Hang on.
Hello?
I'm telling you, it's a ghost.
Wow, he's totally nuts.
I don't feel like cleaning today.
- It never ends.
- I know.
- How much did we eat?
- Lately, a lot.
- Hi again.
- Hi.
I can do those chores
with my eyes closed.
I'm all done.
I'll let you know if there's more.
I'll be too busy to take you
into consideration though.
Why don't you move?
Wow, I can't believe you have
the nerve to say that.
I'll have to find another way then.
- Oh my...
- Wait.
You need to clean your own mess.
Recycle your own trash.
I'm on my way to dinner. I'll do it later.
Look, this woman's not
cleaning her mess.
Shouldn't you make her clean
the trash bin as a punishment?
Why don't you help her out?
- Why should we?- Why not?
You have all the time in the world!
Excuse me, I heard
you're a very famous writer.
My son is an aspiring actor.
Do you want to see his picture?
Can you get the famous actress Kam Sung-Yun's autograph for me?
I hate it when things like this happens!
I ought to yank all those
women's hair out!
It's not worth it. Let's go.
No wonder I didn't feel like cleaning.
Let's go.
I'm glad I finally got it pulled out.
It must've hurt.
Why did you wait so long?
I thought the pain would
go away after awhile.
It was a part of me...
Was this your car?
Oh my, isn't this expensive?
I've been wanting talk to you.
You know the house
where the 3 women live?
Of course, I do.
Why are you kicking me out? Didn't
you want me to live another 2 years?
The president of HOA
makes the calls around here.
- Please reconsider.
- I already made up my mind.
Hello?
You want me to quit?
No, I need the money.
Please! I'll work harder!
Please don't fire me!
With enough people, you can
even turn against heaven.
No one can beat the president of HOA.
This is driving me crazy too.
Get yourself another job.
I have an announcement
to make about Building 303.
Real estate values are going up...
...because of a new elementary school
in the neighborhood.
But we have one problem.
Will people want to live with
a bunch of women...
...who got kicked out of their homes?
No!
Yes! Right on!
Those women spoiled my wife!
What's going on?
- Get out!
Look, can we please live in peace?
We have a good reason for doing this!
Hey you! Listen to me!
I hate people like them!
This is getting on my nerves.
That's a human being, not a ghost.
Lee Yun-Shil!
I thought you killed her!
No, I didn't... Actually, I couldn't.
I locked her up in an inn, and she ran away.
I think the innkeeper opened the door for her.
What about the corpse?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
I thought you checked the corpse!
Didn't you check her face?
Yes, but it was unidentifiable because her face was a mess from drowning.
After all, her ID was in the pocket.
Anyways, your wife is still alive.
My money!
My money! My money!
Yun-Shil...I'm going to get you!
I'm going to get you!
I'm here to open a bank account.
You shouldn't have annoyed Tae-Ran.
You should've left when I asked you.
You want me to leave because I make you and Tae-Ran uncomfortable?
How can you be
so selfish and shameless?
You provoked Tae-Ran first
with a list of chores and such.
Please don't stand against Tae-Ran.
She's on a whole new level apart from you and those women with botox.
You can't match up to her competence.
Competence?
You call that competence?
Is that all you need to be
the wife you need?
Then what do you think it takes to be a good wife?
Just quietly cook and
do the laundry at home?
Is that who you thought I was?
You don't know what's really important.
And what would that be?
Ta-dah!
Are you sure I'm not bothering you?
I'm sorry for interrupting.
I wanted you to interrupt me.
What do you need?
Stop messing around.
I want to know if they have
the right to kick us out.
Once the contract term expires, the tenant does not have a right to renew.
That means she has to get out.
No, I can't let her get
kicked out because of me.
Suk-Doo, look!
This place stinks.
Myung-Pil, open the veranda window!
Got it!
Come on, let's eat.
Myung-Pil!
Hurry up.
Tae-Ran, I'll be back.
I left my car interior light on.
Hurry back!
The owner demanded
to cancel the contract...
...on the day I went to pay
the remaining balance.
She demanded $60,000 on the spot.
That's wrong.
She wasn't supposed to do that to you.
If I can get that house back,
that means we have a place to stay.
Do you think I can get that house back?
Nice going. Very nice.
Are you going out with him?
- Are you out of your mind?
- I'll bring the contract.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Are you jealous?
What?
I don't understand why you keep on butting in between Guk-Hee and me.
You jerk!
Who do you think you are?
Don't call me a jerk.
I'm very grateful to you.
What? Grateful?
Thanks to you,
that fine woman is now available.
Now that she's available,
I can ask her out.
Thanks.
By the way, that was a nice punch. We're even now.
What that little...
I thought you can do those chores
with your eyes closed.
What the? What are you doing here?
I realized something while
you were trying to kick me out.
Maybe I can get what's important back.
Here it is!
Get out. Get out!
Let me remind you.
This is still my house.
I can come here whenever I want
until I'm officially divorced.
Hey!
Oh, no.
Don't put this near the fire.
That's dangerous.
We've been using canola oil
for 2 years to stay healthy.
It'll smell good in stir-fry food.
You need to use homemade
soy paste for stews.
You didn't even add garlic?
You should do the dishes
as soon as possible.
The edges might chip off
if you leave them like that.
Take good care of them until I take them after I find a place to stay.
Hey!
- Who do you think you are?
- Oh, by the way...
Can you tell Myung-Pil
to mind his own business...
...whether I talk to
a college student or not?
Hey!
Tae-Ran! Are you okay?
Tae-Ran!
I saved up for 8 years to buy that house.
I lost my house
after signing the contract.
I want to get it back if I can.
If I can get it, we can live there together.
You have to get it back.
You went through so much trouble because of that house.
Let's get it back!
And...Su-Duk made
an accomplishment today.
We can sell this to get some money.
You don't have any money
because you got fired.
Su-Duk will help.
I have good news!
There's a chance you can
get that house back!
She wasn't supposed to do that to you.
Really?
Let me see the contract.
I'll show it to my friend.
Call the homeowner to set up a meeting.
Follow me.
Suk-Doo is a fine man.
He has a servant boy image.
Guk-Hee looks like his mistress.
Ma'am!
He's practicing to be a good husband.
That's what I like about him.
I hope Guk-Hee makes a move on him.
Should we help her?
What are you talking about?
The servant boy.
Fulfill the contract?
But you even pay me the balance!
That's because you refused to take it!
You demanded $60,000 more on the spot, and forwarded me the contract fee.
You weren't supposed to do that.
I got some legal advice.
That house is now worth $600,000.
Why would I sell it to you for $300,000?
Then I'll sue.
As you wish.
Look, it's too late now.
The owner can cancel the contract.
All she needs to do
is to pay the penalty...
...of double the contract fee
for breaching the contract.
Is it the contract fee
that what you want?
Don't you understand Korean? Why don't you understand what we're saying?
We want the house, not the contract fee!
It's my house. I can do whatever I want.
Tae-Ran, it's been two days.
Please say something!
What did Guk-Hee tell you?
I'm hanging on your every word.
You're making me miserable.
Tae-Ran!
Myung-Pil.
Yes? What is it?
Are you sure you went downstairs because the car interior light was on?
Well, you see...
I saw you fighting with a man
on the night Mr. Yeom was here.
Do you still have feelings for Guk-Hee?
It just happened.
For a minute there,
I thought we were still married.
I quickly came back to my senses
and thought, 'It's none of my business.'
Like Samuel Johnson said,
'Life is not long...
...and too much of it must not
pass in idle deliberation.'
Smart people like us shouldn't
waste our time over this.
This is wrong.
I'll go and get this settled!
I'll kick Guk-Hee out and
I'll make sure never to see her again!
Satisfied? Okay?
Fatso! How dare you sell my ring!
I'm going to kill you.
I'll find Jang-Mi, Yun-Shil,
and get the insurance money.
I'll kill three birds with one stone.
Jang-Mi! I knew it!
She's boy crazy!
What are you doing here? Who are you?
You crazy jerk! I'm here to find my wife!
Your wife?
Let's get this settled.
Is anyone home?
Guk-Hee!
Excuse me.
It's me.
Jang-Mi is with two men?
Who are you?
That's what I want to ask you!
You jerk!
You bunch of...
Why, I ought to...
Don't come near me!
What's going on? Our house!
Thief! Thief!
Wait! Wait!
What happened?
What did Guk-Hee say?
You told her, right?
Yes...
Tae-Ran! I can't take this anymore.
Let's just forget about her.
I don't want to deal with
the losers in that house.
Let's take it to the court.
I'll request compulsory mediation
and a restraining order.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
What now?
See you at the court tomorrow.
I don't want to fight over making you move and what to do about the kids.
Let's take this to the court.
Let's settle this at the family court.
You'll be summoned
in about 5 days or so.
We need the both of you to be here.
It'll be over in 5 days.
You're right.
Where do I file a civil case?
At the 2nd floor of the
next building to the left.
See you in 5 days.
I filed my application.
Tae-Ran, all you need to do is wait.
Lunch?
There's a kimchi stew place
in front of the court.
I'll eat there.
Bye.
Why are you here?
This is my favorite place.
I'm the one who introduced
this place to you.
- How many?
- Oh, one!
One!
We don't have any seats.
Would you like to sit together?
Enjoy your food.
You surprised me.
I thought you'd say no,
but you went along with the divorce.
I pulled my wisdom tooth out.
I thought it'd hurt, but I felt much better.
At the time, I wasn't
ready to divorce you.
I tried to hold onto you
even though it was painful...
...just like my wisdom tooth,
since you were a part of me.
But I think I can get rid of you now.
Actually, I might feel
much better after this.
I'll grant you a divorce.
I'm going to sue
and get that house back...
...the one you said
we lost because of me.
I'll move once I get
that house back. Don't worry.
The house we couldn't get
because she demanded $60,000?
It's not fair.
It's not fair that the
real estate prices skyrocketed.
It's not fair that we lost that house.
Yes! It's not fair!
Things wouldn't be this rough
if we had gotten that house.
I'm going to get it back.
That'll be nice.
But I doubt the homeowner
will sell it to you.
That's useless. Don't do it.
I'll do it.
Now that I know it's wrong,
I have to do something about it.
I want Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk
to be proud of me.
What are you looking at?
Uh...nothing.
Real Estate Laws
What were you doing there?
Do you live here?
What are you doing here?
Is he living with you?
Are you from the city hall?
Are you taking a census?
We're having dinner.
Don't bother us.
This is a book of real estate laws.
You should know the facts
if you don't want to get embarrassed.
I already read that book.
Fine then.
Bye.
Myung-Pil.
Yes, Tae-Ran?
What are you doing with that book?
When Guk-Hee lost that house,
all I did was nag her.
Now she wants that house back.
It's not going to happen...
...but I wanted to give her this book because I feel sorry for her.
But it's over now.
It's over!
I did what I can do!
She's going to sue for a stupid house?
Are you going to follow her blindly?
Dad, there's a storytelling class tomorrow...
Follow her blindly?
A stupid house?
Right, you may not
understand this, Tae-Ran.
But we scraped every penny
for 8 years for that house!
It's not a stupid house.
Are you going to team up with her now?
Do you want me to pretend
I don't know anything?
Now that I know how upset
you are over this matter...
...I'll promise you that
I'll never talk to Guk-Hee again.
I'll never go see Guk-Hee on my own will.
Satisfied?
You know that I never say never, right?
Mom, what am I going to do
about the storytelling class?
The Pauper didn't do anything.
Come over here... I see...
Don't worry, I'll work my magic.
Okay.
It's okay.
Very good.
I'm done.
What else do you want me
to help you with?
Chop the green onions.
I need them to be thin.
Okay!
By the way, I don't think
you should say 'I'll help you.'
Huh?
By saying 'I'll help you,' you're assuming that I'm the main constituent...
...and you're not.
You should say 'Let's do it together' instead of 'I'll help you.'
These chores concern both of us.
That means you should do it too.
Don't say 'I'll help you'
like you're being generous.
Oh...
Didn't you help Guk-Hee
at all with household chores?
Huh? Yes, I did help her!
I mean...we did them together!
Then you should get started
instead of asking me if you can help.
Sure thing...
Then let's get started on
chopping the green onions.
Chop the potatoes and the onions too.
If you bite on this, you won't get tears.
You know that you can reduce propanesulfonic acid...
...by using the same substance, right?
Uh-huh...
I just need to make a lunchbox
for the race tomorrow.
Huh? Oh, no...
The race isn't on tomorrow!
Tomorrow's storytelling time!
Oh, no...
Ji-Hoon and So-Young!
Long time no see.
Gyung-Chul, how are you after
the rollerblading accident?
Myung-Hoon, you got a Ryukendo shirt!
You look exactly like Ryukendo
with that hairdo!
I'm going to tell you a story about
the Prince and the Pauper.
That's my mom! Isn't she pretty?
Ta-dah!
Hi, I'm the Prince of your kingdom.
Hi, I'm Tom from the countryside.
Wow! We look exactly alike!
You're like my mirror image!
This is incredible!
The Prince and the Pauper
were surprised...
...by how much they looked alike.
Mom! When will the
hide and seek be over?
It'll be over soon.
Gi-Suk must be waiting. Let's go.
Okay.
Eun-Suk! Gi-Suk!
Go inside and wash up.
I need to talk to the Pauper.
Yes, Prince mother.
Good afternoon.
You look triumphant
after storytelling time.
Why do you look upset?
Are you stressed out because
you didn't make it to storytelling time?
If you think you can prove your worth through a mother role, you're wrong.
You got booted off your role as a wife.
All you have left is your role as a mother.
What are you going to do if
you get booted from both roles?
Did you wait for me just to show
how concerned you are?
I'm saying this because
I feel sorry for you.
After all, you're my friend.
You're going to feel
very desolate later on.
I'd rather have you leave now.
Desolate?
Myung-Pil promised me that
he'll never talk to you again.
The 8 years you spent
with him was in vain.
Right, you're very competent.
My husband fell for you,
and you kicked me out.
I give you credit for that.
That's probably what
Myung-Pil wanted too.
With enough people,
you can stand against heaven.
Everyone told me
that I couldn't do anything.
But there's something
Myung-Pil and you don't know.
I have something that you don't.
That's enough to stand against heaven.
And what would that be?
Sincerity.
You're always insecure
because you don't have that.
Why do you need Myung-Pil
to promise that to you?
You want to kick me out
because you're insecure.
You're scared that an average person like me might win this fight with you.
I feel sorry for you.
Don't mind me.
Just do your own thing.
You know how to make money, but you don't know how to act like a person.
Hey!
Come over here!
Thanks for the great show.
Gyung Guk-Hee...
Hello, Tae-Ran.
I can't take this anymore.
Can you come home early tonight?
We need to talk.
Okay, I'll be home early.
Bye.
What happened?
I can't get a day of rest!
My back aches and I'm tired!
I can't live like this!
What's wrong with my life?
You said you need a breakthrough.
The pain comes with the breakthrough.
Officer Oh!
Where's Kim Jo-Han?
A large sum of money was exchanged at the time he signed up for life insurance.
Kim Jo-Han was telling the truth.
But I told him to go home.
He kept on talking about ghosts...
Where's Kim Jo-Han?
I don't know.
He's probably home.
I only got $280 for
selling my wedding ring.
That's because it's not a real diamond.
I can't believe he got you
a fake wedding ring.
Aren't you mad?
No, his heart was as precious
as a diamond at the time.
I'm angrier that
he's calling Su-Duk 'Fatso.'
I'll get your ring back after
I get my house and a job.
That ring's important to you.
You can go ahead.
I have to stop by the market.
I'll look for anything to recycle.
Nam Jang-Mi!
What are you doing here?
You told me to come find you
whenever I want!
We need to talk.
Okay, let's talk outside.
Outside?
Okay, let's go outside.
Don't touch me.
Okay.
Don't touch me!
I won't.
Jang-Mi.
Excuse me. Where's building 2?
Building 2?
Over there.
This is building 3.
Thank you.
Help!
Come over here!
- Help!
- You're so dead!
- Stop right there!
- Let me go!
- Let go!
- Let's walk side by side.
Don't touch me.
Fine.
I told you not to touch me!
Fine, fine. Let's go.
I won't touch you.
I told you not to touch me!
Hi.
Let me go! Let go! Let me go!!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get her inside!
Get her inside!
Stop it! Let me go!
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
Jang-Mi!
Hello, Tae-Ran, I'm almost here.
You're already outside?
Come to the roadside.
Stop it!
Officer!
Jang-Mi!
Myung-Pil!
What the heck?
Follow that car!