Myung-Pil...there's a murderer
at your wife's place!
- What?
- I heard someone died.
- Who died?
- Pardon me?
- Your wife...
- Guk-Hee?
Guk-Hee!
- Myung-Pil...
- Guk-Hee!
- Last Episode -
Guk-Hee, don't die!
I love you, Guk-Hee...
You were my one and only love!
I don't want to divorce you,
but I didn't have the nerve to tell you...
I can't live without you...
I'll die with you!
What are you doing?
Guk-Hee!
Guk-Hee! You're alive!
- Get up.
- What the...
Tae-Ran...
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you slap my son!
Mother...just leave her alone.
Hurry! We don't have much time.
Clear the way.
- Let me go!
- Be quiet!
Let me go!
You guys just wait and see.
You're gonna get it.
All hell broke loose.
You reap what you sow.
In other words, serves her right.
What does Guk-Hee's
husband really want?
He's confusing me.
Let's go.
Thank you. Let's take
my car to the station.
- You guys are all okay, right?
- Yes.
I'll take you guys in my car.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
Too bad.
I'm not the fool who's still attached.
You're scared that an average person like me might win this fight with you.
I feel sorry for you.
Don't mind me. Just do your own thing.
You know how to make money, but you don't know how to act like a person.
Hello?
What now?
Can you...stay here with me?
I'm too scared to go home.
What am I suppose to do now?
Why are you asking me that for?
You saw why I got smacked.
I told her that I love you
because I thought she was you....
People can act irrational
when you put them on the spot.
When you asked me for a divorce,
I told you that I'll be an acupuncturist.
That was crazy.
Just tell her that you didn't mean it.
Today has been a rough day for me.
I need some rest.
Guk-Hee...
Hello?
It's me, Tae-Ran.
I have a favor to ask.
You wore those clothes yesterday.
Was it a one-night stand?
I was at the sauna last night.
Mr. Hur!
You're a lucky man.
Mr. Hur, did you do some lobbying?
What? What's going on?
You've been assigned to work
as a correspondent in America.
What?
Hello?
It's me, Tae-Ran.
Why didn't you come home last night?
I guess you didn't have
a good night's rest.
Uh...I was at the sauna.
I heard about the reassignment.
The VP here is a friend of my dad.
I think it's a good opportunity for us.
I wanted to take
a year off from work too.
Uh...Tae-Ran.
I don't think it's a good idea to...
We don't need to talk about
the things we're uncomfortable with.
We can talk about it later
when we're ready.
I'll look into schools for
Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk.
Okay...
You told me that
you don't remember what I told you...
...or how many times I told you, right?
I waited a thousand days.
I'm very confident about my decision.
I hope you enjoy the rest of your life.
What the...
It's her!
Ask her! Yun-Shil is still alive!
Don't making things up.
I'm not making things up!
Remember when you tried
to get Sniff and me but missed us?
Who called the Police?
It was a girl, right?
Did she tell you her name? No!
That was Yun-Shil!
She's still alive.
I want to sleep...
Get up! I'm treating you to tequila!
This is expensive!
I don't care. I want to go home.
Mr. Yeom! I don't want to go home!
Stay here with me.
Just tell Tae-Ran that you love your wife!
Can you tell her for me?
You're nuts.
I want to go home.
I'm gonna go home. Bye.
Mr. Yeom! I'll buy a really
expensive wine for you!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Tae-Ran, I'm sorry,
but it was just a fling....
Let's break up.
Tae-Ran, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry....
I don't want to be a correspondent...
and I...don't want your money.
Tae-Ran...
What are you doing?
It'll take 20 days to arrive by ship.
We should start packing.
Why don't we look for
a place in Rancho Santa Fe?
We can go to the Horton Plaza,
the San Diego Zoo, and Point Loma.
Isn't it great?
Do you have anything else to pack?
Aren't you going to bed?
Tae-Ran, I have an article to write.
I think I need to pull an all-nighter.
Really?
Okay, goodnight.
Myung-Pil.
- Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk!
- Mommy!!
Oh, my babies...
Look at this!
I have Keroro stickers for you!
I got two stickers in one bag!
Awesome!
Hi.
You must've been through a lot.
Taking care of these boys is so tiring.
Kids need their mother
to take care of them.
Don't worry about the kids.
Just do what I've always been doing.
I'm late! I'm late!
Why are you here?
Did you sleep over here last night?
Well, it's none of my business.
I better get going now. Bye.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
You know that this is supposed
to be the man's job, right?
I want to get out of here.
That's the only thing
on my mind right now.
Remember the first day we made love?
It was great and we wanted each other.
I...love Guk-Hee.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I...love Guk-Hee.
How can you say that to me?
But it's true, Tae-Ran.
Get your hand off me!
- Tae-Ran!
- Let go!
- Let go! Let go!!
Tae-Ran, I yearned for a star.
I left because I thought
I would be happier on that star!
But after I got there,
I realized how great the earth is.
I don't want to be a star!
I'm sor...
Don't!
Don't tell me that you're sorry.
I won't let you say that.
I'm the one who's dumping you.
I'm disappointed in you because
you can't get over Guk-Hee.
I'm over you now.
Looking good.
Why, I ought to...
Fatso?
I told you not to call me Fatso!
Why, I ought to...
Wait...
You're Fatso?
What happened to my Fatso?
You should call me Cutie from now on.
Oh yeah! It's been 15 days.
Remember, I'll leave you
when I get enough X's.
Why, I ought to...
Jang-mi, let's go!
All the men in this neighborhood
lust over other women.
How annoying.
What's this?
What's all this?
We came here to play poker
before you leave.
What happened?
Mr. Hur! Mr. Hur!
I'm not going to America,
and I don't want to play poker.
Go away.
Myung-Pil.
Mr. Yeom! Maybe I should
just kill myself?
Don't say that.
That's wrong.
What am I supposed to do then?
Myung-Pil, listen.
Unlike us, the wives we married
in penury are benevolent.
If you play your cards right,
she might forgive you.
Just act dumb.
Go for it!
I am Hur Myung-Pil!
Gyung Guk-Hee, here I come!
Honey! Honey!
Guk-Hee!
Eun-Suk! Gi-Suk!
Hi, Dad!
After a storm comes a calm.
Hardships come to those
who press onward.
Let's just say that this will
strengthen our bond.
Let's just shake it off.
Pack your things and come home!
We can talk at home.
Kids! I'm talking to you too!
Yes, Guk-Hee! Come!
Yes...
You're going to pack your things, right?
See that?
Kids! Pack your things too
and let's go home!
Kids, I have to go.
Honey, I'll be back.
Myung-Pil!
Not you again...
Do you want her now that
she's not yours anymore?
What?
You think I'm ridiculous, right?
Still, I don't have to hear that from you!
Of course you do.
I'm the closest man to Guk-Hee.
I don't know about before, but you can't act dumb in front of Guk-Hee anymore.
As her man, I'd like to
tell you to give it up.
You're too late.
No, I'm not!
What makes you say that?
That's up to Guk-Hee.
Her man?
Yeah right.
I know Guk-Hee very well.
You don't know anything.
More people asked to put ads on our Good Wife Disqualification Club!
Really?
We're making a lot of money.
We won't have to worry
about food anymore.
What now?
I hate bad drunks!
Me too! What's his problem?
So noisy!
I think he's in front of our house!
Who is he?
- I'll go and check.
- Okay.
What is this?
Oh my, who is that?
Guk-Hee!
Hello, everyone!
What are you doing?
Just kidding.
What do you think you're doing?
Get up! Get up!
You've completely lost it.
Get up! Not here!
You've completely lost it. Get up!
What is this, the refugee camp?
How annoying!
Are you out of your mind?
Look at you!
I hate that too.
He's completely wasted.
Guk-Hee. Guk-Hee...
Guk-Hee!
Guk-Hee... Hey...
I'm not Fatso! I'm Cutie...
What's wrong with the people
in this house?
Including him!
He's so...
Why aren't you sleeping?
I knew it from the beginning.
You didn't reek of alcohol at all.
Yes, I put on a show.
What do you think you're doing?
Be quiet!
Why should I be quiet?
You dork!
I was in junior high
when you were in diapers!
So? You don't even act your age.
What the...
Let's settle this once and for all tonight.
Sounds good.
Loser gives up Guk-Hee.
Gives up?
Why, I ought to...
You're going to lose!
You should call home and tell your parents to prepare for your funeral.
Why don't you call them instead,
old man!
Don't call me an old man!
You don't like that one?
Fine then. Hey man!
Hey man?
Don't hey man me!
Okay then.
Yo, Myung-Pil!
Why, I ought to...
I'm going to kill you!
Dork!
You're going to get it!
What's going on?
What are you guys doing?
Stop it!
Not you again!
Honey! He punched me harder!
That's exactly what I told you
when I had a fight with Tae-Ran.
You didn't even listen to me,
and told me that it was my fault.
Get out. Now!
Honey, I have something to tell you.
I just didn't have
the chance to say it to you.
Please let me talk to you tomorrow! Please?
What do you want to give me?
I don't want anything from you.
I saw your notebook.
One thousand days...
These are the divorce papers.
This is the last thing I can do for you.
You're free now.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to go back,
but I didn't have the nerve to.
I was too prideful.
I was agitated because I didn't know when we'll buy a house...
...and pay for the kids' tuition.
I was tired of making it through the day.
I was always being compared to others.
Then I felt as though I got
a magic wand in my hand.
I don't think I gave much though
about where happiness comes from.
I'm not saying that making and raising
a family with you didn't make me happy.
I just wasn't used to it.
Can you please forgive me?
I haven't forgotten the vow
I made at this place.
I was just disillusioned for a short time.
Right, this is where we had our wedding.
You made your vow there, and so did I.
We were happy.
We didn't know what
our marriage will be like.
I trusted your vow,
and I tried to keep mine as well.
After 8 years, our promises faded.
You should've let me keep my faith.
That would've given me
the courage to start all over again.
The promises we made
in the beginning have been tainted.
What has become of them now?
No matter how tough and demanding life is, you shouldn't have gone that far.
I don't want to start over again.
Dig in.
Look at your face!
You've gotten so pale.
Here's your soup.
Mom...
You taught me to study hard
and become successful.
How come you never taught me
to become a good husband?
Teach you to become a good husband?
Was that my job?
I'm supposed to learn.
I need to know in order to live well.
I don't feel like eating.
Gi-Suk, bye.
Bye.
Let's go.
If you don't want to start over,
you don't have to try.
I'll put in all the efforts from now on.
I'll be here everyday
for the next 1,000 days.
I'll show you that
I can be a good husband.
Today's my first day.
And how are you going to do that?
Uh...for as long as I live, you will be
the only woman in my life!
I'll never have any
other woman besides you.
I swear!
Do you think you can be a good husband by not cheating on me?
That's a given.
Guk-Hee!
Time to go to the fish market.
Here's a list of the things we should buy.
- Check if anything's missing.
- I think this is good.
Why, that...
Hi!
Hi.
What are you doing?
I'll do all the grocery shopping
if you live with me.
I'll do all the dishes.
We can split all the household chores.
What do you think?
You don't know what's really important.
That's your problem.
And what would that be?
Guk-Hee!
Why, you...
You wanted to take a seminar
on managing websites, right?
- Yes.
- There's one today.
Let's go and check it out.
Are you sure it's free?
I'll get my purse.
Wait.
Ta-dah!
It's already here.
Good.
Have fun.
Bye.
Why, that little...
You should give me
some credit for trying.
Do Eun-Suk's science and math homework, brush the kids' teeth.
Get flu shots for the kids and
go on family trips every weekend.
Don't play poker.
It's too long to finish
reading in one sitting.
I'm going to do everything on the list! What do you think?
Good job.
But you still don't know
what's really important.
And what will that be?
Tell me. I'll put it on the list.
Find out for yourself.
Guk-Hee, it's almost time.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Where are you going?
Let's take a 5 minute break.
You're beautiful!
Tae-Ran, let's meet up.
I came here to interview you
even though this isn't my story.
Want to play poker?
Hey, we're here to work.
Your new screenplay is titled
"The Murder Case of Mr. Hur."
A man named Mr. Hur is chopped
and murdered into 32 pieces.
Why did you decide to write
something so grotesque?
You usually write about love.
There's no such thing as love...
What happened?
You can overcome your doubt with love!
Tae-Ran, let me help you.
What will happen if people
find out that Yun-Shil is alive?
Sniff and White Pants will be free.
They'll probably blame
everything on Yun-Shil.
That'll be awful.
Hello?
Newspaper?
You want to do an article about
the Good Wife Disqualification Club?
You're getting more and more ads.
Your club is getting lots of
support from other women.
Things really must be tough
for the other women out there.
Myung-Pil, do you have
anything to ask them?
No.
Can I take a picture of you three?
Sure thing!
Hold on...
Ta-dah!
By the way, why don't you cover the Good Wife Disqualification Club's...
...boyfriend?
Ta-dah!
I'm their boyfriend.
Are you the cute boyfriend they write about on their message board?
Yes, Suk-Doo.
I wish I had a boyfriend like you.
I have to use the restroom.
I'm the one who dumped Myung-Pil.
I want to give work
my undivided attention.
You didn't win.
You don't need to confirm that with me.
I never competed with you.
We can't have a competition
because we're walking different paths.
Is that so?
Then why did we end up
meeting each other?
Because everyone's
looking for happiness.
Myung-Pil and you started going out because you both wanted to be happy.
That's how the three of us
got tangled up like this.
Why are you so confident?
Are you telling me that
you found a way to be happy?
Yes, and I hope you find it too.
You don't need to worry about me.
Gyung Guk-Hee!
I'm sorry.
What? Sure, I'll be there.
We're busy as a bee today.
We need to go to the real estate agency right after the interview.
Real estate agency? For what?
For the house you sued for.
Let's go!
Wait, I'll get the car ready.
Okay.
Oh, and another thing.
Women won't agree that you need
to be financially set to be a good wife.
Does that mean you don't think
we have a modern good wife?
No, we need a modern good wife.
But if you think about it,
why say 'good wife?'
Where's the self?
A woman will be unhappy if she lives...
...only as someone's mother
or wife instead of living as herself.
I think a good wife is someone
who pursues her own happiness.
Especially in this day and age,
a woman will go postal...
...if she doesn't pursue
her own happiness.
Su-Duk agrees with Guk-Hee.
I'm with Guk-Hee!
Let's go.
Gyung Guk-Hee, Nam Jang-Mi,
and Kim Su-Duk...
This is the first time I've sold
a house under three women's names.
A place where we can take each other in no matter what the circumstances are...
This is the Good Wife
Disqualification Club headquarters.
Su-Duk is so happy!
How did Yun-Shil think of this?
I'm disappointed in you guys.
What about me?
You're a lifetime member.
You can come by anytime...
as our boyfriend.
Really?
Girls, you do know that
we have a lot to do today, right?
Where are we going now?
We're supposed
to meet up with Yun-Shil.
You're right!
Let's go.
Thank you. Bye!
I'm Gyung Guk-Hee,
and I'm at the beach!
This time, I came at daytime!
Hello, beach!
I'm here too! I'm free!
Hey! Su-Duk is here too!
I don't have to cook tonight!
Their boyfriend Park Suk-Doo
is here too! Yes!
How annoying...
Yun-Shil!
Awesome!
Myung-Pil, you might have
to give that award back.
The women are angry that you need
to be financially set to be a good wife.
We should write about the
Good Wife Disqualification Club asap.
Oh, and about what you wife said...
Okay, I'll make a decision.
A woman who pursuits her own happiness is the modern good wife.
Fine, I'll make her a modern good wife!
This is great.
The air of freedom.
I love freedom.
I'm impressed. You always
tell us that you hate something.
There are things that I like.
It's just that I didn't mention them.
Su-Duk is happy too.
I feel as though I'm flying.
I wonder what would've happened if
we didn't come to the beach that night.
We would've stayed the same.
My family would still be
blaming me for losing that house.
Su-Duk was a Fatso...a woman
who hides food from her husband.
I might've committed suicide after
being cooped up in my house all alone.
I was a loner who couldn't tell
anyone what I was going through.
I think your dreams came true.
We made it big,
but our dreams didn't come true.
Our dream wasn't to throw
White Pants and Sniff into prison.
I've always wanted to help others.
You already did.
You helped size 8 women
by finding clothes for them.
Hey, you're right!
What about Su-Duk?
Su-Duk wanted to be a stewardess.
You said you feel as though you're flying.
Your dream came true.
Is that so?
You're right...
I think I like this better.
I've always wanted to have a family.
I'm still by myself.
You think you're by yourself?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm no longer by myself.
Does that mean I'm the only one left?
I wanted to be a good wife.
No, but you got to be something else.
You became
a modern good wife instead.
You found your happiness and
found your family's happiness.
We're on a roll.
How annoying.
There you go again!
How annoying!
- But we like you!
- Don't!
A mental institute? Me?
We've been keeping an eye
on you for the last few days.
We think you need help.
Hey! Why are you sending me
to the nuthouse?
Yun-Shil is still alive!
Hey! Yun-Shil is still alive!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Why should I go to a nuthouse?
I think it's been about 5 years
since I came to a place like this.
What's up?
Guk-Hee, this wasn't easy.
I've contemplated this over and over...and finally reached a decision.
Remember, not everyone can
make a decision like this.
Just get to the point.
A good wife who pursuits her own happiness is the modern new wife.
Got it!
Truthfully, you do smile a lot
when you're with Suk-Doo.
If Suk-Doo Park makes you happy,
I'll approve of him.
That little kid, Suk-doo Park!
I'll acknowledge him as your boyfriend.
I'll pursue your happiness.
There's more.
Boyfriend Coupon
Tae-Ran and I...only slept
with each other 9 times.
That's it.
I was too busy fighting with you,
and even got a backache.
Why are you telling me this?
I'll give you 9 coupons.
Remember what I promised you?
To get even?
You can get even with me.
I'm speechless.
Guk-Hee!
You're smiling!
You smiled!
It's been so long since
you last smiled at me.
You only smile at Suk-Doo.
Thank you.
Thanks, Guk-Hee.
Okay then!
I'll give you one more coupon!
What?
This is it, Guk-Hee.
This is how we can start over.
Start over?
No...this means a lot to me.
Just give me one month.
I'll show you how much
I can change in one month.
If you still don't want me after
one month, I'll accept your decision.
Even if we don't get back together,
one month is not a waste of time.
You can spare me a month, right?
Please, Guk-Hee?
Fine, you have a month.
That's it.
Since you gave this to me, I'll take it.
Sure! Take it! Take it!
Boyfriend coupon?
How can you give that to your wife?
Guk-Hee smiled.
That's all I need.
What if she uses it on that kid?
Well...
I'm happy right now.
Don't ruin it.
That made her smile, right?
Yes.
Can you tell me
how to make that coupon?
Do I write 'Boyfriend Coupon'
on a piece of paper?
You don't need to
put an expiration date?
How do you make that?
What are you doing?
My wife found out that
I've been sleeping around.
What?
If I don't do something for her,
she'll ask for a divorce.
How am I supposed
to make that coupon?
She sent us plane tickets.
She's going to invite all of us!
Including Eun-Suk and Gi-Suk!
Wow!
You're right! Kim Su-Duk!
That means Su-Duk
can finally get on a plane!
Wait a second...Nigeria?
Yun-shil is in Africa!
But of all the countries, why Nigeria?
Nigeria?
Yun-Shil is awesome!
That place practices polyandry.
I knew she had a dirty mind!
Africa...how exciting!
Something always happens
when I'm with you guys.
Don't say that.
What if we lose someone?
Don't lose anyone.
I'm going to date an African chief.
Me too.
The size 8 women of Korea
are waiting for Su-Duk.
Don't worry! Even if we lose someone,
we'll solve the case again!
Cutie!
Cutie! Cutie!
Cutie! Let me go with you.
I even got a ticket.
No, I don't want to go with you.
Cutie! I'll do anything you say.
I'll call you Cutie and
thank you every time you cook for me.
Take me with you.
I don't want to.
Su-Duk never asked you to come!
Cutie...
Go away! Why I ought to....!
- Let's go guys.
- Let's go.
Guk-Hee!
Honey!
Eun-Suk! Gi-Suk!
Take me with you.
What are you doing?
I got myself a ticket.
I can speak English.
People in Nigeria speak Hausa.
I can speak Hausa.
What about the treasurer?
You need a treasurer
to manage money during the trip.
Yes! That's very important!
Wait! That's my job.
That's his job.
- I think we should go on our own.
- Huh?
Hey, why don't we go together?
What?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
You two can go together.
Are you sure you're not
going to get into any trouble?
Of course not!
Don't mind us two.
Right, don't mind us.
Let's go.
By the way, what was the body
we burned thinking it was Yun-Shil?
You're right.
It's a mystery, I tell you.
I hate mysteries.
Subtitles Provided by MBC America