Yun-Shil!
Yun-shil, where are you?
Answer me!
Yun-Shil!
Yun-shil, where are you?
Yun-shil!
Yun-Shil!
Answer me!
Where is she?
Yun-Shil! Yun-Shil!
Yun-Shil...
What are we going to do?
We can't find her.
It's almost morning.
Su-Duk needs to go and make breakfast.
Oh, no...
Call her.
I don't know her number.
Do you?
No.
Wait, she called her cell phone with my phone because she couldn't find hers.
Really?
I found it!
Is it me?
No.
I think it's from the restroom.
But we were here before.
Yun-Shil... Yun-Shil...
Yun-Shil...
She told us that she's going to the restroom around...3:30am.
We started looking
for her around 4...right?
Huh?
I think so.
Oh no, oh no!
I have to go and make breakfast.
I see.
Let's talk outside.
Is she going to be okay?
Maybe she ran away,
maybe she didn't.
Well, I can't tell you anything as of now.
Did you all see the
pervert from the restroom?
No, only one person did.
I saw him too.
I remember how he looks like.
I need your info.
Your names, addresses...
No! I can't give it to you!
I don't want someone to find me!
Give it to me.
We need it for the missing person.
Don't worry,
we won't disclose it to anyone.
Officer, Su-Duk needs to go
and make breakfast.
Let us go, please?
We need to go home as soon as we can.
We can't be late.
I see, but we need one person
to come to the station with us.
I'll stay.
Okay, you can come with me.
The rest of you can leave after
giving us your numbers and addresses.
Im Tae-Ran! You're so lucky!
You have everything!
Are you okay?
Don't worry, I can swim my way out
even if I fell into a jar of liquor.
You're not the only one
having a tough time.
Who else is having a tough time? You?
Kang Jin dumped me.
We've been going out for over a year,
but he didn't say anything.
So I proposed to him first.
And?
He said he likes me, and that
I'm perfect, except...I'm too old.
What a dimwit!
He's the same age as you, right?
That kid doesn't know anything.
Tae-Ran, you're the kind of girl
a man should marry.
Look at me!
Look what happened to me because
I didn't marry someone like you!
I should've married you when
you told me that you like me.
Don't you think so?
I should've married you instead!
Myung-Pil...
Myung-Pil! That hurts...
Tae-Ran, are you okay?
Myung-Pil, where are we?
You're heavy.
Myung-Pil...
Tae-Ran!
Myung-Pil!
I have to go. I have a meeting to attend.
Why is there so much traffic?
Hurry!
What are we going to do?
Be quiet, will you?
You have nothing to worry about because you don't have a husband.
Are you bragging that
you have husband?
What are we going to do?
If this is a dream, please wake me up.
Oh, no!
It's morning, and this isn't a dream.
I can't believe I didn't
go home last night.
Me too!
My husband should
be back from his shift.
I'm so dead!
I hate people who bring
trouble upon others!
Oh, no...
Lord, what should I do?
My pass! My pass!
Be quiet, will you?
Please let me make
breakfast for my kids.
My husband didn't call.
My husband didn't call either! How come you didn't remember to bring your pass?
Ah!! Be quiet!! Quiet!!
What are we going to do?
Hurry up!
Be quiet!
Were you worried about me?
I had a few drinks because
I was in a bad mood.
I found myself at the bar in the morning.
Things like this happen when men drink!
I wonder if she'll buy that.
She has no choice!
She didn't see what happened last night!
This is driving me crazy...
Honey, I went to the beach
because I was in a bad mood.
No, no... Honey...
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
This is the first time
I stayed out until morning!
Honey...
No.
Please forgive me, honey.
I'll do anything you say.
I shouldn't have had
that cocktail last night...
Honey...
Ho...honey...
Why is she here?
Was she waiting for me?
He's here to get me.
What am I going to do?
This is driving me crazy.
Why isn't she saying anything?
I didn't come home last night.
I thought he'd say something about it.
Mom!
Did you decide to get
on my bad side for good?
Did you guys go for a walk...
...after making your old
mother-in-law take care of the kids?
- Mother..
- Mom..
I sent Eun-Suk to school.
He wants his art homework.
Okay.
B...B..Bye.
Bye, Grandma!
By the way!
You have to get Grandfather's
memorial from his brother's house.
But the house is a little too small...
I was going to let you bring it
after you buy a house...
...but I don't know
when that's going to be.
Let's get the dishes
for the service for now.
Okay.
Goodbye, Grandma.
Are you hungry?
Huh?
Uh...yes.
That's weird.
Why isn't she doing anything?
Maybe she doesn't know that
I didn't come home last night.
He doesn't look mad.
Maybe he doesn't know that
I didn't come home last night.
Did she go to bed early?
Maybe he was too drunk to remember.
I'll make you breakfast.
Okay...
Honey!
When did you sleep last night?
Huh?
Uh...I was too drunk last night.
I can't remember anything.
You can't remember anything?
No...I can't.
Oh...I see...
I went to bed early last night
because I was tired.
I feel asleep in Eun-Suk's room.
I was lost in thought in
Euk-Suk's room, and fell asleep.
I see!
I came home drunk last night.
When I woke up, I found myself
in the computer room!
So that's why you didn't see me.
I see!
You look tired.
You must've had a lot to drink.
Yes, I drank more than I should!
You look tired too.
I guess you didn't get
much sleep last night.
You're right.
I'll make you breakfast.
Good, I need it to relieve my hangover.
Gi-Suk.
Behave, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
What happened?
He must've thrown a fit.
You didn't tell him about me, right?
He doesn't know
that I didn't come home.
He was too drunk last night
and couldn't remember.
Good.
Su-Duk!
Are you okay?
Oh, no...
My husband threw a spoon at me.
He's the pitcher for the
neighborhood baseball team.
I'm grounded now.
He said he'll throw the rice cooker at me if I leave home without permission.
What are you doing here?
I'll be fine as long as I'm within 100m.
I can answer the phone
and pretend I'm home.
I'm sorry.
It was my idea to go to the beach.
I'm glad I divorced.
Her family must be worried about her.
They must be wondering
if she's dead or alive.
I'm sure they called the cops.
Is Yun-Shil back?
I think so.
Wait.
Hello?
Her husband looks like a nice person.
The Police took Yun-Shil's cell phone.
They said no one called her.
Then...why does he look so nonchalant?
Maybe she called.
Maybe she called her family.
Maybe.
Shall we ask her husband if she called?
What if she didn't?
He'll tell us to do something about it.
I hate getting myself into
someone else's business.
Are you telling us that
we should do nothing?
The cops told us not to talk about it.
If she ran away,
then what we say can wreck a home.
What's this?
Look who we have here.
Birds of the same feather flock together.
You guys split last night
without cleaning up, right?
Split?
Come on.
We're all neighbors here.
Let's be nice to each other.
I don't think of you as my neighbor.
Me neither.
Where we you last night?
None of you guys picked up
your interphones.
I don't have to tell you that.
You're not the Police.
Look at these fatheads!
How dare you talk back to me
when you split without cleaning up?
Ooh, I'm scared.
I know...
I'll clean it like you say
by the end of this week.
So...
What do you take me for?
Sure, I'll show you what
it means to mess with me.
Choi! Kim! What's with the long faces?
You guys look like miserable
white-collar workers.
You're going to get wrinkles
on your forehead.
Smile, life's not too bad, right?
Are you happy about something?
Can you tell?
Can you help me be happy, too?
I texted Tae-Ran,
but I heard nothing from her.
Help me meet up with her.
Hey, I was going to ask him that!
Don't take her from me.
I'm not kidding.
I felt a connection with Tae-Ran
when we played poker.
Yeah right.
Did you see how much Tae-Ran
laughed whenever I made a joke?
Thanks.
My father taught me to enjoy my life.
Let's start enjoying our lives.
Mr. Yeom!
Yes?
Just between us, you're a master
when it comes to one-night stands.
People will think you're
serious if they hear this.
It's just between us.
What is it?
What happens if she doesn't call
after a one-night stand?
One night stand means
it's just for one night.
You're not supposed to call
the other person the next day.
She left a note saying she's leaving.
They both know each other's numbers.
She can text him, right?
That means she has come to her senses.
She's disappointed in the guy.
Forget about it.
You're supposed to forget about one-night stands after the night is over.
What if she's someone I know?
That's the worst one-night stand
out of them all!
You'll only get yourself embarrassed
and lose a friend!
You have nothing to gain!
Don't worry.
Just take it one step at a time.
If you want to continue the relationship, you can be her boyfriend.
If you regret what you've done...
...forget about the one-night stand and pretend as if nothing has happened.
I guess I had too much to drink...
Tears aren't the only things
a man shouldn't spill.
I'm getting the memorial dishes from your brother's house.
Can you come and help me carry them?
We should've taken
them a long time ago.
Thanks for taking care of them.
You're welcome.
I'm busy.
Sheesh...
Myung-Pil, I'm at a cafe
near your workplace.
Yes!
Persistence is the key.
I called after getting tired of texting.
She answered the phone!
I was having an interview
nearby when he called.
What's this?
She's too nonchalant.
And I'm sure you know that
love is all about timing.
You should be a writer.
It'll be a waste to use your lines
for hitting on girls only.
What?
Maybe she doesn't remember.
Myung-Pil, stop him!
Huh? Okay...
If you regret what you've done, forget about the one-night stand and...
...pretend as of nothing has happened.
Choi!
What do you think you're doing?
How many good articles
have you written lately?
Myung-Pil...
Now's not the time to hit on her!
Now's the time to! Get coffee.
I'll go and get coffee!
Tae-Ran...
We drank a lot last night.
I haven't been that drunk
in about 10 years.
I must've been a handful.
Thanks.
Were you that drunk?
You don't remember anything?
I was really drunk.
You were drunk too.
We were drunk!
We were both drunk!
We were really drunk!
I wasn't drunk.
I remember everything.
Actually, I enjoyed it.
Yes!
I'm back!
Do you remember
Myung-Pil's friend Ji-Hoon?
He's moving into a huge
apartment in a rich neighborhood.
He never beat Myung-Pil in anything, except for marrying into a rich family.
Myung-Pil will be upset
if he hears that Ji-Hoon bought a home.
Don't tell him.
Excuse me, can you
drop me off over there?
Why?
Why don't we go out for dinner tonight?
I'll tell Myung-Pil to come home early.
Why?
You had a tough day yesterday
because of the house.
I'm not okay with it either,
but we have no choice.
We have to start working hard again.
So...
Okay.
Go home.
Bye!
Don't tell him.
It's me, Tae-Ran.
Where are you?
I don't have anywhere else
to go but my workroom.
'Tis a shame for a beautiful
woman like my Tae-Ran...
...to waste her day in a workroom.
The phone...
Hello?
Hello, Guk-Hee.
But it's very encouraging to see how you're using your talent to benefit...
...the movie industry.
I'll bring some snacks
to cheer you up tonight.
Bye.
Your wife wants you to come home
early to have dinner with your mom.
Go home, your mom's waiting for you.
Geez...
Myung-Pil...
...let me give you some advice.
Stop it. Don't start.
You should be thankful for
the wife who takes cares of you.
You'll be punished if you
hurt a woman like that.
Your wife's an acupuncturist,
and my wife is a housewife.
Are you mocking me?
You always have one-night stands.
What a hypocrite.
I only do one-night stands,
but you're starting a relationship.
Do you think you can wreck your home?
I know a thing or two about you.
You'll want more.
That's why I'm giving you this advice.
Just do one-night stands, like I do.
Yes, Honey.
Your mom's coming too.
Fine! Fine!
I'm coming!
Why are you so irritated?
Is it because of the house?
Why do you want to have dinner today?
Why tonight?
You're the biggest
stumbling block in my life.
Yes! I'm coming!
Do you have a problem with that?
Nam Jang-Mi?
That divorcee came to the station?
Yes, Aunt.
She's the woman I saw at the villa.
Why was she at the police station?
I don't know...
Good evening!
I'm Min Seung-Gi,
a promising young officer.
I found out why Nam Jang-Mi
was at the station!
She was a witness to the case transferred from the Sokcho station.
Sokcho?
They went to Sokcho?
Bye.
The food here tastes great, doesn't it?
This is good.
Myung-Pil, dig in.
Okay.
What happened to the house
was tough for me too...
...but I'm sure we'll pull through.
We've saved up a lot already.
I'm sure we can save more.
By the way, maybe I should work
at the market on Sundays too.
They'll pay me twice as much
if I work on Sundays.
Then... who's going to
baby-sit on Sundays?
You should let Myung-Pil
rest on Sundays.
Don't make him baby-sit.
What kind of a plan is that?
Oh, the landlord said she's only going to increase our deposit by $30,000 more.
She gave us a $7,000 discount.
Good for you.
Why don't we just drop the subject?
Let Myung-Pil eat in peace.
You're right, let's not think about this.
I'll work harder.
We'll buy a house in 2 years.
And when we do,
let's live together.
Sounds good.
Try some of this.
Honey, eat.
I need to use the restroom.
Jang-Mi?
What? The Police called?
Did they find Yun-Shil?
No, they want me to confirm
the pervert I saw at the beach.
I was there during the day too.
I don't want to go again.
What should I do?
I have to stay here.
My husband doesn't know
what happened.
Come to my place when you
get back from the station.
Tell me what happened.
Bye.
Hello? Hello?
Are you expecting a phone call?
I waited for the taxi service to call! Satisfied?
Aren't you two going to eat?
- Good evening!
Hi.
The fruit punch is good.
Myung-Pil's sister will love it.
The rice punch I made for you
doesn't have any sugar.
Attention, everyone.
I have two announcements to make.
First, we're not going to discuss remodeling our villa anymore.
Remodeling? That's for
the homeowners to worry about.
The second one is about the women
who threw away their trash illegally.
I'm sure you are all aware they were punished with cleaning up the trash bin.
But these 4 housewives
instead went to the beach...
...and didn't come home that night.
I ask the other residents
to please refrain yourselves...
...from embarrassing the
other good residents here.
This was your head of the
neighborhood association speaking.
Is she talking about you?
You didn't come home last night?
Did you go to the beach?
You didn't come home?
Oh, my...
I had a good reason.
You see...
We just went there
for some fresh air, but...
You didn't come home?
Does this mean you were
on your way home...
...when you met me
in front of the house?
How can you dare leave your kids
home and stay out for the night?
The end is near.
Oh, Lord...
You must be out of your mind!
You're crazy!
How embarrassing!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Honey.
I only wanted some fresh air.
I wasn't planning on spending the night.
Let's go.
I'll explain everything at home.
I don't want to hear it!
Not even your husband
stays out for the night!
Everyone's good at something.
I guess you're good
at ditching your family!
This is so embarrassing.
I don't think I can come back
to this neighborhood again.
Mother...
Mom...
How can you...
Honey...
Honey!
You're already giving me
enough trouble as it is.
And now this?
Yesterday was a tough day for me to.
Tough?
I worked hard to make
money for my family...
...but my wife screwed up
and lost a house!
How about me?
Why did you go to the beach?
A woman doesn't have a reason
not to come home.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You know what camels are, right?
Do you know how camels can
withstand the desert for a week?
They can store 100 liters of water
in less than 10 minutes.
That's what keeps them alive.
Do you know where you get
your 100 liters of water?
It's me!
I'm the one who teaches you
and scolds you!
This is what gets me!
Why do I always have to be
disappointed and mad at you?
I'm sorry.
Be quiet!
Tae-Ran, I'm so frustrated.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Do you want to meet up?
Honey...
Honey, where are you going?
Here, is this the man?
Yes, he's the pervert I saw at the beach.
That's odd.
He doesn't have anything to do
with Lee Yun-Shil.
He was caught drunk driving.
He's been at the station
ever since he was arrested at 2am.
Lee Yun-Shil was missing since 4am.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
What 's wrong with my life, Tae-Ran?
Everyday is a battle.
Think of how tough it is
for a weakling like me.
What's wrong?
You seem to be having
a lot of trouble too.
I get depressed whenever I stay
in that workroom by myself.
Looking out the window...
...made me think about the people...
...who committed suicide
out of loneliness out of loneliness.
My eyes started watering up.
Your husband left?
It's because of the neighborhood association lady, right?
I can't believe she announced that!
She has a family too.
Oh, and about Yun-Shil.
He said it's probably not a criminal case.
He wants us to wait.
I'm sorry for making you go
to the station by yourself.
I don't know what's wrong with my life.
It's one battle after another.
Honey...
I'm tired.
I don't want to talk.
I'm sorry about not coming home
last night, but I had a reason.
I heard your conversation with Tae-Ran.
You told her that you should've
married her instead.
I'm trying to be a good wife.
I'm not always smiling
because I'm happy.
It's tough for me too, but I'm trying
to act cheerful for my family's sake.
How can you say that to me?
I couldn't help myself
after hearing that, so I left.
I just left.
If I didn't...I thought
my head would burst.
It was because of Tae-Ran?
Did you get Botox on your brain again?
I told you to use your brain!
Why do you think I said that to Tae-Ran?
I only said it because
she's better than you are.
She bought two houses,
but you lost a house.
Don't make me feed the need
to say something like that!
Just become a better woman
than Tae-Ran is!
How can you say that?
Because she's better than you!
Because it's true!
A good wife?
And a good mother?
Not everyone can be a good wife!
Especially if you don't
come home for the night!
You're not qualified to be a good wife!
Those pathetic women
are all disqualified!
All of them!
Don't ever hang out with those
pathetic women again, okay?
I'm not going to talk to you
if I see you with them again!
Got that?
Got it.
Your wisdom tooth will
hurt more under stress.
You're stressed out because
you fought with your husband.
Honey, it's me.
Don't skip lunch...
Jang-Mi?
Is Yun-Shil's husband back yet?
There he is.
You didn't have to come.
I heard what happened from the Police.
Oh, so you heard.
You must've been shocked.
She'll be fine.
I think she decided to go on a trip
after a visit to the beach.
People sometimes want
to get away from everything.
I'm sure she'll call soon.
You're not even mad.
I was expecting you to yell at us.
Why would I be mad?
My wife always talked about
how much she misses the beach.
Let's wait for her.
Good things happen to people
who think positively.
You know that, right?
Yun-Shil is so lucky.
He's a gentleman.
What's wrong?
Well...
I don't think he's a good person.
Look at his pants.
He's wearing white linen
pants on a rainy day.
Those pants will be ruined.
You're right.
He's stylish.
Yun-Shil has two kids and
works at a bank, right?
She must've been busy working
and taking care of her kids...
...and her stylish husband.
All families give the woman a hard time.
She must be a good friend.
You're very concerned about her article.
She's my friend,
but she's good enough to be...
...one of the 10 best writers
in Korean cinema.
If you write a good article about her...
...I'll arrange an interview with
Yoon Jenma for you.
Really?
That's a promise!
Don't wear knockoffs.
You should wear designer's clothing.
I'm only going to buy you the real stuff.
I don't mind knockoffs
as long as they're from you.
Let's sit down.
Why don't we go on a trip when
you're done with the screenplay?
Just the two of us.
Sounds great.
But I don't know when I'll be done.
Do you have writer's block?
This is driving me crazy.
All I need is a lead,
but I can't seem to find it.
Why don't you work somewhere else?
It'll help if you change your setting.
Why don't you go to Yangpyeong?
You can rent a cottage.
A cottage by myself?
Sounds horrible.
You won't be alone.
I'll be with you.
Do you want to go today?
Let's look for a good cottage
for you to write in.
Really?
Hello?
The police station?
I hope they found Yun-Shil.
I hope so too.
I don't believe this.
How many times do I have
to go to the police station?
I hate getting myself into
someone else's business.
Are you going to the station?
Get in, I'm going to the station too.
I don't believe this.
What's the matter?
She called in the afternoon.
She's nonchalant about everything.
Where did she go?
Why did she leave?
She's at a friend's house.
She said she'll be home in a few days.
She said she just felt like leaving.
I'm beginning to hate her.
We were worried sick about her!
I know...
Don't leave anything behind.
Okay.
Why aren't you getting off?
Oh...
Most missing people
end up being runaways.
I'm glad nothing bad happened to her.
I told you that nothing bad will happen.
I don't want to take to Yun-Shil anymore.
We got ourselves into
this mess for nothing.
Maybe she ran away because
she didn't want to clean the trash bin!
Maybe that's why.
Don't you think so too?
Huh?
Yeah...
As soon as we verify the husband's call, the Sokcho station will close the case.
Can you verify it right now?
It'll take a few hours.
Call me if she comes home
before we're done.
Okay.
Hi! Are you done?
What are you doing here?
This is my sister.
She was worried about
Yun-Shil the whole day.
Get in, I'll drive you home.
Thank you for coming on a rainy day.
Thank you.
Let's go and get some food for the kids.
Is there a way to erase my phone number from the police files?
Who are you trying to hide from?
No, I'm doing this because I'm
too popular with my good looks.
Anyways, thank goodness it's over.
I'm never going to the beach again.
Bye.
Wait, hold on... I have something
to tell you... hold on.
What's the matter?
Look...
What's this?
Blood!
Get it off me!
I'm scared of blood!
Did you get hurt?
It's not mine.
It's from the white pants
on a rainy day's car.
White pants on a rainy day?
Yun-Shil's husband.
Doesn't this look like the scarf
Yun-Shil had on at the beach?
Don't you remember?
No way...
I think she had a scarf on...
Stop it, you're scaring Su-Duk.
I'm positive she had this scarf on.
You're right!
This is hers!
You're scaring me!
Why is there blood on this?
Why is this in the white pants' car?
It's the white pants!
Look at white pants!
That's the woman we just saw!
I thought she was his sister!
Why did he kiss his sister?
She's not his sister.
Where are you guys going?
Wait! Wait!
I thought you said she's your sister.
Ma'am, please don't meddle
in someone else's affairs.
I'm sure you're preoccupied with just taking care of your own family.
Carry on.
I'll be on my way.
Wait!
Yes?
Are you sure you talked to Yun-Shil?
Did she really call?
Tell me the truth.
Yes.
Just pretend you didn't see that.
I don't like meddling in
someone else's business.
What about this?
Do you want to disregard this too?
Yes.
Let's disregard it.
I don't like being scared.
Su-Duk has a weak heart.
What if this really is Yun-Shil's blood?
What if she's in danger? We can't just act as if nothing happened!
You're right.
I'm scared.
Fine, do whatever you want.
Just leave me out.
That's none of my business.
Maybe it's a pig's blood or just red paint.
I don't care if white pants
kissed his sister or a pig.
I don't know anyone from this neighborhood anyway.
I want to keep it that way.
Same here.
You're right.
We shouldn't get ourselves involved.
If she's in danger,
then her husband should help her.
Yes, but look,
He doesn't seem worried at all.
He's even cheating on her.
If Yun-Shil really is in danger,
who's going to help her?
She's by herself.
Right this way.
That's the master bedroom, right?
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
Thank you.
Goodnight.
Myung-Pil!
Again?
Myung-Pil...
Tae-ran!
Myung-Pil! Myung-Pil!
Get the phone!
No!
Get the phone! Now!
Hello?
Yes, this is Hur Myung-Pil.
The Police?
How can you do this to me?
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
This is too much for me to handle.
What about this scarf?
Tell me why this scarf
was found in your car.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I've never seen that before!
Are you sure you found this in his car?
Yes.
I'm sure.
I found this on the back seat floor.
Look I can get you
imprisoned for slandering!
Don't you have anyone to verify
where you were that night?
I slept at home!
How can I prove that I went to bed?
You're going to regret
that you did this to me.
And you!
I found a lawyer.
Get ready to go to jail.
Calm down...
The file's here.
Seoul 02TA8025.
Is that your license plate number?
Yes.
You went to Sokcho
on the day of the case!
You were caught on speed camera.
Sokcho...
That's where we went.
Excuse me sir...
This man... This man,
there's something fishy about him.
He's even cheating on his wife.
I even saw them kiss.
You saw that too, right?
Look here!
What was your name again?
Gyung Guk-Hee?
Okay, Gyung-Guk-Hee!
Why can't you arrest someone
on the spot for slandering?
Gyung Guk-Hee! I'm going to
throw you in prison!
Understand?
Sit down.
What's going on?
I'm a reporter for Joongdong Daily.
I'm also her husband.
Honey, listen to me.
Be quiet!
Why won't you listen to me?
Be quiet and come with me!
Just hear me out!
Listen to me for once, will you?
Let me explain why I'm doing this.
Something horrible is going on!
Be quiet!
Ouch...
Come on...
Ow, that hurts!
Guk-Hee, are you okay?
Who is he?
You and your friends always
get stuck with scoundrels like him...
...whenever you go.
I got a phone call to
come in for the missing girl.
Honey, are you okay?
Honey?
You have a husband?
Who are you?
Oh...
I'm... Guk-Hee's friend.
What?
Friend?
Subtitles Provided by MBC America