There was an organization...
... that created a drug
that made us immortal.
Transforming the living dead
into zombies.
That was 20 years ago.
Today, zombies dominate the Earth...
... and feed on people,
who afterwards ...
... also become undead.
Humanity is being killed off.
Their disappearance is imminent.
Let's continue.
Aya!
One Chanbara - Vortex
Try not to move.
You are badly hurt.
You're Aya ...
... and Saki.
The two sisters ...
... of the Imichi Clan.
I have been looking for you.
Who are you?
Misery.
And I also ...
... must live with the
damned blood of the Imichi.
I need your help.
The Organization seeks
a pure blood Imichi.
Saki.
You're the first on the list.
The Organization?
Have you heard of it?
The woman who controls it ...
... is called Himiko.
What is this?
Your parents were
among those ...
... killed by the Organization.
Before they died ...
... I begged them to surrender.
Himiko has incredible power.
They caught me,
but I was of no use to them.
But if no one stops them,
they will dominate the world.
Therefore, we must fight together.
Saki!
We have to exterminate
those zombies at once.
We are not fighting for revenge.
Saki, can you give me the red one.
Girls, come with me right away!
Aya, listen carefully.
Himiko has mobilized
her people.
Himiko?
If something happens to us ...
... protect your little sister.
Take care of Saki!
Misery. Don't creep up on me like that.
Saki, do you want to see your mother?
You said that she was dead.
What do you know?
You might be able to see her, but...
... I don't think Aya will agree.
Why?
Because she doesn't like to talk about your mother.
Besides ...
... the risk would be great.
I would do anything ...
... to see her again.
Are you sure?
Then I'll help.
And one ...
two
three
four
five
We will cut the zombies into pieces.
But first we need a solid foundation.
Lets begin again ... and one ...
two
three
four
five
Keep going! Count with me.
And one ...
Ryo?
Take care of the children.
I will go look for food.
Be careful.
Don't be a hero.
There have been increased attacks
in recent days.
They are becoming stronger and stronger.
I know.
I will make sure that nothing happens to them.
And don't lose the whistle.
No way, I will not be
appetizer for any zombie.
Take care.
Come back soon.
Will you play with us then?
- We want to go too!
- We will tear them to pieces.
Hey! Who said you can rest?
Do I rest? We will destroy them
like the last time.
Reiko was the one that did everything,...
... you were paralyzed with fear.
So do not be boastful.
Follow!
What's up, Saki?
Nothing.
Let's keep going.
It's too quiet.
There should be zombies here, but
where are they?
Himiko is ...
... protected by an elite zombie unit.
This unit is completely ...
... under Himiko's control,
and should not be underestimated.
What do you mean?
Himiko must be very close.
They are there.
Are you ready?
That's ... Himiko.
That girl ?
- Impossible!
- Do not trust appearances
Maybe between the 3 of us we can get her.
she is the carrier ...
...of the pure blood
of the imichi.
We have to kill her before the
other zombies come.
Were you looking for me?
Leave Kei alone, damn zombies!
Take them out back.
Come children!
What do you want?
Aya.
Reiko.
Misery ...
She is not an enemy.
She's an old friend.
What are you doing here?
I could ask the same of you.
You! You are the one that commands the
zombies that I have been killing.
And I'll kick your ass too!
She is lying.
She is one of Himiko's zombies.
Were you looking for me?
Leave Kei alone, damn zombies!
You'll be sorry!
Stop!
Saki, what are you doing?
It must be done!
There is a way to
resurrect our parents.
Don't you want to see them again?
The alarm whistle!
I will continue with Himiko's plan.
Out!
Saki!
Over here!
Over here! Hurry!
Hurry!
Ryo!
Kei and Yuta are gone!
Don't worry!
Stay still and quiet!
Kei.
You're safe!
Come on.
I must find Yuta. Stay here.
The others are in a safe place.
I'll be right back, okay?
Good!
He's mine!
Come on!
Look.
What's happening?
Are you okay?
No!
I could not ...
... protect them.
Continue with the condolences.
You must be furious.
A glorious death.
Kei!
Kei, come back to us!
You will understand, when it is finished.
Then we will be able...
... to live together again.
Saki!
Freeze!
She is an old friend.
That was before.
But what about now?
- How can I trust her!
- Ryo!
Reiko.
He is absolutely right.
You don't know if you can trust me
What's so special about Kei?
Why did Himiko take her?
Kei is just a kid.
It is my fault,
I should have expected it.
Ever since she's been on the run,
I've been like a mother to her
Reiko, you stay here.
You have to protect them.
And as for Kei ...
I will follow them and try to save her.
- It will be the best thing.
- But ...?
You stay here too!
Whatever happens
I still will not trust you.
Hey!
Reiko? Where is Ryo?
I thought he was with you?
Will that letter help you find Kei?
I don't know.
Do you realise? It could be a trap.
Do you think so?
Then you'd better turn back.
No way.
Your sister kidnapped Kei.
So I don't trust you either.
Why don't we do the next step?
First clean off all that blood.
You're a mess.
To resurrect your parents
we need your blood as well as mine.
Let's do it.
Why the rush?
We must wait until your
Imichi blood becomes more powerful.
Then we'll do the ritual.
It shouldn't take too long.
It'll be soon...
I promise.
- I didn't need your help.
- I did not do it for you.
What is the Imichi?
It is a wicked blood.
Saki and I have it.
If I come into contact with blood ...
... I lose control.
If that happens...
... I might even try to kill you.
So it would be safer if you stayed
away from me.
Does Kei have Imichi blood?
Almost certainly.
This is the place indicated on your map?
Anyone who enters ...
... does not come out alive.
Aya!
Aya! Aya!
What's the story?
With so much blood I will lose control.
Go away! Get away from me!
Aya!
Help!
Ryo!
We appreciate ...
... that everything has gone well.
Blood is my elixir
to live forever.
Ryo!
Aya.
Are you OK?
I thought that you were dead.
You have saved me.
Thank you.
I don't know what it is.
It's interesting.
When I am next to you...
... my Imichi blood is not out of control.
There is another room...
... that we must inspect.
Aya.
If something happens to me ...
I want you to avenge me ...
for the death of my brother.
I am grateful that you trust me now
You want to save Kei, right?
I can be helpful.
If they catch me, you should continue.
To know the limit
of our capacity...
... is not that simple, is it?
I can't even control myself.
He asked what I am.
Kei is not here.
Saki.
I knew ...
... that you would come.
Where is the girl?
She is with Himiko.
Do not worry.
She won't suffer much longer.
I will bring her when
everything has finished.
I don't care if its finished ...
Bring her now!
You're right.
We should end all this.
I just want ...
... everything to be like before.
I mean, that we will all
be together again.
You do not know what you're doing!
I just want ...
... to see them again.
I want us all ...
to be alive together
That's why I'm helping Himiko
with her search.
She needs the powerful Imichi blood.
Our blood will be
strong enough.
Incredible!
You would really do it?
You would like ...
... to see them again too, right?
Or would your ...
... stepmother mind?
You're crazy if you trust Himiko.
It was her that murdered our parents!
You don't understand.
If we kill Himiko,
we can't return them from the dead.
But with her formula, perhaps
we can create an antidote.
If you trust in me, allow me to do it.
While helping my parents,
I will bring Kei back.
Have you forgotten what we've become?
We're fighting to
stop this madness!
Our parents do not
deserve to return to life this way.
Then I will have to kill you...
... to be able to resurrect you.
Saki!
They are not
adversaries either!
Aya!
Excuse me, Aya.
Somehow I have
absorbed some of your strength.
I don't know how it happened.
You must
have the ability ...
... to neutralize
the Imichi force.
You said...
... its possible that Kei
also has Imichi blood.
I remember ...
... when Kei was very small.
She came into contact
with the blood of an animal.
When I found her she was out of control,
it was quite difficult.
But it was clear ...
... that this girl was
something special for me.
That's the reason
I was always at her side.
It has to be your blood.
Your blood and hers share the same destiny.
You should rest.
What's happening?
It's too quiet!
All the zombies are gone.
This is very strange.
Do you hear?
Why doesn't it shine?
I thought ...
I had killed all her protectors.
But still some remain!
There you are!
Himiko!
Do you not recognize me?
Aya.
Misery.
Come with me.
Together we will create a world
for eternity.
This is madness!
Only those who are on my side ...
... deserve to live.
Think about it.
Your father ...
... and your mother.
... we could return them to life,
even resurrect the children.
If you had not cheated us,
they would still be alive!
You have chosen badly!
I understand.
Get them!
The elixir is ready
Now I will have eternal life ...
... I won't have to be afraid of anything.
Let go of me!
I knew that you would betray me.
I don't need Imichi blood any more.
You're the last of your clan.
Your lineage dies with you.
Is that all?
It will not be easy for you.
Hey!
Saki!
Sorry.
I know...
.. I did wrong.
I just wanted to resurrect them
You see!
It was all part of the plan.
All this.
And also my immortality.
I will be the Queen of the dark kingdom!
Not you!
Are you still thinking about being on
the good side?
Sorry, but the situation
has changed.
Now you are the bad guys!
Kei!
I'm here.
An Imichi like you doesn't mean
anything to me.
Kei.
Take care of yourself and others, right?
- Kei!
Aya, listen
Can you avenge Ryo for me?
Himiko!
Traducción by rosam72 para
http://rosam72-filmaniadescargas.blogspot.com/
Translated from the Spanish subs by Holo69