Ramón?
Ramón!
- What have they done to you?
- Father...
Holy Mother of God!
Look how they messed up
my son...
Stay calm, Ramón.
You'll recover in no time.
All we can do now, is to ask
Barrett for more time.
He will never listen to us.
Believe me son,
it is worth a try!
I wonder why Barrett is so interested
in taking our land away from us.
Why did he give us the money?
Being nice? No...
Barrett is after our land.
He owns 8.000 animals
he has to feed every day.
They already cleared out
many settlers...
By now they
own the property.
When mother and I arrived here,
there was nobody living 'round this place.
The two us worked hard with
our bare hands in the fields.
For two years we ate nothing
but turnips.
The land appeared
to be dead.
A dried out, godforsaken
dusty stony desert.
During the wintertime too frozen
to get a nail into the ground.
Dried out during the summertime,
not a single worm lived in the ground.
But after two years
the land awakened...
Green grass appeared
when the snow melted.
Then came the rain,
and the grain started to grow.
Then you were born.
Your mother died on this land.
She cared for it
to the very last minute.
And the two of us
buried her here on this land.
You remember,
don't you Ramón?
Nobody will run me off
this place!
And those who will try
I'm gonna kill!
Go and see Barrett, Ramón.
Tell him, we're gonna pay him.
We are honest folks.
Ramón!
Tell him, we're gonna pay him.
We are decent people.
Let's learn those bastards a lesson!
Mount up and come on!
I won't, Steven.
I don't like that kind of game.
What's your choice? You want them
going on burning down our houses?
We won't gain anything burning theirs!
The law will protect us!
Did you hear that? The law!
The sheriff couldn't care less.
We have to take the law in our own hands,
or they will run us off our land!
That's right, Ramón.
We have to find justice for us!
Justice this ain't! It is revenge you want!
Go ahead! But leave me out of this!
What if they had burned down your house
instead of Kenneths place?
- What if they had killed your wife?
- They didn't kill anybody.
They beat them up
and burned the crop!
Go tell the sheriff!
After all it's his job!
You are one lousy bastard!
A coward! Just a dirty Mexican!
Leave him alone, Mick!
We don't need people like him!
Just pray, they won't be after
you next time!
If they burn your house,
don't come and see us about it.
Just remember that
you asked for it!
You did fine my son.
Revenge is too easy and unnecessary.
What will be left is a bitter taste,
like eating a green fruit.
But you know that already,
don't you, Ramón?
Stick' em up!
Hurry up bastards!
Hurry up!
Burn the house down!
Burt!
This man wants to see Mister Barrett.
I have to talk to Mister Barrett.
Where can I find him?
Hey, did you see him?
Here is Ramón.
- Why would Mister Barrett talk to you?
- I'm supposed to bring the mortgage.
- Do you have the money?
- Well, to be honest...
I had the money.
I wanted to tell him that, but...
He took it away from me!
I recognize him!
I was attacked and
Mister Barrett's money was stolen.
- What are you talking about, Bastard?
- It was him. I was robbed, I swear to God!
- It was four of them!
- Did you ever saw this panhandler before?
Not that I recall, Boss.
Lots of panhandlers around this area here.
Sure, but but this one here
calls you a thief.
Let him go and let him repeat
what he just said.
I will,
you are a lousy thief!
What's going on, Slim?
What's wrong with you?
Beating up a guy in my house?
This man says Slim stole money from him
that he was going to bring to you.
That's right.
Ramón,
I was expecting you.
Is that story true?
Who robbed you?
He and three others robbed me while
I was on my way to bring you the money.
Is he right?
- Is it true?
- He is a dirty lyer!
I saw him!
I tore his mask down his face!
- Can you prove what you say?
- No, I was all alone.
I can assure you I'm not wrong
about this. It WAS him.
That is
a serious accusation.
If you can't prove it, you are
in serious trouble.
Believe me, I was on my way
to bring you the money.
I think, he has no money
to pay you.
That's why he came up
with that story.
Now I have no money left to pay you,
but I'm asking you to give me more time.
You should have ask me without
calling my men thieves.
Explain to him that he was wrong.
I'll get it into his head!
Now Ramón, are you still believing
it was me who robbed you?
- Yes, you are a thief!
- What are you saying? I can't hear you.
Speak up,
tell my friends too.
You are
a bunch of thieves!
We're wasting time here.
I want to see you becoming a gentleman.
Don't tell any lies.
Now try to remember.
The guy who robbed you, how did he look like?
He had the face of a thief,
just like yours!
You better admit you made up this story
so you don't have to pay the mortgage.
I didn't, you thief!
When did you came up with that idea
I had robbed you?
You claim to know better
where I was and what happened?
You never saw me there,
ain't that so, Ramón?
You stole the money!
Hurry up guys,
come here!
What happened?
Talk!
Steven burned down the house
at Paso Bolt.
Move on, saddle the horses
and wait for me.
The settlers burned down
the camp at Paso Bolt.
We're wasting time, Barrett.
We have to give them hell.
- If you'd let me go ahead...
- Seems you always do what you want.
- Who burned down Kenneth's Ranch?
- It was necessary.
They wouldn't let pass through
our cattle.
- And they polluted the water.
- I don't like that kind of action.
- By now you should know that.
- I don't care what you like.
You can put on your gentleman
act as much as you want...
...but don't forget that
we are equal partners.
Don't worry,
I won't forget.
But don't come complaining once
the settlers start burning down our camps.
I don't want to start a war
with the settlers, Burt.
I just want the land, that's all.
I prefer to get it by
any means legal.
Legal? You'll spend years trying
to get rid of them adopting lawful means.
Why are you
in such a hurry, Burt?
Steven is gathering all
the settlers around him.
- And once they are united...
- I'll take care of Steven.
You know, certain matters take
a lot of thinking and quietness.
I'm tired of being quiet!
While we wait they might
start using barbwire.
- They'll start giving you hell...
- Enough now, Burt!
You take care of the cattle,
I'll take care of the rest.
Don't talk to me that way!
You think
you are smarter than I am?
You treat me like a bully, because
I don't take my hat off in front of women...
...the way you do it.
Don't forget, I know you as well
as the smell of my own feet.
I could lock you up in jail
while burping in the sheriffs face!
Let's go
and thank those bastards!
Anybody with a weak stomach,
now is the time to tell...
Well hello, Rezza.
Didn't see you for a while...
I'd say so.
You still charge that much?
Even more.
Right. Actually that's why
I'm hiring you.
- Good work has its price.
- We'll see, Mister Barrett.
What are we talking about?
- What's this all about?
- Burt.
- You're short 1.000 Dollars.
- Take this for a start.
In one month you'll
get another 10.000.
When did you become
a benefactor?
Who do you want to kill?
The governor?
- Someone more important.
- He's worth 10.000 Dollars?
Dead even more, you can
count on that.
Maybe it's none of my business,
but why in a month and not now?
A bit of time will
calm the waves first.
By then the farmers will
stop acting like defenders.
In the meantime they'll run
further into dept...
At the right moment,
I'll go after them.
You're 1.000 Dollars short, Senor.
I won't work for less.
Alright, Rezza.
But don't forget to be
secretive about it!
The man will die
at his own hands.
The two of us have a deal then.
I'll expect you in one month.
But I warn you,
it's going to be a difficult job.
I'll keep in shape, Senor.
Besides, a month passes by so quickly.
And don't forget: I'm the one
around here who gives the orders!
Those you give to me cost a fortune.
You better not waste them.
Seven...
...seems to be
your lucky day.
That's the fifth time
you got seven.
- Are you saying that I'm cheating?
- No, I don't. Heaven forbid.
I would never
dare to say so.
Then I guess
I heared wrongly.
Go ahead,
bet your money.
Who's holding the bank?
Nobody's holding the bank?
It's a town
of starving people!
This place should get rid of the pigs
that pollute it!
You could start
by hanging yourself, Burt.
When talking about pigs, you were
talking about yourself, right?
Stop it or I'll call the sheriff!
- Get out to settle your affair!
- Out of my way, Lady!
You think you can scare me off
with your lady manners?
Stop it, Burt.
You drank too much.
- I'll go and tell Barrett.
- Go to hell!
You and Barrett,
that quitter!
I do as I please.
I'm not his mistress.
You dirty whore!
- You're gonna pay for that!
- Watch out, Burt!
The boss doesn't like that kind of talk
when it comes to his broad.
Barett, Barrett, Barrett!
Barrett is trash,
just like her!
So you left Ramón
to become a lady.
But you always stayed a whore!
What's going on?
Who fired his gun?
Seems like no one wants to talk?
The next time I'm gonna
arrest all of you!
Rum.
Seven.
Hey!
- Hey, where do you think you're going?
- I won't continue with this game.
Rum.
- No easy way out. I'm losing.
- But you're winning 500 Dollars.
My friend says he's losing,
so he's losing.
I'm the one
who's behind.
What kind of gentleman would leave
the table while winning.
No more games my friend,
bet your money!
Don't think about it. Hold the bank,
it might pay off.
Go on, bet your money
Will you hurry up?
Put on Banco.
Banco!
Not you my friend.
- Not you I said.
- You heard him?
Thanks.
Banco.
Seven.
You are a cheat.
You hear me?
You are cheating!
My name is Rezza.
I acted in self-defense.
If you want to,
tell it everybody.
Slim! You thief!
Murderer!
- Is he hurt?
- There's a bullet in his shoulder.
- You know him?
- yes.
Take him away, I beg you.
He is Mexican, they will blame him.
I beg you for it.
For the first time in my life
I have to thank somebody...
...and I do it with pleasure.
Don't worry, I'll return him
once he has recovered.
- What happened?
- Archangel Gabriel came along.
And disappeared again.
There's a bullet
in your shoulder.
Try not to move.
I'll try to get it out,
but it won't be easy.
Take it.
Drink it, it's coffee.
As you wish.
What's your name?
You lost your voice?
You still had it when
you tried to kill that man.
Listen to me, Chico:
Shoot first and then talk.
Nobody listens
to that crap anyway.
So it's better
not to talk at all.
Are you afraid?
Let's see whether you
really lost your breath.
Drink, Chico!
So you still have a voice!
Hey Chico, it's thougher
to get it out...
...than to get it in.
At least for me it is.
Drink.
In a few days you're free to go
wherever you want to go to.
The girl is waiting for you.
Hey Chico,
you still think of that girl?
What's her name?
- I don't know.
- She is very pretty.
I bet a lot of bastards
are chasing her around.
I used to know one like her too.
For a dollar she'd spend
a night with you.
She had a boyfriend.
A Mexican just like you.
This guy
was really tight-lipped.
Believe me, Chico,
the boy really was in love with her.
He even promised her,
to marry her someday.
,, For what you need her, just give
her a Dollar", some said.
,, Why would you
marry her?"
Whenever she took some guy to bed
with her, he took his rifle and shouted...
...he was going
to kill them.
In the end he married her.
When he was away to work, she
brought in men and paid them.
- One Dollar, to be specific.
- Enough now!
Hey Chico, what's the matter?
Go to sleep and forget about it.
Women are all alike anyway.
What are you doing?
Are you leaving?
That's fine.
We are even now.
You have a nice trip, Chico.
Hey Chico!
Where are you
going anyway?
Why don't you stay a while.
There's still time to go away.
But don't act like a mummy.
- If I stay, I want to learn from you.
- What do want to learn?
How to shoot.
Don't wait until you're running
out of bullets before you reload.
Fire off five shots and then reload.
So there's always one left in the chamber.
Stand tall.
Just like that.
First stretch your arm,
then we'll go on.
Go!
Too low.
Too high.
Now!
No, not like that. You have to
do it with the first shot, Chico.
There's no risk shooting at bottles.
But facing a man armed with a gun...
...you either kill him or
he might kill you.
Hit him with your first shot
or it will be too late, Chico.
I would never have guessed
that you can play.
I used to play a lot.
The place I grew up,
there was an old man.
Each day at dawn I saw
him play on the street.
Where were you born?
Down south. Walk towards the sun
and sooner or later you'll get there.
Why don't you
go back there?
I will return. I hardly can wait.
Two more weeks and I'm on my way.
Why not now?
There's something left to do.
An important job, maybe the last one.
What kind of job?
None of your business, Chico.
Actually it's not even my business.
I only know I get paid well.
I wanna take the money, go home
and see whether the old man still lives...
...playing music at dawn.
Margaret, come here.
Sit down.
You want a sip?
That's enough now.
You are some kind of guy...
How come, Mister Barrett
is not here yet?
Relax, Paquito.
Barrett is always on time.
You never know when he comes,
but he always comes.
Any more words
and I'll fire you.
Hello.
An interesting table.
May I join you?
- We're playing low stakes.
- Very well...
This place surely changed since
poor Burt left it for good.
- It became less amusing.
- Nobody misses him, Mister Barrett.
You probably
the least of all.
- He was a true friend.
- A son of a bitch.
Whatever. I'm sure now everything
will fall into places.
We have to work together
and change this land...
...into a paradise.
You said that before.
I just discovered my love
for this land my dear...
No matter what it produces.
I'm just a simple man.
I have to talk to you.
Please excuse us.
Just a moment gentlemen.
- A common thief.
- The land that he loves belongs to others.
First and final
commandment:
Do not steal
your neighbors land...
...but die on your own.
Amuse yourself? What's the big joke?
I'd like to see you...
You'll never see me
like that, Chico.
What do you think you got,
holding a gun in your hand?
- A weapon.
- No, Chico.
Just an excuse to get killed.
A gun means nothing
unless you can use it!
- But I'm learning.
- How to shoot, but that's not enough.
This here is you
and that's your opponent.
You're facing each other,
equal rivals.
Each one carries a gun,
each loaded with six bullets.
You're all ready to shoot.
But one of you is in a better position:
the one with the sun behind his back.
First: with the sun behind your back
your opponent stands in full light.
Second: that way your opponent
has difficulties seeing you that well.
Watch your shadow,
Chico.
If you see it in front of you,
you can draw.
If you don't see your shadow, wait.
Move slowly until you see it.
While you're moving,
wet your lips.
Wet them all around.
If it feels cold on the right side,
the wind is coming from that direction.
If it's cold in the middle, the wind
is blowing right into your direction.
Facing the wind is bad.
It will slow down your shot.
It's better to have the wind in your back.
- It won't affect you then.
- What if it blows from the side?
You have to learn to judge its strength.
If you see dust, the wind is deep and strong.
If the leaves in the trees move,
the wind is high up and blowing less hard.
How do you judge the wind?
I feel it in my hairs, Chico.
That's why I wear them long.
It's all instinct, like being an animal.
Forget that you are a human being.
You have to feel like an animal
facing another animal.
Your whole body must be dedicated to kill.
Your skin, your breath, your eyes.
Everything can help you getting
some kind of advantage.
- How come you know these things?
- I understand and learned them, Chico.
When you're facing death,
you feel like an animal.
Nothing but an animal.
If you refuse to become one,
you might not survive.
Did you ever see a mountain lion?
If he's hungry,
he'll slowly walk around.
Then he suddenly stops, stretches out
his snout and waits.
- He doesn't move, just stands still.
- Why?
He smells the wind.
As soon as he feels it,
he stops in his tracks...
...and the wind supplies
him with all kind of smells...
Once he likes a smell, he jumps
and stays leeward.
That way his victim smells him too late,
when he is already on it.
Remember, in a duel of life and death,
the winner is the one with more will to live.
And the living usually are more
hungry than the dead.
You don't eat
before a duel?
No, I just shave.
If someone faces death and
he bothers to shave...
...you can be damn sure he rather
wants to live than to die.
Just like you?
Yes...
I'm not like you.
- My life is not that important to me.
- This too could be an advantage.
You could become an
excellent killer.
Some sort of killing machine.
You could make a lot of money.
I'm not interested in money.
Chico, this girl, she'd appreciate you staying
alive much more than being dead, right?
No.
You're so right.
It's impossible to understand women.
They're like walls: you never know
what's on the other side.
There's a barrier you'll you never
break down, once you killed someone.
- What is that?
- Society.
They will build up a high wall
in front of you, they will respect you.
They will fear you
but never love you.
You'll always stay on one side
of that wall.
- Better that way.
- That's what I used to think.
Then one day you realise life is
on the other side of that wall...
...and you are
no part of it. Ever.
- I think you're getting old.
- Maybe.
I'm tired of this life.
You're always alone, like a dog...
...and you're waiting to die
like a dog, only more miserably.
You're the only friend
I ever met, Chico.
Probably because I never
wanted any friends before.
Are you sure
I am your friend?
Sure, and you can be
sure I am yours.
So take care, you said you still
have a job to do.
Do it first and then think
of the rest.
- You taught me that.
- You're right, Chico.
Work comes first.
You know, Chico,
friendship is one of those things...
...you leave behind at the other
side of that wall.
For ever.
Remember that once you killed
somebody for the very first time.
- I'm gonna tear you to pieces!
- He's letting you have it.
- Why don't you give it a try?
- Order is order.
Enough now!
Stop it I said!
What the hell is the matter with you?
Enough now!
He attacked one of my men
who was unarmed.
Are you crazy?
He attacked me from behind!
He was still not armed
and you are carrying a gun!
My men had enough of
those provocations.
Listen sheriff, I can't calm them down
anymore by now.
Maybe I should put you all in jail
and call the federal judge!
Don't tell any jokes,
sheriff.
If someone has to be
locked up, it's Steven!
He attacks my men as soon as
they are unarmed!
Don't expect to get rid of me
that way, Barrett.
I respected the cease-fire.
But from now on my men
will be heavily armed.
You want a war on your hands,
you got it!
- Dirty bastards!
- Let it be, Steven!
For now I'll lock you up to
calm you down. Then we'll see...
Alright, Chico.
You aim well.
- You're sure to go ahead.
- I proved that, didn't I?
Well...
So you don't mind
facing me in a duel?
- You still want to test me?
- No, Chico. A duel. For real.
If you can kill me,
it will mean you are ready.
No, I won't do that.
I might really kill you.
Are you accepting or
are you a coward?
No.
A real duel, Chico.
Try to kill me - if you can.
So your life isn't important to you.
You are afraid to die, that's it.
Once you are dead, that girl will find
100 men better than you are.
Don't worry.
Then do it for her, give her the chance
to improve herself.
You asked for it.
If I succeed I'm gonna kill you!
That's the way I like you, boy.
We're equal opponents.
So it's either me or you!
Hey, here I am!
Go ahead, kill me!
You felt secure,
you needed a cold shower.
If you can count up to 'six'
you can save yourself.
Otherwise you've had it.
Remember that, son.
It's called math, Chico.
You have to count.
All the time.
Count the steps,
count the shots.
Yours and those
of your opponent.
Count, Chico, always count.
Count the minutes.
No one can hold a pistol
for longer than three minutes...
...without starting
to tremble.
Once you start trembling
you're the loser.
Count Chico,
always count.
If your opponent makes a step
and then stops, he's afraid.
If he makes two steps
he is uneasy.
If makes three steps
he's about to kill you.
Why this cross?
If this bullet hits you it will
have the impact of a canonball.
If such a bullet hits its target,
you can't go wrong.
What's your job?
Who has to die?
I don't know yet,
I don't know him.
Tomorrow will be my last day
as a warrior.
- Then I'm gonna change my life.
- How?
I told you, Chico.
I'll go back to where I came from.
Settling down, raising a family.
A wife maybe.
If that old man is still there,
playing music at dawn...
...I'm gonna invite him to my house
and give him food and drinks.
He may lie down on a bed.
And I will say to him:
,, You walked a long way, old man.
Now it's time to rest.
I saw you walking around
since I was a little boy."
- He must have rested along the way.
- I only saw him walking around.
As far as I'm concerned
that old man never stopped walking.
That old man is you.
And now your mind is set on climbing
that wall you talked about.
- Maybe.
- Don't think too much about it.
I was only joking.
How come you never asked me
why I wanted to learn how to shoot?
Because I knew it.
You're out to kill someone.
Yes, but who?
Don't you want to know?
Maybe yourself.
The old Chico you once was.
I saw many people die,
it doesn't affect me any longer.
I'm sorry I'm leaving you behind.
You'll be in a lot of touble.
- I'm sure.
- Don't worry about me.
I know what I'm doing.
I'm sorry
I can't support you.
One thing
I can do for you.
Take this. You'll find everything:
A razor, a brush and a mirror.
- Thank you.
- Shave my son.
Remember: who bothers to shave
rather wants to live than to die.
Chico!
Practice, practice all the time.
Getting better will cheer you up.
If you miss you'll never
know what you're missing anyway.
- Good luck!
- But... Hey!
- So you missed it too?
- Who can tell, my boy?
Life is an illusion.
The important thing is to believe
that you can make it! Farewell.
- Ramón was here.
- Ramón...
...was here.
And who is Ramón?
You forgot about him?
But he remembered you.
He came back here
because of you.
- He wants to kill you.
- Kill me?
- But why?
- You better ask him.
He said he has time.
That he waited for so long...
...a day more or less
won't make a difference.
What are you talking about?
Come on, tell me what you know!
Seems that you strechted things
with this boy, Barrett.
There's only one thing left for you:
Kill him.
Maybe you'd do him
a favour with that.
Unless he kills you. He might gain
a greater pleasure from that.
Thank Barrett I let you go,
he asked me for it.
He promised he'd do his best
to avoid further incidents.
I can't believe what I hear, Sheriff.
You all believe that Barrett is an angel.
Be prepared for a big surprise.
- Come on Steven, he's no devil.
- He is a devil.
As long as I am here,
the settlers will keep their land.
It would be better if you would
not help this bastard.
Ramón.
May God forgive him.
1.000 Dollars for the man
who will bring me the murderer!
Hey Ramón! Barrett said
you wanted to talk to him.
With Barrett, not with
his bootlickers.
- Talk about what?
- That sort of talk!
You're early, Senor.
How much will you charge me
for a favour?
Another one?
You intend to move up
Armageddon?
No. No jokes.
This is serious business.
- How much do you want?
- Nothing, my work is done.
- Your last job, I promise.
- No way.
In the end I kill the whole village
with only you and me left.
I'm telling you, this is the last job.
I'll give you another 10.000 Dollars.
15.000!
Alright, 20.000.
Who is the guy?
His name is Ramón. You'll find him in
a burned down house near the village.
- You can't miss it.
- I bet you burned it down.
So you accept?
Agreed.
Payment in advance.
- Very well, tonight I'll bring you the money.
- You'll find me here.
who bothers to shave
rather wants to live than to die.
Ramón!
- Did Barrett send you?
- It's him you wanted to kill, right?
- None of your business. Go away, Rezza!
- I'm a professional, Ramón.
Once I got paid,
I'll go all the way.
- Why do you want to kill Barrett?
- You said it yourself once.
By killing him, I kill what
I once was.
You can have my horse. Take it
and leave this place forever.
If you hate somebody,
the world is not big enough.
You will forget very soon,
you'll see.
You wanted to go back
to the place you were born, remember?
- I was born here and I stay here!
- Don't push me, Ramón.
If you stay,
I have to kill you!
I told you to have
the sun behind you.
Don't forget to count the steps.
One step and he is afraid.
Two steps and he is uneasy.
Three steps, Ramón,
he is about to kill you!
But I had a shave!
Rezza... Rezza!
Hey Chico,
you made it.
A small credit goes to me
as well.
Now you'll feel this wall, Chico.
A big wall.
Don't try to climb it, Chico.
You'll never succeed.
Alright, Mick.
What's your decision?
Okay, Mister Barrett,
I'm selling.
I appreciate it, Mick.
That's a splendid idea.
Let's go have a drink and
discuss the selling price.
Barrett!
Don't move, Barrett!
What are you waiting for?
Don't just stare at him.
- Ramón!
- What do you want? What's the matter, boy?
- Out of my way, sheriff!
- I'm not a boy!
- Do something, sheriff!
- This madman is about to kill me!
- What is it that you want?
- I want to kill Barrett!
- Stop it, Ramón, I beg you!
- Why kill him? What has he done to you?
- He is a lousy murderer!
- He killed my father!
- That's not true!
I had nothing to do with it!
It was Burt!
Burt worked for you and you had
him kill my father. Just like Steven!
What do you know
about Steven?
Go ask Barrett.
He knows everything!
If you know something, tell us, Ramón!
I'm gonna arrest him!
Get out of my way, sheriff!
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch!
Then I'm going
to tell you everything.
The killer is not dead yet, Barrett!
He is still alive!
Ramón. Ramón!
What did you say? Who is that killer?
Why did you say he isn't dead?
Now he is dead, sheriff.
He was the last one.
THE END