1
00:00:16,391 --> 00:00:17,859
Hold it right there.

2
00:00:24,899 --> 00:00:26,242
Hold it again.
Hold it.

3
00:00:26,776 --> 00:00:29,120
Oh, come on, Paul.

4
00:00:32,240 --> 00:00:34,538
One more.
One more.

5
00:00:39,956 --> 00:00:41,924
You're not gonna show
those to anyone, are you?

6
00:00:42,083 --> 00:00:43,380
- Sure. Why not?
- Ugh.

7
00:00:43,543 --> 00:00:45,045
- You've got a prime figure.
- Heh.

8
00:00:45,253 --> 00:00:47,005
- You really have, you know.
- Heh.

9
00:00:47,172 --> 00:00:48,719
That's a euphemism for fat.

10
00:00:59,350 --> 00:01:00,727
You wanna go back to the hotel?

11
00:01:02,145 --> 00:01:04,068
What's the matter with right here?

12
00:01:06,191 --> 00:01:07,568
We're too civilized.

13
00:01:09,652 --> 00:01:12,075
I remember when we weren't.

14
00:01:13,198 --> 00:01:15,200
But we'll go back to the hotel.

15
00:01:22,874 --> 00:01:25,218
Paul, I don't wanna go back home.

16
00:01:46,898 --> 00:01:50,402
Trans World Airlines
passengers on TW76...

17
00:01:50,568 --> 00:01:53,822
from Honolulu to New York should
proceed from the check-in counter...

18
00:01:53,988 --> 00:01:56,082
to the Friendship
Lounge for boarding.

19
00:04:40,655 --> 00:04:43,329
Wanna know what happened while
you and Joanna were living it up...

20
00:04:43,491 --> 00:04:45,366
in Maui or Kaui or
Yaui, whatever it is?

21
00:04:45,392 --> 00:04:45,860
What?

22
00:04:45,994 --> 00:04:47,746
There were 15 murders
the first week...

23
00:04:47,912 --> 00:04:51,166
and 21 last week in this goddamn city.
- That's a lot.

24
00:04:51,708 --> 00:04:54,837
You know, decent people are gonna have
to work here and live somewhere else.

25
00:04:55,003 --> 00:04:57,927
By "decent people," you mean people
who can afford to live somewhere else.

26
00:04:58,089 --> 00:05:01,810
Oh, Christ. You are such
a bleeding-heart liberal, Paul.

27
00:05:02,010 --> 00:05:04,763
My heart bleeds a little
for the underprivileged, yeah.

28
00:05:04,929 --> 00:05:08,399
The underprivileged are beating our
goddamn brains out. You know what I say?

29
00:05:08,558 --> 00:05:11,732
Stick them in concentration camps.
That's what I say.

30
00:05:11,936 --> 00:05:13,654
- Henry.
- Hello.

31
00:05:13,855 --> 00:05:18,361
I've been running a cost-and-profit on the
Jainchill development in Tucson, Arizona.

32
00:05:19,277 --> 00:05:21,496
Well, based on these figures...

33
00:05:21,654 --> 00:05:24,658
I don't see how Blue Ridge
can underwrite 50 percent of it.

34
00:05:25,366 --> 00:05:28,290
Well, Jainchill's been very
successful, in a small way.

35
00:05:30,038 --> 00:05:32,962
Well, then I suggest
you send a man down...

36
00:05:33,124 --> 00:05:35,627
from our San Francisco office
to step it out.

37
00:05:35,793 --> 00:05:37,887
Redesign it, if necessary.

38
00:05:38,421 --> 00:05:41,675
Because that's a high risk
for the acreage involved.

39
00:05:42,633 --> 00:05:44,510
I'll talk to Inge about it.
Thanks, Paul.

40
00:05:46,304 --> 00:05:52,027
Oh, uh, Paul, how does it feel to
be back in the war zone after Hawaii?

41
00:05:53,102 --> 00:05:55,571
I was feeling pretty good
until I ran into Sam...

42
00:05:55,772 --> 00:05:58,742
and he delivered the
crime rate statistics.

43
00:05:58,900 --> 00:06:01,244
What this city needs
is more cops than people.

44
00:06:01,444 --> 00:06:05,369
You'll have to find other options,
Samuel. No one could pay the taxes.

45
00:06:46,322 --> 00:06:47,665
$2.17.

46
00:06:48,366 --> 00:06:51,085
Would you have these
delivered, please, Mary?

47
00:06:52,078 --> 00:06:53,170
Goodbye.

48
00:08:21,542 --> 00:08:23,670
Hey, I'm gonna do a thing.

49
00:08:24,670 --> 00:08:26,547
Shit, man.
Got business.

50
00:08:26,714 --> 00:08:28,182
Let's go, man.

51
00:08:51,489 --> 00:08:52,911
I'll get it.

52
00:09:00,998 --> 00:09:02,170
Who is it?

53
00:09:02,541 --> 00:09:03,838
Groceries, ma'am.

54
00:09:24,188 --> 00:09:26,316
Nobody gets hurt, Mother.
Just hold still. Don't move.

55
00:09:26,524 --> 00:09:27,616
What do you want?

56
00:09:27,775 --> 00:09:30,119
Don't jive, Mother.
You know what we want.

57
00:09:30,319 --> 00:09:32,993
- He's not gonna hurt us?
- Not if you got money.

58
00:09:34,824 --> 00:09:36,121
Nobody, nobody.

59
00:09:39,203 --> 00:09:42,503
Hey, Mother.
Look at the artiste doing his art.

60
00:09:42,665 --> 00:09:45,293
- Ain't that beautiful, Mother?
- My purse is in the kitchen.

61
00:09:45,459 --> 00:09:46,961
Just stand still.

62
00:09:47,503 --> 00:09:50,382
We'll do as they say, Carol.
Where is your purse?

63
00:09:58,681 --> 00:10:03,107
- Shit, you only got four bucks.
- I got three, and two bits.

64
00:10:03,436 --> 00:10:05,985
You're gonna get
the shit kicked out of you, Mother.

65
00:10:06,731 --> 00:10:08,984
- It's all we have.
- Rich people like you?

66
00:10:09,150 --> 00:10:12,245
- Shit, we want money, Mother. Now get it!
- It's true. That's all we...

67
00:10:15,072 --> 00:10:17,541
- How'd you like to get fucked?
- No!

68
00:10:18,326 --> 00:10:20,044
I'm gonna stick you in the ass.

69
00:10:25,124 --> 00:10:26,171
Leave her alone!

70
00:10:30,087 --> 00:10:31,805
Goddamn rich cunt!

71
00:10:32,423 --> 00:10:33,640
I kill rich cunts.

72
00:10:34,508 --> 00:10:36,761
Mother's getting the
shit kicked out of her.

73
00:10:47,063 --> 00:10:49,065
Hey, let's screw
this one, man. Huh?

74
00:10:49,273 --> 00:10:52,652
- No, man. Let's travel.
- No, man. Let me paint her ass.

75
00:11:01,911 --> 00:11:05,165
Hey, man. You think you're an artiste?
I'll show you how to paint, man.

76
00:11:05,331 --> 00:11:07,299
I'm gonna paint her goddamn mouth!

77
00:11:08,084 --> 00:11:10,837
He's gonna paint your mouth.
You're gonna like that.

78
00:11:11,295 --> 00:11:13,718
You get any ideas about biting my
paintbrush, you'll get what Mother got.

79
00:11:13,881 --> 00:11:16,555
- You're gonna swallow that paint.
- She'll swallow the paint.

80
00:11:16,759 --> 00:11:18,386
Open that goddamn throat!

81
00:11:27,603 --> 00:11:29,605
Mother's going for the phone!

82
00:11:31,565 --> 00:11:33,488
Shit, let's split.

83
00:11:59,385 --> 00:12:01,353
Thelma, will you get my wife
on the phone, please?

84
00:12:03,431 --> 00:12:04,603
Mr. Kersey's office.

85
00:12:11,689 --> 00:12:14,784
- Is it my wife?
- No, sir. It's your son-in-law.

86
00:12:16,318 --> 00:12:17,695
Hello, Jack.

87
00:12:17,903 --> 00:12:19,155
Dad.

88
00:12:20,239 --> 00:12:21,286
Dad, we got trouble.

89
00:12:21,490 --> 00:12:23,208
Trouble? You and Carol?

90
00:12:23,409 --> 00:12:24,535
Don't tell me about it.

91
00:12:24,743 --> 00:12:26,461
No, no. Dad...

92
00:12:27,621 --> 00:12:29,498
It's Mom and Carol.

93
00:12:30,166 --> 00:12:32,885
They're taking them to the emergency
receiving at Canal Hospital.

94
00:12:33,043 --> 00:12:35,717
- What the hell for?
- Look, I don't know.

95
00:12:35,921 --> 00:12:37,764
The police just called me.

96
00:12:37,965 --> 00:12:39,342
What's happening, Jack?

97
00:12:39,508 --> 00:12:41,385
I don't know any more
than that, Dad.

98
00:12:41,594 --> 00:12:45,269
Look, I'm at my office, I'm going to
the hospital, just meet me there, okay?

99
00:12:48,058 --> 00:12:50,937
Dr. Fanning,
go to the emergency room, stat.

100
00:12:51,103 --> 00:12:53,697
Dr. Fanning,
go to the emergency room.

101
00:12:53,856 --> 00:12:55,278
Dr. Diaz...

102
00:12:56,150 --> 00:12:57,618
How are they?
Are they all right?

103
00:12:57,776 --> 00:12:59,949
I don't know. I just got here
a few minutes ago.

104
00:13:00,196 --> 00:13:03,040
Do you know anything?
Were they cut, stabbed, what?

105
00:13:03,199 --> 00:13:04,246
I...

106
00:13:04,408 --> 00:13:06,410
No, sir. Just beat up.

107
00:13:06,785 --> 00:13:10,255
This is Officer Joe Charles, he came
in the ambulance with Morn and Carol.

108
00:13:10,414 --> 00:13:13,042
- They gonna be all right?
- I've told Mr. Toby all I know.

109
00:13:13,459 --> 00:13:16,212
If there's anything I can do,
ask for me at the 21st precinct.

110
00:13:16,378 --> 00:13:17,675
Good luck to you.

111
00:13:18,464 --> 00:13:20,137
Come on, Dad.
We might as well go sit down.

112
00:13:20,299 --> 00:13:21,471
What'd they tell you?

113
00:13:22,843 --> 00:13:24,060
Not much.

114
00:13:24,261 --> 00:13:25,308
Yeah, but what?

115
00:13:27,473 --> 00:13:28,816
They beat them both up.

116
00:13:28,974 --> 00:13:29,775
Who did? Why?

117
00:13:29,801 --> 00:13:33,004
Take it easy, Dad.
I'm just as rattled as you are.

118
00:13:33,854 --> 00:13:37,154
The officer said that Carol
wasn't making much sense.

119
00:13:37,358 --> 00:13:39,406
Two, maybe three men, they...

120
00:13:39,818 --> 00:13:41,365
She opened the door
to let them in...

121
00:13:41,529 --> 00:13:44,282
because she thought it was the
delivery boy from the supermarket.

122
00:13:46,492 --> 00:13:48,335
Jesus God.

123
00:13:52,957 --> 00:13:54,755
When are we gonna know something?

124
00:13:54,917 --> 00:13:58,137
Will the following
doctors go to the emergency room, stat:

125
00:13:58,295 --> 00:13:59,547
Dr. White...

126
00:13:59,713 --> 00:14:01,431
They know we're here?

127
00:14:01,924 --> 00:14:04,063
The nurses know.
I spoke to one of them.

128
00:14:04,089 --> 00:14:05,453
Somebody ought to come.

129
00:14:05,594 --> 00:14:08,894
There's a man over there.
He's bleeding, and nobody comes.

130
00:14:12,101 --> 00:14:15,822
Nurse, we're waiting to find out
what happened to my wife and daughter.

131
00:14:15,980 --> 00:14:18,984
A doctor will see you
after he's made his examination.

132
00:14:19,149 --> 00:14:21,072
But we've been
waiting a long time.

133
00:14:21,402 --> 00:14:24,451
It hasn't been that long, Dad,
just two or three minutes.

134
00:14:27,866 --> 00:14:29,493
- Mr. Toby?
- Yes.

135
00:14:29,660 --> 00:14:31,003
Your wife is all right.

136
00:14:31,203 --> 00:14:33,080
We've sedated her
and put her to bed.

137
00:14:33,289 --> 00:14:35,417
My name is Paul Kersey.
How's my wife?

138
00:14:37,251 --> 00:14:38,423
I'm sorry.

139
00:14:38,627 --> 00:14:41,176
She died a few minutes ago,
Mr. Kersey.

140
00:14:47,303 --> 00:14:50,807
Almighty God, we commend
to you our neighbor Joanna...

141
00:14:51,015 --> 00:14:53,313
trusting your love and mercy...

142
00:14:53,517 --> 00:14:57,272
and believing in the promise of
a resurrection to eternal life...

143
00:14:57,479 --> 00:15:01,484
through our Lord Jesus Christ.
Amen.

144
00:15:02,318 --> 00:15:07,370
Almighty God, father of the whole
family in heaven and on earth...

145
00:15:07,531 --> 00:15:09,659
stand by those who sorrow...

146
00:15:09,867 --> 00:15:13,417
that as they lean on your
strength, they may be upheld...

147
00:15:13,579 --> 00:15:16,583
and believe the good news
of life beyond life...

148
00:15:16,790 --> 00:15:21,136
through Jesus Christ,
our lord. Amen.

149
00:15:39,188 --> 00:15:41,156
I'm going back with
Sam and Adele.

150
00:15:41,315 --> 00:15:43,192
They go right by my place.

151
00:15:44,401 --> 00:15:46,244
Don't you wanna come
to our apartment?

152
00:15:46,403 --> 00:15:49,452
It's time I went to my own,
I have to sometime.

153
00:15:53,035 --> 00:15:54,287
Baby?

154
00:15:54,787 --> 00:15:56,039
Baby?

155
00:15:57,623 --> 00:15:59,751
I'm going back with Sam.

156
00:16:00,167 --> 00:16:01,919
You get plenty of rest.

157
00:16:08,801 --> 00:16:10,678
She'll be all right, Dad.

158
00:16:39,957 --> 00:16:41,800
Residents
of northern suburbs...

159
00:16:41,959 --> 00:16:44,678
will need quite some time to dig
themselves out of a snowstorm...

160
00:16:44,837 --> 00:16:46,384
that's taking much
of Connecticut...

161
00:16:46,547 --> 00:16:48,766
and Rockland and Westchester
Counties by surprise.

162
00:16:49,091 --> 00:16:50,138
In New York City...

163
00:16:50,300 --> 00:16:52,394
light snow flurries lingering
till about midnight.

164
00:16:52,553 --> 00:16:54,726
- No accumulation, but afternoon...
- Turn that thing off.

165
00:16:54,888 --> 00:16:57,506
I'm listening to the weather.
Why haven't you found my dog?

166
00:16:57,532 --> 00:16:58,508
He's vital to my income.

167
00:16:58,642 --> 00:17:01,316
He paints such marvelous
pictures with his paws.

168
00:17:04,732 --> 00:17:07,986
- Yes. Help you?
- Where can I find Officer Joe Charles?

169
00:17:08,193 --> 00:17:10,992
- What's your business?
- Well, my name is Paul Kersey.

170
00:17:11,196 --> 00:17:13,790
A couple days ago, my wife
and daughter were attacked...

171
00:17:13,949 --> 00:17:16,793
and he was one of the policemen
on the scene, I wanna talk to him.

172
00:17:18,412 --> 00:17:20,460
Yeah, well,
okay, so I think the...

173
00:17:20,622 --> 00:17:24,377
Hattie, is Joe Charles still back
there or has he gone on duty yet?

174
00:17:24,835 --> 00:17:27,258
Yeah, there's someone out here
who wants to talk to him.

175
00:17:27,421 --> 00:17:30,015
- I told you somebody...
- Have a seat. He'll be right out.

176
00:17:30,215 --> 00:17:32,638
.-.Snatched my purse!
The man came up from behind me.

177
00:17:32,801 --> 00:17:35,805
My credit cards is in there,
my rent money, I don't have no key.

178
00:17:35,971 --> 00:17:37,598
- Do I have a description?
- Yes.

179
00:17:37,765 --> 00:17:40,234
The man came from behind me!

180
00:17:40,392 --> 00:17:42,315
- You didn't see who it was?
- No, I didn't see!

181
00:17:42,478 --> 00:17:45,482
- Hello, Mr. Kersey.
- Officer Charles.

182
00:17:45,731 --> 00:17:48,153
I dropped by to see if
you had any information

183
00:17:48,179 --> 00:17:50,136
on the people who
attacked my family.

184
00:17:50,277 --> 00:17:52,871
I'll take you to the detective
in charge of the case.

185
00:18:02,748 --> 00:18:05,046
- Uh, lieutenant?
- Yeah.

186
00:18:05,209 --> 00:18:08,930
This is Mr. Paul Kersey, case number 884.
His wife and daughter were assaulted.

187
00:18:09,129 --> 00:18:11,302
- Glad to know you, Mr. Kersey.
- I'm going on duty now...

188
00:18:11,465 --> 00:18:12,887
so I'll leave.
- Thanks, officer.

189
00:18:13,050 --> 00:18:14,677
- Not at all.
- Right this way, Mr. Kersey.

190
00:18:15,427 --> 00:18:17,145
Will you have a seat, Mr. Kersey?

191
00:18:19,306 --> 00:18:21,274
Have you found out anything yet?

192
00:18:21,642 --> 00:18:24,771
Well, the supermarket security
officer and one of the checkers...

193
00:18:24,937 --> 00:18:28,362
remembers these three characters leaving
right after Mrs. Kersey and your daughter.

194
00:18:28,524 --> 00:18:30,322
They think they could've
gotten the apartment

195
00:18:30,348 --> 00:18:32,144
number off the address
on the grocery bags...

196
00:18:32,277 --> 00:18:35,076
but they haven't been able to pick
the faces out of the mug book.

197
00:18:35,447 --> 00:18:37,620
How is your daughter, Mr. Kersey?

198
00:18:37,783 --> 00:18:40,377
She's under doctor's
sedation right now.

199
00:18:41,119 --> 00:18:45,295
But today I had the funeral
for my wife up in Connecticut...

200
00:18:45,457 --> 00:18:46,800
and she was able to make that.

201
00:18:47,501 --> 00:18:50,550
Your daughter didn't give us
much information, Mr. Kersey.

202
00:18:50,712 --> 00:18:52,885
We wish we could persuade her
to look at the mug books.

203
00:18:53,924 --> 00:18:55,176
Did she refuse?

204
00:18:56,051 --> 00:18:58,645
Her husband asked us
to wait for a few days.

205
00:18:58,804 --> 00:19:00,806
In fact, the sooner
she looks at the mug books...

206
00:19:00,973 --> 00:19:04,147
the better chance she has of
recalling one or two of the faces.

207
00:19:04,768 --> 00:19:07,738
Well, I'll talk to my son-in-law...

208
00:19:08,146 --> 00:19:10,899
and see what can be done.
- I'd appreciate that, Mr. Kersey.

209
00:19:13,527 --> 00:19:15,495
Any chance of catching these men?

210
00:19:16,405 --> 00:19:18,248
There's a chance, sure.

211
00:19:19,366 --> 00:19:20,663
Just a chance?

212
00:19:20,868 --> 00:19:23,542
I'd be less than honest if I
gave you more hope, Mr. Kersey.

213
00:19:24,413 --> 00:19:27,633
In the city, that's the way it is.

214
00:19:39,261 --> 00:19:41,138
I thought you were asleep.

215
00:19:45,183 --> 00:19:47,185
Are you
getting the most out of life?

216
00:19:47,853 --> 00:19:50,777
Are you satisfied,
fulfilled, happy?

217
00:19:51,064 --> 00:19:53,567
Our bank has helped
many to a better future.

218
00:20:49,289 --> 00:20:50,916
- Good morning, Mr. Kersey.
- Morning.

219
00:20:51,750 --> 00:20:54,970
Would you give me
$20 in quarters, please?

220
00:21:09,726 --> 00:21:11,524
- Good morning, Paul.
- Morning.

221
00:21:13,522 --> 00:21:15,775
Paul, you're tough.
You know, you really are.

222
00:21:15,941 --> 00:21:17,568
I told Ives you'd
come in this morning.

223
00:21:17,734 --> 00:21:21,739
I said, "Paul is not the kind of man to
leave the pieces of his life lying around.

224
00:21:21,905 --> 00:21:23,703
He'll just start picking them up."

225
00:21:23,865 --> 00:21:26,209
Just a matter of keeping busy, Sam.

226
00:21:28,286 --> 00:21:30,584
Paul, welcome back.

227
00:21:30,747 --> 00:21:32,715
- Good morning, Henry.
- See you for lunch, Paul?

228
00:21:32,874 --> 00:21:35,798
- Yeah, sure.
- Paul, I'm gonna give you a vacation.

229
00:21:35,961 --> 00:21:37,759
From New York, that is.

230
00:21:38,130 --> 00:21:42,306
The Jainchill development
of Tucson, Arizona.

231
00:21:42,551 --> 00:21:46,055
I want you to take it over.
Redesign it, if necessary.

232
00:21:46,221 --> 00:21:48,565
Whatever you have to do.
All right?

233
00:21:48,974 --> 00:21:51,978
That's all right, but can I give you
an answer in about a week?

234
00:21:52,144 --> 00:21:54,863
I don't wanna leave New York
just now because of Carol.

235
00:21:55,188 --> 00:21:56,235
Fine.

236
00:21:56,440 --> 00:21:58,659
When you're ready, let me know.

237
00:21:59,109 --> 00:22:02,409
Beautiful place, Tucson.
They can breathe out there.

238
00:22:11,496 --> 00:22:13,669
She's sleeping too much.

239
00:22:14,541 --> 00:22:16,134
It's not normal.

240
00:22:16,710 --> 00:22:19,714
I've got a couple of TV dinners
in the oven. Come on.

241
00:22:19,880 --> 00:22:21,507
It'll just be a couple of minutes.

242
00:22:23,008 --> 00:22:25,056
Jack, this drink's enough for me.

243
00:22:26,011 --> 00:22:29,015
- I've never seen you drink without eating.
- I'm not hungry.

244
00:22:30,182 --> 00:22:35,029
I think maybe you ought to
take Carol to see another doctor.

245
00:22:35,687 --> 00:22:39,442
I, uh... I did. Today.
A psychiatrist.

246
00:22:40,484 --> 00:22:44,614
He seems to feel it might help her if I
took her away to another environment.

247
00:22:45,447 --> 00:22:48,792
Out of New York,
on the shore someplace.

248
00:22:48,992 --> 00:22:50,710
Sounds like a good idea.

249
00:22:50,869 --> 00:22:54,123
- I'll go along with you.
- Uh... No, Dad. He...

250
00:22:54,498 --> 00:22:56,724
He seemed to feel that
it might be better if

251
00:22:56,750 --> 00:22:59,074
she didn't have any
association with anyone...

252
00:22:59,211 --> 00:23:03,011
that might remind her of that day.
- How the hell do I remind her of that day?

253
00:23:03,381 --> 00:23:05,179
Well, you know how it is, Dad.

254
00:23:05,509 --> 00:23:07,807
I mean, it happened
in your apartment.

255
00:23:08,178 --> 00:23:12,558
And you're living there.
You remind her of Morn.

256
00:23:14,768 --> 00:23:17,772
Dad, don't make it tough for me.

257
00:23:18,939 --> 00:23:21,783
Okay, I'll make it easy for you.

258
00:23:22,025 --> 00:23:25,700
Ives asked me to go to
Tucson, Arizona on a job.

259
00:23:25,904 --> 00:23:30,000
- How long will you be gone?
- I don't know. Until I look the job over.

260
00:23:30,575 --> 00:23:33,124
But you call me every other day,
let me know how Carol is.

261
00:23:33,620 --> 00:23:35,714
Sure I will, Dad.

262
00:23:36,957 --> 00:23:40,632
You know, that'll be good for you,
I hear Tucson's a really beautiful place.

263
00:23:40,794 --> 00:23:42,637
Yeah, yeah.
That's what everybody says.

264
00:23:50,804 --> 00:23:53,023
How are you today, sir?

265
00:24:37,559 --> 00:24:39,277
Son of a bitch.

266
00:24:39,561 --> 00:24:41,859
Turn around, son of a bitch.

267
00:24:42,230 --> 00:24:44,528
Motherfucker! I said turn around.

268
00:24:44,941 --> 00:24:46,614
And hand me the money.

269
00:26:13,196 --> 00:26:14,573
Paul Kersey.

270
00:26:14,823 --> 00:26:17,167
- Yeah.
- Aimes Jainchill.

271
00:26:17,367 --> 00:26:18,835
How do you do, Mr. Jainchill?

272
00:26:18,994 --> 00:26:21,338
Aimes. I'll call you Paul.
Come on. Let's get your bags.

273
00:26:21,496 --> 00:26:24,466
- How did you know who I was?
- Well, you look like a New Yorker.

274
00:26:33,133 --> 00:26:34,430
Ho!

275
00:26:37,429 --> 00:26:39,727
Ho. Ho, ho.

276
00:26:41,182 --> 00:26:43,401
Howdy, Jud.

277
00:26:50,525 --> 00:26:55,782
I wanted you to see this country before you
looked at the drawings back at the office.

278
00:26:56,156 --> 00:26:57,829
Give you a better idea.

279
00:26:58,199 --> 00:26:59,917
I don't wanna change these hills.

280
00:27:00,076 --> 00:27:02,374
Don't wanna bulldoze them flat.

281
00:27:04,956 --> 00:27:07,129
You'll waste a lot
of building space.

282
00:27:07,917 --> 00:27:10,887
Ha, ha! Wasting space.

283
00:27:11,129 --> 00:27:13,302
Now, those are some words
that you big developers...

284
00:27:13,465 --> 00:27:16,184
have got to change
for something else.

285
00:27:16,343 --> 00:27:17,560
Such as?

286
00:27:17,719 --> 00:27:19,562
Well, space for life.

287
00:27:20,347 --> 00:27:24,727
Like old Jud up there.
Space for people, horses, cows.

288
00:27:25,685 --> 00:27:28,655
I got funny ideas about
building things.

289
00:27:36,112 --> 00:27:39,207
Howdy, folks, welcome to old Tucson,
the famous movie location and studio.

290
00:27:39,407 --> 00:27:40,454
In just a few moments...

291
00:27:40,617 --> 00:27:44,087
Unh. Come on. Let's wet our whistle
before I trot you back to the motel.

292
00:27:44,245 --> 00:27:45,462
Glass of beer, maybe.

293
00:27:45,663 --> 00:27:48,257
Take their positions on the
porches of the Red Dog Cafe...

294
00:27:48,458 --> 00:27:51,257
the Territorial Gunsmith shop...
- What's happening here?

295
00:27:51,419 --> 00:27:53,672
Oh, it's a phony western town.

296
00:27:54,005 --> 00:27:57,930
They shoot movies here sometimes, but the
rest of the time, it's for the tourists.

297
00:27:58,510 --> 00:28:01,605
This is where the actual
performance will take place.

298
00:28:01,805 --> 00:28:04,080
These fellas are pretty good.
Wanna watch?

299
00:28:04,106 --> 00:28:04,674
Sure.

300
00:28:04,849 --> 00:28:06,692
where the Wild West lives again.

301
00:28:08,061 --> 00:28:10,155
- Where's the marshal?
- He's in the bank.

302
00:28:10,355 --> 00:28:12,278
I spotted him through the window
as I came by.

303
00:28:12,440 --> 00:28:15,910
- What have you got in mind to do, then?
- Well, why don't you steal my horse?

304
00:28:16,069 --> 00:28:18,071
All right.
That's a good trick. We'll use it.

305
00:28:18,238 --> 00:28:21,868
You spot yourself on the porch while I
draw the marshal out into the open.

306
00:28:22,283 --> 00:28:24,035
Marshal! Hey, marshal!

307
00:28:24,244 --> 00:28:25,871
What's the matter, fella?

308
00:28:26,121 --> 00:28:27,748
Somebody stole my horse.

309
00:28:27,956 --> 00:28:30,254
I told you to get
out of town by sunset.

310
00:28:30,458 --> 00:28:33,302
You missing a bay mare
that was tied to the hitching rail?

311
00:28:33,461 --> 00:28:35,884
Saw a feller come and take her
just a spell ago.

312
00:28:36,089 --> 00:28:37,762
Well, what did he look like?

313
00:28:37,966 --> 00:28:40,435
Well, he was about
this tall, and he had this...

314
00:28:40,593 --> 00:28:42,061
Get him, Frank!

315
00:29:05,660 --> 00:29:10,461
Let's put him inside here and get to
the bank and make that withdrawal.

316
00:29:15,295 --> 00:29:18,014
All right, boys. The fun's over.

317
00:29:18,548 --> 00:29:21,472
Throw out your guns
and step out with your hands up.

318
00:29:21,676 --> 00:29:25,101
You'd better listen, marshal.
I've got three sticks of dynamite here.

319
00:29:25,263 --> 00:29:26,355
Don't be a fool.

320
00:29:43,323 --> 00:29:45,826
The outlaw life
seemed a shortcut to easy money...

321
00:29:46,034 --> 00:29:49,664
which could buy liquor, women,
and a turn at the gambling table...

322
00:29:49,829 --> 00:29:52,002
but there were honest
men with dreams...

323
00:29:52,165 --> 00:29:54,793
who would fight to protect their...
- Let's get that beer.

324
00:29:54,959 --> 00:29:59,055
and who were to plant
the roots that would grow into a nation.

325
00:30:05,345 --> 00:30:07,268
Blue Ridge won't buy it.

326
00:30:09,516 --> 00:30:12,986
I don't build a thing that's gonna
be a slum in 20 years...

327
00:30:13,561 --> 00:30:15,404
and I won't doze those hills.

328
00:30:15,563 --> 00:30:18,237
What I build conforms to the land.

329
00:30:18,733 --> 00:30:21,486
And you can't hear the
toilets flush next door.

330
00:30:22,654 --> 00:30:25,498
You want our help,
you'll have to let me work on it.

331
00:30:27,200 --> 00:30:29,703
Well, up to a point,
I want your help.

332
00:30:29,911 --> 00:30:32,289
Up to a point, I'll give it.

333
00:31:23,881 --> 00:31:25,929
When do I get a look-see?

334
00:31:27,010 --> 00:31:28,978
In a couple days.

335
00:31:29,429 --> 00:31:32,148
Guard says you were here
till after midnight last night.

336
00:31:32,307 --> 00:31:33,809
Yeah. That's the way I work.

337
00:31:34,559 --> 00:31:36,357
Somebody once said...

338
00:31:36,561 --> 00:31:38,939
I forget who.
...that he never looked back...

339
00:31:39,105 --> 00:31:41,403
because something might
be gaining on him.

340
00:31:42,400 --> 00:31:44,073
What's gaining on you, Paul?

341
00:31:45,903 --> 00:31:48,122
Twenty million dollar investment.
What else?

342
00:31:48,823 --> 00:31:52,953
Well, I was gonna ask you to have
dinner with me at the club...

343
00:31:53,119 --> 00:31:55,042
but I don't think
you'd be very good company.

344
00:31:55,204 --> 00:31:56,421
No, I don't think I would.

345
00:31:56,623 --> 00:31:58,948
It might amuse you, though.
Being from New York,

346
00:31:58,974 --> 00:32:00,824
maybe you never seen
a club like this.

347
00:32:00,960 --> 00:32:04,180
It's a gun club.
We shoot guns.

348
00:32:08,593 --> 00:32:12,268
So goddamn much hoopla
from the gun control people.

349
00:32:12,513 --> 00:32:14,607
Half the nation's scared
to even hold a gun!

350
00:32:14,766 --> 00:32:17,485
You know, like it was a snake,
it was gonna bite you or something.

351
00:32:17,644 --> 00:32:19,772
Hell, a gun is just a tool...

352
00:32:20,772 --> 00:32:23,321
like a hammer or an ax.

353
00:32:23,733 --> 00:32:26,327
Wasn't long ago,
used to put food on the table...

354
00:32:26,527 --> 00:32:30,452
keep foxes out of the chicken coop,
rustlers off the range...

355
00:32:30,657 --> 00:32:31,874
bandits out of the bank.

356
00:32:32,033 --> 00:32:34,252
Paul, how long since
you held a pistol in your hand?

357
00:32:35,536 --> 00:32:38,881
- A long time.
- Hm.

358
00:32:39,540 --> 00:32:42,464
- Which war was yours, Korea?
- Yeah.

359
00:32:42,794 --> 00:32:45,047
- See much action?
- A little.

360
00:32:45,296 --> 00:32:46,718
Were you infantry?

361
00:32:48,466 --> 00:32:51,219
- I was a CO in a medical unit.
- Oh.

362
00:32:51,386 --> 00:32:53,514
Commanding officer, huh?

363
00:32:54,180 --> 00:32:56,649
Conscientious objector.

364
00:32:57,475 --> 00:32:58,943
Oh, Christ.

365
00:32:59,143 --> 00:33:02,864
What a guest to bring
to a gun club. Heh.

366
00:33:03,022 --> 00:33:04,990
You're probably one
of them knee-jerk liberals...

367
00:33:05,149 --> 00:33:09,575
thinks us gun boys shoot our guns
because it's an extension of our penises.

368
00:33:10,113 --> 00:33:12,036
I never thought about
it that way...

369
00:33:12,365 --> 00:33:13,708
but it could be true.

370
00:33:14,283 --> 00:33:16,035
Well, maybe it is...

371
00:33:16,494 --> 00:33:18,462
but this is gun country.

372
00:33:18,621 --> 00:33:20,794
Can't even own a handgun
in New York City.

373
00:33:20,957 --> 00:33:23,255
Out here, I hardly know a man
that doesn't own one.

374
00:33:23,626 --> 00:33:25,253
And I'll tell you something...

375
00:33:25,420 --> 00:33:27,764
unlike your city,
we can walk our streets...

376
00:33:27,922 --> 00:33:30,095
and through our parks
at night and feel safe.

377
00:33:30,383 --> 00:33:34,729
Muggers operating out here, they'd
just plain get their asses blown off.

378
00:33:35,054 --> 00:33:37,773
Here. Slip these on.

379
00:33:38,224 --> 00:33:41,103
All righty.
This is a percussion pistol.

380
00:33:41,310 --> 00:33:42,812
1842.

381
00:33:46,733 --> 00:33:49,031
You ever handled one
of those before?

382
00:33:50,653 --> 00:33:52,200
You know how to fire it?

383
00:33:52,905 --> 00:33:54,282
Watch the kick.

384
00:33:54,490 --> 00:33:57,334
Boy, you're gonna think that
your arm's gonna hit the ceiling.

385
00:34:07,587 --> 00:34:09,134
Goddamn!

386
00:34:09,338 --> 00:34:11,136
Paul, you hit dead center!

387
00:34:11,591 --> 00:34:13,434
Mind if I try this Hogleg Colt?

388
00:34:13,593 --> 00:34:14,970
No.

389
00:34:15,136 --> 00:34:18,231
Well, you a peculiar
conscientious objector.

390
00:34:18,723 --> 00:34:20,646
- These notches for real?
- Yeah.

391
00:34:20,808 --> 00:34:24,187
Belonged to a gunfighter
named Candy Dan, 1890.

392
00:34:24,353 --> 00:34:27,323
Hm. I do know something
about guns, Aimes.

393
00:34:27,482 --> 00:34:30,235
I grew up with them.
All kinds of guns.

394
00:34:31,194 --> 00:34:33,117
You see, my father was a hunter.

395
00:34:33,362 --> 00:34:36,081
I guess out here you'd
call him a gunman.

396
00:34:36,365 --> 00:34:38,959
My mother was the
other side of the coin.

397
00:34:40,286 --> 00:34:43,256
When my father was killed
in a hunting accident...

398
00:34:44,332 --> 00:34:46,630
Some fool mistook him
for a deer, you see.

399
00:34:47,293 --> 00:34:49,136
My mother won the toss.

400
00:34:49,420 --> 00:34:51,548
I never touched a gun since.

401
00:34:53,341 --> 00:34:55,309
I loved my father.

402
00:35:07,230 --> 00:35:09,107
There are your hills.

403
00:35:10,149 --> 00:35:12,572
Every house has a part
of one for a backyard...

404
00:35:12,735 --> 00:35:14,328
for kids, dogs, horses.

405
00:35:14,904 --> 00:35:17,999
Four hundred houses,
100 more than you allowed for...

406
00:35:18,199 --> 00:35:20,247
and you still have 12 hills.

407
00:35:22,578 --> 00:35:24,797
I'm catching the 10:40
back to New York.

408
00:35:25,414 --> 00:35:27,087
What do I tell them?

409
00:35:28,376 --> 00:35:30,174
You tell them I'll buy
it if they will.

410
00:35:50,439 --> 00:35:52,191
You're checking this bag
through, aren't you?

411
00:35:52,608 --> 00:35:53,985
- Yeah.
- Good.

412
00:35:54,193 --> 00:35:57,072
Let me slip a little going-away
present in there for you.

413
00:35:58,990 --> 00:36:00,116
Thank you.

414
00:36:05,371 --> 00:36:07,874
Trans World Airlines Flight 63...

415
00:36:08,040 --> 00:36:09,936
- ...from Tucson to New
York is now boarding...

416
00:36:09,962 --> 00:36:11,535
Good morning, sir.
How are you today?

417
00:36:11,919 --> 00:36:13,262
Checking one bag?

418
00:36:13,462 --> 00:36:17,012
Paul, I can't thank you enough
for what you did for me.

419
00:36:17,216 --> 00:36:22,017
I want you to know if you ever
get tired of living in that toilet...

420
00:36:22,763 --> 00:36:24,390
you're welcome here.

421
00:36:26,851 --> 00:36:29,104
Trans World airlines Flight 7...

422
00:36:29,270 --> 00:36:31,819
to London and Frankfurt
is now boarding.

423
00:36:31,981 --> 00:36:34,484
Passengers should
proceed to Gate 11

424
00:36:34,650 --> 00:36:36,368
- Welcome home, Dad.
- Hi, Jack.

425
00:36:36,527 --> 00:36:38,655
I halfway expected to see Carol.

426
00:36:39,071 --> 00:36:41,165
Come on.
Let's go get your bags.

427
00:36:42,617 --> 00:36:43,914
What is it?

428
00:36:45,369 --> 00:36:47,463
She's in the hospital.

429
00:36:49,957 --> 00:36:51,630
When I last spoke to you on the phone...

430
00:36:51,792 --> 00:36:54,591
you said she was feeling better
after coming back from the shore.

431
00:36:56,422 --> 00:36:59,426
Well, I didn't see any need to get you
all disturbed on a long-distance call.

432
00:36:59,592 --> 00:37:03,768
Will Mr. Cory, a passenger on
Trans World Airlines Flight 100...

433
00:37:03,930 --> 00:37:06,058
from Vancouver,
please report to...

434
00:37:06,223 --> 00:37:08,100
Oh, come on, Dad,
don't do a number...

435
00:37:08,601 --> 00:37:10,228
Don't do a number on me.

436
00:37:10,603 --> 00:37:13,072
Look, there was
nothing you could do.

437
00:37:13,856 --> 00:37:17,076
They haven't even let me see her
for two days.

438
00:37:19,528 --> 00:37:22,156
They tried insulin
shock yesterday.

439
00:37:22,448 --> 00:37:24,667
She's not responding.

440
00:37:25,701 --> 00:37:28,625
You want the technical jargon?
I can reel off yards of it:

441
00:37:28,955 --> 00:37:33,961
Catatonia, dementia praecox,
passive schizoid paranoia.

442
00:37:35,378 --> 00:37:39,349
It all boils down to the fact that she's
had an experience that she can't face...

443
00:37:39,507 --> 00:37:42,056
and she's running away from it
inside herself.

444
00:37:42,218 --> 00:37:45,643
Will Mrs. Lager, a passenger
on Trans World Airlines...

445
00:37:45,805 --> 00:37:47,227
Flight 45 to Paris...

446
00:37:47,431 --> 00:37:50,025
please contact the
information desk...

447
00:37:50,184 --> 00:37:52,061
You didn't handle her right, Jack.

448
00:37:53,062 --> 00:37:55,156
Aw, Christ, Dad.

449
00:37:56,399 --> 00:37:58,401
I'll get other doctors.

450
00:37:58,901 --> 00:38:02,997
- Who are these goddamn doctors you have?
- They're good doctors.

451
00:38:06,325 --> 00:38:08,794
Dad,
she's almost a goddamn vegetable.

452
00:38:41,485 --> 00:38:44,489
If you don't sign the papers,
what happens?

453
00:38:46,198 --> 00:38:49,577
I guess they keep her in the hospital
until the insurance runs out.

454
00:38:49,744 --> 00:38:51,041
That won't be too long.

455
00:38:51,203 --> 00:38:54,924
If you sign the papers and
she's committed, what then?

456
00:38:56,250 --> 00:39:00,050
Well, I've got an insurance policy
that covers it up to about 600 a month.

457
00:39:00,463 --> 00:39:03,512
They've recommended
a sanatorium out in Long Island.

458
00:39:04,508 --> 00:39:06,226
Jack...

459
00:39:07,720 --> 00:39:10,519
This commitment,
is it a one-way thing?

460
00:39:11,891 --> 00:39:14,485
Nobody can answer that, Dad.

461
00:39:15,895 --> 00:39:17,738
You wanna know what they are?

462
00:39:17,897 --> 00:39:20,400
They're statistics
on a police blotter.

463
00:39:20,941 --> 00:39:24,070
Mom and Carol, along with
thousands of other people.

464
00:39:24,653 --> 00:39:27,452
And there is nothing
that we can do to stop it.

465
00:39:28,240 --> 00:39:29,992
Nothing but cut and run.

466
00:41:58,474 --> 00:42:02,945
Oh, what a bummer, man. That was
the worst fucking movie I've ever seen.

467
00:43:33,986 --> 00:43:35,454
You got money, man?

468
00:43:39,992 --> 00:43:41,335
Shit, I'll kill you!

469
00:43:41,535 --> 00:43:43,412
Give me your money
or I'll bust you up!

470
00:44:27,331 --> 00:44:29,004
Oh, Jesus.

471
00:44:29,249 --> 00:44:30,671
Oh, Jesus.

472
00:44:30,876 --> 00:44:32,594
Jesus Christ.

473
00:44:32,795 --> 00:44:35,674
Ohh. Oh, Jesus.

474
00:45:11,959 --> 00:45:13,927
Good morning, inspector.

475
00:45:15,087 --> 00:45:17,215
Good morning.
What do we got?

476
00:45:17,381 --> 00:45:19,975
We got a corpse down here,
one bullet hole in his chest.

477
00:45:20,217 --> 00:45:22,862
Fellow over there was jogging
through the park at daybreak,

478
00:45:22,888 --> 00:45:24,122
found him on the path here.

479
00:45:24,638 --> 00:45:28,233
- You got a make on the dead man?
- Yeah. His name is Thomas Leroy Marston.

480
00:45:28,392 --> 00:45:30,486
He had a parole card,
we got a radio check on that.

481
00:45:30,644 --> 00:45:33,773
He served 42 months of a five-year
hitch for grand larceny.

482
00:45:33,939 --> 00:45:36,408
He's a drug addict.
He's probably popping smack again.

483
00:45:36,567 --> 00:45:38,114
There's punctures, both arms.

484
00:45:38,277 --> 00:45:40,780
We found this on the
grass next to him.

485
00:45:40,988 --> 00:45:42,831
Thing hasn't been fired.

486
00:45:43,323 --> 00:45:45,451
Deceased had a gun
clip on his belt.

487
00:45:45,617 --> 00:45:46,834
Think it must be his.

488
00:45:48,412 --> 00:45:52,087
What would you say if I suggested
that he tried a heist...

489
00:45:52,416 --> 00:45:53,668
he got shot for his trouble?

490
00:45:53,834 --> 00:45:56,462
Maybe two guys trying
to heist each other.

491
00:45:56,712 --> 00:45:59,090
No, no.
This man wasn't robbed.

492
00:45:59,465 --> 00:46:01,513
Still has money in his wallet.

493
00:46:27,242 --> 00:46:28,869
- Good morning, Paul.
- Good morning.

494
00:46:29,077 --> 00:46:31,751
- Hi, Paul. Morning.
- Morning, Sam.

495
00:46:32,414 --> 00:46:36,089
Well, we've marked it out
as you've indicated.

496
00:46:36,752 --> 00:46:38,595
It's beautiful.

497
00:46:38,754 --> 00:46:40,301
What's our profit?

498
00:46:41,131 --> 00:46:44,886
Uh... Not quite three million,
but I believe that our investment...

499
00:46:45,052 --> 00:46:46,599
can be amortized in two years...

500
00:46:46,762 --> 00:46:49,106
and it is a showplace operation.

501
00:46:49,264 --> 00:46:51,016
Look at all that wasted space.

502
00:46:51,225 --> 00:46:52,818
Jainchill loves those hills.

503
00:46:53,060 --> 00:46:55,654
Besides, it's a
take-it-or-leave-it proposition.

504
00:46:55,812 --> 00:46:58,315
Well, it's too pretty to leave.

505
00:46:59,358 --> 00:47:01,326
Okay. I'll run it for the board.

506
00:47:01,568 --> 00:47:04,242
- May need your help, Paul.
- Okay.

507
00:47:06,114 --> 00:47:08,867
Oh, Tucson agreed with you.
You look well.

508
00:47:09,701 --> 00:47:12,545
I feel, uh... Good.

509
00:48:43,253 --> 00:48:46,006
Was he a white man or a black man?

510
00:48:46,173 --> 00:48:47,516
I just don't know!

511
00:48:47,674 --> 00:48:49,768
Come on.
They were under that streetlight.

512
00:48:49,926 --> 00:48:53,021
I wasn't seeing too good.
I had blood in my eyes.

513
00:48:53,180 --> 00:48:55,057
Well, was he tall? Short?

514
00:48:55,223 --> 00:48:56,816
Thin? Fat?

515
00:48:57,392 --> 00:48:59,941
Hank. Forget it, huh?

516
00:49:00,395 --> 00:49:02,443
Ride the ambulance to the morgue.

517
00:49:03,565 --> 00:49:06,114
When they get the slugs
out of those bodies...

518
00:49:06,360 --> 00:49:09,204
run them over to the
lab for ballistics.

519
00:49:16,662 --> 00:49:18,164
You saw him pretty
good, didn't you?

520
00:49:21,166 --> 00:49:23,009
You're full of shit.

521
00:50:25,605 --> 00:50:26,652
- Thank you.
- Thank you.

522
00:50:32,320 --> 00:50:35,199
You know, if we had the brains
to live here in the country...

523
00:50:35,365 --> 00:50:37,663
we wouldn't be here
for the reason we are today.

524
00:50:38,994 --> 00:50:41,463
We'd be going into
the city to work.

525
00:50:41,872 --> 00:50:45,172
And Mom and Carol would be safe at home,
waiting for us to come back.

526
00:50:45,792 --> 00:50:48,045
Nothing to do but cut and run, huh?

527
00:50:48,920 --> 00:50:50,513
Eh, what else?

528
00:50:50,881 --> 00:50:54,886
What about the old American
social custom of self-defense?

529
00:50:55,594 --> 00:50:59,064
If the police don't defend us,
maybe we ought to do it ourselves.

530
00:51:00,390 --> 00:51:02,984
We're not pioneers anymore, Dad.

531
00:51:04,352 --> 00:51:06,025
What are we, Jack?

532
00:51:06,188 --> 00:51:07,440
What do you mean?

533
00:51:08,064 --> 00:51:11,113
I mean, if we're not pioneers,
what have we become?

534
00:51:12,235 --> 00:51:14,033
What do you call people...

535
00:51:15,197 --> 00:51:18,167
who, when they're faced
with a condition of fear...

536
00:51:18,450 --> 00:51:22,626
do nothing about it,
they just run and hide?

537
00:51:23,413 --> 00:51:25,040
Civilized?

538
00:51:28,877 --> 00:51:30,504
No.

539
00:51:34,591 --> 00:51:36,389
Ladies and gentlemen...

540
00:51:36,802 --> 00:51:39,646
we have to start
this investigation somewhere...

541
00:51:40,180 --> 00:51:42,057
so let's start here.

542
00:51:47,771 --> 00:51:49,023
Motive:

543
00:51:49,481 --> 00:51:50,903
Revenge.

544
00:51:51,441 --> 00:51:53,409
I want the records checked.

545
00:51:53,819 --> 00:51:55,662
Go back, say, uh...

546
00:51:55,862 --> 00:51:57,535
Three months.

547
00:51:58,448 --> 00:52:00,450
Limit it to homicide.

548
00:52:00,951 --> 00:52:02,953
We could be looking for
a man who's had a member...

549
00:52:03,119 --> 00:52:06,248
or members of his family
killed by muggers.

550
00:52:09,501 --> 00:52:12,129
Now, he shoots that
pistol pretty good.

551
00:52:12,546 --> 00:52:13,763
Right?

552
00:52:14,256 --> 00:52:15,849
Okay.

553
00:52:16,299 --> 00:52:17,972
Combat veteran.

554
00:52:18,301 --> 00:52:20,895
So put Vietnam vets
at the top of the list...

555
00:52:21,096 --> 00:52:23,349
because they're youngest
and toughest.

556
00:52:23,598 --> 00:52:27,398
Then you can work your way
through Korea and World War ll.

557
00:52:27,561 --> 00:52:29,108
Oh, my God!

558
00:52:30,605 --> 00:52:31,902
Who said that?

559
00:52:32,148 --> 00:52:33,445
Hmm?

560
00:52:34,442 --> 00:52:36,865
Well, whoever said it,
you're right on the button.

561
00:52:37,487 --> 00:52:41,913
By God and Jesus Christ,
it's impossible...

562
00:52:42,826 --> 00:52:45,295
but until we find a shortcut...

563
00:52:45,620 --> 00:52:47,668
we'll at least keep busy.

564
00:52:48,248 --> 00:52:52,173
So when the media demands to know what we
are doing to apprehend the vigilante...

565
00:52:52,794 --> 00:52:56,674
we'll tell them we
have definite clues.

566
00:52:57,799 --> 00:52:59,142
Okay?

567
00:53:00,260 --> 00:53:03,605
We won't tell them we have
about a thousand definite clues.

568
00:55:45,341 --> 00:55:47,560
There's a body
in there! Two of them!

569
00:56:03,485 --> 00:56:05,783
- Where'd he go?
- Did anybody see what he looked like?

570
00:56:05,987 --> 00:56:07,864
We're in Police Commissioner
Dryer's office...

571
00:56:08,031 --> 00:56:11,376
waiting for a press conference
scheduled by Commissioner Dryer.

572
00:56:11,576 --> 00:56:14,876
Last night, there was another double
killing, which appears to be the work...

573
00:56:15,038 --> 00:56:18,588
of the person New York news media
have dubbed "The Vigilante."

574
00:56:33,306 --> 00:56:34,979
This will be
the first official statement...

575
00:56:35,141 --> 00:56:37,360
from Commissioner Dryer
on the Vigilante killings.

576
00:56:37,519 --> 00:56:39,863
I can see the commissioner now
as he walks past...

577
00:56:40,021 --> 00:56:44,401
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
With me is Inspector Frank Ochoa...

578
00:56:45,485 --> 00:56:48,284
who has been placed in
command of a police detail...

579
00:56:48,446 --> 00:56:53,327
assigned to what we've all
been calling the Vigilante murders.

580
00:56:53,535 --> 00:56:57,665
Now, it has been confirmed
by our ballistics laboratory...

581
00:56:58,832 --> 00:57:01,051
that the same
gun, a .32 pistol...

582
00:57:01,251 --> 00:57:04,676
which was used
in the previous three homicides...

583
00:57:04,879 --> 00:57:08,224
was used last night in a shooting
aboard a subway train.

584
00:57:09,342 --> 00:57:13,813
Now, I know that this person
has captured the imagination...

585
00:57:14,013 --> 00:57:16,107
of many people in our city...

586
00:57:16,391 --> 00:57:18,268
and I wanna say to our citizens:

587
00:57:19,352 --> 00:57:23,482
Murder is no answer
to crime in this city.

588
00:57:23,648 --> 00:57:26,322
Crime is a police responsibility...

589
00:57:27,569 --> 00:57:30,448
and if this person
is listening to my voice...

590
00:57:31,281 --> 00:57:34,410
I urge him
in the name of law and order...

591
00:57:35,535 --> 00:57:40,757
to desist from this one-man crusade
and turn himself in to the police.

592
00:57:41,708 --> 00:57:44,427
He'll be given fair treatment.

593
00:57:44,586 --> 00:57:46,680
How do you like it?
That's our police commissioner...

594
00:57:46,838 --> 00:57:48,806
that's Ryder, the
king of clichés.

595
00:57:48,965 --> 00:57:51,639
- vigilante's identification?
- No comment at this time.

596
00:57:51,843 --> 00:57:54,471
Do you think this man's crazy?

597
00:57:54,762 --> 00:57:57,311
Well, he's got a wire down, all right...

598
00:57:57,515 --> 00:58:00,359
but I don't believe we're
dealing with a raving maniac.

599
00:58:00,560 --> 00:58:03,939
Commissioner, it's rumored that
the rate of street muggings has dropped...

600
00:58:04,105 --> 00:58:06,608
since The Vigilante became
headline news. Is that true?

601
00:58:06,774 --> 00:58:07,821
Not true.

602
00:58:08,067 --> 00:58:10,161
If it were true,
would you announce it, sir?

603
00:58:10,320 --> 00:58:13,039
Or are you afraid that would stimulate
imitators of The Vigilante?

604
00:58:13,198 --> 00:58:16,202
I don't wanna get into
these hypothetical questions.

605
00:58:16,451 --> 00:58:19,500
Mm. I bet muggings are down,
they're afraid to tell us.

606
00:58:19,746 --> 00:58:23,341
There's only one way to find out:
Take a walk on Columbus Avenue tonight.

607
00:58:23,541 --> 00:58:26,841
Thanks a lot, Paul, I think
I'll wait for the official report.

608
00:58:27,003 --> 00:58:29,176
successful,
regardless of the...

609
00:58:33,927 --> 00:58:35,474
Yes?

610
00:58:36,429 --> 00:58:40,354
Ah. You wanna confess
to the Vigilante killings?

611
00:58:41,059 --> 00:58:42,311
All right.

612
00:58:42,644 --> 00:58:44,692
I'll put you through to Rosenberg.

613
00:58:44,854 --> 00:58:47,277
He's in charge of
confessions today.

614
00:58:47,774 --> 00:58:49,822
That's the 23rd.

615
00:58:50,151 --> 00:58:51,494
Put him through.

616
00:58:52,111 --> 00:58:55,331
We couldn't get any prints
off The Vigilante's groceries.

617
00:58:55,531 --> 00:58:59,081
- Wasn't there a sales slip?
- Yeah. Here.

618
00:59:00,787 --> 00:59:03,415
D'Agostino's.

619
00:59:03,873 --> 00:59:05,295
Mm-hm.

620
00:59:06,751 --> 00:59:10,551
Some of this code must identify
the particular store.

621
00:59:10,922 --> 00:59:12,595
Find out where it is.

622
00:59:12,840 --> 00:59:14,308
When we get the records...

623
00:59:14,467 --> 00:59:18,222
check on families that have had
somebody killed by muggers.

624
00:59:18,429 --> 00:59:21,899
Let's put them through the computer and
see if any of them live near this store.

625
00:59:23,643 --> 00:59:27,648
People are inclined to buy groceries
in their own neighborhoods.

626
00:59:28,898 --> 00:59:31,902
- Hi, Jack. Come on. Come on in.
- Dad.

627
00:59:32,068 --> 00:59:33,115
Make yourself a drink.

628
00:59:35,697 --> 00:59:37,290
Hey, what do you think?

629
00:59:37,573 --> 00:59:38,870
The new paint?

630
00:59:40,576 --> 00:59:43,075
Well, it's a little
hard on the eyes, but...

631
00:59:43,101 --> 00:59:44,947
Hard on the eyes?
It's cheerful.

632
00:59:48,167 --> 00:59:52,047
Hey, Jack. Turn it back up.
I can't hear.

633
00:59:56,050 --> 00:59:58,394
We got liver and
spaghetti for dinner.

634
00:59:58,553 --> 01:00:00,226
How do you like
your liver done?

635
01:00:00,513 --> 01:00:02,186
- Uh...
- Hey, no drink?

636
01:00:02,390 --> 01:00:03,687
Let me make you one.

637
01:00:04,934 --> 01:00:07,653
No. Dad... Listen, that's all right.
I'll get it myself.

638
01:00:08,896 --> 01:00:10,273
I, uh...

639
01:00:11,399 --> 01:00:13,322
I saw Carol today.

640
01:00:13,985 --> 01:00:16,579
- Aren't you gonna ask how she's doing?
- I know how she's doing.

641
01:00:16,738 --> 01:00:18,536
I went up to see her yesterday.

642
01:00:20,199 --> 01:00:21,951
Then what the hell
are you so high about?

643
01:00:22,160 --> 01:00:25,004
What the hell you want me to do, moan
and groan for the rest of my life?

644
01:00:28,333 --> 01:00:29,880
How do you want
your liver, medium?

645
01:00:31,753 --> 01:00:34,302
Medium. I'll make it medium.

646
01:00:50,104 --> 01:00:53,028
- Hey, there goes the pussy posse.
Ha-ha-ha!

647
01:02:22,071 --> 01:02:24,039
Hey, mister, got a match?

648
01:02:27,243 --> 01:02:28,290
Yeah.

649
01:02:28,536 --> 01:02:30,038
What else you got?

650
01:02:33,624 --> 01:02:35,126
Let's see the money, man.

651
01:02:36,461 --> 01:02:38,509
- You'll have to take it.
- Shit.

652
01:03:18,002 --> 01:03:19,424
He went that way.

653
01:04:43,254 --> 01:04:44,972
Who rode the ambulance with him?

654
01:04:45,965 --> 01:04:47,091
I did.

655
01:04:47,925 --> 01:04:49,051
Well?

656
01:04:49,677 --> 01:04:50,432
Was he talking?

657
01:04:50,458 --> 01:04:52,922
He said he cut whoever
it was that shot him.

658
01:04:53,097 --> 01:04:56,601
Exact words:
"I cut that motherfucker. I hit him."

659
01:04:58,144 --> 01:05:00,943
Can't save him.
Too much internal bleeding.

660
01:05:01,355 --> 01:05:03,107
One slug chewed up the liver.

661
01:05:03,774 --> 01:05:04,991
Here.

662
01:05:09,697 --> 01:05:10,744
.32's.

663
01:05:12,450 --> 01:05:16,421
city tonight, the mysterious
Vigilante is in the news again.

664
01:05:16,621 --> 01:05:20,421
A little more than two hours ago, in
an 8th Avenue subway underpass...

665
01:05:20,583 --> 01:05:22,836
two men were shot.
One died on the spot.

666
01:05:23,002 --> 01:05:25,505
The other managed to reach
the street before he collapsed.

667
01:05:25,671 --> 01:05:28,015
He died shortly afterward
in the hospital.

668
01:05:28,633 --> 01:05:33,309
The two men have been identified
as Joseph Roscoe Adams and George Reech.

669
01:05:33,471 --> 01:05:35,348
Both had long criminal records.

670
01:05:35,556 --> 01:05:39,186
The Vigilante himself
may have been wounded.

671
01:05:39,977 --> 01:05:43,902
The actions of The Vigilante,
as lawless as they may be...

672
01:05:44,148 --> 01:05:48,403
seem to be giving others new
attitudes toward crime in the streets.

673
01:05:48,653 --> 01:05:51,873
Instead of helplessly allowing themselves
to be mugged and robbed...

674
01:05:52,073 --> 01:05:53,746
a few are fighting back.

675
01:05:53,949 --> 01:05:56,748
I have with me
Mrs. Alma Lee Brown...

676
01:05:56,911 --> 01:06:00,040
who today successfully defended
herself against two muggers...

677
01:06:00,206 --> 01:06:01,708
with an unusual weapon.

678
01:06:01,874 --> 01:06:05,754
Mrs. Brown, would you tell us how
you drove off your attackers today?

679
01:06:05,920 --> 01:06:07,422
With a hatpin!

680
01:06:08,172 --> 01:06:12,552
- You ever seen a hatpin?
- I can't say that I have.

681
01:06:12,718 --> 01:06:16,473
Well, that's what we used to use to
hold our hats on with, ha, ha...

682
01:06:16,639 --> 01:06:20,394
and I ain't got no gun
like this Vigilante fellow...

683
01:06:20,893 --> 01:06:25,490
but I went to my closet, and everybody
better look out for me from now on.

684
01:06:26,857 --> 01:06:30,737
Because I've been robbed too many times,
and I've had enough!

685
01:06:31,278 --> 01:06:33,451
Some of the men
building this skyscraper...

686
01:06:33,614 --> 01:06:36,117
made what you might call
a citizens' arrest today.

687
01:06:36,325 --> 01:06:39,169
I'll ask Andrew McCabe,
one of the foremen, to tell you about it.

688
01:06:39,745 --> 01:06:42,965
Me and my crew was working
down in the hole.

689
01:06:43,124 --> 01:06:45,593
One of the boys
up on the steel yelled down:

690
01:06:45,751 --> 01:06:47,469
"There's a mugging going on!"

691
01:06:47,670 --> 01:06:51,595
So we come out of the hole and through
the gate, and we caught this guy running.

692
01:06:51,757 --> 01:06:54,761
And we roughed him up a little bit
before the police came.

693
01:06:54,969 --> 01:06:57,813
The hospital report
says the man had two broken arms...

694
01:06:57,972 --> 01:07:01,192
- ...a broken jaw, and cracked ribs.
- No kidding? Jeez.

695
01:07:01,392 --> 01:07:03,486
Poor guy must have fell down.

696
01:07:04,311 --> 01:07:07,030
Walking distances
from D'Agostino's:

697
01:07:07,189 --> 01:07:11,239
Two blocks crosstown,
six short blocks uptown and downtown.

698
01:07:11,527 --> 01:07:14,030
I mean, that's how far
I'd be willing to walk to a market.

699
01:07:14,196 --> 01:07:18,167
Ahem. Good.
Very good, Miss Gemetti.

700
01:07:18,367 --> 01:07:20,665
We have 12 families
living within this area...

701
01:07:20,828 --> 01:07:23,627
who have suffered a death
in the family in the past three months...

702
01:07:23,789 --> 01:07:26,759
from mugging, stabbing,
shooting, assault.

703
01:07:26,917 --> 01:07:29,466
Two of these families
have no male members.

704
01:07:29,628 --> 01:07:32,427
One family has only
an 80-year-old grandfather.

705
01:07:32,590 --> 01:07:34,684
That leaves nine families.

706
01:07:34,925 --> 01:07:37,895
Total number of male persons
in these families...

707
01:07:38,053 --> 01:07:42,274
who are old enough to have served in the
Vietnam War, Korea, or World War II...

708
01:07:42,433 --> 01:07:44,435
comes to 14.

709
01:07:45,770 --> 01:07:49,775
Wild. It's a real wild shot...

710
01:07:50,941 --> 01:07:53,639
but the fact is that
The Vigilante plugged

711
01:07:53,665 --> 01:07:55,893
his first victim in
Riverside Park...

712
01:07:56,030 --> 01:08:00,376
exactly two and one half blocks
from that D'Agostino market.

713
01:08:00,993 --> 01:08:05,043
Even if all these guys are clean,
we still can't ignore that coincidence.

714
01:08:05,539 --> 01:08:06,756
No, sir.

715
01:08:07,333 --> 01:08:09,461
Our friend lives in
that neighborhood.

716
01:08:09,627 --> 01:08:13,973
But, Frank, he was on a subway
with groceries five miles uptown.

717
01:08:14,799 --> 01:08:18,679
There's no better come-on for a mugging
than a guy with a bagful of groceries.

718
01:08:18,886 --> 01:08:22,561
Means he's got some money in his pocket
and his hands are occupied.

719
01:08:22,932 --> 01:08:26,106
He might have been carrying
those groceries for hours.

720
01:08:28,103 --> 01:08:30,481
I want a preliminary line
on these names.

721
01:08:30,648 --> 01:08:36,906
Where they work, service record,
reputation, police record, if any.

722
01:08:37,530 --> 01:08:40,704
And I want it fast.

723
01:08:41,325 --> 01:08:44,704
You know, like today, huh?

724
01:08:45,955 --> 01:08:49,334
It's probably having as much
effect on the total crime picture...

725
01:08:49,500 --> 01:08:51,377
as putting a
Band-Aid on a leper.

726
01:08:51,544 --> 01:08:53,625
Wait a minute, I
don't know about that,

727
01:08:53,651 --> 01:08:55,870
a mugger's gonna think
twice about who he hits.

728
01:08:56,006 --> 01:08:58,225
Sure. They're hitting more
old ladies, that's why.

729
01:08:58,384 --> 01:09:01,058
Paul, how you doing?
Let me get you a drink.

730
01:09:03,806 --> 01:09:05,604
The guy's a racist.

731
01:09:05,808 --> 01:09:07,606
You notice he kills
more blacks than whites.

732
01:09:07,768 --> 01:09:10,146
Oh, for Pete's sake, more blacks
are muggers than whites.

733
01:09:10,312 --> 01:09:13,065
What do you want us to do, increase
the proportion of white muggers...

734
01:09:13,232 --> 01:09:15,075
so we'll have racial equality
among muggers?

735
01:09:15,234 --> 01:09:18,659
Racial equality among muggers?
Ooh. I love it!

736
01:09:18,863 --> 01:09:20,911
He hasn't been the same
since that terrible incident.

737
01:09:55,983 --> 01:10:00,784
- Who we got here?
- A guy named Paul... Kersey.

738
01:10:00,988 --> 01:10:02,911
His wife was murdered
in their apartment.

739
01:10:03,073 --> 01:10:05,826
Interesting detail:
The attackers, three of them...

740
01:10:06,035 --> 01:10:08,584
gained entrance to the apartment
by posing as delivery boys...

741
01:10:08,746 --> 01:10:12,467
from our D'Agostino's market, where
The Vigilante buys his groceries.

742
01:10:13,167 --> 01:10:14,293
What else about him?

743
01:10:14,919 --> 01:10:16,512
He lives alone now.

744
01:10:16,712 --> 01:10:19,932
Development engineer
for the Blue Ridge corporation.

745
01:10:20,174 --> 01:10:22,222
Served in Korea, medical corps.

746
01:10:22,801 --> 01:10:24,644
Conscientious objector.

747
01:10:24,803 --> 01:10:28,808
No police record.
Credits, reputation excellent.

748
01:10:29,516 --> 01:10:32,315
Conscientious objectors
are unlikely vigilantes.

749
01:10:33,103 --> 01:10:36,232
- We got a finger?
- Yeah. Over there.

750
01:10:36,440 --> 01:10:39,535
Patrolman Joe Charles.

751
01:10:39,693 --> 01:10:40,865
Good.

752
01:10:44,949 --> 01:10:46,326
Good morning, Mr. Kersey.

753
01:10:47,076 --> 01:10:48,623
Joe Charles, Mr. Kersey.

754
01:10:48,827 --> 01:10:50,374
Oh, yes, of course.

755
01:10:50,537 --> 01:10:52,585
How do you do?
Good to see you again.

756
01:10:52,790 --> 01:10:54,383
How's your daughter?

757
01:10:54,959 --> 01:10:56,427
The same.

758
01:10:56,961 --> 01:10:58,508
Take care.

759
01:11:01,757 --> 01:11:03,225
Follow him.

760
01:11:16,063 --> 01:11:17,861
Yes, I'll see to that, Mrs. Cohen.

761
01:11:20,901 --> 01:11:23,154
Just a moment.
You're not residents here.

762
01:11:23,362 --> 01:11:25,114
Who do you wish to see?
I'll call up for you.

763
01:11:25,280 --> 01:11:26,623
No, you won't.

764
01:13:11,011 --> 01:13:13,389
The district
attorney will see you now.

765
01:13:23,148 --> 01:13:26,027
- Commissioner.
- Frank, you know the district attorney.

766
01:13:27,152 --> 01:13:29,575
- Mr. Peters.
- Inspector.

767
01:13:30,989 --> 01:13:33,583
The commissioner says you
have a pretty good suspect.

768
01:13:34,034 --> 01:13:37,584
Well, he fits the bill
in some respects.

769
01:13:38,038 --> 01:13:41,212
We got a blood sample
from the knife...

770
01:13:41,375 --> 01:13:44,720
used on him in the subway and
checked it against the sample...

771
01:13:44,878 --> 01:13:46,505
I found in his apartment.

772
01:13:47,381 --> 01:13:48,678
It narrows it down.

773
01:13:48,924 --> 01:13:50,926
But in the balance,
he could be the man?

774
01:13:51,385 --> 01:13:52,557
Yeah.

775
01:13:53,137 --> 01:13:54,935
Yeah, he could be.

776
01:13:55,597 --> 01:13:56,940
Frank...

777
01:13:58,308 --> 01:14:01,608
Suppose this Paul Kersey
is The Vigilante.

778
01:14:02,146 --> 01:14:04,114
All right. Let's say that.

779
01:14:07,025 --> 01:14:08,242
We don't want him.

780
01:14:10,737 --> 01:14:12,114
Okay.

781
01:14:12,281 --> 01:14:17,037
Inspector, on my desk, I have a statistic
red-hot out of the computer.

782
01:14:17,244 --> 01:14:18,291
Mm-hm.

783
01:14:18,453 --> 01:14:21,502
Mugging has gone down
by how much, sir?

784
01:14:22,040 --> 01:14:25,965
From 950 a week
to 470 reported last week.

785
01:14:26,128 --> 01:14:28,130
You understand
not too many people know that.

786
01:14:28,839 --> 01:14:31,558
And you wanna keep
it that way, huh?

787
01:14:31,717 --> 01:14:34,220
Oh, no, we have to keep it
that way, inspector.

788
01:14:35,179 --> 01:14:36,931
This whole city would explode.

789
01:14:37,139 --> 01:14:41,019
We'd have vigilantes out in the street
killing anybody who even looked greasy.

790
01:14:41,560 --> 01:14:45,315
- You can see that.
- We want this man to quit, desist...

791
01:14:45,814 --> 01:14:49,034
go away.
To stop.

792
01:14:51,528 --> 01:14:53,622
So the mugging rate can go up?

793
01:14:55,324 --> 01:14:57,577
If I arrest him, wouldn't that
get him off the streets?

794
01:14:57,743 --> 01:15:00,041
My God, man. I don't want
a martyr on my hands.

795
01:15:00,204 --> 01:15:03,549
All right.
All right.

796
01:15:04,082 --> 01:15:06,255
I just wanna hear you say it.

797
01:15:12,299 --> 01:15:14,051
I'll try to scare him off...

798
01:15:14,760 --> 01:15:16,854
but that's as far as I'll go.

799
01:15:17,054 --> 01:15:20,433
That's right, Frank.
Scare him off.

800
01:15:22,309 --> 01:15:24,107
Scare him off?

801
01:15:38,158 --> 01:15:39,205
Yes?

802
01:15:39,368 --> 01:15:42,042
A call for you from a man
who says he's an old friend...

803
01:15:42,204 --> 01:15:43,956
and wonders if you'll
recognize his voice.

804
01:15:44,164 --> 01:15:47,213
Do you want the call that way,
or shall I insist upon his name?

805
01:15:47,668 --> 01:15:50,387
- Okay, I'll take it.
- I'm putting you through.

806
01:15:53,131 --> 01:15:55,884
- Hello?
- Is this Paul Kersey?

807
01:15:56,093 --> 01:15:57,766
Yes. Who's this?

808
01:15:59,721 --> 01:16:02,770
Mr. Kersey, you're under
police surveillance.

809
01:16:03,225 --> 01:16:05,319
You're being watched.

810
01:16:13,694 --> 01:16:16,868
Scare him off.
Heh. Ha-ha-ha.

811
01:16:28,542 --> 01:16:31,341
Papers! Papers!

812
01:16:31,670 --> 01:16:34,674
Read all about The Vigilante!

813
01:16:35,299 --> 01:16:37,552
Get your papers here!

814
01:16:37,718 --> 01:16:40,016
Read all about The Vigilante!

815
01:16:40,387 --> 01:16:42,139
How are you this evening, sir?

816
01:16:42,306 --> 01:16:44,855
Papers! Papers!

817
01:16:45,017 --> 01:16:47,440
Read all about The Vigilante!

818
01:17:03,952 --> 01:17:06,017
All right, you.
Get your hands up.

819
01:17:06,043 --> 01:17:07,732
Come on. Hands on the car.
Come on.

820
01:17:07,914 --> 01:17:09,336
Spread your legs.

821
01:17:17,716 --> 01:17:19,184
Okay. Turn around.

822
01:17:19,968 --> 01:17:22,016
Let's see some identification.

823
01:17:27,476 --> 01:17:30,650
- Where do you live?
- 33 Riverside.

824
01:17:30,937 --> 01:17:33,406
Okay, Mr. Kersey. Sorry to have
roughed you up so much.

825
01:17:33,565 --> 01:17:35,818
We're looking for a guy
pretty close to your description.

826
01:17:36,026 --> 01:17:40,281
He's supposed to be armed, and we couldn't
take any chances. I hope you understand.

827
01:17:41,573 --> 01:17:44,326
Look, if you wanna make a complaint,
I'll give you my number.

828
01:17:44,576 --> 01:17:46,123
It's all right.
Nobody was hurt.

829
01:17:46,328 --> 01:17:49,047
- Okay, thanks. Good night, Mr. Kersey.
- Night.

830
01:17:55,337 --> 01:17:56,589
Okay?

831
01:17:57,172 --> 01:17:58,264
Yeah.

832
01:17:59,132 --> 01:18:00,429
Okay.

833
01:18:21,071 --> 01:18:23,165
Went in the building
about 10 minutes ago.

834
01:18:23,323 --> 01:18:25,667
Went to D'Agostino's market first.

835
01:19:25,760 --> 01:19:27,353
Let's check him, huh?

836
01:19:28,638 --> 01:19:30,891
Go to that phone booth on
the corner, call his number.

837
01:19:31,057 --> 01:19:32,559
He's up there.

838
01:19:32,976 --> 01:19:34,603
Check him anyway.

839
01:20:49,177 --> 01:20:51,851
- Police! I need the phone.
- Come on!

840
01:20:52,556 --> 01:20:54,604
- Who is this guy?
- He must be crazy.

841
01:20:54,766 --> 01:20:56,814
He said "police."
I didn't see a badge.

842
01:21:03,483 --> 01:21:06,202
I'll call them. I'll call as soon
as he gets off the phone.

843
01:21:06,361 --> 01:21:09,285
- Thanks, pal.
- Yeah? Up yours!

844
01:21:15,829 --> 01:21:18,582
No answer. He could be
in the shower or something.

845
01:21:18,748 --> 01:21:20,250
Stay here.

846
01:22:16,514 --> 01:22:18,687
- Good night, Mr. Kersey.
- Good night.

847
01:22:47,629 --> 01:22:49,802
I'm supposed to meet Paul Kersey.
Has he gone up yet?

848
01:22:49,964 --> 01:22:53,810
Kersey? Yes, sir. He went up and
came down. Just walked out.

849
01:23:24,249 --> 01:23:27,298
- Where'd you go?
- He didn't show here, did he?

850
01:23:27,502 --> 01:23:29,175
Can I ask a simple question?

851
01:23:29,379 --> 01:23:31,598
Is this Paul Kersey the bird?

852
01:23:33,049 --> 01:23:35,143
I ain't gonna ask
any more questions.

853
01:23:35,427 --> 01:23:37,475
Go home, will you?
I don't need you.

854
01:23:37,637 --> 01:23:39,014
Weird!

855
01:24:08,918 --> 01:24:12,673
Come on down, motherfucker.
We gonna take you.

856
01:24:12,881 --> 01:24:17,057
That's right, motherfucker,
and you can't go back up, either.

857
01:24:24,976 --> 01:24:27,900
Come on down and bring
us the money, honey.

858
01:24:28,146 --> 01:24:30,865
How much money you got, honey?

859
01:24:36,780 --> 01:24:38,248
What the fuck?

860
01:24:39,240 --> 01:24:40,867
Fuck!

861
01:25:15,109 --> 01:25:17,077
Units in the 2-6 precinct.

862
01:25:17,237 --> 01:25:20,741
A 10-34, 1-2-5 Street
and the West Side Highway.

863
01:26:35,398 --> 01:26:36,695
Hey!

864
01:26:43,656 --> 01:26:44,748
Fill your hand.

865
01:26:46,034 --> 01:26:47,456
Huh?

866
01:26:50,663 --> 01:26:52,210
Draw.

867
01:27:34,958 --> 01:27:36,460
Where is he, this patrolman?

868
01:27:52,809 --> 01:27:54,231
- You're Reilly?
- Yes, sir.

869
01:27:54,394 --> 01:27:55,987
- I'm Ochoa.
- Yes, sir.

870
01:27:58,147 --> 01:28:00,275
- You were the first man on the scene?
- Yes, sir.

871
01:28:01,693 --> 01:28:04,572
- God bless you, sir.
- Never mind that.

872
01:28:06,406 --> 01:28:08,829
They told me on the radio
you had to see me?

873
01:28:09,117 --> 01:28:10,619
Paul Kersey.

874
01:28:11,995 --> 01:28:13,918
You spoke to him
before the ambulance got here?

875
01:28:14,122 --> 01:28:15,214
No, sir.

876
01:28:16,165 --> 01:28:17,963
- What did you get?
- His address, sir.

877
01:28:19,752 --> 01:28:21,129
Is that all?

878
01:28:23,589 --> 01:28:24,636
Well?

879
01:28:34,308 --> 01:28:36,060
You enter this on your report?

880
01:28:36,477 --> 01:28:37,524
Not yet, sir.

881
01:28:39,647 --> 01:28:40,739
Why not?

882
01:28:41,649 --> 01:28:42,946
I was, uh...

883
01:28:43,109 --> 01:28:44,736
waiting for instructions, sir.

884
01:28:45,528 --> 01:28:46,780
You never saw it.

885
01:28:48,781 --> 01:28:50,033
Yes, sir.

886
01:28:53,327 --> 01:28:56,171
Oh, uh... What's your full name?

887
01:28:56,372 --> 01:28:59,000
Jackson Reilly, sir.
21st precinct.

888
01:29:00,084 --> 01:29:03,088
Okay. I'll remember it.

889
01:29:15,850 --> 01:29:18,649
Inspector, is it true
that you have The Vigilante in there?

890
01:29:18,853 --> 01:29:20,947
- No.
- Well, who have you got there?

891
01:29:25,610 --> 01:29:27,658
Are you in charge? How is he?

892
01:29:27,820 --> 01:29:31,541
Wounds are clean. Nothing vital.
We have a transfusion going on now.

893
01:29:31,699 --> 01:29:33,918
Soon as we get some blood in him,
we'll sew him up again.

894
01:29:34,077 --> 01:29:35,124
- Is he in there?
- Yeah.

895
01:29:35,286 --> 01:29:37,414
- All right if I go in?
- He won't be able to talk much.

896
01:29:37,580 --> 01:29:40,254
- Can he hear me?
- He is conscious.

897
01:29:51,344 --> 01:29:54,063
Police. I'd like to have him alone.

898
01:30:09,237 --> 01:30:11,239
Good evening, Mr. Kersey.

899
01:30:17,537 --> 01:30:19,505
This is your gun, Mr. Kersey.

900
01:30:21,749 --> 01:30:24,047
We tried to give you a
chance to get rid of it.

901
01:30:24,377 --> 01:30:25,549
You wouldn't take it.

902
01:30:27,004 --> 01:30:28,927
Do you hear me okay?

903
01:30:30,550 --> 01:30:34,271
We have here a peculiar situation,
Mr. Kersey.

904
01:30:34,804 --> 01:30:37,680
We find it necessary to
make you a proposition

905
01:30:37,706 --> 01:30:40,336
since you are not gonna
favor us by dying.

906
01:30:41,352 --> 01:30:45,528
You work for a company
with lots of offices.

907
01:30:46,607 --> 01:30:49,201
Get a transfer to another city...

908
01:30:49,861 --> 01:30:52,080
and I'll drop this
gun in the river.

909
01:30:56,159 --> 01:31:00,414
Are we connecting, Mr. Kersey?

910
01:31:02,290 --> 01:31:04,759
We want you to get
out of New York.

911
01:31:05,459 --> 01:31:07,336
Permanently.

912
01:31:12,550 --> 01:31:13,927
Inspector.

913
01:31:18,014 --> 01:31:19,732
By sundown?

914
01:31:35,823 --> 01:31:37,075
- There he is.
- Here he comes.

915
01:31:37,283 --> 01:31:38,830
Do you have The Vigilante, inspector?

916
01:31:39,035 --> 01:31:41,663
- Can you give us information?
- No!

917
01:31:41,871 --> 01:31:43,544
Isn't the wounded man
The Vigilante?

918
01:31:43,748 --> 01:31:45,216
No. He's just a mugging victim.

919
01:31:45,416 --> 01:31:48,386
How do you explain the first
reports that he is The Vigilante?

920
01:31:48,544 --> 01:31:50,592
False reports.
It happens all the time.

921
01:31:50,796 --> 01:31:52,798
Then The Vigilante's
still out there?

922
01:31:52,965 --> 01:31:54,967
That's right. He's still
out there on the streets.

923
01:31:55,176 --> 01:31:58,225
- Let me through.
- Was he shot by The Vigilante?

924
01:32:09,815 --> 01:32:13,365
The Amtrak train from New York to
Chicago has arrived on Track 8.

925
01:32:14,737 --> 01:32:16,455
- Mr. Kersey.
- Paul Kersey.

926
01:32:16,614 --> 01:32:19,538
Fred Brown. Welcome to Chicago, sir.
Did you have a nice trip?

927
01:32:19,700 --> 01:32:20,826
Yeah, it was okay.

928
01:32:20,993 --> 01:32:22,681
Good. I found a nice
apartment for you.

929
01:32:22,707 --> 01:32:24,648
I hope you like it. It's
on Lake Shore Drive.

930
01:32:24,789 --> 01:32:28,339
You have a view of Lake Michigan, morning
sun. We've got your office ready too.

931
01:32:28,542 --> 01:32:30,260
There's a very good
golf club, if you play.

932
01:32:31,212 --> 01:32:34,056
- Listen, I think you'll enjoy it here.
- Excuse me.

