1
00:00:53,934 --> 00:00:57,438
Frost fills the sky over
Ten Mile Lake

2
00:00:57,616 --> 00:01:01,787
Silken threads anxious of
youth.

3
00:01:02,068 --> 00:01:05,718
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely.

4
00:01:05,791 --> 00:01:09,098
Envious of love, not of
immortality.

5
00:01:09,171 --> 00:01:12,882
This pointing will remind
you of me.

6
00:01:13,727 --> 00:01:16,094
Sian's grave?

7
00:01:17,836 --> 00:01:20,537
Sian died long ago.

8
00:01:20,683 --> 00:01:22,769
She's a ghost?

9
00:01:24,938 --> 00:01:30,079
Yes I'm a ghost but I bring
mortals no harm.

10
00:01:30,330 --> 00:01:32,197
I died far away from my home

11
00:01:32,311 --> 00:01:35,189
An evil spirit took my
corpse and won't let me rest

12
00:01:35,273 --> 00:01:36,368
in peace.

13
00:01:36,524 --> 00:01:40,122
If you want to save me, move
my bones away from here.

14
00:01:40,174 --> 00:01:43,469
Then it will be possible for
me to be reincarnated.

15
00:01:43,657 --> 00:01:44,825
Sian

16
00:01:44,866 --> 00:01:47,056
I will save you.

17
00:01:52,146 --> 00:01:53,637
Sian

18
00:01:53,710 --> 00:01:55,202
Ning

19
00:01:59,310 --> 00:02:03,836
You dare oppose me? I will
never excuse you from death

20
00:02:03,940 --> 00:02:06,756
Let them go, please.

21
00:02:09,091 --> 00:02:11,522
The Diamond Sutra

22
00:02:18,101 --> 00:02:21,021
We've escaped
Sian, we're safe

23
00:02:21,335 --> 00:02:23,138
Dawn is breaking.

24
00:02:23,462 --> 00:02:25,683
Sian, hide in the tower of
ashes.

25
00:02:25,829 --> 00:02:28,405
If the sun's rays shine on
you, you'll never...

26
00:02:28,509 --> 00:02:30,835
be reincarnated.

27
00:02:30,908 --> 00:02:33,578
Ning, good-bye forever

28
00:02:49,105 --> 00:02:51,212
I hope that Sian will be
reincarnated.

29
00:02:51,296 --> 00:02:53,933
I must return to the Orchid
Buddhist Monastery.

30
00:02:54,079 --> 00:02:58,637
If you need me, you can find
me there. Take care

31
00:04:21,907 --> 00:04:24,055
Who is that young man?

32
00:04:24,097 --> 00:04:27,017
He's the poor scholar who
lived 2 blocks away.

33
00:04:27,059 --> 00:04:29,656
Things have changed since he
was last here.

34
00:04:46,644 --> 00:04:49,668
Wasn't he that shop's bill
collector?

35
00:04:49,710 --> 00:04:54,120
He doesn't even know it went
out of business long ago

36
00:05:05,331 --> 00:05:07,730
Welcome Welcome

37
00:05:39,776 --> 00:05:41,581
The bill collector's here.

38
00:05:41,726 --> 00:05:43,531
How much money did you
collect?

39
00:05:43,604 --> 00:05:45,199
We're here to catch escaped
convicts.

40
00:05:45,240 --> 00:05:46,670
It's the police who Run &

41
00:05:46,847 --> 00:05:48,578
Pursue them

42
00:05:51,091 --> 00:05:52,363
You're Bing Chow?

43
00:05:52,478 --> 00:05:55,366
You've made a mistake. He
has a beard and I don't

44
00:05:55,471 --> 00:05:56,722
You shaved it off

45
00:05:56,827 --> 00:05:59,048
Take him back and collect
the reward.

46
00:05:59,194 --> 00:06:00,623
Get in

47
00:06:00,727 --> 00:06:02,667
I haven't committed any
crime

48
00:06:02,813 --> 00:06:05,315
Let me go. I've been
wrongly accused

49
00:06:05,462 --> 00:06:07,641
Let me got I've been wrongly
accused

50
00:06:07,787 --> 00:06:09,487
I'm not Bing Chow

51
00:06:09,664 --> 00:06:11,812
You've made a mistake. I'm
not Bing Chow

52
00:06:11,927 --> 00:06:14,503
I am wrongly accused

53
00:06:27,768 --> 00:06:29,676
My name is Ning,
not Bing Chow.

54
00:06:29,812 --> 00:06:32,137
Old man may I ask who...

55
00:06:32,638 --> 00:06:36,799
A man just like you, fated
to being imprisoned.

56
00:06:37,539 --> 00:06:39,562
So pessimistic

57
00:06:39,667 --> 00:06:42,722
It's all my elders' fault,
insisting I get an education

58
00:06:42,868 --> 00:06:45,892
When I grew up, I was
learned and wrote books.

59
00:06:45,965 --> 00:06:48,040
But when I write of my
travels, I'm accused of

60
00:06:48,186 --> 00:06:49,813
revealing state secrets.

61
00:06:49,959 --> 00:06:52,180
When I write of history,
they say I'm satirizing

62
00:06:52,326 --> 00:06:53,338
the present.

63
00:06:53,516 --> 00:06:55,528
If I analyze military
strategy, they say I'm

64
00:06:55,633 --> 00:06:57,061
planning a rebellion.

65
00:06:57,165 --> 00:06:59,668
I can't even write fairy
tales, for they accuse me of

66
00:06:59,845 --> 00:07:01,024
promoting superstition.

67
00:07:01,128 --> 00:07:03,318
Finally, I wrote the
biography of a powerful man.

68
00:07:03,464 --> 00:07:05,790
Then he was arrested,
accused of being a rebel.

69
00:07:05,935 --> 00:07:08,115
We where both sentenced to
life imprisonment.

70
00:07:08,229 --> 00:07:11,108
Wouldn't you say that prison
is my fate?

71
00:07:12,192 --> 00:07:13,443
A cockroach

72
00:07:13,590 --> 00:07:15,144
Where?

73
00:07:15,331 --> 00:07:17,021
Cockroach?

74
00:07:19,649 --> 00:07:22,214
You're really wasteful The
cockroaches here are of the

75
00:07:22,318 --> 00:07:23,716
best quality.

76
00:07:23,820 --> 00:07:25,552
There are no delicacies here

77
00:07:25,666 --> 00:07:27,502
After you've been here a
while, you'll even salivate

78
00:07:27,648 --> 00:07:29,034
over a housefly.

79
00:07:29,180 --> 00:07:31,161
Old man, how long have you
been here?

80
00:07:31,297 --> 00:07:33,414
I was your age when I
first arrived.

81
00:07:33,561 --> 00:07:36,970
Look how I've changed
Full of character

82
00:07:37,325 --> 00:07:39,505
You've been here a long time

83
00:07:39,651 --> 00:07:41,768
Help I am innocent

84
00:07:41,882 --> 00:07:45,459
I'm not Bing Chow
I am innocent

85
00:07:45,637 --> 00:07:48,973
You've made a mistake. I'm
not Bing Chow

86
00:08:18,976 --> 00:08:23,418
Another nightmare. What did
you dream this time?

87
00:08:23,596 --> 00:08:25,650
I dreamt you were haggard
and exhausted.

88
00:08:25,755 --> 00:08:28,330
Exhausted? True, you will
soon be totally exhausted.

89
00:08:28,465 --> 00:08:31,281
You have nightmares every
night. Look at the calendar.

90
00:08:31,396 --> 00:08:34,316
You've been here so long and
still can't adjust.

91
00:08:34,420 --> 00:08:37,017
Soon you'll even forget that
your last name is Chow.

92
00:08:37,131 --> 00:08:39,708
Old man, my last name
isn't Chow

93
00:08:39,854 --> 00:08:41,511
Bing Chow

94
00:08:42,597 --> 00:08:43,952
Supper

95
00:08:44,098 --> 00:08:45,557
OK.

96
00:08:50,250 --> 00:08:52,544
A chicken leg?

97
00:08:52,722 --> 00:08:55,048
Happy days are here again

98
00:08:56,476 --> 00:08:59,510
Old man There's only one
bowl. You eat first.

99
00:08:59,616 --> 00:09:03,577
No, it's for you. I'd rather
eat cockroaches.

100
00:09:03,683 --> 00:09:06,081
I'll tell you something when
you've finished.

101
00:09:06,185 --> 00:09:08,166
I haven't had chicken in
a long time.

102
00:09:08,343 --> 00:09:10,670
Old man, why are you carving
my name?

103
00:09:10,784 --> 00:09:14,329
All these men ate chicken
legs.

104
00:09:14,434 --> 00:09:17,667
We call that chicken a
headless chicken.

105
00:09:17,771 --> 00:09:21,035
After you've eaten it, they
chop off your head

106
00:09:21,150 --> 00:09:23,861
Chop off your head?

107
00:09:28,074 --> 00:09:32,381
Bing Chow, we have no
personnel quarrel.

108
00:09:32,600 --> 00:09:36,938
Don't come back from the
grave and seek revenge on me

109
00:09:37,189 --> 00:09:39,482
They behead people at noon.

110
00:09:39,597 --> 00:09:42,194
It's now the middle of
the night.

111
00:09:42,277 --> 00:09:45,302
Some official's son got in
trouble, and they're looking

112
00:09:45,406 --> 00:09:47,241
for a substitute.

113
00:09:47,356 --> 00:09:51,945
At night, the executioner
can't tell one from another.

114
00:09:52,539 --> 00:09:56,397
Is there no justice in the
world?

115
00:09:56,606 --> 00:10:00,986
Is there no reward for being
a good man?

116
00:10:03,813 --> 00:10:08,745
It is of no concern to me.

117
00:10:19,956 --> 00:10:21,937
I was always an honest man.

118
00:10:22,041 --> 00:10:24,439
I'll give you whatever I can

119
00:10:24,658 --> 00:10:27,850
This painting was a gift
from my dearest one.

120
00:10:27,923 --> 00:10:30,352
I don't want to part with it
even in death.

121
00:10:30,498 --> 00:10:32,552
Young man, you have a good
heart.

122
00:10:32,731 --> 00:10:34,879
Let me give you a present.

123
00:10:37,183 --> 00:10:38,528
You are so learned.

124
00:10:38,643 --> 00:10:40,969
It is fortunate that I die
rather than you.

125
00:10:41,115 --> 00:10:43,816
You're a good man. Such a
pity you have to die.

126
00:10:43,962 --> 00:10:46,151
It would be a pity if you
died, not me.

127
00:10:46,266 --> 00:10:48,445
Anybody's death is a pity.
You're a rare specimen.

128
00:10:48,560 --> 00:10:50,635
If you die, your type will
be extinct.

129
00:10:50,720 --> 00:10:53,420
It's been a long time since
I set somebody free.

130
00:10:53,534 --> 00:10:56,006
This tunnel leads to the
outside.

131
00:10:56,111 --> 00:10:59,333
Go out and start anew.

132
00:10:59,656 --> 00:11:01,732
Don't give me such false
hopes.

133
00:11:01,847 --> 00:11:04,036
If this is an escape route,
why didn't you escape

134
00:11:04,151 --> 00:11:05,215
long ago?

135
00:11:05,256 --> 00:11:07,311
It's less troublesome for me
to write my book here.

136
00:11:07,383 --> 00:11:09,490
When I finish, then I'll
escape and get it printed.

137
00:11:09,646 --> 00:11:11,232
Don't worry about me.

138
00:11:11,346 --> 00:11:13,369
Always keep this bundle
with you.

139
00:11:13,474 --> 00:11:16,425
Once you're out of here,
never come back

140
00:11:16,571 --> 00:11:18,229
Get going

141
00:11:18,730 --> 00:11:20,669
What will happen to you
after I've gone?

142
00:11:20,816 --> 00:11:22,275
They like hearing my stories

143
00:11:22,348 --> 00:11:24,559
So long as I don't get to
the story's end,

144
00:11:24,673 --> 00:11:26,207
they'll never harm me.

145
00:11:26,311 --> 00:11:28,292
But they'll accuse you of
helping me escape.

146
00:11:28,397 --> 00:11:30,796
I'll say you were put to
death for somebody else

147
00:11:30,942 --> 00:11:32,328
2 days ago.

148
00:11:32,432 --> 00:11:34,414
They won't dare make a fuss.

149
00:11:34,560 --> 00:11:36,614
Go
- Take care

150
00:11:37,939 --> 00:11:41,088
Bing Chow the time has come

151
00:11:41,588 --> 00:11:43,247
Hurry up

152
00:11:45,134 --> 00:11:46,386
Bing Chow

153
00:11:46,459 --> 00:11:48,086
He's dead.

154
00:11:54,917 --> 00:11:57,450
I've escaped

155
00:12:12,874 --> 00:12:16,273
There's even a horse here
waiting for me

156
00:12:18,923 --> 00:12:22,020
That old man is really
remarkable

157
00:12:22,197 --> 00:12:25,742
I must repay his kindness
someday.

158
00:12:29,299 --> 00:12:31,624
Hey That's my horse

159
00:12:31,906 --> 00:12:35,576
What a stupid horse letting
a stranger ride him

160
00:12:35,732 --> 00:12:38,715
I don't even have time to
wash my hands

161
00:12:40,738 --> 00:12:44,045
You think you're fast over
land... I'll go underground

162
00:12:44,149 --> 00:12:45,775
Open sesame

163
00:12:52,846 --> 00:12:55,975
I must find a place to get
out of this downpour

164
00:12:57,684 --> 00:12:59,666
Good A house

165
00:13:03,149 --> 00:13:05,370
Open the door

166
00:13:14,214 --> 00:13:17,102
"Righteous Villa "...

167
00:13:25,424 --> 00:13:27,854
Anybody home?

168
00:13:31,649 --> 00:13:36,280
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8

169
00:13:36,906 --> 00:13:40,201
8 coffins Must be the
whole family.

170
00:13:40,795 --> 00:13:44,800
I won't disturb you. I just
want to stay the night.

171
00:13:44,978 --> 00:13:49,107
Don't bother to get up. I'll
take care of myself.

172
00:13:50,817 --> 00:13:55,197
I told you not to go any
trouble. Please go back

173
00:13:56,105 --> 00:13:59,890
The way you rush about in no
fixed direction

174
00:14:00,047 --> 00:14:04,114
I had a hard time following
you underground.

175
00:14:04,218 --> 00:14:07,169
Don't you have any idea
where you're going?

176
00:14:07,242 --> 00:14:10,089
Your face looks so horrible,
you must have suffered a

177
00:14:10,204 --> 00:14:11,267
painful death.

178
00:14:11,382 --> 00:14:13,749
If you'd rushed around
underground all day like me,

179
00:14:13,895 --> 00:14:17,493
you wouldn't have the energy
to come back to the surface.

180
00:14:19,422 --> 00:14:21,852
I don't know you. Why are
you following me?

181
00:14:21,967 --> 00:14:25,679
I don't know you either, so
why did you take my horse?

182
00:14:25,794 --> 00:14:27,348
That's your horse?

183
00:14:27,494 --> 00:14:29,673
I thought it was the
old man's.

184
00:14:29,788 --> 00:14:32,364
Still you should have asked
before taking it.

185
00:14:33,375 --> 00:14:36,984
You're alive. Sorry It's
all a misunderstanding.

186
00:14:39,497 --> 00:14:42,980
If there's anything I can do
to help, just let me know.

187
00:14:43,053 --> 00:14:46,171
Enough of your tricks. A
good thing my reactions are

188
00:14:46,317 --> 00:14:47,349
so fast.

189
00:14:47,506 --> 00:14:49,518
Friend, you need a place to
stay the night.

190
00:14:49,623 --> 00:14:50,979
Here there's a roof over
your head.

191
00:14:51,083 --> 00:14:52,584
Might as well stay here.

192
00:14:52,688 --> 00:14:55,713
How do I know what you'd
do after I fell asleep?

193
00:14:58,957 --> 00:15:00,614
I knew it

194
00:15:01,803 --> 00:15:04,306
Let's draw up some
boundaries.

195
00:15:04,619 --> 00:15:06,215
I'm staying next door.

196
00:15:06,329 --> 00:15:10,011
If you have something to say
shout it. Don't come over.

197
00:15:22,649 --> 00:15:25,496
I haven't bathed in a long
time.

198
00:17:28,718 --> 00:17:30,626
Who is it?

199
00:17:34,485 --> 00:17:36,571
Are you a mortal?

200
00:17:39,262 --> 00:17:42,557
Hey, friend next door. Get
up There's ghosts

201
00:17:42,630 --> 00:17:45,227
Get up. Do you hear me?

202
00:17:45,445 --> 00:17:47,250
Hurry and get up

203
00:17:47,396 --> 00:17:49,971
Not a sound. Maybe he left
already.

204
00:18:08,971 --> 00:18:10,703
What a nuisance

205
00:18:26,991 --> 00:18:29,286
Friend, there are fierce
ghosts here

206
00:18:29,401 --> 00:18:32,654
Ghosts? I'll use my maglo to
banish them

207
00:18:36,221 --> 00:18:39,860
Ghosts and goblins, I order
you to leave

208
00:18:45,575 --> 00:18:49,184
Oh, you understand the
occult

209
00:18:49,444 --> 00:18:52,009
My nose is sensitive to
other worldly spirits...

210
00:18:52,124 --> 00:18:54,512
So why do I smell nothing
now?

211
00:18:54,627 --> 00:18:56,358
Get out of the way

212
00:18:57,516 --> 00:18:59,173
Abracadabra

213
00:19:01,343 --> 00:19:04,670
Strange. Not even a hint of
ghostly odor

214
00:19:04,857 --> 00:19:07,840
Abracadabra Hocus-pocus
flash

215
00:19:08,090 --> 00:19:10,833
Abracadabra

216
00:19:11,083 --> 00:19:14,525
Abracadabra

217
00:19:25,631 --> 00:19:27,841
Don't come here
- Leave

218
00:19:43,129 --> 00:19:46,290
You're not even real ghosts
Wasting my occult talents.

219
00:19:46,436 --> 00:19:48,020
Phonies?

220
00:20:02,516 --> 00:20:04,279
Want to trick me?

221
00:20:10,483 --> 00:20:13,778
A good thing you have a
waistband.

222
00:20:24,291 --> 00:20:26,512
Stay away from me

223
00:20:28,159 --> 00:20:30,339
I'm failing...

224
00:20:30,558 --> 00:20:32,466
Stop hugging me

225
00:20:35,709 --> 00:20:36,648
Let go

226
00:20:36,752 --> 00:20:38,484
If I let go, I'll fall

227
00:20:38,598 --> 00:20:40,882
If you don't let go, I'll...

228
00:21:10,123 --> 00:21:11,750
Sian?

229
00:21:13,877 --> 00:21:15,087
Sian

230
00:21:19,237 --> 00:21:21,740
Hocus-pocus heebie-jeebie

231
00:21:24,942 --> 00:21:27,194
I order you to freeze

232
00:21:27,445 --> 00:21:28,769
Freeze

233
00:21:29,019 --> 00:21:30,782
Freeze

234
00:21:32,252 --> 00:21:34,264
Sian, is that you?

235
00:21:34,963 --> 00:21:37,602
What kind of black magic is
that? Let them go

236
00:21:37,717 --> 00:21:39,239
Otherwise I'll kill him.

237
00:21:39,311 --> 00:21:40,772
Oh... Freeze

238
00:21:42,232 --> 00:21:45,047
Kill him. He's no friend of
mine

239
00:21:48,113 --> 00:21:50,230
Elder Chu

240
00:21:50,731 --> 00:21:53,358
Are you Elder Chu,
traveling incognito?

241
00:21:53,516 --> 00:21:54,788
Elder who?

242
00:21:54,975 --> 00:21:57,332
Your disciple is deeply
sorry.

243
00:21:57,510 --> 00:21:59,418
Disciple?

244
00:21:59,564 --> 00:22:01,681
Elder Chu?

245
00:22:01,827 --> 00:22:05,686
Sian, it's me. Don't you
recognize me?

246
00:22:05,894 --> 00:22:09,022
We come from a good family.
My name is Windy.

247
00:22:09,168 --> 00:22:11,316
This is my younger sister,
Moon.

248
00:22:11,463 --> 00:22:13,308
Elder Chu.

249
00:22:13,444 --> 00:22:15,112
Elder, you can save us.

250
00:22:15,227 --> 00:22:17,031
My father is Lord Fu, the
ex-Minister of Rites.

251
00:22:17,167 --> 00:22:19,252
He was framed. They're now
transporting him to...

252
00:22:19,367 --> 00:22:20,609
be executed.

253
00:22:20,723 --> 00:22:22,705
We want to attack the
transport wagon and

254
00:22:22,809 --> 00:22:24,393
rescue him.

255
00:22:24,519 --> 00:22:26,699
You are the learned and
brilliant Chu.

256
00:22:26,845 --> 00:22:29,170
You two are loyal imperial
warriors.

257
00:22:29,347 --> 00:22:31,401
Every one is an eminent
personage.

258
00:22:31,506 --> 00:22:34,499
Now it's my turn to
introduce myself, I am...

259
00:22:34,958 --> 00:22:36,689
Spell

260
00:22:40,172 --> 00:22:43,718
My name is Autumn, from the
Kunlun sact.

261
00:22:44,176 --> 00:22:46,950
I've read everything that
the Elder has written.

262
00:22:47,065 --> 00:22:49,662
I never get involved in
affairs of state.

263
00:22:49,808 --> 00:22:53,290
We pay our respects to
Elder Chu.

264
00:22:53,500 --> 00:22:56,419
My name is Ning, not Chu.

265
00:22:56,566 --> 00:22:58,474
I can tell you are clever.

266
00:22:58,651 --> 00:23:01,571
Clever people do not always
reveal their identities.

267
00:23:01,707 --> 00:23:04,417
Anyway, in our hearts we
know who you really are.

268
00:23:04,533 --> 00:23:06,817
How can I make you believe
me?

269
00:23:06,962 --> 00:23:09,560
No need for you to say
anything. Everybody remembers

270
00:23:09,685 --> 00:23:12,114
From now on, Elder Chu will
be known as Ning.

271
00:23:12,218 --> 00:23:13,428
Chu is Ning.

272
00:23:13,574 --> 00:23:14,961
Yes

273
00:23:16,118 --> 00:23:17,923
We will now take an oath.

274
00:23:18,027 --> 00:23:19,800
Whoever reveal their
identities...

275
00:23:19,946 --> 00:23:22,375
will be chopped up into
10,000 pieces.

276
00:23:22,480 --> 00:23:23,804
Yes

277
00:23:23,982 --> 00:23:27,037
Such an honor that you rode
my horse

278
00:23:34,034 --> 00:23:38,383
Sian, do you remember this
painting and poem?

279
00:23:38,592 --> 00:23:41,303
Sian? Poem?

280
00:23:41,480 --> 00:23:44,119
He's reciting poetry.
Quickly, pen and paper.

281
00:23:44,233 --> 00:23:46,768
We must record what he says.
Elder is giving us a hint.

282
00:23:46,841 --> 00:23:48,300
Hurry

283
00:23:50,073 --> 00:23:53,170
Frost fills the sky over 10
Mile Lake;

284
00:23:53,275 --> 00:23:55,778
Silken threads anxious of
youth.

285
00:23:55,893 --> 00:23:58,698
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely;

286
00:23:58,844 --> 00:24:02,108
Envious of lovers, not of
immortality.

287
00:24:02,567 --> 00:24:04,819
Very profound

288
00:24:04,965 --> 00:24:07,573
What does "10 mile" mean?

289
00:24:07,718 --> 00:24:10,315
10 mile

290
00:24:10,743 --> 00:24:13,287
It is all very deep.

291
00:24:15,790 --> 00:24:19,649
His words are too profound

292
00:24:20,806 --> 00:24:23,789
10 Mile? That must mean 10
Mile Pavilion.

293
00:24:23,934 --> 00:24:25,248
What do you mean?

294
00:24:25,394 --> 00:24:28,586
There's a 10 Mile Pavilion
near hear. - That's right

295
00:24:28,669 --> 00:24:31,725
Sister, "10 miles" refers to
10 Mile Pavilion.

296
00:24:31,870 --> 00:24:33,925
It's nearby.

297
00:24:35,447 --> 00:24:37,565
I understand.

298
00:24:37,752 --> 00:24:40,109
10 Mile Pavilion is not
far from here.

299
00:24:40,254 --> 00:24:41,955
"Frost" refers to Frost's
Descent.

300
00:24:42,059 --> 00:24:43,936
Each year has 24 climatic
periods...

301
00:24:44,051 --> 00:24:46,303
After the autumnal equinox
comes the frost...

302
00:24:46,376 --> 00:24:48,598
and today is the day of
Frost's Descent.

303
00:24:48,775 --> 00:24:51,246
Elder is telling us that
father will be transported

304
00:24:51,350 --> 00:24:53,082
past 10 Mile Pavilion.

305
00:24:53,196 --> 00:24:55,376
He's telling us to rescue
him there.

306
00:24:55,564 --> 00:24:58,724
Elder is truly perceptive.
We can save father.

307
00:24:58,901 --> 00:25:01,445
We had it right
- Good.

308
00:25:01,685 --> 00:25:03,489
It hurts

309
00:25:05,064 --> 00:25:07,734
What's the matter? Get up

310
00:25:07,848 --> 00:25:09,788
Reporting

311
00:25:10,038 --> 00:25:12,259
Miss Windy Your father
will pass the 10 Mile

312
00:25:12,374 --> 00:25:13,834
Pavilion tonight.

313
00:25:13,970 --> 00:25:15,847
We already know that.

314
00:25:15,993 --> 00:25:18,621
Elder is truly brilliant

315
00:25:19,194 --> 00:25:21,269
But what about the rest of
the poem?

316
00:25:21,446 --> 00:25:23,710
What do those 2 stanzas mean
- 3 stanzas.

317
00:25:23,814 --> 00:25:25,347
The meaning doesn't matter
now.

318
00:25:25,493 --> 00:25:27,432
Interpret it in any way you
desire.

319
00:25:27,537 --> 00:25:29,487
He means that we should have
our own views...

320
00:25:29,591 --> 00:25:31,740
not just listen to what
other people say, right?

321
00:25:31,855 --> 00:25:33,930
So, should we still listen
to what Elder says?

322
00:25:34,013 --> 00:25:36,026
Not only listen, but take
notes and ponder his meaning

323
00:25:36,172 --> 00:25:38,528
We must pass his wisdom on
to future generations.

324
00:25:38,644 --> 00:25:39,645
Right

325
00:25:39,822 --> 00:25:41,208
Time to leave

326
00:25:41,354 --> 00:25:42,491
Good-bye.

327
00:25:42,605 --> 00:25:44,264
We're off to 10 Mile
Pavilion.

328
00:25:44,420 --> 00:25:46,882
Yes. We're off to 10 Mile
Pavilion.

329
00:25:46,996 --> 00:25:51,188
Miss Windy, please return
Sian's painting to me.

330
00:25:51,376 --> 00:25:53,629
Yes, Elder.

331
00:25:55,026 --> 00:25:57,622
When you call me Sian, is
that a hint that I need

332
00:25:57,707 --> 00:25:58,958
a pseudonym?

333
00:25:59,062 --> 00:26:01,429
From now on, my name is Sian

334
00:26:07,415 --> 00:26:10,930
If Sian were reincarnated,
she would now be a babe

335
00:26:11,076 --> 00:26:12,734
in arms.

336
00:26:17,228 --> 00:26:19,522
She's not Sian

337
00:26:40,995 --> 00:26:43,664
Who are you spying on?

338
00:26:43,810 --> 00:26:46,031
Me?...

339
00:26:47,158 --> 00:26:48,993
No.

340
00:26:56,929 --> 00:26:59,818
Who are you spying on?

341
00:27:00,589 --> 00:27:04,437
I wanted to see who you
were spying on. Time to go

342
00:27:04,625 --> 00:27:07,253
Do you think your fiancé,
Prince Ma...

343
00:27:07,368 --> 00:27:09,391
is as handsome as Elder?

344
00:27:09,526 --> 00:27:12,196
We were betrothed before
birth. How do I know what

345
00:27:12,311 --> 00:27:13,865
he looks like?

346
00:27:13,980 --> 00:27:16,347
Is that what people mean
by fate?

347
00:27:16,451 --> 00:27:18,630
Who are you referring to?

348
00:27:18,787 --> 00:27:22,499
Oh, nobody. It's just that I
feel so fortunate.

349
00:27:22,645 --> 00:27:25,764
Fortunate? You’re e frothing
at the mouth

350
00:27:52,262 --> 00:27:54,170
Evil spirits

351
00:28:00,709 --> 00:28:03,900
Is this a foot print or a
hand print?

352
00:28:04,088 --> 00:28:06,663
We'll know when we find the
monster.

353
00:28:06,736 --> 00:28:07,947
Right

354
00:28:12,305 --> 00:28:14,735
It even harmed a man.

355
00:28:14,871 --> 00:28:18,354
What a pity to leave it here
Better show it to Elder.

356
00:28:18,458 --> 00:28:21,722
OK There really are ghosts
in this place

357
00:28:21,869 --> 00:28:23,151
What is that?

358
00:28:23,266 --> 00:28:25,622
A corpse It's all that
ghost's fault.

359
00:28:25,768 --> 00:28:28,438
Don't hug it. Put it down.

360
00:28:28,928 --> 00:28:30,910
How did this person die so
pitifully?

361
00:28:31,056 --> 00:28:34,663
I'd say this an evil ghost.
The odor is very strong.

362
00:28:34,810 --> 00:28:35,957
It's back

363
00:28:36,061 --> 00:28:37,834
Is it looking for us?

364
00:28:37,949 --> 00:28:40,576
Use your "freeze" magic.
- Right

365
00:28:40,733 --> 00:28:43,121
I command you to freeze

366
00:28:45,770 --> 00:28:48,961
Heebie-jeebie Freeze

367
00:28:50,296 --> 00:28:52,246
That'll stop him

368
00:28:53,674 --> 00:28:55,583
How do you do it?

369
00:28:55,687 --> 00:28:57,836
When you see a ghost, shout
"freeze".

370
00:28:57,992 --> 00:29:01,808
Like this? Freeze! Is that
right?

371
00:29:04,708 --> 00:29:09,151
Oh, no. How do you lift the
spell?

372
00:29:14,719 --> 00:29:17,264
I have to think of a way to
communicate with him.

373
00:29:17,368 --> 00:29:18,995
What can I do? Let's try
this...

374
00:29:19,141 --> 00:29:22,207
If I'm right, move your eyes
up and down.

375
00:29:22,384 --> 00:29:24,292
That's right. Fantastic

376
00:29:24,428 --> 00:29:27,171
If I'm wrong, move them from
left to right.

377
00:29:27,285 --> 00:29:28,714
Great

378
00:29:28,818 --> 00:29:32,083
Will a hand gesture lift
the spell?

379
00:29:42,771 --> 00:29:46,036
What? Not up and down or
left to right.

380
00:29:46,150 --> 00:29:48,194
Don't joke with me.

381
00:29:48,340 --> 00:29:51,489
If we wait too long, that
monster will get us.

382
00:29:51,677 --> 00:29:54,555
Does lifting the spell have
to do with an...

383
00:29:54,701 --> 00:29:56,130
acupuncture point?

384
00:29:56,339 --> 00:30:00,020
Your eyes are moving faster
than a revolving lantern

385
00:30:00,135 --> 00:30:02,387
I understand You're
provoking me into

386
00:30:02,533 --> 00:30:04,160
hitting you.

387
00:30:04,275 --> 00:30:07,226
OK. I'm going to hit you now

388
00:30:07,612 --> 00:30:10,386
Ready or not, here it comes

389
00:30:20,626 --> 00:30:23,130
Let's get out of here

390
00:30:26,404 --> 00:30:28,104
Come on

391
00:30:30,679 --> 00:30:33,182
You're too heavy.

392
00:30:36,769 --> 00:30:39,345
I can't carry you.

393
00:30:39,866 --> 00:30:41,598
Drag it

394
00:30:44,424 --> 00:30:46,447
Dragging you isn't fast
enough either.

395
00:30:46,583 --> 00:30:48,658
Better hide upstairs.

396
00:30:58,836 --> 00:31:02,997
I told you not to fool
around at a time like this.

397
00:31:03,258 --> 00:31:06,553
That monster is so tall,
it'll see us if we stand

398
00:31:06,699 --> 00:31:08,607
up straight.

399
00:31:10,975 --> 00:31:13,644
How can I undo the spell?

400
00:31:17,034 --> 00:31:18,837
How do I lift the spell?

401
00:31:18,984 --> 00:31:21,653
It's safer inside. Better
hide yourself quick.

402
00:31:34,324 --> 00:31:36,232
I told you to hide inside.

403
00:31:36,378 --> 00:31:40,164
Why did you go down there,
where it's so dangerous?

404
00:32:18,269 --> 00:32:20,386
Try the "freeze" curse

405
00:32:21,439 --> 00:32:22,826
Freeze

406
00:32:32,639 --> 00:32:35,632
Let's continue without
guessing game.

407
00:32:37,103 --> 00:32:39,772
You're getting heavier and
heavier. Can't carry you

408
00:32:39,918 --> 00:32:41,274
much longer.

409
00:32:41,378 --> 00:32:43,005
Since that monster isn't
here...

410
00:32:43,151 --> 00:32:46,072
let's try to lift the spell.

411
00:32:47,541 --> 00:32:50,868
Does it have anything to do
with this amulet?

412
00:32:50,951 --> 00:32:53,236
Yes? What then?

413
00:32:55,123 --> 00:32:58,762
Point at me. Point at me and
the curse will be lifted.

414
00:32:58,877 --> 00:33:00,952
Point

415
00:33:01,391 --> 00:33:04,060
How do I undo the spell?

416
00:33:08,586 --> 00:33:12,340
No good asking you I must
figure it out for myself.

417
00:33:27,033 --> 00:33:29,015
Freeze

418
00:33:34,719 --> 00:33:38,056
Don't move... Move Move

419
00:33:39,694 --> 00:33:41,769
Don't move

420
00:33:43,594 --> 00:33:45,607
Why does he "unfreeze" so
quickly,

421
00:33:45,711 --> 00:33:49,016
but you haven't moved for
so long?

422
00:33:49,122 --> 00:33:52,250
Do you mean... I pointed to
this amulet...

423
00:33:52,573 --> 00:33:56,359
Then I asked you how to lift
the spell...

424
00:33:56,609 --> 00:33:59,758
And he moved Freeze

425
00:35:07,834 --> 00:35:10,858
I'll take care of it.
Get out of here fast

426
00:35:11,036 --> 00:35:13,362
Finally lifted the spell

427
00:35:13,956 --> 00:35:15,552
Get out of here

428
00:35:15,593 --> 00:35:18,189
Abracadabra Open up a
way out

429
00:35:20,672 --> 00:35:24,280
Abracadabra Open up a
way out

430
00:35:26,866 --> 00:35:29,963
Out of the way I'll take
care of it

431
00:35:38,317 --> 00:35:40,673
Abracadabra

432
00:35:44,855 --> 00:35:47,358
Hocus pocus

433
00:36:07,860 --> 00:36:11,082
I order all ghosts to be
expelled

434
00:36:23,137 --> 00:36:26,569
Wow It doesn't fear my
incantations

435
00:36:30,855 --> 00:36:32,586
Take this

436
00:36:37,883 --> 00:36:40,209
It's still moving

437
00:36:40,532 --> 00:36:43,557
I order all ghosts to be
expelled

438
00:36:48,051 --> 00:36:50,335
Hocus pocus

439
00:36:58,938 --> 00:37:01,858
Even when it's chopped up he
can still run away

440
00:37:01,962 --> 00:37:03,808
It could still come back at
any time.

441
00:37:03,913 --> 00:37:05,988
Elder, get out of here.
I'll pursue it

442
00:37:06,175 --> 00:37:08,772
Be careful
- Earth, open up

443
00:38:11,833 --> 00:38:13,908
Hey Stop Stop

444
00:38:14,377 --> 00:38:16,911
Are you stupid? I told you
to stop

445
00:38:16,984 --> 00:38:20,352
We don't even know each
other. Why are we fighting?

446
00:38:20,499 --> 00:38:22,271
I learned magic to deal with
evil spirits.

447
00:38:22,375 --> 00:38:26,547
If you don't stop, I'll use
my magic to "freeze" you.

448
00:38:26,662 --> 00:38:28,768
Why are you blocking my way?

449
00:38:28,956 --> 00:38:31,135
I was just taking a rest
after battling some ghosts,

450
00:38:31,250 --> 00:38:32,877
and you say I'm blocking
your way.

451
00:38:33,023 --> 00:38:35,098
When that monster makes a
run for it tonight, you'll

452
00:38:35,254 --> 00:38:36,642
be in deep trouble.

453
00:38:36,819 --> 00:38:38,279
Brother
- Call me Master.

454
00:38:38,415 --> 00:38:40,041
Master, your skill is
extraordinary.

455
00:38:40,198 --> 00:38:42,555
If you worked for the
imperial court, your future

456
00:38:42,670 --> 00:38:44,223
would be boundless.

457
00:38:44,338 --> 00:38:46,204
You know that I'm a
Taoist monk.

458
00:38:46,319 --> 00:38:48,541
Seeking wealth and position
is for the likes of you

459
00:38:48,614 --> 00:38:49,823
mere mortals.

460
00:38:49,969 --> 00:38:52,785
I don't want to end up like
you... Earth, open up

461
00:38:56,059 --> 00:38:57,551
What a pity.

462
00:38:57,728 --> 00:39:01,096
Hu, our horses' hoofs are
rigid. They won't move

463
00:39:06,289 --> 00:39:08,616
It must be that monk's
magic at work

464
00:39:08,730 --> 00:39:11,264
He said there are evil
spirits. Be careful

465
00:39:11,410 --> 00:39:12,870
Yes

466
00:39:25,186 --> 00:39:27,094
Lord Fu

467
00:39:27,448 --> 00:39:29,556
There's nothing I can do
about squabbles in the

468
00:39:29,712 --> 00:39:31,234
imperial court.

469
00:39:31,349 --> 00:39:33,977
It's hard to tell right from
wrong.

470
00:39:34,269 --> 00:39:36,177
I'm just following orders.

471
00:39:36,323 --> 00:39:38,680
But don't worry.

472
00:39:38,826 --> 00:39:41,944
I'll make sure your journey
is safe.

473
00:39:42,059 --> 00:39:43,790
After we get to the capital,

474
00:39:43,936 --> 00:39:48,702
whatever the emperor does to
you is not my responsibility

475
00:39:52,018 --> 00:39:53,436
Let's go

476
00:40:04,647 --> 00:40:07,974
Where can I get something
to eat?

477
00:40:12,051 --> 00:40:14,794
Please give me a bowl of
your cheapest food.

478
00:40:14,940 --> 00:40:16,609
What? The cheapest?

479
00:40:16,754 --> 00:40:20,362
Sit down If you're starving
don't waste your money.

480
00:40:21,520 --> 00:40:23,700
Show me your face.

481
00:40:23,814 --> 00:40:25,243
Go

482
00:40:25,378 --> 00:40:27,151
Stand up.

483
00:40:27,579 --> 00:40:29,832
Don't lower your head.

484
00:40:30,394 --> 00:40:31,782
Go

485
00:40:35,233 --> 00:40:38,080
Don't run away
- Don't move

486
00:40:44,139 --> 00:40:45,975
Monks?

487
00:40:46,747 --> 00:40:49,072
Don't move

488
00:40:49,290 --> 00:40:51,501
Stand still

489
00:41:01,189 --> 00:41:02,921
Out of the way

490
00:41:03,067 --> 00:41:05,246
Get out of the way

491
00:41:22,348 --> 00:41:24,977
What kind of magic is this?

492
00:41:47,533 --> 00:41:49,651
It's Windy...

493
00:41:52,299 --> 00:41:53,999
Wait

494
00:41:54,948 --> 00:41:57,023
Come back

495
00:41:57,179 --> 00:41:58,702
Hey

496
00:41:59,057 --> 00:42:01,267
The soldiers never came to
10 Mile Pavilion last night.

497
00:42:01,382 --> 00:42:04,448
Rush back to Righteous Villa
and lie in ambush for them.

498
00:42:04,583 --> 00:42:06,012
Hey

499
00:42:07,232 --> 00:42:10,111
Back to Righteous Villa?
It's haunted

500
00:42:10,883 --> 00:42:12,540
Come back

501
00:42:19,621 --> 00:42:22,155
Elder Elder

502
00:42:23,970 --> 00:42:25,879
I wonder if Elder has
already gone?

503
00:42:25,983 --> 00:42:28,381
Better search for him.
- Yes

504
00:42:30,404 --> 00:42:32,479
Do you think father's
transport has already

505
00:42:32,531 --> 00:42:33,981
passed by here?

506
00:42:34,127 --> 00:42:37,151
No. They're not supposed to
reach here until after dark.

507
00:42:37,256 --> 00:42:39,622
Miss Windy, the villa has
been ransacked.

508
00:42:39,728 --> 00:42:41,782
I'm sure Elder did it to
remove any traces of

509
00:42:41,917 --> 00:42:43,064
our presence.

510
00:42:43,210 --> 00:42:45,223
Set everything up. Prepare
to attack. - Yes

511
00:42:45,400 --> 00:42:47,454
Hurry up Over there

512
00:43:36,343 --> 00:43:38,001
Who is it?

513
00:43:39,440 --> 00:43:41,766
I'm Ning.
- Ning?

514
00:43:43,789 --> 00:43:45,665
Oh, it's Elder

515
00:43:45,844 --> 00:43:47,574
This villa is haunted.

516
00:43:47,720 --> 00:43:48,857
Haunted?

517
00:43:49,014 --> 00:43:50,598
Where is Miss Windy?

518
00:43:50,745 --> 00:43:52,069
Inside.

519
00:43:52,215 --> 00:43:53,310
Ghosts?

520
00:43:53,466 --> 00:43:55,156
Real ghosts?

521
00:44:17,441 --> 00:44:19,767
Miss Windy

522
00:44:19,913 --> 00:44:21,853
My clothes

523
00:44:23,427 --> 00:44:26,024
Miss Windy

524
00:44:26,586 --> 00:44:28,610
Miss Windy

525
00:44:33,480 --> 00:44:36,254
Elder, they said you came.

526
00:44:36,849 --> 00:44:38,402
Miss Moon

527
00:44:38,558 --> 00:44:40,633
Who are you?

528
00:44:45,901 --> 00:44:48,894
Oh, it's Elder. I recognize
your back.

529
00:44:48,998 --> 00:44:50,802
Elder...

530
00:44:51,886 --> 00:44:53,419
I...

531
00:44:59,124 --> 00:45:02,002
With your beard shaved off,
you're so, so...

532
00:45:02,116 --> 00:45:04,098
Yes.

533
00:45:04,275 --> 00:45:08,238
When my sister sees you,
she'll be so happy for me.

534
00:45:08,311 --> 00:45:09,551
Happy?

535
00:45:09,666 --> 00:45:12,242
When you came in, did you
see my sister?

536
00:45:12,346 --> 00:45:14,078
Your sister? No. No

537
00:45:14,224 --> 00:45:17,560
Sister Sister Sister

538
00:45:21,357 --> 00:45:23,411
What are you grinning about?

539
00:45:23,546 --> 00:45:25,694
It is improper to look.

540
00:45:29,043 --> 00:45:31,753
There are some things you
shouldn't look at.

541
00:45:31,900 --> 00:45:33,256
You're all right

542
00:45:33,360 --> 00:45:35,758
I didn't recognize Elder
with his beard shaved off.

543
00:45:35,863 --> 00:45:38,126
Really? I must see for
myself.

544
00:45:38,407 --> 00:45:40,763
Elder, if you have something
to say, just say it.

545
00:45:40,910 --> 00:45:43,027
It scares me when you hint
at things.

546
00:45:43,110 --> 00:45:44,455
I'm cold.

547
00:45:44,601 --> 00:45:47,448
Your face is so hot, how
can you be cold?

548
00:45:47,625 --> 00:45:49,471
Wouldn't this be faster?

549
00:45:49,576 --> 00:45:51,975
Not fast enough. Faster
would be better.

550
00:45:52,079 --> 00:45:53,883
Faster?... OK.

551
00:46:00,255 --> 00:46:01,955
Elder...

552
00:46:04,540 --> 00:46:07,283
Elder said he was cold.

553
00:46:07,565 --> 00:46:09,546
Cold?

554
00:46:09,964 --> 00:46:13,519
Elder, you're overly
exerting yourself.

555
00:46:22,144 --> 00:46:24,960
Have you seen Miss Windy?

556
00:46:25,074 --> 00:46:27,848
No, I'm looking for her, too

557
00:46:27,953 --> 00:46:30,320
Where did she go?

558
00:46:32,061 --> 00:46:33,521
There's noise coming from
upstairs.

559
00:46:33,667 --> 00:46:35,648
Let's go up for a look.

560
00:46:52,771 --> 00:46:54,503
Don't go up there.

561
00:46:57,881 --> 00:47:00,457
Strange Nobody up here.

562
00:47:03,450 --> 00:47:07,194
Maybe it's next door. Let's
go over and look.

563
00:47:19,104 --> 00:47:21,127
What are you doing?

564
00:47:21,231 --> 00:47:24,182
Sister, Elder came back to
find me... us.

565
00:47:24,359 --> 00:47:27,457
Why are your clothes so
disheveled?

566
00:47:28,051 --> 00:47:31,763
Don't be so impolite in
the future.

567
00:47:35,570 --> 00:47:38,198
Miss Windy, this villa is
haunted.

568
00:47:38,313 --> 00:47:40,909
Do we still have to pretend
to be ghosts?

569
00:47:41,066 --> 00:47:43,839
No matter what, we must wait
here for father.

570
00:47:43,986 --> 00:47:45,862
We mustn't leave.

571
00:47:46,113 --> 00:47:47,604
In this moment of danger,

572
00:47:47,781 --> 00:47:50,034
we must thrust out our
chests and be fearless.

573
00:47:50,180 --> 00:47:53,246
We must be utterly devoted
to our cause.

574
00:47:54,112 --> 00:47:56,614
Elder, let's go in.

575
00:47:59,503 --> 00:48:03,435
Elder - Your clothes are
torn in the back.

576
00:48:23,999 --> 00:48:27,639
How do you write the
"freeze" incantation?

577
00:48:32,530 --> 00:48:37,087
I didn't spy on him. I didn't
even know he was outside.

578
00:48:37,223 --> 00:48:41,331
Better tie your heart down.
Otherwise, it might fly away

579
00:48:41,467 --> 00:48:44,178
If I could tie it down,
I would

580
00:48:58,142 --> 00:49:01,614
This is how you do it...

581
00:49:05,483 --> 00:49:07,246
Freeze

582
00:49:10,104 --> 00:49:11,980
It works

583
00:49:16,996 --> 00:49:18,425
This is the "freeze"
incantation.

584
00:49:18,561 --> 00:49:20,927
If you see that monster, do
this and he'll freeze in

585
00:49:21,063 --> 00:49:22,346
his tracks.
- Like this?

586
00:49:22,461 --> 00:49:25,339
Don't do it haphazardly. This
spell is hard to reverse.

587
00:49:25,485 --> 00:49:26,872
Give me your hand.
- Yes

588
00:49:39,230 --> 00:49:41,941
Sister, what's that sound?

589
00:49:50,607 --> 00:49:53,527
It's coming from up there.

590
00:49:54,330 --> 00:49:56,176
Windy

591
00:49:56,384 --> 00:49:58,439
Windy, give me your hand.

592
00:49:58,574 --> 00:50:00,764
Elder, shouldn't you be
calling me Sian?

593
00:50:00,837 --> 00:50:02,985
Whether I call you Sian or
Windy, there's no need

594
00:50:03,100 --> 00:50:04,341
to be bashful.

595
00:50:04,456 --> 00:50:06,437
I'll never reveal what
happened just now.

596
00:50:06,583 --> 00:50:08,388
I was really anxious on
your behalf.

597
00:50:08,533 --> 00:50:10,744
Actually, I kissed you
because I couldn't

598
00:50:10,827 --> 00:50:12,184
control myself.

599
00:50:12,319 --> 00:50:14,342
Fortunately you made a
quick get-away.

600
00:50:14,446 --> 00:50:17,074
Otherwise, if Moon had seen
you undressed and with me...

601
00:50:17,189 --> 00:50:20,349
it would be hard to explain,
even if I were Elder Chu.

602
00:50:20,495 --> 00:50:21,996
Give me your hand.

603
00:50:22,131 --> 00:50:23,759
Moon?

604
00:50:24,155 --> 00:50:26,554
Moon, what are you doing
here?

605
00:50:26,731 --> 00:50:28,493
I was looking for you.

606
00:50:28,639 --> 00:50:30,516
Don't bother explaining.

607
00:50:30,621 --> 00:50:31,726
Moon

608
00:50:31,882 --> 00:50:34,062
No, Windy Give me your hand

609
00:50:34,177 --> 00:50:36,804
We're not fated for each
other. I'm betrothed to

610
00:50:36,919 --> 00:50:38,515
Lord Ma's son.

611
00:50:38,630 --> 00:50:40,163
You're betrothed?

612
00:50:40,267 --> 00:50:41,956
We weren't meant for each
other.

613
00:50:42,039 --> 00:50:44,886
You should be looking for
Moon, not me.

614
00:50:45,063 --> 00:50:48,578
Windy, one at a time. I'm
after both of you.

615
00:50:57,734 --> 00:51:01,029
Miss Moon, it's getting dark
Give me your hand.

616
00:51:01,176 --> 00:51:03,231
Go to my sister instead.

617
00:51:03,408 --> 00:51:06,108
I'll go to her next. Quick,
give me your hand.

618
00:51:06,224 --> 00:51:08,027
Elder, aren't you the
playboy

619
00:51:08,173 --> 00:51:09,904
You can only choose one of
us.

620
00:51:10,081 --> 00:51:12,720
I'm not going to compete
with my sister.

621
00:51:12,866 --> 00:51:15,536
No need to compete. When I
finish with you I'll go

622
00:51:15,650 --> 00:51:17,350
to her.

623
00:51:35,068 --> 00:51:39,406
Elder, there is something
I must tell you.

624
00:51:39,907 --> 00:51:43,160
Actually, love is a strange
thing.

625
00:51:43,317 --> 00:51:47,343
My heart beats wildly when
I look at you.

626
00:51:50,513 --> 00:51:55,069
I don't even have the
courage to glance at you.

627
00:51:56,018 --> 00:52:00,085
I'm afraid that my heart
would jump right out.

628
00:52:03,736 --> 00:52:06,729
I'd be willing to die if
that's what you wanted.

629
00:52:06,874 --> 00:52:10,379
As long as I can be with you
for ever & never part.

630
00:52:13,757 --> 00:52:15,113
Help

631
00:52:15,259 --> 00:52:16,469
What's that?

632
00:52:16,615 --> 00:52:19,316
Hurry up That monster is
back.

633
00:52:20,723 --> 00:52:22,486
Elder, what happened?

634
00:52:22,601 --> 00:52:24,582
Go inside and search.
- Yes

635
00:52:25,385 --> 00:52:27,669
Inside there's a huge
creature.

636
00:52:27,783 --> 00:52:30,485
I don't know what it is.

637
00:52:38,608 --> 00:52:40,933
Be calm Use the "freeze"
incantation.

638
00:52:41,079 --> 00:52:43,217
Together: Freeze

639
00:52:45,949 --> 00:52:48,129
It really works

640
00:52:48,275 --> 00:52:50,299
It sure does

641
00:52:56,316 --> 00:52:59,382
We froze it in its tracks.

642
00:53:06,338 --> 00:53:08,934
Everybody, jump up there

643
00:53:11,552 --> 00:53:13,356
I...

644
00:53:23,523 --> 00:53:25,994
The archery machine

645
00:53:39,635 --> 00:53:41,856
Be careful
- Elder

646
00:53:59,543 --> 00:54:03,579
Moon, go and rescue Elder.
I'll lure away that monster.

647
00:54:09,492 --> 00:54:11,326
Put out the net.
- Yes

648
00:54:14,225 --> 00:54:15,811
Your hand...

649
00:54:30,368 --> 00:54:32,945
Let's retreat from here.

650
00:54:38,410 --> 00:54:41,528
See what's going on up ahead
- Yes

651
00:54:43,352 --> 00:54:44,771
Soldiers

652
00:54:44,875 --> 00:54:47,722
Hu, they've set up an ambush

653
00:54:48,775 --> 00:54:50,328
Windy, Moon?

654
00:54:50,486 --> 00:54:51,726
It's father

655
00:54:51,872 --> 00:54:53,645
Lure the soldiers into the
villa.

656
00:54:53,791 --> 00:54:57,190
Use the archery machine to
mow them down - Yes

657
00:54:59,182 --> 00:55:01,330
Trying to get away?

658
00:55:02,489 --> 00:55:04,814
The monster destroyed the
archery machine

659
00:55:04,918 --> 00:55:07,420
We're surrounded by our toes

660
00:55:07,567 --> 00:55:08,881
Let me out

661
00:55:09,027 --> 00:55:10,904
Right... Let Elder go

662
00:55:11,290 --> 00:55:12,948
Elder, what should we do now

663
00:55:13,063 --> 00:55:14,617
We'll stay on the sidelines.

664
00:55:14,731 --> 00:55:18,339
When the enemy comes in, the
monster will deal with them.

665
00:55:25,378 --> 00:55:28,612
Obviously a fake ghost.
Unmask it.

666
00:55:33,701 --> 00:55:35,713
Let's rescue father
- Yes

667
00:55:45,005 --> 00:55:47,257
You're hopelessly
outnumbered.

668
00:55:56,737 --> 00:55:58,781
I'll save you

669
00:56:00,700 --> 00:56:03,995
Swords are too dangerous
Let's use our fists.

670
00:56:19,178 --> 00:56:21,682
I told you that swords are
too dangerous

671
00:56:43,675 --> 00:56:45,301
Father

672
00:56:45,479 --> 00:56:47,846
Get out of here. Don't worry
about me

673
00:56:47,888 --> 00:56:49,797
Get over here fast.

674
00:56:51,089 --> 00:56:54,176
Don't worry about me
Rescue father

675
00:57:00,100 --> 00:57:02,248
The monster is here

676
00:57:02,425 --> 00:57:05,168
Abracadabra Hocus pocus

677
00:57:07,754 --> 00:57:10,527
Abracadabra Hocus pocus

678
00:57:13,322 --> 00:57:14,846
Windy Windy

679
00:57:15,023 --> 00:57:16,723
Possessed by evil spirits?

680
00:57:16,900 --> 00:57:18,047
Sister

681
00:57:18,151 --> 00:57:19,653
What happened to Windy?

682
00:57:19,789 --> 00:57:21,321
She's been possessed by
evil spirits.

683
00:57:21,425 --> 00:57:22,636
What should we do?

684
00:57:22,782 --> 00:57:25,847
Still a lot of soldiers
around. Better get inside.

685
00:57:28,350 --> 00:57:29,977
Don't move

686
00:57:30,165 --> 00:57:31,927
Press down on her

687
00:57:32,073 --> 00:57:33,178
Sister

688
00:57:33,293 --> 00:57:35,347
Think of a way to save
my sister.

689
00:57:35,451 --> 00:57:37,141
She's possessed by them

690
00:57:37,256 --> 00:57:39,686
She could turn into a giant
monster at any moment.

691
00:57:39,801 --> 00:57:41,333
It's your fault, you traitor

692
00:57:41,437 --> 00:57:42,960
I'll kill you

693
00:57:43,065 --> 00:57:44,838
Wait His troops are still
out there.

694
00:57:44,952 --> 00:57:47,100
We must keep him as a
hostage.

695
00:57:48,946 --> 00:57:51,386
She's turning into a corpse
monster

696
00:57:51,731 --> 00:57:53,055
Sister

697
00:57:53,190 --> 00:57:54,651
We must kill her immediately

698
00:57:54,765 --> 00:57:56,747
Otherwise she'll turn into
a monster.

699
00:57:56,851 --> 00:57:58,581
You can't kill her

700
00:57:58,728 --> 00:58:00,261
Are you a good person or
evil?

701
00:58:00,323 --> 00:58:02,544
You won't kill Hu, but
you'll kill my sister.

702
00:58:02,660 --> 00:58:03,942
Kill Hu

703
00:58:04,088 --> 00:58:06,372
No matter how many you kill
here, you still won't save

704
00:58:06,518 --> 00:58:07,665
the kingdom.

705
00:58:07,738 --> 00:58:10,137
The emperor is surrounded by
sycophants and has no idea

706
00:58:10,241 --> 00:58:12,014
of the suffering of his
people.

707
00:58:12,191 --> 00:58:14,339
Take my head to the emperor.
Maybe it will move him.

708
00:58:14,422 --> 00:58:16,676
He'll be convinced of our
sincerity and loyalty.

709
00:58:16,821 --> 00:58:18,834
Father, if you die we'll
have no one to lead us.

710
00:58:18,907 --> 00:58:20,262
Take my head instead.

711
00:58:20,439 --> 00:58:22,390
No. Take our heads.

712
00:58:22,494 --> 00:58:25,487
Bastards. What good is it to
cut off your heads?

713
00:58:25,591 --> 00:58:27,427
Who are you, ordering people
about?

714
00:58:27,572 --> 00:58:29,899
I am the learned and
brilliant Elder Chu

715
00:58:30,044 --> 00:58:32,860
The learned and brilliant
Elder Chu.

716
00:58:37,803 --> 00:58:40,024
Please guide us.

717
00:58:40,243 --> 00:58:42,423
None of you are permitted
to die.

718
00:58:42,506 --> 00:58:43,675
Please explain

719
00:58:43,821 --> 00:58:44,926
Explain?

720
00:58:44,968 --> 00:58:46,991
Your severed heads will mean
nothing to the emperor.

721
00:58:47,126 --> 00:58:49,107
You'll have died in vain.
Need I explain more?

722
00:58:49,180 --> 00:58:50,714
Stupid pigs

723
00:58:50,849 --> 00:58:52,799
What about her?

724
00:59:05,887 --> 00:59:09,599
To exorcise her, she needs
a dose of "yang" energy.

725
00:59:09,672 --> 00:59:11,445
I am not powerful enough.

726
00:59:11,559 --> 00:59:14,094
We better do something soon
or it will be too late.

727
00:59:14,240 --> 00:59:15,480
What can we do?

728
00:59:15,626 --> 00:59:17,848
Try this magic charm. It may
or may not work.

729
00:59:17,963 --> 00:59:20,632
Hurry up and pull Miss Windy
down. - OK.

730
00:59:33,929 --> 00:59:37,224
I order the evil spirits to
be exercised.

731
00:59:50,697 --> 00:59:52,230
How did this happen?

732
00:59:52,303 --> 00:59:54,243
Really ugly

733
00:59:56,204 --> 00:59:57,997
I've forced the evil spirit
from her.

734
00:59:58,112 --> 01:00:00,364
If she gets a quick dose of
"yang" energy, there will be

735
01:00:00,479 --> 01:00:01,898
a gleam of hope. Hurry up.

736
01:00:02,044 --> 01:00:03,118
Hurry

737
01:00:03,264 --> 01:00:05,245
I'm a monk. I must not get
too close to women.

738
01:00:05,422 --> 01:00:07,226
Don't be afraid of her
ugliness.

739
01:00:07,299 --> 01:00:09,208
How do we give her "yang"
energy?

740
01:00:09,312 --> 01:00:11,502
With your mouth, of course.
- Mouth?

741
01:00:11,575 --> 01:00:13,379
What then? Your ears?

742
01:00:13,494 --> 01:00:15,152
Send me to her.

743
01:00:15,267 --> 01:00:17,592
Abracadabra Hocus pocus

744
01:01:12,091 --> 01:01:13,551
Sister

745
01:01:21,310 --> 01:01:23,010
A real man is afraid of
nothing.

746
01:01:23,124 --> 01:01:24,918
It's you

747
01:01:49,247 --> 01:01:54,045
Lord, a golden-robed priest
is on his way here.

748
01:01:54,607 --> 01:01:57,079
A golden-robed priest?

749
01:02:12,013 --> 01:02:13,670
Lord

750
01:02:14,515 --> 01:02:17,143
Put your swords down

751
01:02:19,146 --> 01:02:22,024
Not enough. More

752
01:02:24,537 --> 01:02:26,612
Lower your swords

753
01:02:26,758 --> 01:02:29,678
Put all your swords down

754
01:02:32,848 --> 01:02:36,602
There are evildoers behind
every country's downfall.

755
01:02:36,717 --> 01:02:40,357
Take my head and collect
your reward.

756
01:02:47,323 --> 01:02:50,316
The way that you look death
calmly in the face,

757
01:02:50,420 --> 01:02:53,236
proves that you are loyal to
our country.

758
01:02:53,798 --> 01:02:56,229
Even though our political
views are different,

759
01:02:56,406 --> 01:02:59,180
I'm still willing to help
you.

760
01:02:59,743 --> 01:03:03,424
The golden-robed Taoist
outside is the High Priest.

761
01:03:03,643 --> 01:03:05,479
The High Priest?

762
01:03:05,593 --> 01:03:07,543
All the rites and rituals in
the palace...

763
01:03:07,679 --> 01:03:10,495
the emperor consults him
for guidance.

764
01:03:10,568 --> 01:03:14,155
If he speaks on your behalf,
justice will triumph.

765
01:03:14,499 --> 01:03:16,126
Father

766
01:03:17,596 --> 01:03:22,393
Lord Fu, if you trust me,
let me go to him.

767
01:03:23,165 --> 01:03:26,231
I'll explain the true
situation.

768
01:03:30,997 --> 01:03:33,250
Father, he might betray you

769
01:03:33,395 --> 01:03:37,077
He could have killed me had
he wanted to.

770
01:03:40,945 --> 01:03:43,646
Still not awake?

771
01:03:44,804 --> 01:03:47,099
Enough I'm going to puke.

772
01:03:48,746 --> 01:03:50,269
Elder

773
01:03:55,347 --> 01:03:57,266
Ning

774
01:04:24,651 --> 01:04:28,259
I am here to pay my respects
to the high priest.

775
01:04:28,374 --> 01:04:30,730
Lord Fu is not a traitor.

776
01:04:30,845 --> 01:04:33,515
He is a loyal subject,
a patriot.

777
01:04:33,630 --> 01:04:36,258
I hope that you will uphold
justice.

778
01:04:36,414 --> 01:04:39,855
There are many who cannot
tell between good and evil.

779
01:04:39,959 --> 01:04:42,285
They do not know the
hardships of the

780
01:04:42,504 --> 01:04:43,891
imperial court.

781
01:04:44,069 --> 01:04:46,811
The purpose of my journey
is to pacify the people.

782
01:04:46,957 --> 01:04:49,137
I'll intercede at court on
behalf of these

783
01:04:49,252 --> 01:04:51,160
loyal subjects.

784
01:04:51,306 --> 01:04:52,724
Amen Amen

785
01:04:52,901 --> 01:04:55,821
Thank you, High Priest

786
01:05:16,355 --> 01:05:18,993
How are you, Autumn?

787
01:05:22,445 --> 01:05:24,395
Women are very tempting.

788
01:05:24,531 --> 01:05:26,512
If I didn't exercise
self-control...

789
01:05:26,658 --> 01:05:29,578
my energy would have been
dissipated.

790
01:05:31,768 --> 01:05:34,062
Hu is treacherous and
disrupts the...

791
01:05:34,240 --> 01:05:36,086
High Priest's harmony.

792
01:05:36,263 --> 01:05:38,244
Please stay here.

793
01:06:01,562 --> 01:06:05,202
The convict Lord Fu is here
to see the High Priest.

794
01:06:05,348 --> 01:06:07,850
I pay my respects to the
High Priest.

795
01:06:07,964 --> 01:06:11,396
Amen Amen. You have a
murderous air about you.

796
01:06:11,511 --> 01:06:14,044
Put down your weapons.

797
01:06:14,847 --> 01:06:18,143
I've been framed, but I am
concerned about our nation.

798
01:06:18,300 --> 01:06:22,606
You're so merciful. Guide the
emperor to save the nation.

799
01:06:23,128 --> 01:06:26,319
Life is chaotic.

800
01:06:26,788 --> 01:06:30,041
Mistakes can always be
corrected.

801
01:07:08,397 --> 01:07:11,911
In my former life I was evil
so I must do good in

802
01:07:12,016 --> 01:07:14,164
this life.

803
01:07:17,835 --> 01:07:20,890
Release my soul from
purgatory.

804
01:07:21,589 --> 01:07:25,271
Release my soul from
purgatory.

805
01:07:37,805 --> 01:07:39,984
Evil chanting?

806
01:07:41,424 --> 01:07:43,822
Don't be tricked

807
01:07:43,895 --> 01:07:45,387
Sit down

808
01:07:46,503 --> 01:07:47,566
His mercy is false

809
01:07:47,754 --> 01:07:50,872
Don't be tricked by his
devilish voice

810
01:07:51,269 --> 01:07:53,448
Abracadabra Freeze

811
01:08:00,425 --> 01:08:03,522
I order the evil spirits to
be exercised

812
01:08:15,107 --> 01:08:19,550
I am the absolute Buddha.

813
01:08:21,334 --> 01:08:23,763
What kind of evil spirit
are you

814
01:08:23,909 --> 01:08:26,537
Even before Buddha you
refuse to reveal your

815
01:08:26,694 --> 01:08:28,226
true appearance

816
01:08:28,331 --> 01:08:30,719
The spirit of evil? I am
what I look like

817
01:08:30,865 --> 01:08:32,982
I don't believe you are
Buddha

818
01:08:33,054 --> 01:08:35,724
Let's go over and see if
you're real or false.

819
01:08:35,839 --> 01:08:37,539
Don't

820
01:08:46,007 --> 01:08:48,113
Abracadabra

821
01:08:48,614 --> 01:08:50,762
Hocus pocus

822
01:09:07,990 --> 01:09:09,272
Elder

823
01:09:09,388 --> 01:09:11,400
The bastard Hu betrayed us.

824
01:09:11,473 --> 01:09:13,830
I'll take care of things
here. Leave quickly

825
01:09:14,017 --> 01:09:17,522
Abracadabra Hocus pocus
The universe revolves.

826
01:09:23,204 --> 01:09:25,385
May Buddha be in your heart.

827
01:09:25,531 --> 01:09:29,117
I knew he was false, but
couldn't conquer him.

828
01:09:29,284 --> 01:09:31,203
I failed

829
01:09:32,736 --> 01:09:35,197
I can't perform my magic
with you here.

830
01:09:35,344 --> 01:09:38,368
I'll open a tunnel in the
earth for you. Hurry

831
01:09:44,844 --> 01:09:46,157
Autumn

832
01:09:46,335 --> 01:09:48,108
Hurry up

833
01:09:48,807 --> 01:09:51,100
I can't hold out.

834
01:09:51,246 --> 01:09:52,801
Hurry

835
01:09:52,988 --> 01:09:55,523
Abracadabra. Hurry

836
01:10:05,064 --> 01:10:06,650
Father

837
01:10:18,559 --> 01:10:22,167
They've escaped for now but
I'll get them in the end.

838
01:10:22,281 --> 01:10:24,054
Guard the three we've
captured

839
01:10:24,231 --> 01:10:25,931
Yes

840
01:10:33,106 --> 01:10:34,910
What about Lord Fu?

841
01:10:35,087 --> 01:10:37,518
They have admitted their
errors. They have departed.

842
01:10:37,632 --> 01:10:39,363
People should acknowledge
the immensity of

843
01:10:39,510 --> 01:10:40,542
the universe.

844
01:10:40,730 --> 01:10:42,805
I just heard a fight going
on.

845
01:10:42,992 --> 01:10:45,067
Your ears aren't clean

846
01:10:45,245 --> 01:10:49,353
Vacate your mind to attain
perfect peace of mind.

847
01:11:49,275 --> 01:11:51,454
I'm very cold.

848
01:12:25,430 --> 01:12:27,297
Sian

849
01:12:35,973 --> 01:12:39,164
Don't leave me

850
01:12:51,417 --> 01:12:53,368
Sian

851
01:12:59,114 --> 01:13:02,232
Don't be reincarnated
so soon.

852
01:13:02,482 --> 01:13:05,058
It's too hard to be mortal
now.

853
01:13:05,162 --> 01:13:07,529
You're so good to Sian.

854
01:13:07,707 --> 01:13:10,825
I never realized how much
you missed her

855
01:13:10,940 --> 01:13:15,392
I never realized how much
you missed her

856
01:14:17,472 --> 01:14:20,497
Frost fills the sky over
10 Mile Lake.

857
01:14:20,633 --> 01:14:23,824
Silken threads anxious of
youth.

858
01:14:24,981 --> 01:14:28,589
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely.

859
01:14:28,746 --> 01:14:32,907
Envious of lovers, not of
immortality.

860
01:14:45,755 --> 01:14:47,736
Sian

861
01:14:55,255 --> 01:14:57,278
Sian, what are you doing
here?

862
01:14:57,382 --> 01:14:59,436
Hide You can't let the sun
shine on you

863
01:14:59,572 --> 01:15:02,242
If the sun shines on you,
your soul will be scattered.

864
01:15:02,429 --> 01:15:04,933
You would never be
reincarnated

865
01:15:05,037 --> 01:15:07,362
Why don't you listen to me?
Sian

866
01:15:13,525 --> 01:15:15,747
Oh, it's you I'm sorry.

867
01:15:15,893 --> 01:15:18,917
Once again I've made a
mistake.

868
01:15:19,094 --> 01:15:21,837
I mistook you for she.

869
01:15:24,945 --> 01:15:27,896
So there really is someone
named Sian

870
01:15:28,042 --> 01:15:30,471
Is she the one in the
painting?

871
01:15:30,648 --> 01:15:33,152
Do you miss her very much?

872
01:15:33,287 --> 01:15:35,832
She's already dead and
buried.

873
01:15:35,967 --> 01:15:39,273
We'll never meet again.

874
01:15:40,983 --> 01:15:44,383
If you want, you can call me
Sian for now.

875
01:15:44,529 --> 01:15:46,709
For now?

876
01:15:49,367 --> 01:15:54,342
I understand. You’re e
betrothed to another.

877
01:15:55,312 --> 01:15:57,116
When I knew Sian,

878
01:15:57,262 --> 01:15:59,859
she was also betrothed to
somebody else.

879
01:16:00,015 --> 01:16:02,517
It's beyond my control.

880
01:16:03,498 --> 01:16:06,752
Sian said exactly the same
thing.

881
01:16:13,760 --> 01:16:17,232
You are mortal; she's a ghost

882
01:16:17,722 --> 01:16:21,268
But you're both exactly
the same.

883
01:16:23,635 --> 01:16:26,482
Are we very much alike?

884
01:16:26,597 --> 01:16:28,777
Too much so.

885
01:16:28,933 --> 01:16:31,738
You gave me false hope.

886
01:16:31,884 --> 01:16:36,056
Anyway, false hope is
better than none.

887
01:16:37,766 --> 01:16:39,601
Excuse me

888
01:16:41,322 --> 01:16:43,261
Here's your tea.

889
01:16:44,169 --> 01:16:46,463
Your meal will be served
presently.

890
01:16:46,609 --> 01:16:49,070
Please make yourselves at
home.

891
01:16:51,865 --> 01:16:54,983
I've seen that man before.
He's...

892
01:16:55,337 --> 01:16:59,404
The tea is poisoned This
inn is run by thieves

893
01:16:59,582 --> 01:17:00,896
Really

894
01:17:01,042 --> 01:17:02,846
Is the water boiling?
- Yes.

895
01:17:02,992 --> 01:17:04,764
The blade sharpened?
- Nice and sharp.

896
01:17:04,838 --> 01:17:06,194
Everything's ready.

897
01:17:06,298 --> 01:17:08,071
Put the man in the cauldron
immediately.

898
01:17:08,175 --> 01:17:11,553
Save the woman for tonight,
to warm our cold beds.

899
01:17:14,860 --> 01:17:16,517
Kill

900
01:17:16,705 --> 01:17:19,177
Slice them up good

901
01:17:19,312 --> 01:17:21,367
Right on

902
01:17:22,587 --> 01:17:24,840
Stop

903
01:17:29,199 --> 01:17:31,732
Watch where you're stabbing

904
01:17:34,142 --> 01:17:36,706
They escaped through the
window.

905
01:17:49,690 --> 01:17:53,059
It's dangerous here. This is
no way to escape

906
01:17:54,947 --> 01:17:58,064
Better jump into the tree
and hide.

907
01:17:58,387 --> 01:18:01,902
I still haven't recovered.
No energy to jump.

908
01:18:02,600 --> 01:18:04,540
Don't worry about me. Run

909
01:18:04,655 --> 01:18:07,648
No, I won't leave you.

910
01:18:09,733 --> 01:18:12,132
This time there's no escape

911
01:18:12,236 --> 01:18:14,530
I never thought we'd die
here.

912
01:18:14,635 --> 01:18:17,899
Elder, it's our fault for
getting you involved.

913
01:18:18,045 --> 01:18:19,744
I'm not Elder Chu.

914
01:18:19,891 --> 01:18:22,216
I'm just a poor scholar.

915
01:18:22,362 --> 01:18:24,021
No matter who you are...

916
01:18:24,135 --> 01:18:28,484
I feel fortunate to die with
the one I love.

917
01:18:31,445 --> 01:18:34,782
We'll never be parted again.

918
01:18:38,860 --> 01:18:43,053
We'll never be parted again.
Hold me

919
01:18:45,847 --> 01:18:51,582
Let me be on the outside so
that the wolf eats me first.

920
01:18:51,728 --> 01:18:54,690
You're wonderful.

921
01:18:56,223 --> 01:18:58,330
So are you.

922
01:18:58,486 --> 01:19:02,553
If we could be like this
for ever, it would be great.

923
01:19:35,017 --> 01:19:38,489
Orchid Monastery

924
01:19:39,199 --> 01:19:40,585
Orchid Monastery

925
01:19:40,690 --> 01:19:43,120
What's the Orchid Monastery?

926
01:19:46,155 --> 01:19:48,209
How could I have forgotten
about Yan?

927
01:19:48,344 --> 01:19:49,554
Who is he?

928
01:19:49,700 --> 01:19:51,431
The bearded man in the
Orchid Monastery.

929
01:19:51,577 --> 01:19:53,079
A wizard in the occult.

930
01:19:53,183 --> 01:19:56,551
If we find him, we can deal
with the High Priest.

931
01:20:06,646 --> 01:20:08,763
Isn't the High Priest
returning to the

932
01:20:08,877 --> 01:20:10,338
capital city?

933
01:20:10,473 --> 01:20:12,548
Why go to his palace?

934
01:20:12,705 --> 01:20:14,915
He needs a tranquil place
to meditate.

935
01:20:21,267 --> 01:20:23,769
Only holy people may enter
this sacred place.

936
01:20:23,873 --> 01:20:25,949
Stay where you are.

937
01:20:47,286 --> 01:20:50,695
This is the hour of the
eclipse.

938
01:20:53,376 --> 01:20:57,797
My body is changing against
my wish.

939
01:21:17,601 --> 01:21:22,158
Why are all the officials of
the imperial court here?

940
01:21:28,519 --> 01:21:31,856
Lord Chiang Lord Yang
Lord Lee

941
01:21:33,879 --> 01:21:36,476
I was escorting Lord Fu back
to the capital...

942
01:21:36,591 --> 01:21:40,554
But couldn't complete my
mission. Allow me to explain

943
01:21:42,514 --> 01:21:44,350
Lord Chiang

944
01:21:47,457 --> 01:21:49,532
A hollow shell?

945
01:21:49,678 --> 01:21:52,494
Lord Yang is a hollow shell,
too?

946
01:21:53,297 --> 01:21:55,893
What kind of a place is this
Are you demons?

947
01:21:56,008 --> 01:21:58,261
What did you do with the
flesh and blood of

948
01:21:58,418 --> 01:22:00,399
these officials?

949
01:22:04,017 --> 01:22:07,344
You demons, come out and
face me

950
01:22:11,630 --> 01:22:13,684
Why did you do with the
flesh and blood of

951
01:22:13,757 --> 01:22:14,967
these officials?

952
01:22:15,114 --> 01:22:17,231
What evil intentions do you
harbor?

953
01:22:17,376 --> 01:22:19,358
Are they all hollow shells?

954
01:22:19,431 --> 01:22:22,205
I'm going to destroy all of
you evil monks.

955
01:22:30,078 --> 01:22:33,238
Strange, where have they
hidden?

956
01:22:44,865 --> 01:22:48,087
Autumn? Moon? Lord Fu?

957
01:22:49,392 --> 01:22:51,018
Lord Fu

958
01:22:53,979 --> 01:22:56,649
What happened? Where are
the others?

959
01:22:56,795 --> 01:22:59,465
I was wrong to believe you
You've caused so much harm

960
01:22:59,580 --> 01:23:01,728
What other plots do you have
up your sleeve?

961
01:23:01,884 --> 01:23:03,824
We were tricked. The High
Priest is a demon

962
01:23:03,970 --> 01:23:05,951
He turned many officials
into walking corpses.

963
01:23:06,055 --> 01:23:07,412
We must report this to the
emperor.

964
01:23:07,485 --> 01:23:09,841
Otherwise, the kingdom will
be beyond redemption.

965
01:23:09,914 --> 01:23:12,062
Oh, he's the one who
instigated this calamity

966
01:23:12,178 --> 01:23:13,835
No wonder the court is in
upheaval.

967
01:23:13,919 --> 01:23:16,870
We must hurry to rescue the
others. We can talk later.

968
01:23:19,727 --> 01:23:21,532
Moon

969
01:23:28,810 --> 01:23:30,719
Autumn

970
01:23:30,834 --> 01:23:33,013
There are demons in the
court, so I must get

971
01:23:33,159 --> 01:23:34,755
involved in affairs of state

972
01:23:34,901 --> 01:23:36,674
Every one must do his bit.

973
01:23:36,778 --> 01:23:38,478
Hurry There's danger
everywhere.

974
01:23:38,593 --> 01:23:40,574
Let's get past this hurdle
first.

975
01:23:41,408 --> 01:23:43,317
These demonic monks have
great magical powers.

976
01:23:43,431 --> 01:23:46,310
Once he's awake we won't be
able to escape, so hurry

977
01:23:46,456 --> 01:23:49,376
Autumn, get out of here
Don't fight anymore

978
01:23:50,210 --> 01:23:51,565
This is a scene of
desolation.

979
01:23:51,711 --> 01:23:53,516
Lord, ride my horse.

980
01:23:56,300 --> 01:23:57,687
More chanting
- Father

981
01:23:57,801 --> 01:24:00,992
I'll use my powers to help
you concentrate.

982
01:24:01,169 --> 01:24:04,684
Come back, Hu. You'll
never beat him.

983
01:25:17,171 --> 01:25:21,792
Put down your butchers'
knives. Bow before Buddha

984
01:25:24,263 --> 01:25:27,496
Hu, don't sacrifice yourself
in vain

985
01:25:27,642 --> 01:25:30,562
I mistakenly trusted these
demons and slaughtered

986
01:25:30,666 --> 01:25:32,022
righteous officials.

987
01:25:32,167 --> 01:25:35,391
To atone for my sins, I'll
fight him to the death.

988
01:25:35,536 --> 01:25:36,642
Don't

989
01:25:36,756 --> 01:25:39,155
I'm headed for hell anyway.

990
01:25:43,086 --> 01:25:44,588
Hu

991
01:25:47,654 --> 01:25:50,355
Yan, why does the wind
suddenly blow so violently?

992
01:25:50,470 --> 01:25:52,649
It's hard to tell which
direction is which.

993
01:25:52,837 --> 01:25:54,454
Yan, what should we do?

994
01:25:54,610 --> 01:25:56,862
Evil spirits pervade this
road. Our lives hang by a

995
01:25:57,008 --> 01:25:58,145
slender thread.

996
01:25:58,259 --> 01:26:00,450
We mustn't stop. Follow me

997
01:26:09,261 --> 01:26:12,453
Oh, boundless heaven and
earth Help me

998
01:26:20,389 --> 01:26:23,976
Recite the scriptures with
me Prajna paramita...

999
01:26:27,042 --> 01:26:30,368
Prajna paramita...

1000
01:26:36,083 --> 01:26:38,555
The Diamond Sutra
incantation?

1001
01:26:38,691 --> 01:26:40,953
Prajna paramita...

1002
01:26:44,614 --> 01:26:48,253
Ignoramus, behaving so
boorishly in front of me

1003
01:26:48,336 --> 01:26:50,965
Prajna paramite...

1004
01:26:52,195 --> 01:26:54,771
Ning, Windy... get out of
the way

1005
01:26:54,907 --> 01:26:57,795
Oh, boundless heaven and
earth. Help me

1006
01:27:02,947 --> 01:27:07,504
Buddha is present

1007
01:27:13,000 --> 01:27:15,597
If you dare to impersonate
Buddha, what would you not

1008
01:27:15,753 --> 01:27:16,765
dare to do?

1009
01:27:16,827 --> 01:27:19,539
You think you can hoodwink
the people for ever?

1010
01:27:19,716 --> 01:27:22,980
I'm going to let every one
know what you really are

1011
01:27:23,167 --> 01:27:26,264
The masses love to worship
their idols.

1012
01:27:26,474 --> 01:27:29,007
Why set yourself against
the people?

1013
01:27:29,184 --> 01:27:32,772
It's their ignorance that
has allowed you to succeed.

1014
01:27:32,939 --> 01:27:35,515
I'll never let them worship
demons like you.

1015
01:27:35,619 --> 01:27:37,318
You'll never deceive the
people again

1016
01:27:37,433 --> 01:27:39,968
If you refuse to follow my
shining beacon...

1017
01:27:40,072 --> 01:27:43,096
you will be destroyed

1018
01:27:43,451 --> 01:27:46,923
What crap. Look out

1019
01:27:53,858 --> 01:27:55,840
Justine for all

1020
01:28:04,432 --> 01:28:07,008
Swords are part of the
infinite

1021
01:28:12,786 --> 01:28:14,621
We've only destroyed the
false cuter body.

1022
01:28:14,736 --> 01:28:16,676
He can come back & attack
us at any time.

1023
01:28:16,780 --> 01:28:18,522
We must use our swords to
fight back

1024
01:28:18,595 --> 01:28:20,534
Let me introduce myself.
I'm from the Kunlun sect...

1025
01:28:20,618 --> 01:28:22,662
At a time like this, let's
not separate into sects.

1026
01:28:22,735 --> 01:28:24,914
We're all fighting the same
enemy. Destroy this demon

1027
01:28:25,029 --> 01:28:26,311
Chant with me

1028
01:28:26,457 --> 01:28:28,991
Prajna paramita...

1029
01:28:29,137 --> 01:28:32,538
Prajna paramita...

1030
01:29:01,048 --> 01:29:02,957
The old demon has stolen
into the earth and broken

1031
01:29:03,103 --> 01:29:04,489
through our ring of swords.

1032
01:29:04,594 --> 01:29:06,502
What should we do?
- Watch

1033
01:29:08,807 --> 01:29:10,360
What kind of demon?

1034
01:29:10,506 --> 01:29:12,311
Come with me

1035
01:29:17,921 --> 01:29:19,997
Hold on to me as I fly.

1036
01:29:21,926 --> 01:29:23,657
Ning

1037
01:29:23,834 --> 01:29:26,952
You pulled my sleeve off.

1038
01:29:31,698 --> 01:29:34,512
What are you coming back for

1039
01:29:35,284 --> 01:29:37,224
What happened?

1040
01:29:37,339 --> 01:29:39,351
Gone?
- Keep quiet

1041
01:29:44,367 --> 01:29:48,226
Be careful. The demon has
changed its appearance.

1042
01:29:55,923 --> 01:29:57,831
It's huge

1043
01:30:01,971 --> 01:30:03,817
Be careful

1044
01:30:11,398 --> 01:30:14,526
Moon, look after your father
I'll help Yan.

1045
01:30:14,673 --> 01:30:16,727
Autumn, be careful

1046
01:30:16,863 --> 01:30:18,813
The demon's actually a
giant centipede

1047
01:30:18,990 --> 01:30:20,930
That worm can never be a
dragon.

1048
01:30:21,044 --> 01:30:22,566
Elder

1049
01:30:31,170 --> 01:30:33,871
I've never had to deal with
such a giant creature.

1050
01:30:34,017 --> 01:30:35,196
What should we do now?

1051
01:30:35,341 --> 01:30:37,396
Pierce the crown of its head

1052
01:30:46,896 --> 01:30:49,076
Ning

1053
01:30:58,972 --> 01:31:00,662
Windy

1054
01:31:08,056 --> 01:31:10,235
The flying sword

1055
01:31:51,646 --> 01:31:54,118
Prajna paramita

1056
01:31:56,203 --> 01:31:58,674
Exercise the demons

1057
01:32:01,741 --> 01:32:04,807
Oh, boundless heaven and
earth. Help me

1058
01:32:13,399 --> 01:32:15,162
Elder
- Autumn

1059
01:32:17,123 --> 01:32:18,927
Two heads are better than
one.

1060
01:32:19,073 --> 01:32:21,117
Abracadabra. Hocus pocus.

1061
01:32:28,740 --> 01:32:30,763
Hocus pocus.

1062
01:33:05,281 --> 01:33:07,857
I've been in the Orchid
Monastery for so long...

1063
01:33:07,961 --> 01:33:10,766
I didn't know the world was
so full of devils and demons

1064
01:33:10,881 --> 01:33:13,165
It's hard to separate the
living from the dead.

1065
01:33:13,279 --> 01:33:14,834
The world is in chaos.

1066
01:33:14,990 --> 01:33:16,898
It's a good thing you hid in
the Orchid Monastery.

1067
01:33:17,076 --> 01:33:19,130
Otherwise I might never
have found you.

1068
01:33:19,265 --> 01:33:20,725
We share the same ideals...

1069
01:33:20,872 --> 01:33:22,675
We should roam this world
together and fight

1070
01:33:22,853 --> 01:33:24,907
for justice. We should
work together.

1071
01:33:25,043 --> 01:33:26,429
What are you saying?

1072
01:33:26,502 --> 01:33:28,161
I've always led a solitary
existence.

1073
01:33:28,348 --> 01:33:30,496
Last time, I almost died
trying to help you save Sian

1074
01:33:30,611 --> 01:33:32,864
This time, I've helped you
battle the demons...

1075
01:33:32,979 --> 01:33:34,709
and almost lost my life.

1076
01:33:34,887 --> 01:33:36,482
It's better if we go our
own ways.

1077
01:33:36,628 --> 01:33:40,101
When you need my help, I'll
return and save you.

1078
01:33:47,839 --> 01:33:50,092
Be careful, Autumn

1079
01:33:51,906 --> 01:33:54,378
The demon still isn't dead.

1080
01:33:54,555 --> 01:33:56,171
Autumn

1081
01:33:56,359 --> 01:33:59,654
I really need your help this
time, or I'm finished.

1082
01:33:59,800 --> 01:34:02,022
We must be jinxed

1083
01:34:02,168 --> 01:34:04,743
I'll take care of things
Quickly, crawl out of there.

1084
01:34:04,848 --> 01:34:06,443
No good.

1085
01:34:06,797 --> 01:34:08,185
Autumn

1086
01:34:12,815 --> 01:34:13,784
Autumn

1087
01:34:13,900 --> 01:34:15,422
That centipede flew over

1088
01:34:15,568 --> 01:34:17,476
What about Autumn and Yan?

1089
01:34:17,622 --> 01:34:20,771
We're locked in. We must
think of a way to escape.

1090
01:34:20,887 --> 01:34:23,880
You're right I've really
caused you harm.

1091
01:34:28,718 --> 01:34:30,314
Our bodies are restrained.

1092
01:34:30,460 --> 01:34:33,161
We can be saved only if our
souls can escape.

1093
01:34:33,317 --> 01:34:34,454
Souls.

1094
01:34:34,600 --> 01:34:37,343
Will we have enough energy
to later let the souls

1095
01:34:37,488 --> 01:34:38,729
back in?

1096
01:34:38,918 --> 01:34:40,502
This is the only way

1097
01:34:40,690 --> 01:34:43,224
Chant along with me.

1098
01:34:45,633 --> 01:34:48,855
The spirit of Buddha
conquers all

1099
01:34:52,276 --> 01:34:55,394
Goodness is indestructible.

1100
01:35:07,793 --> 01:35:11,266
Oh, boundless heaven and
earth. Help me

1101
01:35:13,331 --> 01:35:15,864
Help me
- Hocus pocus

1102
01:35:43,917 --> 01:35:45,679
Autumn

1103
01:35:50,279 --> 01:35:51,592
Yan

1104
01:35:53,063 --> 01:35:54,596
Yan

1105
01:35:54,731 --> 01:35:56,806
Soul, return

1106
01:36:02,178 --> 01:36:04,722
My soul can't return to my
body

1107
01:36:04,930 --> 01:36:07,110
Autumn, catch the soul

1108
01:36:12,303 --> 01:36:15,046
His power isn't strong
enough. I'll help him.

1109
01:36:15,192 --> 01:36:17,101
Prajna paramita...

1110
01:36:18,706 --> 01:36:21,074
I can't catch it.

1111
01:36:21,251 --> 01:36:22,638
Moon

1112
01:36:33,952 --> 01:36:35,934
Too late

1113
01:36:43,588 --> 01:36:45,466
Autumn

1114
01:38:09,331 --> 01:38:11,125
What's all the hubub outside

1115
01:38:11,239 --> 01:38:13,908
What hubbub? I don't hear
anything

1116
01:38:31,460 --> 01:38:35,173
Who's getting married? Such
a large golden pig

1117
01:38:35,454 --> 01:38:38,197
It's a gift to Lord Fu from
the emperor.

1118
01:38:38,447 --> 01:38:41,638
Since he exposed the
traitors in the imperial

1119
01:38:41,794 --> 01:38:44,745
court, he performed a great
service for the emperor.

1120
01:38:44,922 --> 01:38:48,531
It's a wedding gift for Lord
Fu's daughter.

1121
01:38:49,688 --> 01:38:51,347
Moon

1122
01:38:52,265 --> 01:38:53,995
Moon

1123
01:38:54,559 --> 01:38:56,582
Ning

1124
01:39:02,943 --> 01:39:05,018
Is Windy getting...

1125
01:39:05,143 --> 01:39:06,937
Sister is already married.

1126
01:39:07,051 --> 01:39:09,971
Don't cause her any trouble.

1127
01:39:10,326 --> 01:39:12,235
I'm about to start on a
journey.

1128
01:39:12,381 --> 01:39:15,957
Give her my best wishes for
a happy marriage.

1129
01:39:18,011 --> 01:39:21,276
I will. Take care of
yourself.

1130
01:39:31,996 --> 01:39:33,873
Adieu

1131
01:39:48,807 --> 01:39:52,071
It's hard to differentiate
between true and false hopes

1132
01:39:52,217 --> 01:39:54,720
Now I understand why you
stay away from our

1133
01:39:54,866 --> 01:39:56,138
mortal world.

1134
01:39:56,284 --> 01:39:59,099
Mortals are forgetful. Good
deeds fade like the wind.

1135
01:39:59,215 --> 01:40:02,510
No matter what you've done,
it's soon forgotten.

1136
01:40:02,760 --> 01:40:05,127
Is forgetting good or bad?

1137
01:40:05,263 --> 01:40:07,838
Should we have hopes?

1138
01:40:21,030 --> 01:40:23,700
You said you'd cherish no
hopes

1139
01:40:23,846 --> 01:40:26,943
Sister, don't hesitate
Go to him

1140
01:40:34,003 --> 01:40:35,015
Windy?

1141
01:40:35,161 --> 01:40:36,923
Ning

1142
01:40:41,877 --> 01:40:44,786
Farewell
- Take care

1143
01:40:45,527 --> 01:40:47,331
Let's go

