Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
The Muslim League will avenge
the suffering Denmark has caused...
My blood will be shed
and many will die along with me.
Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
The video was on his website.
Brix thinks
you can give us a new angle.
David Grüner, 28-year-old veteran.
- What do you know about the squad?
- 3-2-AIpha. Eight soldiers.
Raben was squad leader. There were
accusations of civilian casualties.
- The judge advocates cleared them.
- And the rest of the squad?
Raben is on the run.
We are looking for Lisbeth Thomsen.
The Government has put a lot of work
into the terrorism package.
- Will you be Minister of Justice?
- Why didn't we see this coming?
We never imagined such madness.
It seems you're on your own
with the People's Party.
- We want a national agreement.
- The Minister will see reason.
The Prime Minister wants to see you
and the Minister of Defense.
- Monberg knew the first victim.
- Do you listen to rumours?
We must take action.
Agree to the People's Party's demands.
- The Probation Service turned you down.
- Why?
- Why can't I see him?
- Myg Poulsen has been killed.
Raben knew both victims.
He lied about it and escaped.
I must find Thomsen.
She's the only one left of our squad.
- Turn yourself in.
- Tell me if you hear from Jens.
- She had an uncle. In Sweden.
- It's in this file.
Has he been here? Someone made off
with five kilos of plastic explosives.
Thomsen is living
on the Swedish island of Skogö.
- The police are expecting Raben.
- He's not likely to find this place.
- How can you explain the anger?
- I'm sick of those accusations.
Raben and the squad risked their lives.
Don't slag them off.
- You're not alone on the island.
- Stay there!
- Something happened in the village.
- Why do you think so?
My dead mates had talked about
some fucked up officer called Perk.
- The lawyer believed them
- Dragsholm.
- Come out, or I'll shoot.
- Stay here.
- Krabbe is getting impatient.
- We planned this press conference.
Dragsholm wasn't having
an affair with Monberg. I was.
- Did you see Dragsholm?
- No. And he told me nothing.
It's a judge advocate's report
on an incident in Afghanistan.
- I realise I must resign.
- The victims' names!
- What's happening?
- Get back to Thomsen. Now!
- I stopped you.
- Were you in here?
No. Why?
THE KILLING
They can't get far on this island.
- What's in that direction?
- Nothing. Just forest.
- And over there?
- More of the same.
20,000 acres of forest.
And Thomsen knows it well.
Bertil and Ralle
were trying to cut them off.
- But I don't think they saw them.
- Where is our backup?
They told me half an hour,
but knowing them it'll be longer.
- My brother-in-law is on his way.
- Your brother-in-law?
Yes. Had we known
you'd let Thomsen go
we'd be better prepared.
It was easy to get into the house.
Flimsy doors and open windows.
- Any traces of the suspect?
- Only Raben's.
We can't be certain, he didn't do it.
He was a soldier.
And that's a booby-trap
with a kilo of explosives.
Had Thomsen touched the rifle,
the house would have blown up.
Raben may have made the roadblock,
but not the booby-trap.
We must find Thomsen and Raben.
Why the hell...
My brother-in-law and his mates.
They found Thomsen's car.
They must have continued on foot.
Come on!
- What's wrong?
- Could you...
Come here.
- How far is it?
- It's still some distance.
Be careful.
- Someone was in your house. Who?
- I didn't see anyone.
- I haven't used the rifle lately.
- What's going on?
The lawyer came to see me.
She asked me to testify again.
- She wanted to reopen the case.
- Why? What did she say?
- She'd uncovered new information.
- What sort of information?
She wouldn't say.
What happened in that village?
- I don't know. What else?
- That's all she would tell me.
- Did you do wrong? What happened?
- I can't remember, damn it.
I remember the screams.
The stench of death.
The children trying to...
He called himself Perk.
Did anyone survive?
Is it someone seeking revenge?
They've found the car! Come on.
- Why did he need explosives?
- He didn't. I told you!
The codes for the ammunition depot
are in your father's computer.
Jens wasn't here.
I accessed that computer.
I know nothing of your explosives.
He wanted to find Thomsen.
I found the address
of her uncle in Sweden.
- So you met. Where?
- It doesn't matter.
It does! He's wanted.
And you are an accessory...
In a car park. OK?
- He just turned up.
- Have you planned to meet?
- Do you know where he is?
- No.
Yes? Come in.
The police have searched the depot
for forensic evidence.
The colonel's code was not used
to gain access.
They wish to speak to you. They've found
explosives identical to ours.
- Where?
- On an island in Sweden.
It was placed in a house
belonging to Lisbeth Thomsen.
Where was Jens heading?
He didn't say.
But he was asking about
Thomsen's house in Sweden.
Now that they've found the explosives,
there's no danger.
Will you let me know
if the police mention Jens?
Of course.
The police will want to speak to you too.
But it won't be as bad as this.
The number you called
cannot be reached at the moment.
- They were here, not so long ago.
- Let's see.
Perhaps they chose the footpath.
- Where does it lead?
- East. Towards the harbour.
- What's in that direction?
- A caravan park, but it's closed.
- Is there a harbour?
- It's just a landing stage.
Thomsen owns a boat!
Inform the coast guard!
We must search this area. Go!
They found the car. And they know
where my boat is moored.
- They've called the coast guard.
- Never mind. Come on.
No! Take this.
Row north. I'll go the other way.
The coast guard will follow me.
- We stay together!
- It will give you a head start.
The police will let me go.
It's our only chance.
We'll stick together. Come on.
Fuel! We don't have any fuel.
There's a jerry can in my boat-shed.
Over there. You can't miss it.
There are no bogeymen!
Hurry up.
Thomsen! Stop!
Stop! Don't start it!
- Take the kayak. See you.
- Stop!
- The Minister is coming.
- We can't wait any longer.
- The Prime Minister is on a plane.
- The news is going on air.
- What is happening?
- Keep calling him. I'm sorry.
Something's come up. I must
discuss it with the Prime Minister.
- What is it?
- Can't tell you, but it's important.
I don't believe the Prime Minister
would want this postponement.
The investigation may influence
the ban on Islamic organisations.
Buch...
Will you stop stalling, damn it!
Our country is waiting
for us to take action.
- Don't be so bloody soft.
- Krabbe, I've had enough...
I don't give a damn!
And neither does the Prime Minister.
I demand an explanation now.
Or I'll tell the press the Government
is incapable of making decisions.
I'm sorry,
but it's your responsibility.
I won't be made accountable
for your indecision.
The reporters are anxious
that you'll be too late for the news.
You may be nervous,
but this is a historical crisis.
Let us go and tell them
what we agreed upon.
Good evening.
Good evening and welcome.
The Government is pleased
to present the terrorism agreement
which has been reached
with the People's Party.
Terrorism has become a fact of life
so we must be up front
with improving security.
These threats must not force us
to compromise our democratic values.
We must protect our freedom
and fight dark forces.
Since the recent killings
of demobilised soldiers
this seems more urgent
than ever before.
Before we recount
the terrorism package
Erling Krabbe will say a few words.
Thank you.
The negotiations
have been lengthy and difficult.
But we have succeeded
in reaching an agreement.
I wish to commend the Government
for the good political work
and for having the courage
to take the bull by the horns
even if the Opposition
has thrown in the towel.
The People's Party makes a point
of guarding our freedom.
We will not be trampled
by medieval fanatics
hatched from Muslim schools
and organisations
subsidised by the Danish state.
We must take strict measures
against certain groups
who try to undermine our society.
Otherwise we sell out on the core
of our identity as Danes.
We can't allow that.
The People's Party is proud
to contribute to the new legislation.
The Minister of Justice
will give a summary of its contents.
Buch...
Buch!
Well... it's no good.
We'll have to stop this.
Yes. I'm sorry.
I can't go into details.
- Excuse me.
- What's going on?
The launch of the terrorism package
took a surprising turn.
Minister of Justice Buch walked out
during a press conference
having stated
that the terrorism package is off.
The Minister of Justice
had no further comments
but Erling Krabbe was astounded.
I can't reach König
at Special Branch.
Ask Karina to get whatever she can
on that old military case.
I'll do it. We can't be sure
about Karina's involvement.
It is possible, a disciplinary...
I haven't been here
since Monberg's 50th birthday.
These portraits should remind
the Minister of his responsibility.
- It doesn't look good, but...
- Are you aware of the reactions?
Do you realise the magnitude
of the crisis we are now facing?
It would be wrong to agree
on that terrorism package. Monberg...
Don't blame Monberg.
So you're still on about those allegations.
Not just allegations.
There is written evidence.
Monberg met with the first victim.
She was a lawyer
and wanted Monberg to help her
reopen a military criminal case.
The case involved the soldiers
who have been killed recently.
A squad was accused
of killing civilians in Afghanistan.
The squad was cleared, but the lawyer
wanted the case reopened.
She gave Monberg the case file.
Five days later, she was killed.
- How did you get hold of this?
- Monberg circulated it.
I received it
just before the press conference.
Monberg should have
brought this up long ago.
We can ask him when he recovers,
but we must act upon it now.
Monberg didn't have a heart attack.
His wife said he took some pills.
He was depressed.
Their marriage was on the rocks.
She was devastated. We agreed
to give the press another story.
- That hardly improves the situation.
- What was Monberg trying to hide?
Why should he be concerned
with some old military case?
I don't understand it.
Look into it. Mum's the word.
We must know what it's all about,
as soon as possible.
Considering the latest rumour.
- What rumour?
- Something happened in Sweden.
It seems another soldier
has been found dead.
How were we to know she'd run off?
There's no trace of Raben.
They split before the explosion.
Maybe he got away in another vessel.
We're searching for the perpetrator.
The coast guard and the Swedish Navy.
We're doing all we can. Bye.
Brix and Special Branch
want a meeting.
Explosives were stolen
from the barracks.
They're checking if the same explosives
were used here.
We couldn't have prevented it.
We tried to help her, but she ran off.
They found a bag. Let's look for clues
in the boat house. Maybe...
Where are you going?
Lund!
Right. Thanks.
The bombing
of a Danish citizen in Sweden
was connected to
the so-called terrorism killings.
The victim was a woman,
previously connected to the army.
This makes her the fourth victim
in the unsolved terrorism case.
Neither Special Branch
nor the police have any...
What the hell
are they talking about?
Hedeby is in there too.
We mustn't give up now.
We're on to something.
No, we're not.
All we do is find the bodies.
What happened in Afghanistan,
we don't know for certain.
But some fundamentalists
find the soldiers guilty
notwithstanding
the judge advocate's report.
We've found websites
and fatwas against the soldiers
and the system that exonerated them.
We will concentrate on this.
Unfortunately, the investigation
has not solved the case.
I have asked Brix to restructure
his team as of today.
- What's the idea?
- You are still on the case.
- But you must take a few days off.
- We're just about to...
You let your main witness go
when the killer was in the area.
She ran off!
We could hardly put her in chains.
You knew some religious fanatics
were out to kill that squad.
You shouldn't have gone to lunch.
What if someone else
wants to get rid of the squad?
What if it's all a set-up?
The flyers, the video, Faith Fellow,
Kodmani, the Muslim League.
What are you saying?
What is she talking about?
Dragsholm asked Thomsen to testify
if the case was reopened.
What if somebody doesn't want
the case to be reopened?
Who would that be?
They are all dead!
And the last one with a good alibi
was committed to Herstedvester.
The army. The explosives
were stolen from the barracks.
And the detonators were like
the ones used in the army.
We're not sure the incident occurred,
nor if the case was to be reopened.
Yes. The reopening
of the case was on the cards.
I have only just been informed.
It's become a political issue.
But it has nothing
to do with the killings.
- It would explain a lot.
- The army doesn't kill its own.
Not the army as such.
Someone in the army, with a motive.
Rubbish! I expect to be briefed
when you've restructured your team.
I already have. Lund and Strange
will continue to work on the case.
It's in everyone's interest
to have this matter cleared up.
I'm sure you will understand.
If not, I will invite you
to see the forensic morgue.
We'll do it.
But they mustn't find fault.
- Agreed?
- Of course.
We'll investigate
the case from Afghanistan.
And we'll check out this officer Perk
Thomsen mentioned.
As long as you're discreet about it.
- What is she doing here?
- Hello?
- She met with her husband.
- How? She is being watched.
Right. She told him about
Thomsen's house in Sweden.
I have ordered a search.
Shall we set off?
The police have been here twice.
And Louise called.
FOURTH DANISH SOLDIER
KILLED LAST NIGHT
I need money.
Can you lend me some?
- For what?
- Just a couple of thousand.
This will have to stop.
You're the last one.
- Can I have some money or not?
- Turn yourself in.
Thomsen said the lawyer
wanted to reopen the case.
- What case?
- About what happened out there.
She must have discovered
something.
If I give up now,
they'll all have died in vain.
- Did Dragsholm contact you?
- Who?
- She was killed in Memorial Park.
- I never met her.
- You think I'm insane.
- No. I was in that camp too.
- They checked. There was no officer.
- It must have been a cover-up.
The same people are behind this.
You have a wife and son
to think of too.
- Just give me some money.
- I can take you to the police.
I could tell them you're innocent.
Trust me.
I just saw Thomsen get blown up.
Don't tell me
to turn the other cheek.
Now give me some money, damn it!
Don't you have a cash card?
You must have!
We excused your behaviour
at the press conference
with the necessity to discuss
the case with the security committee.
After the latest killing,
the media calls it a massive blunder.
Several of your colleagues wash their
hands of you, Erling Krabbe for one.
- And the Prime Minister?
- He expects an explanation.
According to the Ministry of Defense
nothing connects Monberg
to the old military case.
But I've been wrong
about Monberg before.
- Didn't you see a change in him?
- No.
I suppose I didn't really know him.
We're here.
You'd better go in by yourself.
If there's to be a disciplinary case,
we should not be discussing this.
Damn it, Plough. She merely
had an affair with the Minister.
We can't be sure
that there isn't more to it.
You just don't want
to hear about Monberg's sex life.
I'd prefer not to.
- Hello?
- Just a moment.
PARALYSED
- Hi!
- Hi.
Sit here, darling.
Look in your book.
I'll give the nanny a hand
throwing this out. One moment.
- Hello. What's your name?
- Merle.
Come along, dear.
Lotte will help you get dressed.
I'm sorry. I must go to the post office.
Don't forget to let her wee.
If it's about my resignation,
I'll do whatever the Ministry wants.
If I'm a suspect,
they must take me to court.
- I didn't know you have a daughter.
- I didn't say at the job interview.
- Her father is a musician, it seems.
- No. That's mine.
Her father is a lawyer. He wanted
to earn a lot of money. In Dubai.
I would like you to come back.
I have misled you
and the Permanent Secretary.
Plough doesn't think
you've done anything wrong.
He could do with
a roll in the hay, too.
Sorry. But I need your help.
I must find out how Monberg
is involved with all this.
Do you have any idea
why he wanted to hide these matters?
- I would have told you.
- Why all this secrecy?
- Why did he try to kill himself?
- What?
It wasn't a heart attack
He took some pills.
He probably had a bad conscience.
But I need some solid facts.
- I don't know what to say.
- Right.
If you think of something,
please call me.
I wish you all the best.
I'm on my way.
The Minister of Defense
is calling a meeting.
- What about?
- They didn't say. This afternoon.
Tell him we don't have time.
Major Søgaard
isn't answering his phone.
He's at the officers' send-off.
He'll get back to you.
Myg Poulsen was
in charge of ammunitions.
His key and access code
were misused.
His killer must
have got it from him.
Don't you cancel a code
when the holder dies?
It was cancelled, but the technicians
hadn't reprogrammed the lock.
Nobody imagined this could happen.
No... When I picked up the judge
advocate's report, there was no guard.
The depot is locked electronically.
Only seven people know the code.
- Normally, no guard is needed.
- What time was the burglary?
According to the log files,
the lock was disengaged at 0:39.
And once again at 1:04,
25 minutes later.
As you can see, the burglar
made his way in here.
I assume your forensic staff
can explain how.
The explosives
were taken from that shelf.
We've made a list of outsiders
who know their way about the barracks.
- How did Lisbeth Thomsen die?
- It could be an insider.
Maybe nobody noticed anything
because the burglar belongs here.
- A hole was cut in the fence.
- That could be a diversion.
- The burglar knew this place.
- Who else has access?
Three platoon commanders.
And two officers.
What about you?
Come with us to police headquarters.
We'll get back to you. Stay in town.
- Why?
- We want you in for questioning.
- It will have to wait
- Either you come voluntarily...
...or else we'll have to arrest you.
Yesterday, you told me no civilians
were assaulted in that village.
According to Thomsen,
3-2-AIpha gave a different account.
Yes. But they were proved wrong.
You lost three men.
Maybe you weren't quite focused.
So the squad was flown back
to the main camp.
What did the soldiers report?
They'd had a call from a patrol
under fire behind enemy lines.
On arrival they found
only one officer, Perk.
He'd been under fire
and they came to relieve him.
- What else did they say?
- They took refuge in a house.
They were under siege for 48 hours
without radio contact.
During this siege, something
allegedly happened to the family.
- What?
- The Danish officer killed them.
What did you think of that?
The report was pure fabrication.
Nobody could confirm that the squad
had received any such message.
None of our men were in the area,
nobody called Perk, and no bodies.
- Why would they lie?
- That mission cost three lives.
They were trying to shift the blame
for the tragedy they had caused.
So you think squad leader Raben
was to blame for the tragedy.
I'm not obliged to answer that.
- What about the family in the house?
- Everybody had fled.
It was a dangerous area.
We did all we could...
- Did you yourself check all this?
- It goes with the job.
I wasn't in the camp during
the incident, but I was briefed...
- Hold on! You weren't in the camp?
- No.
I was at the Security Force's meeting
with the Afghan Government in Kabul.
My second-in-command kept me posted.
Everything was by the book.
Who was your
second-in-command?
Captain Søgaard.
Presently Major Søgaard.
- Søgaard was in command.
- Correct.
- I came back two days later...
- That will be all for now.
Jarnvig.
Hello. Just a moment.
- Any word from Søgaard?
- We've left messages.
He doesn't return our calls.
Special Branch is investigating
Islamic organisations
who maintain that Danish soldiers
committed atrocities in Helmand.
- Is there any actual evidence?
- I don't know.
König will brief you. They have
nothing on Monberg and the case.
They are complaining about lack
of cooperation with the police.
- Why's that?
- I'll look into it.
I have posted the vacancy
for your new Personal Secretary.
- I know of two, who...
- Do you have a moment?
You caught me at a bad moment.
But I'll be seeing you later.
Two minutes.
The Prime Minister briefed me.
We'd better have a chat.
Rossing, I realise
Monberg is a friend of yours.
You may not like what you hear,
but we must get to the bottom of this.
I remember
when I was first appointed.
You're anxious to make a good
impression on the Prime Minister.
- It's like going back to school.
- I'm rather busy...
You're digging a grave.
Not for Monberg, but for the country.
I know there is no connection between
Monberg and that military case.
- If you say so.
- You need to realise this.
Frode has been under
extreme pressure for a long time.
The terrorism package negotiations.
A very unhappy marriage.
May I?
And then he was approached
by Anne Dragsholm.
For the past 15 years
she has been the love of his life.
They met at university. He was
a visiting lecturer, she a student.
But Frode had a wife and children.
He broke up the relationship.
I don't believe they have
been in touch since then.
Until now, when she made
use of her connection to him.
Is there a point to this?
Monberg wasn't interested in the case.
He wanted Dragsholm.
When she was killed
a few days later, he cracked.
I had lunch with him
a couple of days before...
He spoke of all the mistakes
he'd made in his life.
I had other things on my mind.
He was talking about
his break-up with Anne Dragsholm.
So you'd like me
to forget the whole thing.
No. I'm not saying that.
I want everything out in the open,
but not right now.
If you're kicking up dirt that only
concerns Monberg's personal life
you may as well
be setting fire to our flag.
It's your choice.
I'm just asking you to think
before you act.
Thanks for the coffee.
- Is this your address book?
- Yes. You won't find his in there.
We'll have to take it with us.
You'll get it back.
- Mummy...
- Hi, darling.
Did you have fun?
They're helping Mummy clear up.
They're leaving now.
- Did you like the zoological museum?
- Please sign here.
Hi, Jonas. Nice bag.
Did your Daddy give you that?
- Where are they taking our computer?
- So long.
It's all right, darling.
They just want to borrow it.
We'll buy a PlayStation
on Monday.
- Louise. Hello?
- It's me.
Would you mind coming over
to my office?
Come in.
He really isn't well.
He needs help. He must get out
of harm's way before it's too late.
Call him. Say you want to meet him.
Let the police see to the rest.
- I did. He doesn't answer the phone.
- Try again.
Try this one. One cool piece.
- How much are you good for?
- About 600.
600? You can't even
buy a gas pistol for that.
I'll have this one.
I need it. Get it?
Leave!
- Louise?
- My dad knows about this phone.
- How? Was it Priest?
- They are worried about you.
- Are you all right?
- Do the police know about it?
Not yet. Are you all right?
Priest says something's not right.
I know what I'm doing.
We can't talk now.
I'm looking for Major Søgaard.
Has anyone seen him?
"Jam tarts for breakfast?"
She gives him an icy look.
"That's all you can get
through the letterbox."
Hi.
I've been leaving messages all day.
You know I want to talk to you.
This is my last day with the officers.
We have a full schedule.
- It's about your stationing.
- With Team Ægir, right?
Shall I question you here?
I need to go to the john.
Unless you want to join me there too,
I'll meet you outside.
Go ahead. Shoot. But I know
no more than the colonel.
He wasn't in the camp. You must
have heard the soldiers' statements.
But I can't tell you anything
you don't already know.
The soldiers mentioned
an officer called Perk.
There was no officer.
And nobody called Perk.
They claim they received a distress call.
There wasn't any.
The squad leader should have
confirmed it before going in.
You don't like Raben, do you?
I didn't say that.
He used to be a good soldier.
How can you be sure
no atrocities were committed?
I led the operation that got
Raben's squad out of that mess.
So you were one of the first
to arrive at the scene.
- Correct.
- And you saw nothing significant?
I wouldn't say that. Three soldiers dead,
the rest of them wounded.
But I saw no civilians.
Neither dead nor alive.
A few months later, you were
decorated and promoted to Major.
Did it have anything
to do with that mission?
We did save the rest of the squad.
If anything happened in that village,
it would have been your responsibility.
Yes, but had anything happened,
it was no big deal.
War is a dirty business.
Innocent people die too.
Politicians send us to war, so that
you don't get blood on your hands.
Go.
Lund here. I want Søgaard's
alibi checked. Where was he?
Who did he see, what did he do,
around the time of the four killings.
Brix reports that they checked
officers stationed abroad after 1996.
There is no officer
by the name of Perk.
But some recruits were trained
by a lieutenant they called Perk.
- OK.
- His real name is Per K. Møller.
- He was on Team Ægir.
- Did you get his address?
Thank you very much.
It seems to tally.
Monberg was a visiting lecturer
while Dragsholm was at university.
They may have had an affair.
After that,
she applied for a job in the army.
I hope you weren't too rude
to the Defense Minister.
- I tried to call you. Where is he?
- He just went in.
- We can't talk about the case.
- That's not it. I must speak to him.
It's important.
- Thank you.
- I want a word.
- Do you have a moment?
- Yes, of course.
I just wanted to thank you.
I had lost perspective.
We must regard it
as being for a greater cause.
I'll propose to the Prime Minister
that we let sleeping dogs lie.
I'm pleased that we see eye to eye.
- Buch...
- Yes. What?
- Karina.
- Talk to Plough.
Monberg is connected
to the military case.
The lawyer complained
to him about procedure.
The soldiers' statements
were being disregarded.
- Monberg knew about the case.
- We've been through all that.
- If you've come to impress...
- At first, I found nothing.
Then, I cross-checked the soldiers'
names with the Ministry's files.
You don't have computer access!
The case went through
the Ministry of Defense.
But the Minister of Justice
attended a meeting about a soldier.
Jens Peter Raben,
who was committed to Herstedvester.
There are no minutes of the meeting.
Defense Minister Rossing
called the meeting.
Buch... We're waiting for you.
Come along, darling.
Those were Per Kristian's
favourite sunglasses.
Won't you sit down? My husband
is abroad, but I hope I can help.
- When did your son die?
- In May two years ago.
- May?
- Yes. In an explosion.
Leave her in peace. He died
three months before the incident.
I tried to talk him into
choosing another profession.
But he was an army man.
He wanted to make a difference.
He was promoted to First Lieutenant.
We hardly ever heard from him.
And then they phoned
to tell us what had happened.
He had the funeral
he would have wanted.
- That's a comfort.
- Maybe we should...
- Thank you for your time.
- Yes, but...
Has it to do with the investigation?
A lawyer was here
asking the same questions.
A lawyer?
We've kept his things.
Every time we're about to throw
them out, we have second thoughts.
The lawyer asked to see the documents
concerning his accident
in case we were entitled
to compensation.
When I came back, she was
searching through his things.
- What for?
- She wouldn't say.
She asked a lot of questions.
About the funeral, and all.
About the funeral?
It bothered her, we hadn't seen him.
- Seen him? Where?
- In his coffin.
We wanted to, but they told us
we'd better not. For our own sakes.
- Who said that?
- Captain Søgaard and the chaplain.
Did they say, you shouldn't see
your son in the coffin?
- Where is he buried?
- In the churchyard nearby.
Would you like to see
a photo of the grave?
Yes, please.
- Forget it!
- Dragsholm was on to it too.
She must have been.
Søgaard claimed he didn't know Perk.
- He's covering for him.
- He died before the incident.
- He didn't let them see the body.
- It was blown to bits.
If there was a body.
We must ask for her permission.
We'll have to dig up the coffin
to see if it's empty.
I want you to leave.
Jens?
I never really believed in God.
It always seemed so weird.
If there is a God,
what is the meaning of all this?
I would like to have faith.
But it's hard.
Do you understand?
We'd better go to the police.
You'd better take this.
What was I thinking?
You're doing the right thing.
Let me just change, before we go.
ANNE DRAGSHOLM
BARRISTER-AT-LAW
Priest?
Priest!
PER K. MØLLER
REST IN PEACE