Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
The Muslim League will avenge
the suffering Denmark has caused
in Palestine, Iraq
and Afghanistan.
Brix thinks
you can give us a new angle.
- You're wasting your time.
- I could use your help.
- Allan Myg Poulsen, soldier.
- And the murder weapon?
- Round his neck.
- You're not on this case.
- The case calls for a clean slate.
- This is what I do best.
I'll tell your workplace
we want to borrow you.
Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
The video was on his website.
Police!
The Government has put a lot
of work into the terrorism package.
We need you to head the negotiations.
Will you be Minister of Justice?
The link was activated at 5:03pm.
At sunset, the end of Ramadan.
Not only this victim,
but also the woman served abroad.
- How can this come as a surprise?
- Your predecessor knew of the case.
But none of us thought
it would develop into such madness.
We should announce
our agreement today
to show the killers
we won't falter.
- My party will decide nothing now.
- It's up for vote next week.
I know about the memo Special
Branch gave your predecessor
warning him about terrorism.
We no longer have confidence in you.
The Probation Service
turned you down.
- Why?
- Why can't I visit him?
He had a fit of rage
and won't take his medicine.
- We have many decisions to make.
- There is nothing wrong with me.
The police want to question you
about Myg Poulsen. He's been killed.
I was contacted on my website
by someone calling himself Faith Fellow.
He wanted to upload
a religious video.
I didn't know what it was
before it was on my website.
Just focus on Kodmani
and his followers. Agreed?
- I like football and opera.
- Take the next left turning.
Myg Poulsen was a good soldier.
- Were there any threats?
- All the time.
This was his bunk
and this was his closet.
- Who is Raben?
- He was invalided.
Suffering from delusions,
he took a nurse hostage.
He was sectioned indefinitely.
Did you know Anne Dragsholm?
Was she connected to Myg Poulsen?
- She was killed two weeks ago.
- I don't know her.
I'm really sorry about Myg.
But I need you now.
See you, love.
- What am I to see?
- Next to Myg Poulsen is Raben.
So what?
- Anne Dragsholm?
- He said he didn't know her.
THE KILLING
He left his ward to see the clinical
director, but never showed up.
He got past the alarm system
and escaped through the sewers.
- Do you know how far he's got?
- No, but it can't be far.
We were quick to pursue him,
and it's dark as hell.
- Where does the sewer pipe lead to?
- It ends up at the disposal plant.
But it'll take more than luck
to find the way.
The prison followed
all the correct procedures.
We are investigating the getaway.
- But he'll soon tire of the stench.
- Strange speaking.
They're searching the sewers.
He's more cunning than they think.
- What are you looking for?
- Anything about him.
- Brix is asking for us.
- Is the medical director here?
Yes, but Brix wants a report.
Special Branch arrested three...
We'll see the medical director first.
Raben had applied for parole,
but then he was turned down.
- It must have caused a relapse.
- A relapse of what?
Post-traumatic stress caused
by his experiences in the war.
What experiences?
He was committed
to this institution
due to his aggressive
behaviour on his return.
- What were these experiences?
- It's confidential. Is it relevant?
You are not bound to secrecy
when people's lives are at stake.
You just claimed
that this man is dangerous.
Some of his mates died in the war,
and he felt guilty.
However, his amnesia
spared him some grief.
Did he mention an army buddy
called Allan Myg Poulsen?
Not until yesterday.
He wanted to call him.
He was worried about him.
- What was he worried about?
- That he would harm himself.
Why do you ask?
What about her? Military legal
consultant Anne Dragsholm?
Raben hardly talked about war.
He focused on his future
and his family.
Could he have been
in touch with her?
No. Not without my knowledge.
Why?
- We're trying to get a picture...
- How can you be sure?
This is a list of his phone calls
and visits during his time here.
I don't know what you're after,
but we're not trying to hide anything.
His escape is unfortunate,
and we should have foreseen it
considering his diagnosis.
This is a recording of Raben's
examination before he was committed.
It may give you some idea.
He spent three weeks in that cell
before we could start treatment.
- Of course. I understand.
- He got out at the pumping plant.
It's 5km away. Shall we go?
The area must be searched and
we must visit his family and friends.
He's a missing person, not a suspect.
So no APE is issued.
He was photographed with the two
victims, but let's not mix things up.
We're not.
He knows something.
He knew both victims, lied and fled.
- Does he know the Muslim League?
- How should I know?
Brix says they have more on Kodmani.
He must be questioned again.
Raben could have escaped
a long time ago.
- He's capable of anything.
- Yet he chooses this moment.
- Let's just get on with it.
- Admit, it's strange...
I respect your methods, but they
have been known to lead to disaster.
- So now you're listening to gossip?
- No, I'm just saying...
Right. I'll talk to Brix.
I'm driving. Hand me the key!
No, he has no previous convictions.
I have it in writing.
I'll send you everything.
Thank you for looking into it. Bye.
Hi. I just spoke to another lawyer.
Louise... Do you have a moment?
He thinks we have grounds
for an appeal.
I promised to send him
all the documents...
It seems he had been planning
his escape for a long time.
- When did he escape?
- Just after your daughter's visit.
If you have any idea where
he's heading, you should tell us.
We have no idea.
- Does he have any foreign contacts?
- Yes, he's an ex-serviceman.
He was stationed several places abroad.
So it's a possibility.
And did he tell you anything?
If my daughter knew anything,
she'd let you know.
You must understand
we are shaken up by this.
Right... Here's my card, in case
he contacts you. He is dangerous.
Thank you.
We got the message.
Do you want me to give you a hand?
Something's amiss.
He said he'd resume treatment.
Whatever he's done,
it must be for a reason.
He would have told me.
I know he wouldn't just run off.
Mummy...
Why aren't you asleep, Jonas?
Come along, darling.
Excuse me.
Could you give me a lift?
Go ahead, jump in.
Don't forget your seatbelt.
- I just need to cross the bridge.
- I'm not going across it.
- Can I drive with you anyway?
- I suggest you find someone else.
Are you crossing the bridge?
Can I ride with you? I'll behave.
Newly appointed
Minister of Justice, Thomas Buch
failed to get broad agreement
on the terrorism package.
The Opposition accuses
the Government of withholding facts
about the two murders,
believed to be acts of terrorism.
In a secret memo, Special Branch
warned the Ministry of Justice
that the killings
could be acts of terrorism.
I know nothing of that memo!
The Government did nothing.
Yes. I'll call the Prime Minister,
when I know more. Bye.
- Krabbe, People's Party
- First, I must talk to Plough.
- Where the hell is he?
- He's not answering his phones.
I'm sure
Plough can explain everything.
Yes, but where is he?
Shall I institute a search?
I apologise for the delay.
Shall we?
I asked our legal staff to assess
whether Agger's statement
is a breach of the Official Secrets Act.
- But is it true, what she says?
- Nobody knows what went wrong.
Is it true? I'm asking you!
Yes. There was a memo.
And, yes, it warned about terrorism.
Nobody can explain
how she got hold of it.
I don't give a shit how she got it!
But why haven't I got it?
- If you'll allow me to...
- I want to see that memo, right now!
The memo was sent directly to me.
I presented it to your predecessor.
It sums up the Memorial Park killing.
Special Branch were concerned
because of the location
and the victim's past.
- Is terrorism mentioned?
- Yes.
- Should I not have been informed?
- Yes, in hindsight.
Your predecessor Monberg and I
removed the memo from the file.
We couldn't risk it getting around.
Monberg said the information
could compromise national security.
- Which information?
- About the victim's past, I suppose.
- You suppose?
- Monberg fell ill after that.
- But I'm certain...
- So you don't know!
Monberg was going
to consult Special Branch.
He knew what he was doing.
He was a very conscientious Minister.
We must find that information.
Arrange a meeting
with König, Special Branch.
Will do. But the Prime Minister
wants to see you right away.
- Why didn't you act upon the memo?
- It was removed from the file.
- Removed? Why?
- That was before Monberg fell ill.
- It compromises national security.
- How?
I hoped you could help me
answer that question.
- Did Monberg ever tell...?
- I can assure you he didn't.
- If he had, it hadn't gone so far.
- Of course not.
Agger wants to smear us.
Put a lid on it. Focus on the package.
Do you have a hold
on the People's Party
- I wouldn't say that.
- They're biding their time.
You must repudiate
Agger's accusations.
Right. Monberg hasn't
regained consciousness.
So I am waiting for a report
from Special Branch.
This has shocked us all. We should
join forces instead of arguing.
It will only get worse
if the case isn't solved.
- It will be. I'll see to it.
- I'm counting on it.
You've been given a raw deal.
My door is open
if you need anything.
- Excuse me.
- I'll find my way out.
Agger is going to be
even more troublesome.
They want a consultation tomorrow.
They want answers
regarding the memo
but they hope you have none,
and will fry you in front of the press.
- I don't have any answers.
- You'll find some.
Find out why Monberg feared
for our national security
and get this business
out of the way. Understood?
Hello, darling. Yes!
Are the girls asleep?
I'm sorry I didn't
get to say goodnight.
Something came up...
Raben denied knowing the first victim.
But we found this.
Team Ægir consisted of 500 troops
stationed in Afghanistan.
Jens Peter Raben, Allan Myg Poulsen
and Anne Dragsholm.
I don't see any connection
to the Muslim League.
The killer got hold of the list
of all Team Ægir's members.
So we must get hold of Raben.
He knows what all this is about.
Special Branch found
a printout of the team list.
They've arrested three suspects
connected to Kodmani's organisation.
When searching
the organisation's premises
they found a key
to a PO box in Vesterbro.
It's registered in Kodmani's name.
The contents speak for itself.
- Lennart.
- Shall we get started?
You sympathise with the Taliban's war
against the international forces.
The Afghan people
have the right to defend themselves.
Is it OK
to kill Danish soldiers?
What can you expect?
You're at war. You kill too!
Is that why you collect dog tags?
- I have an alibi.
- This was in your PO box.
Also, we found a list of Team Ægir.
Among them are the two victims.
You registered the PO box
about a month ago.
It's not ours.
I've never seen it before.
The dog tags were made with tools
found at the crime scenes.
- They don't belong to us.
- They were in your box.
- Why?
- Why did you get that box?
Look at these photos.
Did you order this?
- I didn't give any orders.
- Look at the pictures!
Faith Fellow told me
to set up a PO box.
Bullshit! You were preaching
to the young members about injustice.
- Why have a PO box?
- You let others do your dirty work.
- In which language did he write?
- You must come clean.
Did he write in English?
Shut up, for the moment!
What did Faith Fellow write?
What about Raben?
Did he mention someone in Team Ægir
by the name of Jens Peter Raben?
- I'm not saying any more.
- Tell me something, damn it!
Who is Faith Fellow?
What do you know?
He and the three others
remain in custody.
- We'll keep at it.
- Yes.
Lund has been hired as a consultant.
She was formerly...
Thank you. I know about Lund.
She was with the border police
for a couple of years. Lennart,
I won't interfere
with your investigation, but damn...
She was thrown out,
and for many good reasons.
I'm sure she was accomplished,
but what we saw today
was extremely incompetent.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my intention to...
- I want a word with Lund.
- Right.
I would like to say
that I support Lund.
I can't see how the evidence
could have been planted.
But we'd never have got so far,
if it hadn't been for Lund.
If she feels so strongly about Raben,
it may be worth checking.
Right. OK. Thanks.
Apart for his wife and son,
hardly anyone visited Raben.
- No friends?
- Myg Poulsen and his lawyer.
Someone from Team Ægir
can tell us about him and the victims.
The list has over 500 names.
We could start at the barracks tomorrow.
- I'll follow up on Raben.
- I'll look at Team Ægir.
And thank you for...
Don't mention it.
You would have continued,
no matter what.
- Is that a problem?
- No, on the contrary.
Strange? Someone is waiting for you.
I'm coming.
- See you tomorrow.
- Right.
Call me if something turns up.
Lund. I was to give you this.
Raben was seen at a filling station
south of Copenhagen, on their CCTV.
He was trying to get a lift
heading west.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
The church is closed.
Come back tomorrow.
Hey! I said it's closed.
Hi, Priest.
Long time no see.
- Does any of it fit?
- Yes. It's fine.
This is all I could find.
Apart from hosts.
The altar wine is quite good.
What are you going to do?
- Have you been home, ever since?
- Yes.
I found a nice little parish here.
It suits me perfectly.
- Are you seeing any of the old team?
- No.
But I heard about Myg.
I don't know what you are up to.
But be careful.
Use your head.
Think of your wife and son.
I need your help, Priest.
There is someone I need to talk to.
It's important.
I don't know who else to ask.
Will you help me?
THURSDAY, 17 NOVEMBER
8:45AM
DAY 4
Raben appears to have crossed
the bridge. We're checking his contacts.
The three suspects are in custody.
I have search warrants for several
members of Kodmani's organisation.
Right. And what about Team Ægir?
I was on a date last night.
It got rather late.
Hold this for a moment.
Team Ægir was in active service abroad,
two and a half years ago.
Raben and Myg Poulsen
were together
but I don't know about Dragsholm.
- Is that all?
- Do you have a painkiller?
No! I haven't got any painkillers.
There's no reason to be jealous.
She's just an old friend.
- I couldn't care less!
- OK! What did you find on Raben?
Raben is 37. He's been in the army
most of his adult life.
His rank is staff sergeant. Trained
at the sergeant school in Sønderborg.
He was stationed abroad
with the armoured infantry.
- The last time with Team Ægir.
- OK.
He was decorated several times,
but was wounded and sent home.
He was getting better, but something
snapped. You know the rest.
However, he is married to Louise Raben,
and they have a son.
- Why is that important?
- Louise's father is Colonel Jarnvig.
Jens Peter Raben is his son-in-law.
OK. It's a small world.
The colonel was with Team Ægir.
He was battalion commander.
But he denied knowing
Anne Dragsholm.
Why didn't you tell me before?
You were busy being jealous.
Shall we drive on?
- You claim you never met her.
- I never did!
She's on a photo and a list of Team Ægir.
And you were their commander.
The picture was taken at Oksbøl,
before deployment.
Maybe she was there to teach
the soldiers about the law of war.
I can assure you
she was not on Team Ægir.
You can't remember all 500 of them.
Check with the Army
Operational Command.
I know my advisors.
She was never one of them.
I trust that will be all...
I'd like to hear about
your son-in-law, Jens Peter Raben.
- Why?
- He was wounded and demobbed.
What actually happened?
- What do those questions lead to?
- We found some coincidences...
Who cares about your coincidences?
Two soldiers were killed.
My men and their families are worried,
and you ask about Raben!
Do your work, and we'll do ours.
OK, thank you. Bye.
Army Operative Command confirms
that Dragsholm was only
at Oksbøl for a legal seminar.
- She was on the team list.
- They say she opted out.
If she knew Raben and Myg at all,
they weren't close.
- Any news about Raben?
- No. We must follow up on Kodmani.
The searches paid off.
We'll have to book them all.
Strange speaking.
- Just go. I'll follow later.
- Now what? Where are you going?
All right. We're on our way.
At least one of us is. Bye.
It's a network
connected to Ahl Al-Kahf
founded by Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
We've arrested three more suspects.
There are more to come.
- So the case is almost solved?
- Yes. The evidence is incriminating.
We have caught the culprits.
We'll inform the public today.
How could Agger know the contents
of a memo from Special Branch?
She doesn't have it from us.
It's important to know
the course of events.
What did my predecessor know?
What action was taken? And why?
We were investigating
the Memorial Park killing.
The victim had been in the army,
so we sent the Minister a memo.
- And you didn't pass it on to me?
- You hadn't been briefed.
And we weren't alone in the room.
How did my predecessor
react to your memo?
Isn't he the best person
to answer that?
I'm facing a consultation later
to clear things up.
I'm sure my predecessor would
appreciate it if you help us along.
Yes, of course.
The Minister was very concerned.
Why didn't Special Branch
inform the police?
For a very good reason.
Special Branch was looking for terrorism.
But why was the police
kept in the dark for two weeks?
- You knew it was terrorism.
- We weren't sure.
The Minister deemed it too risky
to inform the police.
He thought certain information would
compromise the nation's security.
- What information would that be?
- I'd like to know that too.
It's usually my business to know.
He would get back to me with
an explanation, but he didn't make it.
- So you don't know?
- Unfortunately not.
- Two files. The rest were shredded.
- It must be there, somewhere.
Agger's got a point. We didn't take
the threat of terrorism seriously.
I was Monberg's
Permanent Secretary for nine years.
- He never took a wrong step.
- He omitted to inform about this.
He must have had his reasons.
Buch, you're damaging the walls!
I've found something.
I went through the files.
Monberg requisitioned
information about Anne Dragsholm.
- What sort of information?
- From the Ministry of Defense.
It was requisitioned and returned.
They should be able to retrieve it.
I don't understand. The Minister
can't do that without my knowledge.
Maybe you went to the loo, Plough!
We are busy. What can you do?
I'll contact the Permanent Secretary.
Karina, get the Minister ready.
- Run through the questions.
- Hurry up, damn it!
- Grüner...
- Hi, Priest. Where's the choir?
- The choir isn't coming, after all.
- Why not?
I brought my music.
Someone is here to see you.
The work is all right.
Not very interesting.
I'm still a bit choosy.
- How's Marie?
- Fine. We're doing all right.
- And the baby?
- Not a baby any more.
He is everything to me, man.
She wants to have a wheelchair
when she grows up, just like Daddy.
And I'm playing music again.
- When did they let you out?
- They didn't.
I didn't exactly walk out the door.
Have you spoken to anyone lately?
- Did Myg look you up?
- Why did you escape?
Because he's dead.
So is that lawyer woman.
Don't you watch the news?
Yes. But we don't exchange
Christmas cards.
- What is going on?
- I don't know anything.
Myg and the lawyer woman are dead.
Maybe it's the will of God.
Myg visited me
the day he was killed.
I know nothing!
Don't stir up that old shit.
- What are you on about?
- Let me go, damn it!
- I don't know shit!
- You know something.
Come here.
Let me go!
See you, Raben.
And good luck to you.
Grüner! If you want to talk
to me, call Priest. OK?
- I must get hold of the others.
- I don't know where they are.
You have connections.
You can find their whereabouts.
- Can I borrow your mobile?
- What for?
- I must tell Louise why I escaped.
- I don't understand it.
Be careful.
PRISONER ESCAPED
I told the police what I know.
Can't you leave me alone?
This woman is Anne Dragsholm.
Your husband knew her.
I don't know who she is.
- Did he seem worried or concerned?
- His mate had just been killed.
He had been turned down
by the Probation Service.
Do you think
that's why he escaped?
How long have you been married?
We met 14 years ago
and got married four years ago. Why?
How did you meet?
I visited my dad at the barracks.
Jens gave me a lift into town.
- He had just started here.
- And then you got together?
No. He wanted to travel the world
and make a difference.
I didn't want to be a soldier's girlfriend.
So it wasn't to be.
He decided
it was for the last time.
What happened?
They were ambushed
and cut off from the rest.
He was flown to a field hospital
until he could be transferred
to a hospital back home.
Several weeks passed
before they knew if he'd survive.
Do you have any idea
why he escaped?
No.
Do you know where he is?
Did he leave a message?
- I have to collect my son.
- Yes, of course.
If he contacts you,
you must call me.
- The border police at Gedser?
- My number is on the back.
That woman on the picture...
I think she visited Jens
in the hospital.
But she had a different surname.
Many people came to question him,
and I think she was among them.
- Lund here.
- I tried to call you.
Kodmani sent an email inciting
continuation of the war on Danish soil.
We've arrested everyone
connected to his organisation.
Anne Dragsholm
visited Raben in the hospital.
Louise Raben recognised her.
Dragsholm questioned Raben
about what happened in Afghanistan.
OK. Why would she question him?
You'll have to ask someone
in the army.
- I've talked enough with the army.
- Try again. Go there.
What was Dragsholm doing in the army
while Raben was in hospital?
- What will you do?
- I'll ask her husband.
Bad idea. He's suing for wrongful arrest.
And her funeral is today
Strange?
Special Branch wants a press conference
about the arrests.
If you uncover something new,
please let me know ASAP.
Lund, listen to me. Lund?
Louise...
- Do you want a lift?
- Yes!
I just took someone to the station,
so it's very convenient.
- This is Grüner.
- What's up?
That lawyer woman contacted me,
a few weeks before she was killed.
- What about, Grüner?
- Can we meet?
Hello. Sarah Lund, police detective.
May I offer my condolences?
I'm afraid I have
to ask you some questions.
I wouldn't bother you today
if it wasn't important.
I fear that others will suffer
the same fate as your wife...
Why did you confess?
In the end, I didn't care what you believed.
It was easier to confess.
It was more important
that she knew it wasn't me.
- Did she speak of her army work?
- Not much.
- Did she ever mention Myg Poulsen?
- No. I've already been asked that.
- What about Jens Peter Raben?
- No.
Did she quit the army
because you met?
No. We knew each other
years before we got married.
I wanted her to find another job,
but she liked the army.
- Why did she resign?
- She was fired. So it seemed to her.
Fired? Why?
There was a conflict.
About an incident
with some soldiers in Afghanistan.
- What incident?
- That's all I know.
I must get home and see to my guests.
But the army got her
to investigate that incident.
That was part of the problem.
She did it on her own initiative.
The army didn't seem to take
the team's account seriously.
The team of soldiers.
She conducted their case.
- So she was their lawyer?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- All right.
I asked around at Defense Command.
They'll look into it.
No need for that now.
Do you have the list of Team Ægir?
We must get hold of someone
from Raben's group.
The Opposition claims
the memo was not taken seriously.
That is incorrect. Special Branch
was investigating the case
and was keeping the groups
involved under surveillance.
Terrific! But why did your
predecessor withhold information
to the fact
that it was a terror threat.
This was out of consideration
to national security.
- I wish to hear more about that.
- This meeting was at short notice.
Patience is a virtue
that would suit Ms. Agger.
I'm expecting Karina
to bring the documents.
Is it correct that members
of Ahl Al-Kahf have been arrested?
That is correct, but...
That is one of the organisations
the People's Party want to ban.
If your predecessor thought
it was an act of terror
why did the police spend ten days
questioning the victim's husband?
Because Special Branch
focused on the terror lead.
Surely, the police were informed about
Special Branch's terrorism theory?
No, the police were not informed.
- Who was responsible for that?
- Special Branch was on the case.
So your predecessor decided
to keep the police in the dark
thus jeopardising
the entire investigation.
My predecessor cannot answer,
but I've told the committee everything.
Yes, about national security.
But what does that cover here?
The People's Party
has not been informed about this.
If there is no further explanation,
we will have to conclude
that the Ministry of Justice
has withheld information
thus misleading our Parliament.
The Minister seems confused.
He must be informed
of the rules of these consultations.
Although he probably won't need
to know for much longer!
I apologise for the interruption.
Where were we?
The Government's responsibility
for this tragedy.
The Special Branch memo
was classified information.
Publishing it would cause discord
when we should stand united.
The Government has caused mistrust.
We demand a thorough investigation.
You shall have one. But first,
you should see this document
about the risk involved
in publicising what the victim knew.
An open investigation
could reveal information
which would compromise
our military strategy in Afghanistan
thus endangering
the lives of Danish soldiers.
- We will have to look into this.
- It is classified information.
It must be treated
with absolute confidentiality.
Obviously, it is not
to be released to the press.
So unless others doubt
my predecessor's motive
I will withdraw and resume my duties.
Thank you.
- Damn, we were good!
- You wrapped it up neatly.
- Thanks to you. Did we go too far?
- No! She asked for it!
We just need to find out
how she got hold of the memo.
- It's the Prime Minister.
- Send out a press release.
Hi, Thomas. Congratulations.
I hear it went quite well.
Thanks.
My staff prepared me well.
Now you can concentrate
on the terrorism package.
- I'll talk to the People's Party.
- Good luck.
Come in. Have a drink.
Krabbe will try to force you
to ban that organisation.
- They know who they're up against!
- Karina, come and have a drink.
Send some bottles
to the Ministry of Defense.
I was collecting Monberg's private
documents and came across this.
- Just send him everything.
- Cheers! Thanks for your help.
Plough, Monberg had a private diary
I didn't know about.
Evidently,
he knew Anne Dragsholm personally.
I don't get it, but at least twice
he has had a meeting with her.
It has been confirmed
as her mobile number.
Their last meeting was in a hotel,
the weekend before the killing.
- Check it out.
- Right.
- Are we having dinner soon?
- In a moment, darling.
I'm chopping off the dragon's head,
but he has acid for blood.
Good. You must be hungry.
How would you like
to have your own room?
Granddad says you can have his.
We could make it really cosy
with all your toys.
Shall we do that?
And I've found a school for you,
which we should go and see.
- Am I starting school this summer?
- Yes, that's right.
Hello?
Isn't Daddy going to have
his own room?
Yes, but...
We'll see about that.
It's dinner time.
- May I draw?
- Of course.
- Our guards found Jonas' mitten.
- Oh? Thanks.
You must have dropped it on the way.
Lucky, it had his name tag.
There was no name tag.
And we drove in Søgaard's car.
Well, anyway,
it was found by the gate.
How are things, Jonas?
Grüner?
- Was Dragsholm the team's lawyer?
- Yes. We need to confirm that.
But that was several years ago.
- What was his name?
- David Grüner.
- He's on the evening shift.
- Are you sure it's here?
Yes. Go inside. I'll drive round
and look for a main entrance.
Hey!