Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
The Muslim League will avenge
the suffering Denmark has caused...
Brix thinks
you can give us a new angle.
Kodmani must be questioned again.
Raben knew both victims.
He lied. And now he's escaped.
- We must send out a search party.
- Why him?
I respect your methods, but they
have been known to lead to disaster.
The Government has put a lot of work
into the terrorism package.
We need you to head the negotiations.
Will you be Minister of Justice?
The link was activated at 5:03pm.
At sunset, the end of Ramadan.
The woman who was killed
had also been in the army.
Buch failed to get broad agreement
on the terrorism package.
- There was a secret memo.
- Is what she says true?
Yes. The memo warned against
terrorism, after the first killing.
Monberg and I removed the memo.
I knew nothing of that memo.
It was removed from the file.
Why was Monberg concerned
about national security?
- The Probation Service turned you down.
- Why?
- Why can't I see him?
- He refuses to take his medication.
He wouldn't escape
unless he had a good reason.
Hi, Priest!
I need to talk to certain people.
- Myg and Dragsholm are dead.
- Myg came to visit me.
- Why set up a post office box?
- Faith Fellow told me to.
In which language?
Shut up, for a second!
- Lund is...
- I know all about Lund.
She got kicked out
for several good reasons.
That interview was conducted
in the worst possible manner.
Monberg requested documents
concerning Anne Dragsholm.
Why did Monberg withhold
information about a terrorism alert?
It could compromise
military strategy in Afghanistan
thus endangering Danish soldiers.
Frode had another diary.
He knew Anne Dragsholm personally.
Anne felt the army didn't take
the squad's statement seriously.
- Which squad?
- She conducted a case for them.
Dragsholm contacted me
a few weeks before she was killed.
Do you have the list of Team Ægir?
We must find Raben's squad.
THE KILLING
THURSDAY, 17 NOVEMBER
6:34PM
- Can't you stop that?
- We're working on it.
He was attacked in his car and
wheeled down here in his wheelchair.
We saw the smoke,
but couldn't get in.
- And the sprinklers?
- They were turned off.
The CCTV had been switched off
shortly before 5:00pm.
Petrol had been poured
all over and around the victim.
The fire was ignited
with a call from a mobile phone.
The victim was tied up
and the wheelchair was chained.
He sat there
watching the mobile phone
while he waited
for all hell to break loose.
- What do we know about him?
- David Grüner, 28-year-old veteran.
He has worked here
as a security guard for a year.
His legs were shot to bits
in Afghanistan. Raben's squad.
- Perhaps he was burnt alive.
- Is that a car tyre?
- Yes.
- I need to make a call.
- And no dog tag?
- Yes, it was dangling in his car.
It looks like the same perpetrator.
If only we'd been briefed in time.
We didn't know what to expect.
Lund didn't know either.
We drove out here, and suddenly...
I should have known.
I should have...
I should have done something.
If only we'd come half an hour earlier.
Just 15 minutes.
- Lund?
- I'm all right.
The car tyre round the neck is used
on informers in South Africa
and American
security personnel in Iraq.
- I hear there were witnesses.
- Raben. Whatever he was doing here.
It seems to be the same perpetrator
as in the previous killings.
- Sarah Lund uncovered all this?
- Yes.
They didn't inform us
in time for the press conference.
- That would have been preferable.
- Kodmani could still be involved.
I am going to take Lund
off the case for a few days.
Why?
I know what I said yesterday.
But there are two good reasons
to keep her on it.
I'd like to know what she thinks of
this Faith Fellow Kodmani mentioned.
We must take
a broader view of the case.
And what's the second reason?
Kodmani has agreed to being
questioned, on one condition.
- Meet Bjørn before the wedding.
- This is not a good time.
Coffee this evening?
We could drop by.
- Any news about Raben?
- No, he's gone.
- And the others from his squad?
- The search is on.
- Lund!
- Coffee tonight, then.
- I'll buy some cake. Call you later.
- Good. See you.
Remember: no nuts in the cake!
Bjørn is allergic to nuts.
Kodmani will talk.
But only if you do the questioning.
But you couldn't see,
if he was the victim.
- It was him.
- Maybe he just...
Priest!
He is dead, dammit! Face it!
He had a wife and a child.
- Did you find the others?
- There is only one more left.
- Thomsen.
- What about HC?
HC died in a car accident last year.
Thomsen no longer lives
at her address in Copenhagen.
It's locked. It's your wife.
She said you gave her a sign.
I said I didn't know where you were,
but she insisted on staying.
Jonas, do as she says. Go to bed.
Sleep tight, darling.
- Who knows you're here?
- Nobody.
I told the babysitter
I was visiting a friend.
- Are you sure nobody followed you?
- Why did you escape?
Myg and Grüner have been killed.
I don't know why.
They knew something.
They were scared.
What are you talking about?
Something happened in Afghanistan.
I never told you. I can't quite remember it.
I thought it was over.
And that it was all in my mind.
But maybe I was quite sane.
If I don't find out, I'm going to rot
in that mental institution.
What haven't you told me?
Jens, turn yourself in.
We'll explain it somehow,
so that it won't ruin everything.
- No. I can't turn myself in.
- Why not?
We've waited for two years!
We've talked to doctors and lawyers.
- You're ruining our chances...
- What do you expect?
Should I wait ten years,
let my son forget me
and let you run off with Søgaard?
I'm sorry.
I'll sort it all out.
I know what I'm doing. OK?
I need your help to find Thomsen.
Look in the files at the barracks.
I must talk to her.
She is the last one of our squad.
Take this. It's safe.
I'll call you tomorrow morning.
I must leave now.
They will look for me here.
Kiss Jonas for me.
The war in Afghanistan has failed.
Terrorism is the consequence of it.
You are shamelessly exploiting
a national crisis.
You would abolish the rule of law,
freedom of speech and human rights.
We support the Government,
but the terrorism package is too lenient.
The Government
has brought this country to a crisis.
The Government should not lose
its head, like those present.
The terrorism package
is crafted out of necessity.
Personal intrigue must not prevent us
from solving the problems.
The Ministry of Justice
is trying to withhold information.
But the Minister of Justice explained
about the memo from Special Branch.
We are not sure what part
the Ministry of Justice plays in this.
Buch's predecessor withheld
information about the first killing.
We have explained...
Notwithstanding security measures,
it seems stupid not to tell anybody.
So it seems you're on your own
with the People's Party.
- We still want a broad agreement.
- And failing that?
Everyone knows what I think
of the People's Party's proposal.
- We are sure you will see reason.
- And thus we end the debate.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for coming.
That went well. Shall we meet up
tomorrow morning?
- We are on to something.
- I just want it resolved.
I'll show up. Or do you want
to think things over?
What's up?
Monberg and Dragsholm
didn't know each other personally.
Special Branch knows nothing of it
and König was surprised to hear it.
We know they met at a hotel
the weekend before she was killed.
That weekend Monberg spoke
at a seminar on human rights.
It was arranged by Amnesty
and Dragsholm was on the board.
- Did they stay the night?
- The Minister did, alone.
- I left the hotel in the afternoon.
- Did you know of their meeting?
They weren't having an affair.
I would have noticed.
What is Plough doing here?
They found him
in a multi-storey car park.
It seems to be the same killer
who committed the two previous killings.
Special Branch is not sure
they've got the right man.
The Prime Minister wants a meeting
with you and the Minister of Defense.
How was Monberg
connected to the first victim?
We must find out if Monberg withheld
information for personal reasons.
Recent events
force me to tell you something.
In the past few months,
Monberg cancelled certain meetings.
- He always had a plausible excuse.
- Get to the point, Plough.
He wasn't always
where he said he'd be.
I sensed he was seeing someone
probably without
his family's knowledge.
- Having a bit on the side?
- By the looks of it...
Do you think it was Dragsholm?
The days he cancelled meetings,
he stayed at Hotel Hammershøj.
We know he met Dragsholm there.
Special Branch knows nothing of it.
And if an affair was relevant to
the investigation, he would have told us.
Don't mention it at the meeting.
We need to know more.
The Minister of Defense
is close to Monberg
so we can't just blurt it out.
Good evening. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Please sit down.
My colleague here will join us.
Sit down.
You wanted to tell me something.
I want to tell you all I know
about the Faith Fellow.
But the members of my organisation
who you arrested have no part in it.
We won't cut any deals.
Who we arrest is our concern.
I know I am going to pay
for my mistake.
- Just make sure others don't.
- What mistake is that?
My first contact with Faith Fellow
was on one of my websites.
- That was almost two months ago.
- We didn't find anything.
I didn't suspect anything, but now
I can see he played me like a fiddle.
My faith, my political views,
my hatred...
Don't give us the story of your life.
I was certain I could trust him.
He wrote convincingly.
He asked me to set up
a PO box for his donations.
He also asked me how to upload
a video on my website.
- Did he ask you to kill too?
- No.
There was none of that.
My only crime is that
it made me feel good, at first.
For once, your lot were being punished.
I felt vindicated.
Until you showed me the photos.
Until I understood
that we were going to pay for it.
- How do you mean?
- You only see what you want to see.
The killers aren't fundamentalists,
but people who hate us.
- Who are they?
- That's for you to find out.
In which language
did Faith Fellow write?
- English with some Arabic.
- Was he an Arab?
No. That was to please me.
His sentences
seemed out of context.
Did Faith Fellow write about
an army squad, or Anne Dragsholm?
- You must know more...
- The words he chose...
He was very precise and brief.
I'm convinced
Faith Fellow is a military man.
Or used to be.
Kodmani isn't in the clear yet.
But what do we know
about Faith Fellow?
He is probably the man
behind the Muslim League.
- The video, army lists, dog tags.
- I agree.
Now, we must focus on Raben's
squad and look for a motive.
What motive is there
if Kodmani didn't do it?
What do you know
about the squad?
They are all decorated.
The squad was called 3-2-AIpha.
It consisted of eight persons.
Raben was squad leader since 2001.
The squad was often stationed abroad
and did well in Afghanistan.
But on their last mission, the squad
lost three men and was disbanded.
- What about the rest of the squad?
- There are only two left.
Jens Peter Raben, on the run. Lisbeth
Thomsen, whereabouts unknown.
The first victim was not part
of the squad, only connected to it.
Yes. Anne Dragsholm represented
the squad at an inquiry.
Concerning what?
The last mission.
The local civilians accused them
of breaching the Geneva Convention.
Meaning?
Alleged killings of civilians.
Dragsholm and the judge advocate's
report cleared the squad.
According to Dragsholm's husband
there was some disagreement.
- That's why the army fired her.
- She may have borne a grudge.
But the fact is, she resigned.
This is Dragsholm's resignation.
- Do you have a minute?
- Yes.
Kodmani talked of a military man.
Maybe he was in Afghanistan
at the time.
We might find someone who was
involved and is now seeking revenge.
What is a judge advocate's report?
Judge advocates may prosecute,
but in this case they didn't.
Right. I want that report
sent to my address ASAP.
We must find Lisbeth Thomsen
before it's too late. Call me.
Thanks. Do you know
any bakeries that are open now?
I'll call you.
What's up?
I see you decided
to keep Lund on the case.
- Is that a problem?
- No.
But it may be unwise if you have
a future career to consider.
My future is hardly
to be discussed with König?
We were talking about the Minister
of Justice being under pressure.
Ruth, what is going on?
I don't like being kept in the dark.
If you or König know something...
You'll be informed in due course.
You have enough on your plate.
Including Lund.
She is your responsibility.
Agreed?
We weren't talking
about anything important.
Shall we meet up later?
Good.
I'll be counting on it. Bye.
This evening,
another terrorism victim was found.
28-year-old David Grüner served
at Ryvangen army barracks.
His body was found
in a multi-storey car park.
Like the two previous victims,
he was subjected to ruthless violence.
The police and Special Branch
have arrested some suspects
but there is no conclusive
breakthrough in the investigation.
- Buch... Nice to see you.
- Thank you. Likewise.
- Am I late for something?
- We were just catching up.
- Are you holding your own?
- I'm coping. It's crazy.
It'll all work out.
You did quite well.
Monberg would've been pleased
to know you've taken over from him.
Right, let's get started.
It doesn't look too good, but police
and Special Branch are on it.
- But it may take some time.
- I'm afraid so.
The terrorists have chosen
a most inconvenient time.
It is imperative that we reach
agreement on the terrorism package.
And, Gert, we can't wait for Agger
and the Opposition to see reason.
We'll agree with the People's Party
and ban certain organisations.
The investigation doesn't point
to any of those organisations.
We can't be sure. To ban them
because of this case would be wrong.
I understand your concern.
Had this been peace-time
I would have shared your opinion.
I agree with the Minister of Defense.
We must send a clear signal.
Not on that basis!
Other things
are blurring the picture.
Monberg may have known the first victim,
Anne Dragsholm, personally.
He never told anybody.
How did he know her?
What does Special Branch say?
They are not aware
of the connection.
- Are we talking about rumours?
- Somehow, things don't add up.
If Special Branch doesn't see
any connection, why worry?
Thomas, do you know something?
No, I don't know anything.
Let Special Branch do their work,
and let us focus on ours.
It may seem rash to accuse
this particular organisation.
But these Islamic organisations
have made statements
that are reprehensible and hostile.
We must take action.
So I want you to agree
to Krabbe's demands
and seal up the terrorism package
with the People's party ASAP.
Our next deployment
faces difficulties.
We have informed about security
and procedures abroad.
But the risk of being in danger
when they return
will make some soldiers opt out.
Any solutions?
We've invited the soldiers
and their relatives to a meeting.
- Bilal will talk to them tomorrow.
- Grüner's death makes it harder.
Explain to them that this is a temporary
and untypical situation.
It's high time
we got this thing sorted out.
One more thing.
Grüner was in 3-2-AIpha,
and so was Myg Poulsen.
The first victim, the legal advisor,
was connected to the squad.
- This must cause some speculation.
- We have nothing to hide.
Give the investigators
any files they want.
Of course.
And then there is Raben.
His escape may be relevant.
- He was squad leader...
- Why bring that up now?
Raben will seek out
his military contacts.
- We'll arrest him on sight!
- It's a matter of security.
If you're worried
about my daughter's loyalty, Bilal,
you're barking up the wrong tree.
Understood?
Søgaard, come with me to Grüner's wife,
to pay our respects.
I'd like an agenda for the meeting
with soldiers and relatives.
- Do you have a moment?
- Later.
I'll see to it that my furniture
is cleared out by tomorrow.
I heard about Grüner.
He was in Jens' squad.
What's going on?
I don't know, but Jens
was spotted at the crime scene.
I expect the police will be
keeping an eye on you and Jonas.
Louise...
...if Jens contacts you,
it's important you let me know.
Will you agree to that?
Yes.
Good. When will the forensic reports
be ready?
Right.
- Thanks. Sorry. I'm all yours now.
- Take a look at this.
We'll have a traditional
horseshoe table setting.
Nothing else is traditional
about our wedding!
- These cakes are good.
- You'll be seated there.
Can't I sit next to Mark?
Bjørn's cousin is on his own,
because his wife is ill.
- You are welcome to invite a companion.
- No.
- Don't you have a fella?
- No. Sarah is taking a break.
I was taking a break too.
But then I thought better of it!
- Do you know how we met?
- Let me just answer this. Yes?
That's all right. Just get them to me
as soon as possible. Excellent.
Thanks. Bye.
So where did you meet?
It was a second-hand shop.
- Where you find well used things.
- Of good quality.
Known brands.
I was looking for a coat.
That's for me.
We should have talked
when she was still working in Gedser.
- Are you all right?
- Sure.
Hi. This is the judge advocate's
report and a file on Thomsen.
Any progress with Thomsen?
She has sublet her flat and comes
every three months for mail and rent.
- That's all, at present.
- Why can't we find her?
I suppose she's trying hard
not to be found.
We have to leave now.
Bjørn is feeling unwell.
Are you sure there were
no nuts in the cakes?
- Yes...
- Gluten also does that to me.
- And you are...?
- Ulrik Strange. A colleague.
Vibeke. Sarah's mother.
Nice to meet you.
We must dash. He really
doesn't feel well. We'll call you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
I've asked Colonel Jarnvig to come in
and explain about the report.
- Still no news about Raben?
- No.
- OK. See you tomorrow.
- Unless you invite me in for cake.
- See you tomorrow.
- Right.
The police have intensified
the search for the escaped inmate.
Jens Peter Raben, aged 37,
height 190cm, dark brown hair.
He is presumed dangerous.
Hello?
- It's me. Where are you?
- I just left the nursery.
- Are you being followed?
- I don't think so.
I have to be back in half an hour.
Did you find anything?
I brought you some documents.
- Did you check her file?
- Yes.
There's only her Copenhagen address.
- Thomsen is from Hirtshals.
- There is nothing about Hirtshals.
What about next of kin?
She had an uncle.
In Sweden. Some island.
- She went there on leave.
- Yes... It's noted here.
But the uncle is dead.
That's all there is.
I'm here.
Where are you?
Stay put.
They're watching you.
I don't want you mixed up in this.
Thanks for helping me, love.
- I'll call you, whenever I can.
- Jens...
I love you.
But I can't take any more of this.
I'm not moving from the barracks.
They'll keep me on at the infirmary.
I have to think of Jonas.
He needs me.
- Louise...
- I have to leave now.
Wait.
Take care.
The judge advocate's report
mentions civilian casualties.
We often get that allegation
after engaging in combat.
The enemy wants
to cause aggravation.
- It's the nature of war rhetoric.
- It could still be true.
The Taliban
often hide among civilians.
There was a thorough investigation
which cleared the squad.
So you don't believe
the allegations?
- No. They were groundless.
- But in the report...
I came to help,
not to be made accountable.
We lost three men on that mission,
all of whom were from my barracks.
I believe that's in the report too.
Would anyone want to take revenge
for the accusations?
Possibly.
It damaged our reputation.
We tried to make amends.
But someone might still bear a grudge.
Do you know if any soldiers here
are connected to Afghanistan?
No. Not to my knowledge.
Do you think a Danish soldier
is killing off the squad, one by one?
That's an insane idea!
Thank you. That will be all.
- What?
- Lisbeth Thomsen lives on Skogö.
She's staying in her late uncle's house.
The local police have got her.
- When can we be on Skogö?
- In a couple of hours, if I drive.
Lisbeth Thomsen volunteered
for national service.
- I take it you didn't?
- No way!
I feigned a bad back
but ended up in a field in full kit.
How did you like it?
Actually, I stayed on for a few years.
The army's all right.
Shouldn't we have turned off?
We have a ferry to catch.
The E6 is quicker.
How do you know?
Do you have a summer house?
I used to have
a Swedish boyfriend.
Mr. Nilsson?
- Why didn't it work out?
- It just didn't.
I was about to move to Sweden,
but then a lot of things happened.
It's hard to imagine you holding hands
in the forests of Sweden.
Has the local police been informed
that Raben may turn up?
Isn't it rather unlikely?
The Prime Minister said to accept
all demands of the People's Party.
- It's far too hasty.
- Write it up!
- You wanted this agreement.
- Not on that basis.
- There are too many loose ends.
- And you were against the ban.
It's not up to me.
It's a political decision.
Those organisations
have an unfortunate image.
And we can't prove that Monberg and
Anne Dragsholm had a thing going on.
So let's do as we are told.
- Am I early?
- Not at all, come in.
Karina. Will you set up
our press conference?
The ban on certain organisations
is included.
Yes. I see you've talked
to the Prime Minister.
- About the press conference...
- One small detail.
"Organisations said to encourage
or incite terror..."
You've had plenty
of time for amendments.
Yes. But it ought to read:
"...incite terror or any other
subversive activities..."
Let's get it sorted out now.
We're back to where I finished
negotiating with Monberg.
- A pity he couldn't finish it.
- Quite.
In spite of his heart condition,
he really put in a lot of effort.
He only cancelled one meeting.
The day the Minister of Integration
was attacked outside her home.
It gave us something to talk about
at our next meeting.
Send me the corrected agreement.
See you at the press conference.
- This letter was returned.
- Thanks.
Monberg cancelled a meeting
on 7 October.
- Did he say where he was going?
- No. Why?
It's one of the days
he checked into that hotel.
- He was going to the doctor.
- Get me the chief of Special Branch.
That day, Special Branch was
watching out for certain ministers.
If Monberg was with Dragsholm
in a hotel
it must be in their report.
Welcome. Lisbeth Thomsen lives
on the other side of the island.
- But she is being picked up.
- Is it safe?
We have a couple of men out there.
But she can look after herself.
- Have you met her?
- Yes. But she keeps to herself.
- What does she do?
- She works in the forest.
Chopping wood. Hunting.
She's very capable.
Let's go to the police station.
Raben will probably contact her.
Right. We're ready for him.
Turn left up ahead.
The Danish police called.
You must come in for questioning.
- Where are you going?
- Do you want me to bring this?
- Have you been briefed?
- Yes.
- Can you explain these events?
- I only know what was on the news.
- Have you received any threats?
- No.
Have you had any recent contact
with Myg, Grüner or Raben?
I haven't seen any of them
for two years.
In addition to members of your squad,
your lawyer was also killed.
Anne Dragsholm.
Has she contacted you?
What happened in August,
two years ago?
We lost three soldiers.
It's in the report.
We want to hear your version.
We have to ask these questions.
It's important for us, and for you.
We were patrolling the area.
After a while,
we were called up on the radio
by another Danish squad,
which was under fire.
They were in an area
near the river.
In the Green Zone
which was controlled by the enemy.
We were going to cross the river.
But the bridges were mined.
The bridge was blown up.
And our armoured vehicle with it.
Bo, sitting across from me,
got the barrel up his throat.
The gun barrel
went upwards and into him.
We were cut off
from the rest of the platoon.
But we were told that help
was on its way, for the wounded.
Raben ordered the rest of his squad
to head for the village
to assist those
who were under fire in there.
Then what?
That was the last time I saw them.
They were found and brought
back to the camp, two days later.
- Why weren't you with them?
- I was to stay with the wounded.
But he died
before the helicopter came.
Didn't your mates tell you
what happened in the village?
Yes, you know what's in the report.
They were ambushed.
Two more died.
Raben and Grüner were wounded.
There were accusations of atrocities
and civilian casualties.
I know nothing about that.
How can you explain such anger?
I'm sick of those accusations.
We lost three men.
The squad was exonerated.
Raben, Myg and the rest
put their lives at stake.
Don't slag them off.
We risk our lives out there,
and then we are reproached.
Sorry. But according to the report
there was no patrol under fire.
- We received a radio message.
- But it seems mysterious...
- Are we done now?
- It's for your own good.
- Why are you in hiding here?
- I'm not!
I enjoy the peace.
At least I did, until you lot came.
- Are we finished?
- No. Please look at these photos.
Perhaps you can help us.
My God...
Bloody hell...
It's Krabbe. What shall I tell him?
I must hear from Special Branch.
- We called a press conference.
- What did König say?
- I haven't spoken to him.
- We have to go now.
- Give me his number.
- There's no need for that.
Dragsholm wasn't having
an affair with Monberg.
I was.
I didn't think it mattered.
The evening of Monberg
and Dragsholm's meeting
I was staying at the same hotel.
Monberg was giving a talk
in the afternoon
and asked me to come that evening
to discuss some work.
I had just ended the affair,
so I feared it was a false pretence.
I met him in the hotel bar
after his meeting with Dragsholm.
He was rather quiet.
But he was drinking too quickly.
I was concerned.
He was carrying a folder.
But it was not for me to see.
And then he let me leave.
- Did you see Dragsholm?
- No. And he didn't mention her.
I knew nothing of their connection.
- But his behaviour changed.
- In what way?
I thought it was due to my ending
the affair. He became introvert.
He avoided me.
Until the eve of his heart attack.
Last Sunday, he wanted me
to help him send something.
I gave him an envelope,
and he put it in the out tray.
That was the last time I saw him.
Now the envelope has been returned.
It contains the folder
from his meeting with Dragsholm.
He wanted to make sure
the envelope and folder came back.
It's a judge advocate's report
on an incident in Afghanistan.
And the CVs of soldiers
of a certain squad.
- The names of some of the victims!
- Why did Dragsholm give him this?
There is a covering note
from Monberg.
"Request re-opening of case"
I realise I must resign.
I'm really sorry.
It's Krabbe again.
What are we to do?
- How was the meeting?
- Five of them cancelled.
Some relatives were upset
about Grüner's death.
Everyone has till 9:00am
tomorrow to think it over.
Tell Søgaard to be here tomorrow
morning. We'll take it from there.
Did you access Lisbeth Thomsen's
file on this computer last night?
- No.
- Do you know if Søgaard did?
- No. I'll ask the security officers.
- That won't be necessary.
- I just meet the security officer.
- I said there was no need.
There is now.
- There's not much furniture.
- There will be.
- Now what?
- That's fine.
Jonas is staying over with a friend.
I must paint his new room.
- Do you want me to help you?
- It's kind of you to offer.
But painting is good therapy.
You got a little...
There's still some...
I'm very grateful for your...
Just say the word.
I'll come and give you a hand.
Thanks.
When did you see him?
Was he here at the barracks?
- I'd better be off.
- Stay here. It concerns you too.
He wanted to know
Thomsen's whereabouts.
I accessed your computer.
Sorry. He said it was important.
- Did you let him into the barracks?
- No.
I told him to give himself up
or else leave us in peace.
- Happy now?
- Where is he?
- I don't know. Why?
- There's been a burglary.
At the depot.
Someone who knows
our security procedures
made off with five kilos
of plastic explosives.
- You must know more.
- No. I want to go home.
Lund...
- What?
- Nobody has seen Dragsholm here.
She knows something.
What about Raben?
We haven't seen him.
Shall we drive Thomsen home?
- No. We're taking her with us.
- I'm not going to Copenhagen!
- We'll let you pick up some things.
- What the hell for?
Come on.
The ferry departs in 45 minutes.
If you're in charge of the roads here,
I have a few complaints.
- Brix here. Any news?
- We're bringing her in.
- We're on our way to the ferry.
- We talked to her subtenant.
A week ago, he got a call
from the tax authorities.
Threatening to throw him out,
they demanded he call them
when Thomsen turned up.
They wished to pay her a visit.
- Why is that important?
- We asked the tax people.
None of them have enquired
about Thomsen.
You may not be alone
on that island.
OK. Thanks.
- Have you seen this before?
- Let's turn back.
- I'll just check it out.
- No, Strange...
Turn around. Let's go!
Stay where you are.
Something happened in that village.
It's all about that.
- I wasn't there. I know no more.
- Then why do you think so?
My mates said so.
And now they're dead. Go!
- Did they say civilians were killed?
- They didn't do it.
Some fucked up Danish officer
had gone crazy.
According to the judge advocate's
report there was no officer.
They spoke of an officer called Perk.
Nobody believed them.
The case was closed.
But the lawyer believed them.
She asked if I would testify.
Police!
Come out, or I'll shoot!
Stay here.
What's happening?
Get back to Thomsen. Now!
- I stopped you.
- Were you in here?
No. Why?
Get out!