Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
- What do you have on the squad?
- Raben was squad leader.
- Nobody called Perk, no corpses!
- They had a lieutenant called Perk.
- That coffin is empty!
- Clear your desk.
- Return to your work in Gedser.
- I'm sorry, it...
- Four dead, and we do nothing.
- What the hell is going on?
It's best the Prime Minister
knows nothing.
Thomas has 24 hours
to look into certain matters.
- He would never harm the priest.
- What did Dragsholm know?
- Myg talked about that officer.
- Find Sarah Lund!
You signed up when Jonas was born.
Don't come to see us, ever again!
Why not arrest him?
- Raben is the only survivor.
- Live bait.
- Did you know Anne Dragsholm?
- No. And I've never seen that card.
- We must check the priest. Lund...
- Lund no longer works here.
- Karina! Why ruin your career?
- I spoke with Monberg's wife.
He has regained consciousness
We must get to him before Rossing.
- You want to put the blame on me!
- What did Rossing say?
- Another visitor?
- Right. I need rest.
Who had the coffin exhumed?
What about this Raben?
He had reason to escape. He was
turned down by the Probation Service.
You'll take the blame, not Rossing.
- What did Dragsholm say?
- She'd found the officer.
Krabbe told the PM, "Either you resign,
or the Government falls".
Who brought these flowers?
- Perk's dog tag was never found.
- What?
- We must talk to the priest.
- Ask Brix.
The priest's fingerprints are on
the calling card. He denied seeing it.
I need an ambulance at St Simon's
Church. He's still breathing, but...
THE KILLING
SUNDAY, 20 NOVEMBER
6:11 PM
Arrest the priest.
Charge him with obstruction.
He claimed he didn't know the lawyer.
Why did he lie?
- Lund, I'll call you...
- The priest is badly wounded.
The ambulance is coming.
I'm in pursuit of the suspect.
He can't be far away.
Send backup, all you've got!
- Stay there. We're coming.
- Talk to the priest. He saw him.
Lund. You're off the case.
Don't do any more. Get it?
Yes.
No, wait...
You are not to do anything!
Lund!
Former Minister of Justice Frode
Monberg passed away this evening.
He was hospitalised, following
a heart attack last week.
Frode Monberg was
Minister of Justice for nine years.
His successor, Thomas Buch,
had just visited him...
The Prime Minister
has called a meeting
about the People's Party's threats.
If you hadn't pressured Monberg,
he'd never have admitted anything.
- How much did you pressure him?
- He did what was necessary.
You weren't present.
Buch! What exactly happened?
This mess is Monberg's fault.
At least he's party to it.
We mustn't let the Defense Minister
get away with it.
Monberg can't confirm anything.
We must focus on the meeting.
Krabbe and the Defense Minister
will take over the terrorism package.
If the People's Party gets the better
of you now, all will be lost.
The Prime Minister's office called
to say the meeting has started.
- We should wait for instructions.
- We have to stop the meeting.
You can't just do that.
I need to know more about Monberg.
Why did you leave him?
What did you say to him?
I'm shocked by the loss
of a good colleague
a great political personality,
and, above all, a dear friend.
It is a great loss, at a time when
our country faces serious problems.
- Don't defend him!
- I want to know what happened.
He chose to die, because he
couldn't face an impeachment!
Call in the press. Straight away!
With all due respect,
you have better candidates than him.
Possibly, but Buch is my Minister.
The People's Party should leave off.
We'll see
what's decided this evening.
We can alter the terrorism package
to suit the People's Party.
- But without Buch, of course.
- I'd rather get rid of him.
We don't fire a Minister
after one week.
Buch has been hindered
by irregularities on Monberg's part.
- What irregularities?
- No need to talk about that now.
Frode wasn't quite
master of the situation.
- We can look into the matter later.
- The problems must be solved.
But it causes me some concern
that new surprises keep turning up.
Rumours about this, that,
and the other.
And now there is talk of some
old army case. What's that about?
- Do you listen to such nonsense?
- You just set my mind at ease.
Let's get that terrorism package passed.
Then things will settle down.
...very critical questions
to the Ministry of Defense.
I demand a report
from the Defense Minister
concerning a military case
which may be connected
to the recent killings.
Evidently, the Defense Minister
has withheld information
to cover up his own negligence.
My predecessor Frode Monberg
confirmed my suspicions.
That's all I can say at present.
We'll keep the press informed.
What did the Defense Minister do?
Who is behind the killings?
Have you informed
the Prime Minister?
Is this what you mean
by everything settling down?
Lund surprised him, pursued him,
and they ended up here.
No, it's in there.
- Did the priest say anything?
- No. He was unconscious.
He died on his way to hospital.
- He was beaten to death.
- What did Lund say?
We should look for the dog tag of
the exhumed soldier. It was missing.
- I haven't followed up on that.
- Well, then do it!
Call his mother.
Find out if there was a dog tag.
- Where is she?
- At the Emergency Ward.
She's to be debriefed at HQ.
We need to talk. Right now!
Didn't you see his face?
Any special characteristics?
No. I told you.
Why didn't you call earlier?
You'd been taken off the case.
Are you all right?
I'll drive you home.
Should I call anybody?
No, I'm not going home.
My mother is getting married.
Some wedding guests
are staying over.
Come on.
Let's go.
The exhumation was a bit much,
but we were on to something.
- No comments. Goodbye.
- His dog tag was never found.
Not now.
Someone misused his identity.
Why was Lund in that church?
If you've gone behind my back...
No. Special Branch is mistaken.
We must talk to König.
König is busy. The Minister of Justice
made an announcement.
And Raben is on his way
to the officers academy.
Special Branch will take action.
Why don't you trust me, for once?
I'm not saying I'm always right.
Neither is Lund.
You should have
more confidence in me
after all our nightly rendezvous
in random hotel rooms.
I can work around König.
Yes. All right.
I'll see what I can do about it.
Are many soldiers opting out?
Yes, but we'll sort that out.
The only surviving member
of the squad is your son-in-law.
Your former son-in-law.
What do the police say
about his involvement?
I don't know much about it.
- How was your hunting season?
- I haven't been hunting much.
If he attacked the army chaplain,
he must be quite mad.
Yes...
- Good evening. Sorry I'm late.
- Søgaard!
- I didn't think you were coming.
- I see you haven't left me much.
I think Søgaard was
about to ask me to dance.
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry, Torsten.
But I'm prying into this affair
because they are about to catch Raben.
That's confidential.
Army Intelligence
knows Raben's whereabouts.
Special Branch is watching him,
hoping to find the killers.
Excuse me. Jarnvig speaking.
But what do the police say?
OK. Thanks, Bilal.
If you do as I say and tell the truth,
you may return to the ball.
You covered up for
an officer called Perk.
He had a dog tag on with that name,
but who was he?
- There was no officer.
- The army chaplain told me about it.
What? I just heard the priest
was found killed, this evening.
- You need help.
- I want to see the personnel files.
I don't have them.
They are at the personnel office.
And you are being watched
by Special Branch.
- Give yourself up.
- Are the files at Holmen?
Special Branch believes
you'll lead them to the killers.
Don't! You're only making things worse.
I'll go with you. OK?
- We'll have a quiet talk.
- Keep your mouth shut!
I was coming home.
I had only two weeks to go.
And now it's been two years.
- You could have investigated it.
- There was nothing to investigate.
You ruined everything, for yourself,
for Louise, for Jonas.
- What were you thinking?
- Why should I be lying?
Why should anybody?
I tried to stop him.
It was as easy
as blowing out a candle.
He had the officers' academy logo
tattooed on his shoulder.
I could recognise him on sight.
There is a back entrance.
It leads out into the garden.
The toilets are
at the end of the hallway.
That's all I could do.
I wanted to prevent...
I'll let you in on a secret.
I didn't hesitate to appoint you
I knew I could trust you.
Nothing in your political past suggests
that you would stab
your own Government in the back.
Your accusations
cannot be retracted.
I don't wish to retract them.
I want the matter to be cleared up.
There is no documentation.
Rossing is my trusted Minister.
Just let me ask him those questions
before the Security Committee.
I have no choice, now that you've
handed out tickets to the press.
I don't suppose you realise
what you've started.
If there is anything amiss,
I want it out in the open.
But if it's pure speculation...
I won't betray your trust.
Things are looking up.
They found him in his church.
He died in the ambulance.
Former field chaplain.
That makes it five people killed.
Unless we count Monberg, too.
- No dog tag?
- Yes.
But the killer was interrupted
by the police woman. He dropped it.
- By Lund?
- Yes.
The priest was on Team Ægir
and knew the first victim, Dragsholm.
Maybe all the victims knew
about the incident in Afghanistan.
All was investigated and reported,
according to procedure.
Nothing points towards
the killing of civilians.
Maybe they're taking extra care
for a reason.
- No more sweets. I'll have a pear.
- We must look at the case once more.
Do we know anyone
inside the Ministry of Defense
who bears a grudge
against Rossing?
I'd like to know what is uncovered
regarding that officer.
Lund is not on the case anymore.
It's Special Branch's investigation.
- And what do they say?
- They're following Monberg's lead.
But they're not sure
it's relevant to the investigation.
Isn't it odd that the soldier's
dog tag was never found?
No, not really. And it doesn't mean
that there are crooks in the army.
Nothing indicates that
fundamentalists are behind it.
- Only what we found at Kodmani's.
- That may belong to Faith Fellow.
Ruth Hedeby speaking
Yes?
Why aren't we investigating
the army and Team Ægir?
Stop it. I don't want
to wrestle with you.
Let us have Raben in
for questioning.
It will have to wait.
He seems to have escaped.
We are looking for him.
And we'll find him.
We are still working
on different theories.
Have a little confidence in me.
Damn it, Lennart. If I knew
there was something to hide
would I be sitting here,
lying to you?
That was the Ministry of Justice.
They wish to inform us about
Buch's talk with his predecessor.
Monberg saw the first victim,
Anne Dragsholm.
She found the officer
the squad was referring to.
That is not confirmed. We don't know,
if there even was an incident.
The Ministry of Justice is adamant.
They want everything out in the open.
If there are any obstructions,
the Minister wants to know.
You forgot your...
Thanks. That leaves
only one matter to discuss.
No. Lund is not coming back.
Have you decided?
Yes. Number 38.
With extra cheese.
And a number 38
with extra cheese.
Yes, please.
Sì, sì!
- How is your head?
- I took some painkillers.
- I can manage.
- You can't see what you're doing.
It looks fine.
Yes, I know it stings.
- I don't understand.
- What?
Why didn't he pull the trigger?
- Never mind that now.
- No. He had enough time.
It won't happen again.
I promise you that.
Damn, that was quick!
- It's for you.
- For me?
Excuse the intrusion.
I won't take much of your time.
Lennart... Brix
can fill you in on the details.
We were a bit rash, it seems.
You may return to your
temporary position, as of now.
This is due
to developments in the case
and a change of attitude
in the Ministry of Justice.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
I want a guarantee that I can stay
on the case until it's closed.
- It's my case, I work with Strange.
- Fine, if you can agree.
No restrictions. All Team Ægir's
officers are to be questioned.
Fine. Then that's how it will be.
And stop the tail on Raben.
I want him in for questioning.
Raben got away.
I'm sorry,
but that's how it is.
- Where am I to sleep?
- The food is on its way.
- I'll save mine till tomorrow.
- OK.
Lund never saw his face,
but we have a theory.
He was one of Team Ægir's officers.
The team was led by 28 officers,
all of whom are suspects.
Get them in for questioning,
no matter where they are.
Per K. Møller's dog tag
was never found.
We have reason to believe
somebody used his identity.
We must check these bills
for items ordered in this name.
Anne Dragsholm found the officer
who called himself Perk.
We must be able to find out
how she found him.
Special Branch's report on
who came and went at the ball.
- What do they say about Raben?
- He abandoned the car he came in.
After the ball, he disappeared.
His wife and the Colonel were there.
- But they didn't necessarily meet.
- He is looking for the same.
What are we to do
about the Ministers?
- We should have a talk...
- Hold your horses.
- Did you check Søgaard's past?
- Yes. Very interesting.
We are sending a new team to war.
This is very disturbing.
Where were you yesterday evening
from 5:00 to 9:00, before the ball?
One of my officers needed
to have a talk before leaving.
Who was it?
Call him. You won't have the chance
for the next six months.
- You called the army chaplain. Why?
- I had nothing to do with his death.
Were you afraid
that he should tell tales?
Raben had attacked him.
Dragsholm contacted the priest
about the old military case.
- I wasn't aware of that.
- That case bothered you.
You called Raben
unpatriotic and cowardly.
Possibly.
Raben's story harmed us all.
What is your relationship
with Raben's wife?
You took her home last night.
How long have you known her?
Five years ago, you gave orders
to have some cadets tied to a tree.
You claimed they had been disloyal.
You civilians know nothing
about risking one's life for others!
I train men for war.
We must be able to trust each other.
Was that the problem
with Raben's squad?
Did they let you down by accusing
an officer of killing civilians?
That gives you
and your fellow officers a motive.
I'll say no more
before I've talked to a lawyer.
Join the crowd.
You and 20 or 30 of your colleagues.
- So you left the ball with him?
- Søgaard gave me a lift home.
- Did you notice anything unusual?
- This is for the armoured vehicles.
Bandages, painkillers, morphine, etc.
- And the day Grüner was killed?
- I already told you.
We met Søgaard by coincidence.
He gave us a lift to the barracks.
- Where did he go from there?
- I've no idea!
Maybe he went to Sweden
to deliver some explosives.
He helped me redecorating
and later we joined my father.
Right, thanks. We'll get back to you
if there are any developments.
- I know about the investigation.
- Excuse me for a moment.
I need the key to the depot.
I want to get the rest of our things.
- I'll see to it. But we're busy now.
- I'll manage on my own.
I want to have everything ready
before Jonas comes home.
By the way, you have a visitor.
That idiot from last night.
The police have focused
on the officers of Team Ægir.
- Why? Did they explain?
- In connection with the murders.
Madness! They are our best officers,
hardly terrorists!
We're doing all we can
to help the police.
Just the police?
Raben was
at the officers' academy last night.
- Did you know that?
- No. Why? What was he after?
He seems interested in the officers.
I find it rather disconcerting.
Raben managed
to give Special Branch the slip.
Early this morning, someone broke
into our personnel office.
Raben was recognised on CCTV.
No valuables were stolen.
But all the files on the officers
on Team Ægir are missing.
REPORT
CAPTAIN TORBEN SKÅNING
...MENTALLY UNSTABLE...
...FITS OF RAGE...
Three soldiers die on a mission.
The Ministry of Defense is informed.
Allegedly, a local family
was executed by Danish soldiers.
- Is there any proof of that?
- Only the judge advocate's report.
The soldiers claim the officer,
who they came to relieve, did it.
The accusations were disregarded
as propaganda for Taliban.
- The soldiers withdrew them.
- Why did they change their story?
None of them lived to tell.
They are all dead now.
- What about Raben?
- No news. They'll let us know.
The Minister of Defense
knew something was amiss.
- There's a journalist to see you.
- That will have to wait.
She has an axe to grind
with the Minister of Defense.
She worked in the Ministry of Defense
when the case came up.
Come in.
I worked for the Ministry
of Defense Press Service
when the case came up
two years ago.
On the day of the soldiers' funeral,
when the Minister gave his speech
I was at work. A fax came in.
Anonymous, from Afghanistan.
Is it all right, if I smoke?
- No.
- Go ahead.
Thank you.
- Where was I?
- A fax.
A medical report from
the field hospital at the main camp.
Apparently,
there was a mismatch
among the collected body parts.
- What sort of mismatch?
- A hand.
- There was a hand too many.
- A hand?
- It wasn't from any of the soldiers.
- The hand of a dead civilian?
An appropriate supposition.
I pass on the fax
to the Permanent Secretary
expecting the matter
to be investigated
seeing as it confirms
the soldiers' allegations.
But nothing happens.
Nobody reacts.
The fax doesn't enter into the case.
I need you to tell this
to the Security Committee.
I can't. I must adhere
to the Official Secrets Act.
I risk being accused of high treason.
Otherwise, I'd have written about it.
- If you're out to make some deal...
- Of course not!
I've been waiting
for someone to look into the case.
If you won't step forward,
it's of no use to me.
- What is that?
- The fax.
I photocopied it, before passing it
on to the Permanent Secretary.
Right...
Thanks.
Buch, we don't know her.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I apologise for the delay.
I'm sorry.
This meeting is about the accusations
by the Minister of Justice
against the Minister of Defense
regarding recent and past cases.
Present are: myself, the Home
Secretary, the Foreign Minister
the Minister of Defense,
and finally, the Minister of Justice.
Let me start two years ago,
when an incident in Afghanistan
was reported.
As from now referred to
as the Helmand case.
Raben stole information
about the officers on Team Ægir.
He's up to something.
We must find him.
He must have taken another car.
Look for stolen cars.
- Right.
- Thanks.
Ouch! Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- You'd better take a look at this.
Lund? Take a look at this.
They had to pick him up.
He didn't turn up for questioning. Lund?
- Yes. Who is he?
- Lieutenant Peter Lænkholm.
It seems he was kicked out
a couple of years ago.
Thanks.
I'm no longer in the army
so I can't help you.
You were on Team Ægir.
How did you like Major Søgaard?
He was great! He trained me
at the officers' academy.
I thought he was terrific.
I chose to serve under his command.
- But you didn't serve for very long.
- I got as far as Afghanistan.
It says you were uncooperative
and there were disciplinary problems.
- I won't slag off Søgaard.
- This is how it is, mate.
You have enough weed at home
to send you to prison.
- But I'm not a dealer.
- Tell us about Søgaard.
What went wrong?
As long as you follow the rules,
all is well. He's cool.
But you didn't.
I smoked a joint.
I was no more high
than the bloody Taliban.
And then you were kicked out.
No. Søgaard doesn't
just kick people out.
- I got the full treatment.
- What treatment?
They fetch you at night
when you're asleep.
They tie you
with cable binders and duct tape.
Then they string you up,
with a flare up your arse.
A flare?
Yes. It's not that great,
I can tell you.
Didn't anybody help you?
Out there, Søgaard is God.
Nobody moves unless he gives the order.
What about Raben and his squad?
How did Søgaard like him?
- Eh?
- Not very much.
They were into deep shit.
- What was your impression?
- We heard the rumours.
And then this officer
was discharged.
Søgaard doesn't discharge a soldier
before time, just like that.
He'd done something worse than
smoke joints. What was his name?
- His name was Skåning.
- OK. What else?
I don't know.
Is this him?
Great!
No answer. It sounds like
the phone is switched off. Come on.
Why was Parliament
not informed of the accusations?
We can hardly inform Parliament
every time the Taliban pull a stunt.
You saw no reason to investigate
the alleged killings of civilians?
Damn it, Buch.
The Minister has already answered.
Is it too much to ask to be informed
of what this is all about?
- What's this then?
- A report from the field hospital.
The fax was sent to your Ministry
on the day of the soldiers' funeral.
Among the body parts
there was a hand too many.
- The hand of an Afghan.
- Where did you get this?
The reporting doctor concludes
that the alleged civilian killings
should be investigated.
The case has been investigated,
and to tell you the truth...
The truth is, you did sod all!
You knew something was amiss.
But you didn't tell anyone, and you
told Monberg to keep it a secret.
And when the first victim was found,
you still didn't do shit!
Five people have been killed.
Five lives
could have been spared.
- Do you have an explanation?
- Yes. Of course.
The fax was kept out of the case files
due to an inaccuracy.
Nonsense! Time and place
is on the fax. It all fits.
I'm sorry you force me to go
into these macabre details.
Further investigation proved it to be
the hand of the suicide bomber.
Nevertheless...
It's in the corrected medical report
which they received later.
I won't waste any more of your time.
You're welcome to read the report.
This has been quite an ordeal.
How did you know I was going
to talk about that fax?
- How could you know?
- You ignore expert opinion.
You force the police and Special Branch
to hound our soldiers.
You put pressure on Monberg
when he was unwell.
And now you try to make me
responsible for your incompetence!
Your husband isn't answering
the phone and he isn't at home.
Right, then try...
No. Why?
When was that?
OK, thanks. She doesn't know
why he's not answering his mobile.
Skåning is studying languages
and was going to the library.
- What else?
- Someone else called, two hours ago.
And old army buddy.
She didn't know him.
- Hi, I didn't expect you back.
- I was delayed.
- I'll lock up.
- Good night.
Buch? The Minister of Defense
denies all accusations.
Will you give him
an official apology?
After only a week
as Minister of Justice
Buch faces an uncertain future
due to what is described
as a political blunder
The People's Party is likely
to give a vote of no confidence
demanding the Minister's resignation
and to press
for a stricter terrorism package.
- Did you call the journalist?
- Yes, but in vain.
It was a set-up,
planned by the Minister of Defense.
No one likes to be smeared,
so I'm relieved to hear
the Minister of Justice has been
asked to withdraw his accusations.
It's my own fault.
The Minister of Defense was right.
I pressured Monberg too much.
I kept on at him.
I didn't consider his health.
- Not for a second.
- You had good reason.
- You were on to something.
- It doesn't seem so now.
Oh, excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
If you've come to gloat,
you chose the wrong moment.
- Do you mind if I smoke?
- Don't talk about the package.
And I won't butter you up...
I'll get the terror package I want.
And I still want to be rid of you.
But how sure are you about
your accusations against Rossing?
Why?
You're hardly losing sleep over it.
- Do you still believe in them?
- Why do you ask?
The Minister of Defense
was unusually well prepared.
- Perhaps even too well prepared.
- Yes, and for a reason.
I was tipped off about a fax.
It was most likely set up by Rossing.
And I walked right into the trap.
Satisfied?
You'd told no one about the fax?
I didn't phone to warn him.
- Only you and your staff knew.
- Krabbe, for Heaven's sake!
Had the Prime Minister
been informed?
Of course. I wouldn't get up
on my high horse without...
Excuse me.
The Prime Minister's office called.
The Prime Minister
would like to see you.
Excuse me.
I won't disturb you any longer.
Thank you for listening.
It's fantastic. Come on!
Yes, come along.
Don't film me. I'm so fat!
Nonsense! You are beautiful.
Hi. Sorry I'm so late.
They kept me at it, all day.
- I'm sorry. I'll come back later.
- No. Stay.
- Is the little squirt at home?
- No, he's with my father.
You didn't let him down, Louise.
You held out longer than most.
I'd like you
to help me with something.
Let's try his address again.
Maybe he's come home.
Shut up!
You said your name was Perk.
- You had a dog tag. It was you!
- It wasn't me.
Admit it!
I know it was you.
We came to your rescue.
Leave me alone. I was discharged
after a nervous breakdown.
I flew home
with the wounded soldiers.
- Which soldiers?
- From 3-2-AIpha.
The survivors. They had been under
siege in a village for two days.
Were you on that plane?
Please leave me alone!
Raben...
Put the gun down.
You're the only one left.
Raben, think about it.
Put the gun down
and come here. Come on.
It's OK. He's my partner.
Just put the gun down.
Raben! Put the gun down!
Put it down, damn it!
- Put the gun on the floor.
- Perk...
Put the gun down, I said.
Put it down, now!
Do as he says.
No!