Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
- What does Special Branch know?
- Raben was squad leader.
No officer Perk. No corpses.
Why didn't he pull the trigger?
He had enough time.
The Defense Minister
must account for
a military case,
possibly connected to the killings.
If it's true, I want it
out in the open. If not...
We got a fax from the camp
in Afghanistan.
There was a mismatch among
the body parts. A hand too many.
It was the hand
of the suicide bomber.
- You are bound to say that!
- It's in the amended medical report!
This has been very taxing.
The Minister of Defense
was well prepared for the meeting.
Had the Prime Minister
been informed?
Of course he had!
- There was no one!
- Why would I lie?
He had a tattoo on this shoulder.
I'd recognise him on sight.
You didn't let him down.
You held out longer than most wives.
I want your help with something.
You may resume
your temporary position.
- What did Søgaard think of Raben?
- Not much. They were in deep shit.
Concerning the officer
who was sent home.
I know it was you! We came
to relieve you. You think I'm an idiot?
I was sent home because
I had a nervous breakdown.
Raben... Put the gun down.
- Perk...
- Put the gun down, now!
No!
THE KILLING
MONDAY, 21 NOVEMBER
7:19PM
Left side of the thorax.
The bullet perforated his lung.
- Has he eaten recently?
- He's lost a lot of blood.
- Is he allergic to any drugs?
- They have his medical record.
He needs a suction drain.
Get him ready!
You can't come in here.
They've brought the officer in
for questioning.
Should they start or wait for us?
Is he going to be all right?
I had to shoot.
He was waving a gun about.
- Why didn't he drop it?
- I don't know.
He was about to put it down.
Then you arrived.
He seemed to think
you were Perk.
- Where is he?
- On the operating table.
What the hell happened?
He took the officer hostage.
He had a gun.
And then he took off.
He wouldn't put down his weapon.
- Who shot him?
- I did. I aimed at his arm.
Put guards on Raben. No one has
access to him without asking us.
Is he going to pull through?
Why didn't he put the gun down?
I don't know.
But we got the officer.
Raben found him,
so he's probably the right one.
- Saturation?
- Pressure's falling.
- Ventricular defibrillation.
- More oxygen!
- Put the gun down, now!
- Perk...
Raben said the officer they
were relieving was called Perk.
Søgaard had attended Perk's funeral,
three months earlier.
- Didn't he think it strange?
- It couldn't be the same Perk. Why?
What about the radio call
the squad claimed to have received?
- From a Danish unit in trouble.
- None of our radios picked it up.
We're on a tight schedule. I suggest
we postpone these questions.
There was no officer.
We had no troops in that area.
No...
We didn't have any.
I want a transcript of all radio
communications in that area.
Ask Army Operational Command
to send it to us.
Oh, Bilal?
Mum's the word.
Something's happened to Jens.
The police called.
I'll stay with Jonas.
You'd better go immediately.
What's happened?
- What sort of alibi?
- Skåning had a nervous breakdown.
He flew home with Raben
and the wounded soldiers.
Check him again.
I'm on my way.
- He just came out of surgery.
- What happened?
He took an officer hostage.
He had a gun. He tried to escape.
Why did you shoot?
We had a... situation.
He tried to take his own life.
Then he thought better of it.
But he wouldn't put down his weapon.
Excuse me. Just a moment.
These are his personal belongings.
They are questioning the officer.
His statement has been confirmed.
But it must be him.
We've checked all the rest of them.
- What did the doctor say?
- We may interview Raben tomorrow.
There's a problem. Raben spoke
before he was anaesthetised.
He said, repeatedly, that the policeman
who shot him was Perk.
The doctor said he was delirious,
but it'll crop up in the police inquiry.
- Is your report accurate?
- Yes, it is.
What exactly did the doctor say?
Something was not right.
When Raben saw Strange,
he said, "Perk!"
But, really...
He'd just been threatening
to commit suicide.
He was in a state.
He was completely beside himself.
- What does Strange say?
- What can he say?
- I'm on my way to HQ.
- We have to take this seriously.
When we took on Strange
a year ago, I read his CV.
- He was in the army for some years.
- Yes, I know. At Vordingborg.
He had back trouble.
He's hardly a suspect.
Strange wasn't just at Vordingborg.
Strange was with Special Forces.
He was an officer.
Shall we leave now?
Raben, the only survivor of his squad,
is in a critical condition.
Minister of Justice Buch
accused the Minister of Defense
of withholding information about
killings of civilians in Afghanistan.
The Prime Minister
has called a meeting with Buch.
- Krabbe will call me back.
- I can't keep making excuses.
I'm sorry I'm late,
but things are rather hectic.
It's all right. Have a seat.
- Can I offer you a drink?
- No, thank you.
I'm anxious to find the Minister
of Defense and talk things over.
- Talk what over?
- I realise I was a bit rash.
I'm sorry about the misunderstanding.
I'll offer him my apologies
so that we may continue
our working relationship.
And Krabbe too. The terrorism package
has put us under pressure.
But if I can just have
a talk with him, I'm sure...
You've been a Minister for seven days.
God created Earth in that time.
But you've destroyed everything.
Politicians must be team players.
Don't try to be a solo dancer.
All those accusations have
left you with egg on your face.
I've listened to you, but I'm sure
you're barking up the wrong tree.
- You will have to resign.
- But I'm not ready to resign.
There are far too many loose ends.
How did the Minister of Defense
know I'd mention that fax?
What fax?
The fax about the medical report
and the surplus hand.
Very convenient!
And I didn't tell him.
- Then who did?
- Shall I call Rossing over here?
No
No. Never mind.
- Will you be at the reception?
- No. I don't have time.
This is what we'll do: tomorrow,
we'll pass the terrorism package.
Then you call a press conference
as your grand finale.
Don't worry. In a few years,
you can be back on the political scene.
See you tomorrow.
Best regards to you family.
- How long were you in the SAS?
- Come on, Brix!
You'd better answer. There will be
an inquiry about the shooting.
- We have to know where we stand.
- I was in the army for a few years.
They asked if I'd like to join
Special Forces. And I accepted.
I grew tired of it and quit.
Then I applied to the Police Academy.
And that was the last of it?
After 9/11,
I was asked to sign up again.
I had a boring job in the drug squad,
so I gave it another go.
I quit 18 months ago
and joined the police force again.
Were you in Afghanistan?
Yes. Three times.
I had nothing to do with Team Ægir.
I was demobilised
six months before they left.
And I never met Jens Peter Raben.
Don't you think I'd have told you
if I had knowledge of this case?
- Why didn't you say anything?
- I wanted to forget about it.
My life fell apart while I was out there.
My marriage, my children.
It's taken me a long time
to get back on my feet.
According to Raben's hostage,
he took great interest in a certain tattoo.
"Ingenio et Armis."
"With cunning and weapons".
We're wasting time.
Why don't we question that officer?
He's not the one.
We sent him home.
Then we must have
overlooked something.
Just show me your shoulder.
Let's get it over with.
Before you handcuff me, check how
many officers have the same tattoo.
Hand over your gun and badge
until we get this matter cleared up.
After they've questioned you, go home
and stay there, until further notice.
Strange is being suspended.
Take over his assignment.
Report to Lund and me.
- OK.
- Lund will brief you.
I'll contact Special Forces.
We need a list of their officers.
Had he been involved,
I would have found out.
The case is connected to Afghanistan,
but he never let on.
The case took a surprising turn.
Until proven otherwise,
he's a suspect.
When he shot Raben...
Was there really no alternative?
No.
It was justifiable.
Were you with Strange
at the time of all the killings?
Either Raben is crazy, or Strange
is lying. I'd rather believe the former.
But you better think carefully.
- How is he?
- He'll sleep until tomorrow.
But he's going to be all right.
You may go in and see him.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Will somebody collect his clothes?
It's important for him to feel
that someone is there for him.
The doctor said
I should talk to you.
I don't know what to say.
I saw an old video this evening.
We were at the beach
just before Jonas was born.
Remember?
We couldn't decide
on a name for him.
We had written a long list of names,
but couldn't decide.
In the end,
you wanted to go for a swim.
But I didn't, because I thought
I looked like a whale.
But you took me in your arms and
carried me out to sea. You kissed me.
You said that now you knew
what his name should be.
He should be named Jonas
Because Jonas was inside the whale.
I'd better get home
No comments. Goodbye. We won't
talk to the press until we know more.
- His driver hasn't seen him.
- He left the Prime Minister an hour ago.
He's not answering his mobile
and his wife hasn't seen him.
- I hear rumours.
- Let's hear it from him.
Maybe he met up
with that journalist woman.
Is that the secretariat?
Plough. Our Minister is missing.
Could he be at a committee meeting?
What did you say?
Where? For how long?
- Never mind. Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Where is he?
- In the Ministry of Integration.
What's this?
I'd better have another one.
Hi there! Hello?
- Connie Vemmer wants to talk to you.
- Try the champagne!
The Minister of Defense was warned
we'd bring up that medical report.
What did Krabbe want?
They've got Raben.
He's injured, but...
It's over!
I'm resigning tomorrow.
- We can't just give up.
- Something is amiss.
We're in this together.
We have to keep calm.
The truth is we weren't up to it!
That's going a bit far.
Let's get back to our office.
You had no idea
what Monberg was up to.
And you even slept with him!
Bloody hell!
Don't go! Come back.
Come here, won't you?
I must ask you to leave.
Yes?
All right, I'm coming! Goddamn it!
- Will you stop that!
- Hello?
- Buch! What are you doing here?
- Sorry. We've got to talk.
Dig in!
- We talked about it too.
- What?
- Getting an au pair.
- That's my wife.
And my children.
What is it you want?
I'm sorry, if I made you confused.
- Why did you come?
- It was nothing.
I had the Prime Minister's confidence.
I demand to know
what you talked about.
After your TV stunt, I was furious.
The terrorism package was in ruins.
I had to call a meeting
in the party's executive committee.
But you're right here!
I was on my way when I heard
from the Prime Ministers' office.
They said the Minister of Defense
was in the clear
and the terrorism package
was up for vote tomorrow.
How could they know that,
before the Security Committee meeting?
I couldn't understand that either.
However, I've thought it over
and I think I get the picture.
So what, if the Prime Minister's office
had prior knowledge?
They knew your allegations
would be repudiated.
So they call me up, to avoid me
stirring things up within my party.
Or perhaps
they just lost confidence in you.
Or, as you would have it,
the Minister of Defense fucked you over.
But that doesn't mean
the Prime Minister is a villain.
I spoke to him this evening.
All was well.
I'm sorry to say, I'm glad he gave you
the push. I've fought for this.
I'll call you a taxi.
We need to know exactly
when Strange was sent home.
- He claims it was six months before.
- They don't give out information.
But General Arild is coming
to see us tomorrow morning.
Good. About Strange's CV.
Could you send me that?
Thank you.
Lund...
Documents on the soldiers who died
on the last mission of Raben's squad.
I'd left them in the car.
You'd better take over.
I don't care what Brix thinks
or that nutcase Raben.
- We can't talk about the inquiry.
- What do you believe?
You should have told me.
Why? Did you tell me about your life
and your partner who was shot?
A detective told me you were nuts
and caused Jan Meyer's death.
I stood by you, all the time,
even though you told me nothing.
I told my kids about you.
They asked me
why I looked so happy.
I told them I'd met someone at work.
We've been very cooperative.
Your interrogations at the barracks.
And now Special Forces.
Were Special Forces in the area
in question two years ago?
- Yes, they were on missions there.
- While Team Ægir was there?
Had Ulrik Strange been demobilised
six months prior to that?
- You know I can't disclose that.
- I want a list of who was there.
I'm not at liberty
to disclose that information.
But no one from Special Forces
was involved in that incident.
Brix?
The Danish Special Forces
don't kill innocent civilians.
Excuse me.
We are busy deploying troops.
These soldiers were deployed too
and we need information.
The ramblings of a traumatised
soldier don't suffice.
And how could Jens Peter Raben
elude Special Branch?
This is the score.
Either you give me what I need
or I'll raise the question
with the press.
Why won't you assist us
in solving this case?
Get my drift? Or shall I find
someone who is "at liberty"?
Evidently, this information is important.
I'll see what I can do.
Jens Peter Raben has woken up.
He wants to be questioned, immediately.
Without an attorney.
We did surgery on your artery.
Take care or you could die.
Wait. Wait a minute.
I'll find someone to get you ready.
I'm sorry to have caused you
embarrassment.
You should know
that I liked being here.
I hope you will be just
as helpful to my successor...
...whoever he may be.
Thank you.
Today's schedule.
The Prime Minister's office
expects you
to give the usual speech
and to be present.
- About Jens Peter Raben...
- Forget it.
I'd like to apologise
for my behaviour last night.
You were there for me all along.
This cock-up is my responsibility.
This is the best solution for
the Government and the Ministry.
I wish you all the best.
There you are.
And for you...
Excuse me, I have to answer this.
- Was it the wrong Armagnac?
- No, it's fine.
Plough has worries of his own.
He's been called to a meeting
in the Prime Minister's office.
They want to appoint him
as an EU consultant in Skopje.
If Plough goes, I go too.
But that's fine by me.
The journalist woman
told me she'll explain it all
but only to you, personally.
I really think, you...
I'll talk to the Prime Minister
about your future careers.
I'll put it right.
See you downstairs.
We never should have backed him up.
They just called me back.
Skopje it is. EU consultant.
- After 23 years, I end up in Skopje.
- Not necessarily.
What am I to tell my wife?
Where is Skopje anyway?
Do we have an atlas?
Listen to me! Perhaps your wife
gets to stay in Denmark.
At 9:32am we got a message
from a Danish unit under fire.
We crossed the river,
and there was a foul-up.
Thomsen may have told you
what happened.
We reached the village
and fought our way into the building.
But there was no Danish unit.
Just one officer, who had ensconced
himself with a local family.
Why did you think he was called Perk?
He said so. I saw his dog tag.
I'd never seen him before. I assumed
he was from another Danish camp.
- How had he ended up there?
- He'd been cut off from his squad.
The Taliban were hounding him.
He sought refuge in the building.
There were only four of us left.
Myg, HC, Sebastian and myself.
And Perk. Dolmer had been killed
as we forced our way in.
Grüner's leg was shot to bits.
He was in urgent need of help.
But we were under fire.
And we'd left the radio with Thomsen.
- What about Perk's radio?
- He said it had been blown to bits.
He decided we'd better wait
than fight our way out.
So that's what we did.
The shooting continued.
The next day, the heat got to us.
There wasn't enough water.
The stench was unbearable.
Time went by, but no help arrived.
Perk became tense.
He wanted to find a way to get away.
He wanted the father
to help him get hold of a radio.
But the father said
he didn't know of any.
Perk fetched one of the children.
A little girl.
He held a pistol to her head.
He asked the father if he'd rather
help the Taliban than us.
And then he fired.
He grabbed hold of the children's
mother and shot her too.
The father held the youngest, a boy,
and begged for them to be spared.
Perk shot them both.
What did you do?
I held the first child.
The little girl.
- I never thought he'd shoot.
- What did the others do?
Everybody was shouting.
Sebastian was crying.
Would that be Sebastian Holst?
The youngest of us.
He took more interest
in his camera than in his gun.
I put my arms around him
and made him calm down.
When darkness fell, we suddenly
heard the sound of an engine.
A man drove his moped into
the courtyard and blew himself up.
I don't remember much more.
They came to our aid soon after.
- Where was Perk at that time?
- I don't know.
He must have found a way out
just before help arrived.
- And the bodies of the family?
- He must have got rid of them.
Ask him!
Perk is the policeman
who shot me yesterday.
- Where is he?
- Why do you think it was him?
It is him. He killed the others.
He has a tattoo on his shoulder.
You were equally convinced that
the officer you took hostage was Perk.
I'd like you to look at these.
Just take your time.
Raben has cause to tell that tale.
He's facing several charges.
- Could Strange have been there?
- They haven't confirmed it yet.
But Raben is mentally unstable.
We have written proof of that.
He may have confused Strange
with another Special Forces officer.
We are checking that.
Strange has been investigating the case.
He's had no time
to play Muslim League.
In the course of last week
his alibi is incomplete.
Before we got to Myg Poulsen,
more than an hour had passed.
Grüner was burnt in a fire
triggered by a mobile phone
whose owner we can't find.
I met with Strange before we left
for the multi-storey car park.
In Sweden he'd left a bit, while
I was questioning Lisbeth Thomsen.
And he was at the barracks,
the night the explosives were stolen.
But when you found the chaplain
in the church, Strange was in Helsingør.
Has that been checked?
I saw them return
but I'll have it checked.
I'm going to see
Sebastian Holst's parents.
We've looked though his photos.
There was no officer.
He always had his camera with him
but it was never found.
- What shall we do with Strange?
- Bring him in for questioning.
Our superiors will want to know
why you took him on.
I didn't actually appoint him.
Strange came to our department
in connection with the police reform.
If anyone, our superiors will
be washing their hands of him.
Thank you. Bye.
He's asked to see me. I'm going now.
They've already questioned him.
Don't forget to pack those.
- Let me know if I can help.
- Why?
He's under arrest, facing charges.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Here is the programme
for the ceremony.
I'll leave it to you. I'll attend,
but I'd like you to make a speech.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
Operational Command asked about
the transcript of the radio message.
I told them you'd want a printout
as well as a computer file.
- Why do you need it?
- Just take care of the ceremony.
There will be a short break
in the third reading before the vote.
At the press conference
afterwards, Buch will resign.
Here's the man himself.
May we have a comment?
- Do you have a moment?
- Of course.
A silly mistake.
Plough has been given the slip.
That's no mistake. We need
to signal a new beginning.
- Get rid of the skeletons.
- But I'm the one, who...
The Prime Minister tells me
you apologised.
I'm glad to hear it.
No hard feelings.
We'll work things out.
However, in for a penny, in for a pound.
Did you see our draft for your
speech at the press conference?
- Yes, thank you.
- Excuse me. I must talk to him.
Plough. Everything is ready for
the press conference in an hour or two.
Your wife has turned up.
Karina has gone to receive her.
- My wife?
- I said you'd meet her outside.
Where is she?
We must talk about
the medical reports.
Get in.
We'll go for a drive.
You think I was running errands
for the Minister of Defense.
I got kicked out.
If he knew about it in advance
one of your people must have
tipped him off. Never mind that.
It was right under your nose,
all along.
Why didn't you check the dates
on the two medical reports?
What dates?
I believe Sebastian always
had his camera with him.
He was always taking pictures.
There's a whole box of pictures.
You've seen them.
Did they say why his camera
was missing two years ago?
- It wasn't. He'd sent it home.
- He'd sent his camera home?
Yes, it was broken.
He asked me to repair it.
- Why do you ask?
- I won't trouble you any further.
I heard on the radio that you've
found his squad leader, Raben.
I expect the whole business
will be stirred up again.
What do you know of it?
I don't think it was an officer.
They made that up, as an excuse
for heading out to that building.
It was Raben's fault Sebastian
and the others were killed.
Why do you think so?
Sebastian predicted it.
I've lost both my sons
to a war I don't understand.
One came home in a coffin.
The other just went back.
I've no idea what we did wrong.
Is there anything
you haven't told us about?
- A video diary.
- I'd like to see it.
I'd like you to sign
your written statement.
- I'm allowed to see my wife.
- She's waiting outside.
You'll be taken back to hospital.
You have five minutes.
- May we have a bit of privacy?
- I'm afraid not.
Come and sit down.
You've heard what happened yesterday.
I was beside myself.
It won't happen again.
- We'll talk about it later.
- I let you down.
I wasn't ready.
A rotten boyfriend, a rotten father.
If only I could turn back the clock.
But things are looking up.
They listen to me now.
You and Jonas
mean everything to me.
- We can work things out.
- I'm seeing Søgaard now.
It's got nothing to do with him.
I missed you, every single day.
I just can't stand it any longer...
Can't you see? It's no use.
- We want you in for questioning.
- Just a minute.
Sorry...
Can I see my wife?
- Do you want a lawyer?
- No. I want to see my wife!
Sebastian Holst sent a video diary
home, shortly before his death.
Don't get worried, but something
is not right in our squad.
- Why must I see this?
- Raben is the worst off.
He sees Taliban everywhere,
and thinks only of killing.
He runs too many risks. Makes us
do things we're not ordered to do.
He fabricates messages,
just to get out and "kick ass".
This morning, we crossed the river
to raid a house for the third time
because Raben thinks
the father is Taliban.
We took the place apart. Raben
accused him of being an informer.
He poked his gun in his face.
For no reason.
The children were crying. The mother
and old women were crying.
Raben is running wild.
He wants to do it again.
I try to talk to the others,
but they say everything will be fine.
They don't want to cross him.
But I suppose
he knows what he's doing.
And he's the best man to be with,
when the shit hits the fan.
In a couple of weeks we'll be home,
so it'll all work out.
I miss you. See you soon.
I'll give your love
to Big Brother. Bye.
Is it true, what he's saying?
Sebastian was only there
to compete with his elder brother.
It's not about Sebastian,
but the officer.
The family he mentioned...
Is it the same family
you claim was killed?
Yes.
You and the squad had been
at the family's house several times?
You were convinced they were Taliban.
You wanted to go again.
- That's irrelevant.
- No. It isn't.
There is no indication
of your receiving any message.
And there was
no officer called Perk.
I've explained everything.
Look at these.
Five people have been killed.
I've done everything I can
to find that officer.
If you are lying,
and he doesn't exist
now is the time to admit it!
It was my decision to enter
the village. The others didn't agree.
I should have listened to them.
But there was an officer.
And he's the one I saw yesterday.
We just received documentation
from the army to the effect that
the person you identified
as the officer in question
was not in Afghanistan at the time.
What about Sebastian's elder brother?
Do you know him?
- He's a doctor. He was in our camp.
- An army surgeon? What's his name?
Frederik. Frederik Holst.
Frederik Holst, army surgeon.
We need to pay him a visit.
Ask the father what the elder
brother said about Raben's squad.
The Minister just popped out.
He'll be back soon.
What did she say?
I'm sorry I tricked you.
But you needed to see Vemmer.
We realise
you can't tell us everything.
Even if you don't act upon it,
you should have the information.
I've resigned myself
to going to Skopje.
If you decide to act,
you must go the whole hog.
- How far have they got?
- The vote starts in ten minutes.
- Is Krabbe there?
- Yes.
But he's got nothing to do with it.
Krabbe?
- Krabbe? Is that you?
- Bloody hell!
If you want to talk to me,
you can call my secretary.
The medical report about the
surplus hand was faxed in August.
The revised medical report
didn't arrive until October.
First, there's one report,
implying that civilians were killed.
What a pathetic attempt
to cling to office!
In spite of the obvious, nobody
acted upon it, for two months.
There was no cause. It was
the hand of the suicide bomber.
Why didn't they say anything?
What were they up to?
When the first report arrived
the Prime Minister
was proposing extra appropriation
in order to step up
our military effort in Afghanistan.
It was promptly approved
when Parliament opened in October.
You and your party
voted in favour of it.
This proves nothing.
Pure speculation.
- Why would the Prime Minister...?
- That's what happened, damn it!
Go ahead and push for a strict
terrorism package, if you like.
But it's going to affect
the wrong people.
I'm asking you to help me
do something about it.
We got them sent off
in high spirits.
You never told me of the message
we received five days earlier.
Yes, we got a message.
In August two years ago.
Five days before the incident.
From a Special Forces unit.
I don't understand.
They were only 150km from
where Raben's squad ended up.
- I never saw that message.
- You were in command.
What do you mean?
Raben's squad said someone was there.
We didn't believe them.
- We said they were seeing ghosts.
- So they were. This proves nothing.
- Why didn't you mention it?
- I have no knowledge of this.
If an official complaint has been filed,
I'd like to see it.
- I'm leaving for the airport.
- No.
Stay at the barracks
until further notice. Understood?
I'm glad you came.
I was about to call you.
You've been out all day.
Raben's squad
could have been right.
There was radio contact
with a Danish unit five days before.
- We must tell the police.
- They're focused on Special Forces.
But why are you so concerned?
Søgaard may have
withheld information.
I was in Kabul. He was in command.
Something is amiss,
but Søgaard isn't the problem.
Did you help Raben
elude Special Branch?
I gave you confidential information
about his surveillance.
I've been tipped off that you
met with him shortly after that.
This is important information
which we need to investigate.
- Can't we leave the...?
- Torsten, just answer me!
Did you help Raben or not?
When?
Yes. Right. Thanks.
The elder brother is in Afghanistan.
He only left yesterday.
He was home on a three week leave.
We found this.
We must question him.
Get us on the soldiers' flight tonight.
- What the hell are you saying?
- We've been wasting time.
Frederik Holst
saw his brother's video diary.
He was at the field hospital, when
they brought in his brother's body.
We need to get permission.
I'll ask Hedeby to...
That will take days!
We can't wait for that.
I need a copy of the medical reports.
- Are you travelling as a tourist?
- You can fix it if you want to.
You have connections.
Don't tell me Ruth Hedeby
is wearing the trousers.
Right! TNT, tetryl, RDX.
You name it
And fireworks for New Year's Eve.
My partner... Jan Meyer.
We arrived at a warehouse.
I went inside. I didn't think
there was anyone in the building.
Then Meyer went inside.
I should have stopped him.
It was my mistake.
We caught the perpetrator.
But it seemed... unimportant.
I shut myself down.
I got that job in Gedser
and it suited me fine.
I wanted to hide myself away.
If you hadn't turned up with word
from Brix, I'd still be there.
I'm sorry.
Now what?
We have to leave.
Where to?
They didn't let me get my jacket
when they dragged me in here.
Then you'd better fetch it.
Coming?
Frederik Holst's CV.
A warrant for his arrest. Contacts.
Strange, you be pathfinder.
You stop over in Istanbul.
I'll forward your visas
and documents by fax.
You fly with the army's aircraft
to Afghanistan under their command.
Follow their instructions.
Get that, Lund?
In 36 hours you'll be back here.
Take care.