- Emergency services.
- Something's happened.
What is your name?
There's blood everywhere.
I can't find her.
- Where are you calling from?
- Oh, my God!
- I need an address.
- Anne?
Someone's been in the house.
I can't find my wife.
- Is anyone injured?
- I don't know!
Tell me what's going on, so I can
get you the help you need... Hello?
- What have I done?
- Hello? Stay on the phone.
Anne? Anne...?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Anne?
There are 15-20 stab wounds
on her torso and neck.
It looks like a crime of passion.
I don't think she was killed here.
Much indicates that she was already dead
when she was strung up.
- Can someone shut that dog up?
- Brix?
They found the husband in his car
on the ramp to the motorway.
- He is covered in blood.
- Bring him in for questioning.
If he's covered in blood,
we're halfway there.
THE KILLING
It's 7am on Monday
November 14. This is the news.
Minister of Justice Frode Monberg
was rushed to the hospital
after a heart attack.
His present condition is not known.
Parliament is to read
the new terror package.
The Prime Minister says Monberg's
absence will not affect negotiations.
The terror package is necessary.
The fight against terrorism must go on,
both here and in Afghanistan.
The suspect in the Memorial Park murder
is still in custody.
Little information has been released
about the murder of ten days ago.
MONDAY 14 NOVEMBER
7:41AM
DAY 1
- Any news?
- No.
- Sleep well.
- Have a nice shift.
Hi.
My name is Ulrik Strange.
I left several messages
but apparently your machine doesn't work.
- There's coffee if you like.
- Thanks.
- I'm Chief Inspector...
- You mean Detective Inspector.
No, that title is obsolete.
It was changed after the reform.
There's a case we'd like to discuss
with you. About...
About 10 days ago,
a woman was killed
under very strange circumstances.
- I'll wait till you're finished.
- I can hear you.
We've withheld information,
but you've probably read about it.
We'd like you to go over the case
to see if we missed something.
- We?
- Brix, your former boss.
He thinks you can give us
a new angle.
- Lennart Brix?
- Yes. He'd like you to read the brief.
I can stay till midday.
We could meet and discuss it.
I don't with work with briefs
and perpetrators much anymore.
We're pretty sure
we have our man.
The victim's husband is in custody.
The remand expires in 32 hours,
and then we have to release him.
- You'll be paid for your time.
- That's fine.
- But tell Brix it's of no interest.
- Why not?
Brix said you would say no,
but I was to emphasise the importance...
And now you have, haven't you?
I have to go. It's been a long night.
Close the door when you're done...
OK.
- What is his condition?
- Will the minister return?
I have no further comments.
We hope the minister will recover.
Thank you.
Have a seat. The Prime Minister
will be with you shortly.
- Hi, Thomas. How are things?
- Fine, thanks.
- And the family?
- They're fine.
- Is there any news?
- His condition is stable.
But he isn't coming back,
not now or later.
We're all relieved that he'll survive,
but it's bloody bad timing.
- Of course.
- As you know, I have chosen you.
Your primary task is to get
our terror package passed.
The voting is next week,
and right now this place is like a zoo.
Our supporting party is pressuring us,
and the Opposition...
Excuse me, there's something
I have to say.
I'm honoured
to be given the offer. Truly.
But I've decided to decline.
- Why?
- I don't feel I'm ready.
I'm not a lawyer.
I don't know enough.
There are more suitable candidates.
Perhaps in a few years' time
when I've been here longer.
The government has put a lot of work
into the terror package.
We need someone to head
the negotiations immediately.
To me it's very simple.
You have the ability,
so you're obligated.
I could appoint someone from our group,
but you're the one I need.
So if you don't have any further objections,
I'll ask you again.
Will you be our new
Minister of Justice?
Raben, you have a visitor.
He wanted to come,
but today is Bake Day in day-care.
- The other kids were going.
- I understand.
I brought some of his new drawings.
Would you like to see them?
It's all about fairytales
and role-playing right now.
This is a very important dragon.
I can't remember its name,
but it's huge and very dangerous.
- He's getting good at it.
- We bought a shield and sword.
It was a gift from my father.
Otherwise
there's not much going on.
- Shall we...?
- Let's wait a while.
- When is it?
- Soon. It'll be fine.
They interview me
and then evaluate me.
It'll be fine. The lawyer says
my chances are good.
The clinical director says
I've made great progress.
This time they can't turn me down.
What's wrong?
He doesn't want to come anymore.
Jonas doesn't want to come anymore.
I know you love to see him,
and I tried, but he won't come.
It's OK.
- You mustn't pressure him.
- I don't.
But he isn't a baby anymore.
He won't even talk about you.
I think someone has been teasing him
because they heard something.
I'm sorry, honey.
Forget it. I'll work it out.
We will work it out.
It'll be fine. I promise.
We'll be together so much
that you two will miss being alone.
Because I snore
and smack my lips
and get toothpaste
on my upper lip.
This is Vibeke Lund.
I'm not home, but leave a message.
Hi, Mum. I'm taking the train
in a couple of hours.
I can only stay till tomorrow,
so... See you.
She said no.
The ferry traffic gives her plenty to do.
How's it going?
Brix.
- Strange here.
- Sarah Lund. Is Brix there?
He's busy. Can I help you?
I'm visiting my family today.
I don't know if I'll have time
but if you still think
I can help, then...
- Then what?
- I have to go. I'll call later.
Hello?
Thomas Buch, age 38, was accepted
as Minister of Justice by the Queen.
In political circles,
his appointment was a surprise.
His first task is to get consensus
on the terror package.
I shook her hand.
I'm in the ministry now, dear.
Talk to you later.
Karina Munk Jørgensen,
secretary to the minister.
- Thomas Buch.
- Welcome.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
This is where we reside.
Our staff of 170
takes up the 3rd and 4th floors.
This is the minister's office.
- There are a few things left to move.
- That's all right.
I presume this is my predecessor's.
No, I put it there.
It's the negotiation process.
Carsten Plough,
Permanent Undersecretary.
- The reception is all set.
- Good.
I'd like to be briefed
on the status of the negotiations.
An agreement will probably be made
with the People's Party.
The Opposition has opted out,
but you can read all about that.
And I will.
First I'd like to tell you
my thoughts.
We're at war.
Whether we like it or not,
we have to find unity.
So we need to work towards
a broad, national agreement.
That's been attempted.
Your predecessor acknowledged...
I understand.
But it's important that we succeed.
- Is that a problem?
- Of course not.
I'd like to show you your gift
from the People's Party.
"German occupation never again".
I'm no expert on political messages,
but I don't think they'll give in.
- We'll see about that.
- Yes.
You can discuss it with your personal
adviser whenever he or she starts.
I don't need an adviser right now.
I think the three of us can manage.
OK. I'll call a meeting
for all parties right away.
Great. Let's try those canapés.
Just don't be naive. The bike mender
has been evaluated the last 15 years.
- He thinks he'll get out every time.
- Why doesn't the buzzer sound?
Don't get your hopes up.
They'll just screw you over. Get it?
I get it. See you.
Director Toft!
Raben!
Stop!
- Step away from the fence.
- It's OK.
- How do you think it went?
- I can't tell you.
- Talk to your lawyer.
- I won't see him for a few days.
- Then you'll have to wait.
- I'm not asking for myself.
I have to call my wife.
I don't know what to say.
If it's bad, tell me now.
The institution approved you,
but it doesn't matter.
The Probation Service has the final say,
so nothing's definite.
Get moving, Raben!
-What exactly did she say?
- The doctors think I'm ready.
- When will you know for sure?
- In about a week.
It depends on the Probation Service,
so you need to get hold of Myg.
Hang on.
I'm going in the other room.
- Myg? Why?
- He can get me a job.
It would make me look good.
Tell him it's urgent.
- Is Jonas there?
- He's showing Dad something.
My phone card is running out.
Give Jonas a kiss. Don't forget Myg.
I won't.
- Hi. There's some dinner left.
- Excellent.
- How did it go?
- Waste of time. We deploy 200 men.
And the brass can't understand
that Materials Command can't keep up.
You're usually good
at explaining that.
- Jonas, put your pj's on.
- No, I want to fence with Grandpa.
Hurry up. If you're quick,
he'll read you a bedtime story.
I looked at the schools.
The one on Sionsgade sounds best.
- And it's nearby.
- True.
- Gravy?
- Just a bit.
He has be to enrolled,
so you should get it done.
We'll see.
But it depends
on whether we'll be living here.
Why wouldn't you?
They're crazy about you in the infirmary.
I need a personnel list with
phone numbers. Do you have one?
Yes, it's in the drawer.
I've offered to remodel the basement,
and you can move down there.
We'll see.
- Do you think he'll be released?
- I heard there's a good chance.
And if he isn't?
You've been waiting
for over two years.
You keep putting off the decision.
It affects Jonas and you...
He's his father, and I love him.
If that's a problem,
we'll leave right now.
OK?
Sorry to interrupt, sir. The major said
you wanted an update on the APCs.
Later, Bilal.
- And there's a lance corporal...
- Yes.
- Thank you. Later.
- Yes, sir.
The woman came home at 7:32pm
and switched off the alarm.
- She talked to her husband...
- Perhaps I should wait for Brix.
He's been delayed.
He asked me to show you around.
The couple were getting divorced.
He had an affair with his secretary.
The wife threw him out
a month before that.
She refused to talk to him,
and he says she hung up on him.
- Where was their daughter?
- At her grandparents'.
At 7:41 pm she used her laptop
to go on the Internet in here.
She had some wine, looked at
some housing sites and took a bath.
So she might not have heard
the basement window being forced open.
She took a long bath and returned
to the kitchen in her robe.
Was that her usual routine?
Coming home late, taking a bath?
Eating alone in the kitchen?
- It's hard to say since she was alone.
- Yes.
The perpetrator attacked her
before she ate, according to the coroner.
They moved to the living room
where he stabbed her.
We haven't found the weapon.
She was stabbed 21 times.
Once in the heart, which was fatal.
She was forced into the chair.
The amount of blood indicates that.
- Did you find ashes or cigarettes?
- It's not from a pack of cigarettes.
- Chewing gum?
- Maybe.
The husband says he arrived
after midnight and called it in.
- Does he have an alibi?
- His mistress, who's extremely blond.
He had been drinking
and came to talk some sense into her.
She didn't answer the door. Then he
saw the open window and entered.
He claims he got blood on himself.
Didn't he have a key?
The wife had the locks and alarms
changed a few weeks ago.
She was very concerned about safety.
She fired her old security company
because she was dissatisfied.
According to the new company,
she ordered sensors for the garden.
Good to see you.
- Shall we check out the rest?
- Yes. This way.
The woman was entitled
to half her husband's fortune and firm.
So he certainly had a motive.
- That's where we found her.
- She had no connection to the park.
Or the execution site,
but she was dragged over the fence.
There are pictures
in the back of the brief.
Thanks.
The husband isn't stupid.
We think this is a diversion.
A lot seems to point in that direction.
What are you thinking?
I think this is a mistake.
I think I'm wasting your time.
I just want your opinion.
Why don't you sleep on it
and then we'll talk tomorrow?
- I don't have any idea...
- If you do, then come and see me.
If you don't, that's fine, too.
I need your help.
Otherwise I have to release
the guy tomorrow.
- Buch here.
- Karina. I talked to the Opposition.
They can meet with you
and the People's Party in the morning.
Fine. I only have 7-800 pages to go
before I'm up to speed.
- See you tomorrow then.
- Wait.
There are pictures of a dead woman.
From the Memorial Park.
- Sorry. That's a mistake.
- Why is the ministry involved?
Your predecessor wanted updates
due to the scene of the crime.
But the police haven't found
a political motive.
- Thank you. See you tomorrow.
- Yes.
Goodnight.
TOMORROW AT 5:03PM
TOMORROW 5:03PM
TUESDAY 15 NOVEMBER
9:32AM
DAY 2
One Islamist society
after another pops up...
- It's a scare campaign.
- They want to overthrow democracy.
- And reintroduce the Middle Ages.
- But you love freedom of speech.
The terror package doesn't take
the actual situation into account.
If the People's Party won't budge,
we can't be a part of this.
I have a meeting.
I hope you learned something.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations.
Good luck.
- Bye, Agger.
- Have a good one, Krabbe.
Nice try. I'm sorry about the last bit,
but it had to be said.
We have to protect ourselves.
Just think of London and Madrid.
I agree with Agger. Special Branch
doesn't see it the way you do...
- Did you get our gift?
- Yes, thanks.
Since you're falling in the polls
one might think that a scare campaign
would be welcome, right?
My grandfather was a freedom fighter.
He ended up in Neuengamme.
- Make no mistake. What I say is true.
- That doesn't change anything.
- Your proposal is problematic.
- Who says it's just a proposal?
What do you mean?
We need each other to get a majority.
Right now, as I see it,
you need us more than we need you.
My support base
wants your answer later today.
Is a couple of hours enough
to clear it with the PM?
Thanks for the delicious coffee.
OK, we'll take
a five-minute break.
Hi.
Let him eat and go to the bathroom,
so we can continue the interrogation.
The hearing is in three hours.
We need more.
- Hi.
Yes, that's fine.
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
I'll get to that later.
AII right. Bye.
This is Deputy Commissioner
Ruth Hedeby. She wants to listen in.
I've heard a lot about you.
Have a seat.
As you know, the Memorial Park
is a national monument.
It gives rise to speculation,
which we'd like to quash quickly.
But the suspect has an alibi,
and if we're to charge him today
we need more to go on.
So I'm interested in hearing
if you can help us find more.
I don't know if I can.
I can't find fault with the investigation.
And the forensic evidence is clear...
But you entertain your own views.
I don't think he did it.
That is, her husband.
Of course, it could be him,
but I don't think so.
He didn't have anything
to do with it. It says...
It says that it was a crime of passion,
yet the body was dragged away...
Probably to divert the investigation.
Forensics said his clothes
were covered in blood...
I'd like to hear what Lund has to say
if you don't mind.
The victim was afraid of the murderer.
She's been afraid for a while.
Her husband had a motive
and was manipulative, but not violent.
There are no prior incidents.
I think...
the perpetrator wanted to make
a statement with the execution site.
Yes. What did he want to state?
- What did she do before she married?
- Quite a bit.
Some education in the US,
NGOs in Africa and Asia.
Sent out by the military and Amnesty,
but never for long.
What did she do in the military?
A military legal adviser.
She was sent to the Balkans,
Iraq, Cyprus and Afghanistan.
- That was several years ago.
- Did she still have army contacts?
No, except for a monthly contribution
to a veterans' club.
It was a regular transferral and...
Excuse me.
I don't know
if I'm right about this.
But if I am, it seems like
there's something you haven't found
or something is missing.
Yes.
The husband just confessed.
Confessed to murder
and the disposal of the body.
I see. Right.
The lawyers need a detailed
confession to write up the charges.
Then we can close this case.
I'm sorry. Thanks for your time.
I was worried there for a minute.
- I'm sorry if you...
- No, it's fine.
- I'd like to pay...
- No, I was going to drop by anyway.
Congratulations.
Happy birthday to you!
- Blow the candles out. Is that on?
- I have to put in a new tape.
- There we go.
- Go ahead.
Well done.
Since you're all here,
Bjørn and I have an announcement.
Some good news.
Bjørn has been so careless
as to propose and I said yes.
You're all invited.
But it will be a quiet ceremony.
I won't be in white.
Have a seat.
Here, Mum.
Thanks for the sweatshirt.
Sorry about the size.
I'm just glad you're here.
When do you have to leave?
- In a minute.
- Grandma said it was a job interview.
She must have misunderstood.
- How are you doing?
- Fine.
Dad, Ulla and the girls are in Spain,
- so I have the house to myself.
- Mark.
Come on, Sarah.
- Strange here.
- Lund. I can't get hold of Brix.
- I'm in an interrogation.
- It's about the perpetrator.
- I'm talking to him right now.
- That plastic wrapper...
- I have to go.
- He filmed the whole thing.
Unless you think the husband would
do that, you have the wrong man.
I'd like to visit the house again
if that's OK.
Raben, you have a visitor.
Raben, for Christ's sake...
- Myg. What's up? How are you?
- Fine. How about you?
I'm OK. I get a lot of reading done,
as they say.
- Sit down.
- OK.
I'm sorry I don't come more often.
Full speed ahead, you know.
That's OK.
- Did you talk to Louise?
- Yes. Yesterday.
I don't know if this is of any help.
It's a master carpenter.
A retired sergeant, who rambled on
about the good old days.
He needs a man in a couple of months.
- Does he know where I am?
- Yes. He's helped the club before.
Just have someone call him,
and he'll send in the paperwork.
- Thanks, Myg.
- We help each other, right?
The club could get you an apartment.
I'll tell Louise before I go.
- Go where?
- I'm being deployed next week.
Louise can call them herself.
Barracks life has never been my thing.
It's too boring.
It's time to move on.
Where?
Helmand. Maybe up north.
It all happened so quickly.
I have to get going.
- Last time, you said you wanted out.
- I have to go.
What have you done?
I can help you, Myg.
You don't know jack shit.
When we got back,
I thought it was over and done with.
It's not over at all.
- Do you understand?
- Take care.
Guard, let me out.
- Hi.
Hi, sweetie.
He seems to be all right.
Someone from day-care dropped him off,
and I brought him here.
Thanks, Søgaard.
Let me know if I can help.
See ya, kid.
Let's take your jacket off.
I know the other kids can be idiots
but fighting isn't the answer.
You can only fight dragons.
And Grandpa.
They said things about Dad.
I'll talk to them.
Is Dad coming home?
Yes, he is.
But I'm not sure when.
I lost a tooth.
Really?
That's a nice one.
Can I see?
Did it hurt?
Is it OK if I give it to Dad?
I want to give it to him myself.
Yes. I'll call and see if we
can visit him today. AII right?
Special Branch's latest threat
assessment. Where is he?
- Still in the PM's office.
- I hope they set him straight.
He's only been here a day.
I have a question.
A day is plenty
to remove our parliamentary basis.
A link can't be opened till 5:03pm
It's from the Ministry of Finance.
It's their turn to host
the Friday get-together.
That's what I thought,
but they said no.
Am I interrupting?
A Special Branch report.
What did the PM say?
I didn't see him.
Instead I talked to people here.
- What about the People's Party
- Krabbe is on his way.
Let's go in.
- Did you work it out?
- Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry I sounded a bit...
- But these things really matter.
- Of course. I feel the same way.
But our point of view is very simple.
Neither now nor in the future
will we compromise
on our constitution's protection
of basic democratic values.
No threat or scare campaign from you
or even from terrorists can change that.
I see.
If the government thinks
it's best served without us
we'll have to take that
under advisement.
Of course I'll have to tell the press
if you're quitting our collaboration.
I'm no ace at history,
but as far as I know
a Danish government has only once
before prohibited a legal association.
1941.
The Communist Party.
However, at the time they were
pressured by the Wehrmacht.
- There's no comparison.
- I have experts on constitutional law.
I enclosed their statements
at the back if you're interested.
Do you want to be part
of a broad agreement
or stand alone with an opinion
that hasn't been stated since the Nazis?
Lund, I can't stay here all night.
Get to the point. Why film it?
You said the victim was forced
into the chair after being stabbed.
- The amount of blood indicates...
- What if she was in the chair first?
And then stabbed?
- It doesn't fit a crime of passion.
- Who says it was a crime of passion?
Only one of the stab wounds
was deep enough to hit a vital organ.
Why didn't she defend herself?
Why are there no defense wounds?
You think she was tied up.
He stabbed her to get her talking
and saved the fatal wound till last.
She was in the middle of a divorce.
Why would someone interrogate her?
- What's that?
- A military ID.
Half of it is broken off.
Do you have
the address of the veterans' club?
Did you talk to the warden?
I left your application on his desk.
- You'll get an answer tomorrow.
- That's too late. Can't I call now?
Relax, man.
Hi. I applied for a phone call.
Do you know if the warden has seen it?
- No, I don't.
- Raben!
An army buddy visited me.
He isn't doing well.
- I need to call him.
- I'll tell the warden it's urgent.
- Thanks.
- We need to talk.
- Can't I make my call first?
- We'd better talk now.
The Probation Service
turned you down.
They usually take a long time
and follow our recommendation, but...
I don't know on what grounds yet,
but I'll let you know when I do.
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
- As I said...
- I completed the treatment.
You can apply again in six months.
It's important to keep up...
- I have a son.
- Step away from the clinical director.
I have to...
Fuck off!
Take it easy.
- You must remain calm.
- I am calm. I don't understand.
- I'm not a psycho or a paedophile.
- Move away from her, Raben.
Calm down!
Easy now!
I'll let him know. Thanks.
The People's Party accepts
the agreement with minor changes.
Good.
You don't look happy.
The law of 1941 cannot be compared
to the People's Party's suggestion.
Next time I'd appreciate it
if you asked me and not my legal experts.
- You're right. I'm sorry.
- There's something you have to see.
The Minister of Justice
will unfortunately be late. Thank you.
- I've just opened the link.
- What link?
- It's just been activated.
- Two minutes.
- IT says it's from a Hotmail.
- Come on. What is it?
- It's all very interesting, but...
- Wait. Here it comes.
I accuse the hypocritical
Danish government
and the infidel Danish people
of crimes against humanity.
The time has come
for Allah's revenge.
The Muslim League will punish
the sufferings Denmark has caused
in Palestine, Iraq and Afghanistan.
I plead guilty.
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
I haven't done anything...
I have a little girl...
The club for ex-servicemen
has 10-11,000 members nationwide.
The secretary of the local chapter
is Allan Myg Poulsen.
He lives in no. 46.
Wait here. I don't want any problems
with my report.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Hey!
Allan Myg Poulsen. Get a description
from the army and put out an APB.
Get a team out here
to search his place and... Hey!
I told you to wait outside.
What are you? Deaf?