About ten days ago, a woman
was killed under strange circumstances.
You'll have read about it
in the papers.
Brix believes
you may give us a new angle.
Tell Brix I'm not interested.
Sarah Lund here.
I'll take the train in a couple of hours.
I'm only staying
until tomorrow.
Minister of Justice Monberg
is in hospital due to a heart attack.
Hi, Thomas. The government
has worked hard on the terror package.
We need you to head the negotiations.
Will you be Minister of Justice?
We are at war. Like it or not,
we have to find unity.
So we need to work towards
a broad, national agreement.
The terror package
doesn't cover the actual threat.
The People's Party won't budge,
so we're out.
They interview me
and then evaluate me.
According to my lawyer and the doctor
I stand a good chance this time.
We'll be together so much
the two of you'll miss being alone.
- Is Daddy coming home?
- Yes, he is.
- Is he getting out now?
- It is possible.
What if it doesn't happen?
She was attacked in her kitchen.
She was stabbed 21 times.
- This is where we found her.
- She had no connection to this place.
- She was in the Danish Defense?
- As military legal advisor.
I have some photos of a dead woman
in Memorial Park.
Your predecessor wanted
to be kept up-to-date.
Memorial Park
is a national monument.
This gives rise to speculation,
which we want to quash.
Did he stab her to make her talk?
What about?
- Dog tag.
- My old army buddy is troubled.
- I can help you, Myg.
- You don't know shit!
The Probation Service
turned you down. I'm sorry.
- Easy now, easy.
- Let me go!
- The killer got it on film.
- I just opened the link.
I accuse the Danish government
of hypocrisy.
The Muslim League will avenge
the suffering Denmark has caused
in Palestine,
Iraq and Afghanistan.
Where is the veterans' club located?
The secretary is Allan Myg Poulsen.
Hey!
THE KILLING
News special. A terror threat
has been issued against Denmark.
Our sources confirm
the validity of this threat.
A video recording
lasting 45 seconds
was streamed onto an Islamist website
at 5:03pm today.
Sources in The Ministry of Justice
do not wish to comment
until they have been informed
by the police and Special Branch.
The victim is Allan Myg Poulsen, 36,
unmarried. Professional soldier.
For some years, he worked for the army
out of the nearby barracks.
He also did odd jobs
for a veterans' club,
The Black Berets,
whose office is at this address.
We have instituted a search
for the man who ran off.
But Lund barely saw him.
- Are there any other witnesses?
- A neighbour saw him come home.
The back door was forced open.
His assailant was waiting for him.
According to Forensics
the victim threw up and shat himself.
I think the perpetrator was alone
with the victim for some time.
He must have known
the building was derelict.
- Have you found the murder weapon?
- It's around his neck.
Lund found him.
What about Special Branch?
Where is Lund?
We must search the tracks.
He scaled a barbed wire fence.
He may have bled.
I saw only him,
but there might have been others.
Have Special Branch said anything?
They were clearly taken by surprise.
We have to start from scratch.
May I have a copy of the video?
Lund, you're not on this case.
What do you mean?
- You sent someone for me.
- To have you look at the case.
You knew something was amiss,
or you wouldn't have asked me.
The situation has changed.
But your record hasn't.
There are disciplinary problems,
and you threatened
a colleague with at loaded gun.
They haven't forgotten
at police headquarters.
Your negligence may have caused
the death of Jan Meyer.
Why should I trust you?
Give me one good reason
for taking you on.
I know I have made mistakes.
I only wish I could...
But I can't.
This is what I do best.
I'll contact
your work place in Gedser.
We'll borrow you for a while,
a couple of days to start with.
We'll take it from there.
Are we agreed on the matter?
The video is ready for you
at police headquarters.
- They have arrived.
- Kiss the girls for me. Bye.
I told the press
to wait for your comments.
The Prime Minister's office
must be kept informed about the case.
Erik König, chief of Special Branch.
Deputy Commissioner Ruth Hedeby.
The link was activated at 5:03pm.
At sunset, the end of Ramadan.
We traced the website
to a server in London.
The authorities closed
the website down at 5:23pm.
- How many saw the video?
- Quite a few.
They were sent
to the ministries and the media.
Can't you trace who sent them?
No. They were sent from hotspots.
The website is a forum
for fundamentalists.
It was registered in Denmark.
By whom and when?
Six months ago.
We are tracing the holder.
- What about the Muslim League?
- We have nothing on them at present.
Either the group is new
or a branch of an existing one.
What do we know
about the woman in the video?
She has been identified
as the victim in Memorial Park.
Anne Dragsholm, 35, solicitor.
There is also a second victim.
When did that happen?
We found him,
while the video was being sent out.
The victim is a man of 36,
Allan Myg Poulsen, soldier.
He has served abroad,
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
It seems quite important
that the woman also served abroad
as military legal advisor.
Both are symbolic targets
connected to the army.
It was clearly an act of retribution.
How could this take us by surprise?
Well, it's an unusual case.
There was no indication of terror
at the Memorial Park killing.
Had we heard
about the dog tag earlier...
It wasn't found until this evening.
Nobody's blaming anybody.
- But how do we solve this?
- We will coordinate with the police.
Issue a warning to all barracks.
But keep the media in the dark
concerning the second victim.
Out of the question!
Two people are dead.
We are under threat.
People are entitled to know
what is going on.
The Prime Minister
has agreed to a press release.
Great. I'll see him later today.
- Have the bereaved been informed?
- Yes.
Do you have a moment?
- You'll need your tie.
- Thanks.
Please note how the ministry
has followed procedure in this case.
I'm sure you have,
but the question still has to be asked.
The former minister
was aware of the case.
But none of us thought
it would develop into such madness.
Carina and I must know your position.
This is a serious matter.
It doesn't allow for any more
spontaneous reactions on your part.
- It won't happen again.
- Thank you.
We should announce
the agreement tomorrow.
We must show unity.
- If indeed we have it to show.
- Why shouldn't we?
- We're ready.
- Go on. The press is waiting.
We must search the tracks
and interview the train staff.
Look for any CCTV recordings.
He didn't vanish into thin air.
Couldn't Special Branch
give us a list of suspects?
We'll hear from them
in due course.
Find out about the victims,
their past, their military records.
Is Black Berets the connection?
Have their files been accessed?
Did they contain the victim's names?
The two dog tags were forged.
Where did they come from?
And who ordered them?
Sarah Lund is here to assist us.
Some of you know her, others don't.
- I expect you to welcome her.
- Right! Let's get started.
You'll be driving with Strange.
Report directly to me.
The Muslim League?
Why have we never heard of them?
That's not unusual.
Groups are formed spontaneously
for a certain cause.
- What about the website?
- No new facts yet.
Special Branch
will get back to us on that.
Let's start with visiting
Allan Myg Poulsen's barracks.
- That's all the family he had.
- I agree. Let me...
Sorry.
You'd better take
the desk opposite mine.
I have some degree of tidiness here.
But the other side is all yours.
Here you are.
Strange will show you
where the lockers are.
- Shall we hit the road?
- Yes.
Both victims have been
stationed abroad by the army.
The murders may be retaliation
for our part in the war against terror.
Jarnvig here.
Are you watching the news?
Yes.
I spoke to the Defense Command.
Put guards on all exits and triple shifts
in the surrounding terrain.
...the perpetrator asap.
This is all I can say at present.
- Why didn't you know about it?
- What about the perpetrator?
Very well.
I'll be right there.
- ...hard for us. Thank you.
- And the terror package?
Louise, I have to leave now.
Jonas is asleep.
I put a coin from the tooth fairy
under his pillow.
Thanks, Dad.
I want to know
what happened out there.
The Probation Service
refused his application.
They wouldn't let me see him.
The doctor said he was in a rage.
- Did Jonas hear anything?
- No, nothing.
The doctor postponed
any further talk till tomorrow.
- I want a meeting with the lawyer.
- What about?
We must file a complaint
about the refusal.
Our solicitor said he stood a fair chance.
So it doesn't make sense.
- We can apply again in six months.
- Why did you take Jonas?
He wanted to go.
If you have to wait six months,
we could redecorate our ground floor.
Jonas can have his own room.
I'll get it started tomorrow.
You don't care
whether Jens gets out or not.
- Yes?
- I have a message to the colonel.
Come in.
Do they know who did it?
Thank you.
What's up?
Have you seen Myg Poulsen today?
How are you?
I don't know what came over me.
Can I talk to Louise?
She came to visit you.
You weren't told in time.
I told her why you didn't come.
I didn't tell your son anything.
Are you ready to return to your cell?
Was Jonas here too?
- I wish to speak to Louise.
- One thing at a time.
- You must get back on medication.
- I don't want any.
- Then I can't get you out of here.
- There's nothing wrong with me.
If you won't cooperate,
you'll have to stay here.
The police want to question you
about Allan Myg Poulsen.
But judging by this conversation
they will have to wait.
Question me. Why?
Our number is on his mobile.
And he came here to visit.
He was found killed this evening.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell them
to come back tomorrow.
- Killed?
- That's all I know.
I'll look in on you tomorrow.
If you need anything, ask the guard.
OK. Thanks. Bye.
The flyers by the body
have been translated.
"Fight for God's cause. Kill those
who place others next to God."
- Citations from the Koran.
- Do the flyers give any other clues?
They are trying to find out
where they were printed.
OK. I'm Ulrik.
I've been in the department
a year or so.
I'm recently divorced
and that's OK.
I have two wonderful kids.
It's hard for them now,
but in the long run, it's best for everyone.
I like football
and opera, up to a point.
Take the next left turning.
Allan Myg Poulsen was decorated.
- How about you?
- I was never decorated.
There is not much to tell.
You've been to Gedser.
And the rest of it you've heard about.
- I don't listen to gossip.
- I'd rather not talk about it.
We can talk about everything else.
It's not, that I don't want
to talk with you.
- Next left turning?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Colonel Torsten Jarnvig.
- Ulrik Strange.
Sarah Lund.
Major Christian Søgaard.
Please be seated.
One of your men was found killed
a few hours ago.
In which way was he connected
to the barracks here?
Lance corporal Myg Poulsen
did service for many years.
We are deeply distressed
upon receiving the news.
How long had he been here?
He started as a conscript
and went on to be a contract soldier.
He was stationed in the Balkans,
Iraq and Afghanistan.
- When did you last see him?
- This morning, at roll call.
He was to be stationed
in Helmand, in a week.
- How was he killed?
- We can't reveal the details.
Is his death connected
to the terrorism threat?
- Is he one of the two victims?
- So it would seem.
- Had he been threatened?
- Not as far as I know.
- Have you received any threats?
- We get them all the time.
Phone calls and mails, every day,
but never from the Muslim League.
Could we have printouts
of the mails and phone calls?
And Allan Myg Poulsen's
personnel file.
Søgaard will give you
what you require.
If that's all, I would like
to inform my staff personally.
Do you know this woman?
- Anne Dragsholm.
- No. I don't know her.
She wasn't trained here,
but she was military legal advisor.
We would like to talk to someone
who knew Myg Poulsen well.
His company commander
will show you around.
This case will cause
insecurity and worry.
The last thing my men need
before getting into that plane.
It is vital that all communication
go through me or major Søgaard.
- Are we agreed on this?
- Of course.
The barracks room is for eight,
but most of them are at home now.
This was his bunk
and this was his closet.
How well did you know him?
Not very well. Nobody did.
- He was a loner.
- When did you last see him?
At roll call this morning at 06:30.
And later in the day?
No. They had the rest of the day off.
- When?
- After physical training.
When did he sign up
to be stationed abroad?
- Last week.
- Last week?
Was it a sudden decision?
He had been
considering it for a while.
- Strange speaking.
- Who is Raben?
- I don't know.
- Right. Thanks.
They've found the printers.
The flyers were delivered at Aisha
Oman's bookshop in Nørrebro.
- Anything else?
- No. Thank you.
The People's Party and the Opposition
support the government.
However, they insist
on being informed about the case
before going public
with the agreement.
So they won't make
any statement of agreement yet?
- Not until they've heard from you.
- Plough was right.
They're just waiting
for an excuse to criticise us.
Telling them we're at a loss in the case
is playing into their hands.
Go home.
There's nothing you can do here now.
- Still no news of the investigation?
- No.
We'll call you
as soon as we hear anything.
Give me Krabbe's and Agger's
phone numbers.
I'll call them on my way home.
I checked your diary
for the next couple of days.
- You should warn your family.
- No problem.
My wife would prefer me to be here
and try to sort things out.
See you tomorrow.
Shall I call the driver?
No, I'll find him.
Thank you. Goodbye for now.
Thank you.
- Hi, Buch. Did you get my message?
- Yes, Krabbe. Thank you.
- Of course you should be informed.
- How bad is it?
- At present the situation is...
- Thomas?
Special Branch have discovered
who set up the website with the video.
Excuse me,
I needed to consult my diary.
I'll brief you tomorrow morning.
- Why not now?
- Something came up.
And I'd like Agger to be present.
How about eight o'clock?
- Yes. Fine.
- Good. Bye.
Thomas Buch speaking.
- No one of that name lives here.
- Are you sure it was a bookshop?
Hi. We are looking for Aisha Oman.
- You've come to the wrong place.
- She owns a bookshop.
Check the ground floor.
Kodmani. He sells books.
But I haven't seen him today.
- We'll check.
- Thanks.
Perhaps you're looking for his wife.
- But she died a couple of years ago.
- Thanks.
- Did you knock on the door?
- Yes.
Open the door! Police!
Police. Hands up!
Why don't you answer the door?
My children were in bed asleep.
What do you want?
- Anyone else in the flat?
- No. Who are you looking for?
Don't be afraid.
Just go back to bed.
It's all right.
Three months ago, you ordered
some flyers using your wife's name.
- Why did you do that?
- Do you have a search warrant?
- Where were you earlier today?
- I demand a solicitor.
I know my rights.
And you have no right to do this.
I want to see your search warrant.
- Move aside a bit.
- Come on.
That's my storeroom.
I demand to see a search warrant.
Stay where you are!
We'll just wait here. Stay calm.
WEDNESDAY 16 NOVEMBER
7:43AM
Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
Fundamentalist, widower.
Moroccan, living in Denmark
for 16 years.
The video was on his website.
But he has several cover names.
- That was the good news.
- And the bad news?
Special Branch is calling a meeting.
Kodmani served time
for inciting to terrorism.
They had their sights on him
and are pissed off about the arrest.
- Why?
- You shouldn't stay at a hotel.
- I've made up a bed for you.
- I don't want to disturb you.
I'll give you the key. I'm at Bjørn's place
most of the time anyway.
- We'll talk about Sunday later.
- What about Sunday?
Our wedding.
Bjørn's relatives are staying here.
We'll be more than 30 people.
I'll get you that key.
I hope you'll have time
to have dinner with Bjørn and me.
I'd like to get to know him,
but I'm going to be busy.
- And I'd like to see Mark too.
- You must have time to eat!
Bjørn has a very nice colleague
I would like you to meet.
Well, I suppose it doesn't
have to be right now.
That's for me. Must dash.
I'd love to have dinner
with Bjørn and you.
- Who is he?
- Have you got that key for me?
- Yes, of course.
- Thanks.
- Sarah?
- See you, Mum.
We had to act upon the situation.
Maybe you should have informed us.
You jeopardised the investigation.
It had ground to a halt.
There are two corpses
in the forensic morgue.
Right. Where do we go from here?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
- The main thing is we got our man.
- No.
We are not only after him.
Kodmani has an alibi.
And since we're watching him,
his alibi is watertight.
It could be part of a greater plan.
He had time to make preparations.
We'll intensify the investigation.
Any other suspects?
Just focus on Kodmani
and his followers.
Agreed?
Shall we?
- What about the man they arrested?
- He has not yet been questioned.
Let's go public
with the agreement today
to show the killers
that we shall not be moved.
Why were you taken by surprise?
The first murder seemed
to be a crime of passion.
The ministry couldn't know
it had any connection to terrorism.
- Anything else you need to tell us?
- No. What is your position?
God knows
we're opposed to this war.
This won't make us
change our attitude.
- But we must stick together.
- It is important to show unity.
But you must admit that the
People's Party warned you about this.
We don't pass any bills
on the basis of current cases.
Two people died.
A fundamentalist was arrested.
Save your breath.
We will not vote
for the terror package
if the killing points to the groups
we warned against.
- You don't know that.
- No, but it's a probability.
What if the suspect is guilty?
I can't justify it to our voters.
Might I make a suggestion?
Let's find out more about the suspect
and meet later.
If all is clear,
we can go public this evening.
- A very good suggestion.
- Right. We'll get back to you.
I want to make sure
you realise...
If you alter the agreement,
you can count us out.
That won't happen.
I'll call you later.
Must we negotiate with Krabbe now?
He is under pressure due to the case.
He must feel
that we are forthcoming.
- I won't compromise.
- Let's hear what the police say.
- Maybe there's no problem.
- I think there is.
The police made the arrest
without asking Special Branch
The suspect isn't just anybody.
- My client is willing to cooperate.
- We're looking forward to it.
- Tell us about the Muslim League.
- I only heard about it yesterday.
- The video was on your website.
- I have the following statement.
"My client sells and publishes books
to spread the word of the Koran.
"Using his freedom
of religion and of speech
"he offers the website as a literary
platform and an international forum.
"He knew nothing of the video
and has never incited to terrorism."
You've got wiser.
Nevertheless we found evidence
at your address,
videos and written material
inciting to militant action.
AII of it is within my legal rights.
Your flyers were at the scene
of the crime.
Your website was used.
It's either solitary confinement
or cooperation. Nobody believes you.
In the last few weeks I have been
contacted through my website
by someone calling himself
'Faith Fellow'.
Faith Fellow
seems to share my ideals.
He described a religious video,
which he wanted to upload.
It suddenly appeared
on my website last night.
- Do you still have his messages?
- I've deleted them, unfortunately.
If your Faith Fellow exists,
you'll know who he is.
No. If my flyers
were being used by criminals
they must have got them
at the public library.
- May we see a list of libraries?
- Sure. If you think, it's any use.
Thank you.
That'll be all for today.
Why shouldn't it be of any use?
We are all in the hands of Allah.
Allahu akbar.
Don't waste your time
on the Faith Fellow.
Here's a list of Kodmani's
religious circles, his customer file
and a print-out with names
of people in Denmark
who have visited his website.
They must all be questioned.
And by the way,
we found blood on the barbed wire.
- But we have no match on the DNA.
- Right.
- I'll be gone for an hour or so.
- Now what?
Raben is the name of the army buddy
Myg Poulsen visited yesterday
in the institution
at Herstedvester.
He should have been questioned,
but the institution put it off.
Brix told us
to concentrate on Kodmani.
Why would Kodmani upload
the video onto his own website?
- Why question some army buddy?
- I can't say.
No!
Sorry.
- See you.
- AII right...
Søgaard?
- Did the police find anything?
- Not that we know of.
The men are in shock,
so let's hope they do, soon.
- Did you know him well?
- Not really.
But we met the other day.
He was an old friend of Jens'.
I'm sorry to hear
he was turned down yet again.
Your father told me
his basement is being redecorated.
- Evidently you're staying on.
- For a while, at least.
I'm going to see them now.
I left a list of vaccinations
for you in the infirmary.
Let me know,
if your father needs help moving out.
- Why can't I see him?
- AII things considered.
His rage.
He won't take his medicine.
He hasn't for a long time.
Why now?
Let's hope it's not a relapse.
He'll have to cooperate.
He usually does.
Let's give it another week.
We have a meeting with our lawyer.
There are decisions to be made.
His case and the ruling.
I understand.
But your husband needs rest now.
AII my husband needs
is to see me.
I'll see what I can do.
But he must be more cooperative.
It's a bad time to question him.
There was an incident. Can't it wait?
I won't be long.
Why is he here?
Abduction and threats.
How's that?
He was wounded
and discharged from service.
He was committed
suffering from delusions.
He took a nurse hostage
and threatened to kill her.
He was committed
to this institution indefinitely.
- He hadn't been here for a while.
- I asked him to come.
He had found a job for me.
But I won't be needing it now.
Was he nervous?
Did he seem afraid of something?
Myg wasn't easily scared.
But he seemed very uneasy.
Perhaps he was in trouble.
- Of what sort?
- I don't know.
How did he die?
He...
He had been strung up by his legs,
head down.
He had been slashed with a dog tag.
Does that ring a bell?
No.
He hadn't served abroad for years.
Why didn't he want to now?
He wasn't happy about being at home.
If that's all,
I'd like a bit of peace now.
Of course.
Actually,
there was one other thing.
Do you know this woman?
Anne Dragsholm,
former military legal consultant.
Was she connected
to Allan Myg Poulsen?
Why is that important?
She was killed two weeks ago.
We believe
there may be a connection.
I don't know her.
If Myg did, he never mentioned her.
- You're quite sure you don't know her?
- I don't know her.
No...
Well, thank you for your assistance.
Goodbye.
Thanks.
I wish to cooperate.
Tell the clinical director.
- Did you find anything?
- I'm not sure.
OK. We have many of Kodmani's
disciples in for questioning.
But none of them seem suspicious.
But something else came up.
Remember the guy at barracks?
- Who?
- Said Bilal, company commander.
- He's in Kodmani's customer file.
- What?
Yes. He's bought
a lot of rabid Islamist literature.
I'm on my way.
He is a member of several
Islamist organisations.
He claims his website was misused
by others to get the video out.
But he has a criminal record.
Isn't that correct?
Until the investigation is over,
we can't be sure.
We don't make laws according
to current cases, but we have an offer.
We can form a committee
to investigate the necessity
of banning the organisations
mentioned by the People's Party.
Buch.
I don't want it
to land on the shelf.
The People's Party could take
full credit for this committee.
And the minister is willing
to set fixed dates for its conclusions.
You won't let your voters down.
- Problem solved.
- Thanks.
But we won't make any decisions
as things are now.
Discuss it
and get back to us tomorrow.
By tomorrow?
Indefinitely is more like it.
- It's is up for vote next week.
- That may be too soon.
If we are to prove ourselves able
we must talk about
how to fight fundamentalism.
What next?
You'd have me ban Islam?
I think it's time we call it a day.
He's taking advantage of the case.
I won't tolerate it!
- The Prime Minister must step in.
- It's your supporting party.
- You must work things out.
- No. We agree with the Opposition.
Tell Birgitte the press conference
tonight is off. I'll call her.
She has her own press conference.
What? There isn't any.
- Let the press know the plain facts.
- Just give me a moment.
- I was going to call you about it.
- What's going on?
We are out. You'll have to make do
with the People's Party.
The party is agreed.
We no longer have confidence in you.
You agreed
on our proposal to Krabbe.
- Buch. You have cheated on me.
- Let's have a talk.
I know about the memo.
What memo?
The memo Special Branch
gave your predecessor,
warning him about terrorism
in connection with the first killing.
Someone in your ministry
has been asleep on the job.
The control committee should
have looked at the case long ago.
- I've no idea what you're on about.
- I've seen that memo.
If I were you, I'd wouldn't
make too many promises.
Do you have a moment?
The colonel
is at a meeting in town.
- It's you we want to talk to.
- Take over.
Do you know
Abdel Hussein Kodmani?
No.
You've bought many books of him.
'AI Jihad' and 'Radical Islam'.
Is this a special interest of yours?
- I bought the books on the Internet.
- Why?
- What is this about?
- Just answer the question.
So that my platoon commanders
may get to know the mentality.
They should know what to expect.
I want them back in one piece.
You yourself are a Muslim...
I was ordered to buy those books.
Ask my superior officers.
If that's all,
I'd like to get on with it.
I think you're bleeding.
What were you up to last night,
before we came out here?
- I was in my office.
- Any witnesses?
- You are wasting your time.
- Stay here. We want a word with you.
Do you consent
to giving a blood sample?
Not before the colonel gets back.
We can apply again in six months,
but you must cooperate.
But that's what
he's been doing all along.
There can be no repetition
of the incident yesterday.
- Can you manage that?
- Yes, of course.
Can we have a moment alone?
Yes.
I'm really sorry about Myg.
But I need you now.
- How is Jonas?
- He's fine.
But you must focus on this.
This is more important.
I would like us to plan a strategy.
Should we find another lawyer?
Should we file a complaint?
- What shall we do?
- It will have to wait.
I have to see the clinical director
about my medication.
We have many practical matters
to decide upon.
Where should Jonas go to school?
Where shall we live?
I have messed up.
So I have to put it right.
- But it can't wait.
- See you, love.
- What's up, Raben?
- I missed you all.
Raben?
If you need to change clothes,
you'd better hurry.
- Do I have time for a shower?
- I'll give you two minutes.
Raben?
Coming...
Let Raben out.
Jens Peter Raben is on his way
to the psychiatric ward.
He'll be with you in four minutes.
- Raben? Dinner in half an hour?
- Right. In half an hour.
I can assure you that Bilal
has nothing to do with the killing.
If he doesn't start talking,
we'll book him.
AII communication must pass
through me or major Søgaard.
Then get your man
to open his mouth.
Lance corporal Myg
was under my command.
I went to see him
to sort things out.
The door was open,
so I walked in.
I saw him hanging from the ceiling.
I didn't see anyone but him.
I heard you arrive, and bolted
to protect the barrack's reputation.
- Some explanation!
- What had Myg done?
There had been
a serious security breach.
How's that?
Our chief of security informed me
of an illegal entry into our database.
The log files showed that Myg Poulsen
had accessed confidential data.
What is in that database?
- He had downloaded a pdf-file.
- Containing what?
A list of soldiers in a team.
His own team in Afghanistan.
He probably needed the list
for the veterans' club.
You'll have to give up some DNA.
Had you given us that yarn yesterday,
we might have believed it.
It was reported.
After you left,
Bilal came and told me all about it.
I contacted Special Branch, and
Bilal's explanation has been accepted.
You would know about it,
if you'd contacted me as agreed.
OK.
That was Brix.
Special Branch has arrested
three persons connected to Kodmani.
May I borrow that photograph?
Coordination with Special Branch
only seems to be one-way.
Never mind. Send two officers
to the institution at Herstedvester.
Yes.
Bottom left corner.
What am I supposed to see?
Next to Myg Poulsen.
That's Raben, his friend,
whom I visited today.
So what?
- Anne Dragsholm?
- He claimed not to know her.
Concerning a detainee
Jens Peter Raben. Unlock it please.
He is to be brought in
for questioning immediately.
He disappeared behind the building.
There's a blind angle.
But he didn't come
out on the other side.
Over here!