Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
- What does Special Branch know?
- Raben was squad leader.
- They excelled in Afghanistan.
- I want to see that place.
No officer Perk. No corpses.
A Taliban doesn't wear gold.
Therefore, it couldn't have been
a suicide bomber.
- This is ridiculous!
- I gather you have resigned.
You've got the wrong man!
My wife and son are at the barracks.
Bilal, someone erased
the radio messages. Who?
We've searched the place.
There are no bodies!
THE KILLING
The Government is facing
its worst crisis ever.
The Prime Minister
has fired the Minister of Defense
for covering up the killings
of civilians in Afghanistan.
The killings seem to be connected
to the terrorism case.
We're on our way. Bye.
Bilal escaped in a jeep.
The entire force is after him
and the borders are guarded.
Raben's wife is missing
from the barracks. Bilal took her.
There's no trace of Raben,
but he can't do much in his condition.
You're probably right.
Where is Brix?
Bilal rented a flat
where he planned the five killings.
- Brix is expecting us.
- I'll meet you there.
Lund? You haven't said a word
during the entire journey.
- What's wrong?
- Hello there!
How sweet of you
to come and meet us.
- Where have you been?
- In Prague. Living it up!
What have you been up to?
I had a terrible nightmare.
I dreamt you were lying alone and lifeless.
I couldn't revive you.
- I was crying, Mark was crying.
- I'll get the car.
I'm so glad
you no longer have that job.
Bjørn and I will
visit you often in Gedser.
- Lund here.
- Why did your nice partner leave?
We found the remains
of two adults and two children.
They had been burnt in an oven
which was hidden by debris.
Well done, Lund.
I passed your fax on.
Each skull has a bullet hole.
It looks like an execution.
- Anything on Bilal?
- We found Per K. Møller's dog tag.
- The one Raben saw on that officer.
- Ask if anyone here has seen him.
- Did we get a Special Forces list?
- That is no longer our concern.
The killings of civilians
will be investigated by the army.
We're not finished with the officer.
I saw what he had done.
It was like a ritual killing.
Like the killings here.
- Focus on the present.
- It could be an officer.
- It could be Strange.
- Check Bilal.
- Brix!
- We'd like to get off soon.
Mum... It was just a nightmare.
Everything is all right.
We found the key to the flat,
a mobile phone
and the broken-off halves
of the five dog tags.
There are no other tenants
in the building.
It's used only
for parking and storage.
- Shouldn't we wait for Strange?
- No, let's get on with it.
Camera, discs,
a computer, explosives.
They all match
the evidence from the killings.
We found the murder weapons
used on Dragsholm and the chaplain.
Forensics confirmed it's their DNA.
Bilal is a Muslim.
But he hates Islamists
more than anyone knew.
He saw Raben's squad as traitors
for attempting to reveal
the killing of civilians.
Bilal invented the Muslim League
and tried to frame
Kodmani and the like.
He was inspired
by his knowledge of military history.
Dragsholm was his first victim.
She wanted to re-open the case.
They met a few months ago.
Then he rented these premises.
He arranged it all, using Hotmails
and Per K. Møller's name.
He opened a PO Box
in the same name.
- How did Bilal know Per K. Møller?
- From Team Ægir.
Did anybody see Bilal?
Any fingerprints or DNA?
No. He must have taken great care.
The only proof that this is Bilal's
is the key at the barracks.
He gets the Colonel fired because he
was investigating old radio messages.
Then he takes off
with Louise Raben.
- Radio messages? From the officer?
- Is Bilal of no significance?
Yes. He can help us find the officer.
But he may not be the killer.
Why would Bilal hide a key
and a mobile phone at the barracks?
Who called it up
to make you search the place?
- You were in Afghanistan.
- We don't know who Faith Fellow is.
Dragsholm said
she'd found the officer.
We won't get that Special Forces list.
It's not our jurisdiction.
This proves nothing.
Raben's been right in everything.
- And he accused Strange...
- I double-checked Strange!
All the army authorities confirm
that Strange was demobilised
long before the incident.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What is the matter with you?
Maybe it's lack of sleep.
Jet lag.
Sometimes I get the feeling
you like some things about me.
But you have
a bloody odd way of showing it!
Now that we have cleared the air...
I'm really sorry, if...
Right. Where do we go from here?
- It's important to find Bilal.
- Yes.
And we must talk to Søgaard
about the radio messages.
If it's Bilal,
he must hate Islamists.
The video was sent
just at the end of the Ramadan.
He must be an extremist in reverse.
If it's Bilal,
he needn't look far for inspiration.
MUSLIM LEAGUE
The jeep was seen on the bridge,
heading for Funen.
- Have you no clues?
- No. Maybe she was on to something.
My daughter is missing.
What are you doing to find her?
- Could Bilal be hiding more?
- Ask Operative Command.
- Do you know where Bilal went?
- No! If I did, I'd be there!
- Are we done here?
- Did you know he hated Islamists?
We shared the same enemy.
He seemed the perfect soldier.
Look at this.
It doesn't seem so now.
Let us know, if you hear anything.
Also concerning Jens Peter Raben.
Jonas... You've got your jacket on.
Have you been playing outside?
Joakim and his parents
are taking you to the zoo.
When you get back,
Mummy will probably be here.
I know. That's what Daddy says too.
It's a secret.
He's waiting for you by the fence.
- Have the police found anything?
- The police know nothing.
Bilal isn't at any of the facilities.
You must have some idea.
- Jarnvig. Just a moment.
- Did you contact the barracks?
She mustn't be hurt. Keep away.
- We must help each other.
- It's your fault!
She was helping you. Stay away.
You've done enough damage. Hello?
We must stick together
against the enemy.
We are not the enemy!
- Where are you?
- I only did my duty.
- Where is Louise?
- I won't take the blame.
- Bilal. Come back.
- Why did you turn against me?
- We didn't!
- The police found evidence.
- Someone is trying to frame me.
- Let Louise go!
Tell General Arild
to get me out of this!
What are you talking about?
- Let me talk to Louise.
- I'm talking to the Colonel!
We'll do nothing
until we hear from Louise.
- Louise?
- We drove for three to four hours.
- A place underground.
- Don't you touch her!
I'll call again this evening.
If you contact the police,
she dies.
She said a three to four hour drive.
A place underground.
- Where could they be?
- It could be a military facility.
There are many in North Zealand,
but that's only an hour away.
Bilal, let me go.
What's wrong with you?
The Prime Minister knew
I had something on him.
The Minister of Defense
was about to reveal it all
but the Prime Minister
put the blame on us.
The Minister of Defense
refuses to comment.
- How could the Prime Minister know?
- Someone warned him.
You've detained me all night,
for no reason.
- For the sake of national security.
- I've done nothing to jeopardise it.
Let's sum it all up
and see if it adds up to anything.
A confidential Special Branch memo
gets leaked from your office.
You met with a suspended
police officer, Sarah Lund. What for?
You visited the former Minister
of Justice, who then took his own life.
Your Personal Secretary
accessed data, illegally.
You undermined
Special Branch's investigation.
You fired König.
You defended Islamist organisations
and their rights.
You have been in contact
with a member of the PFLP.
Journalist, formerly employed in
the Defense Ministry, Connie Vemmer.
Everything indicates that you,
at a time of war
have been undermining the national
interest and our elected Government.
It doesn't enter in to it whether
or not civilian Afghans were killed.
Do you maintain your accusations
against the Prime Minister?
No. I'll do even worse.
He is the traitor!
What is going on?
Tell me what's happening!
- Are you all right?
- Yes. What is going on?
They found something in Afghanistan.
You should see this.
Sarah Lund found it. The police
are chasing a Danish soldier.
He committed the recent murders
to prevent the case from being solved.
- And the officer who did this?
- The army is taking care of it.
Why didn't they find the bodies,
in the first place?
Call a meeting with my parliamentary
party, but without the Prime Minister.
They're anxious to see you too.
You can get what you want
if you play your cards right.
There is nothing on the Prime Minister.
The Minister of Defense was lying.
That's what they all say.
The Prime Minister
wanted you out of here.
He'll get no brownie points.
We must arrange that meeting.
Are you back at Christiansborg?
Do you support the Government?
Do you maintain your accusations?
What did Special Branch want?
- Hi, Buch. Good to see you.
- Likewise, I'm sure.
Excuse the mess.
I left in a bit of a hurry.
We were rather pro-active yesterday.
- But we had to protect the party.
- At the expense of the truth?
Yes, right.
But we are much the wiser for it.
On the part of the parliamentary party,
I wish to apologise.
Very well.
It's important to look ahead.
We must act quickly.
There are only two options.
Either the Prime Minister resigns,
or we force him to do so.
Gitta, you know the rules. Find out
how many it takes to topple him.
That would mean an election.
- Of course!
- There's no need for that.
The Minister of Defense said
Gert is behind all this.
He wants the Prime Minister
to take the blame.
We can blame
the Minister of Defense
and Monberg
to get this matter sorted out.
But there's no need to throw
the baby out with the bath water.
The Prime Minister wants to see you.
He is preparing a reshuffle.
Rumour has it
you may be promoted.
- You wanted us to sort it out.
- Leave!
- So you like being a minister!
- An election would ruin the party.
I'll talk to Krabbe. Is he really
the guardian of our democracy?
- Krabbe and the Prime Minister agree.
- Only until I've talked to him.
Thank you!
Goodbye. Chop, chop!
- Do you know Bilal's contacts?
- Friends, family?
- I don't know him that well.
- Contacts in the army?
- I don't know. It can't be Bilal.
- We have evidence.
Radio communications.
Some messages were deleted.
- Who was responsible?
- Bilal was, but...
Civilians were killed.
And an officer was there.
Bilal concealed the messages.
Tell us what you know.
I never knew about the messages.
Just like you had never
talked to Anne Dragsholm?
You'll have to ask Bilal.
The message, five days previously.
You must have known about that.
Special Forces were heading
for the village. Who were they?
- I don't know.
- Did Anne Dragsholm mention them?
- Did they split up?
- I don't know, damn it!
The killer used
Per K. Møller's identity.
- Did Bilal know him?
- Not personally.
- Was Bilal there when he died?
- No.
- Were Special Forces there?
- I wouldn't think so.
He was alone in the explosion
and was taken to the ISAF hospital.
- The one in Lashkar Gar?
- Yes, I believe so.
- Was he wearing his dog tag?
- Normally, a part gets broken off.
It is sent to the bereaved,
or put in the coffin.
Lund?
- Hey! Now what?
- They found the jeep.
No Bilal, no Louise Raben.
Bilal changed the number plates.
We've tapped
Colonel Jarnvig's phone.
Bilal phoned him from
somewhere north of Copenhagen.
- What did Bilal say?
- The Colonel must find a solution.
The Colonel and Raben
are chasing him.
- We're trying to stop them.
- Bilal must have a hiding place.
What military facilities
are there in the area?
We've got that covered.
There's a derelict
Cold War facility in this area.
Has that been checked?
Get Frederik Holst.
He's army surgeon at Lashkar Gar.
Ask him what happened
to Per K. Møller's dog tag.
Come on, Lund!
And ask if any Special Forces
officers were in hospital then.
Yes, will do.
We can't keep looking.
We must call the police.
- Drive on.
- Arild could cut a deal with Bilal.
- We'll continue.
- He's not here, damn it!
Stop!
Call the police.
The People's Party won't support
the Government at all costs.
We always aim to get to the truth.
You're welcome. Goodbye.
- What's up?
- I've left you a few messages.
I meant to call you back,
but I'm on my way to a meeting.
Just tell me,
if you'll join the Opposition
in bringing down the Government.
Damn it, Krabbe! We made a deal.
The Prime Minister mustn't stay in office.
The Prime Minister is guilty.
They found proof that civilians were killed.
You only have
the Minister of Defense’s word for it.
He has chosen to take the blame.
Krabbe... Hey! Hello?
What is going on?
The polls were in our favour when
Muslims seemed to be the killers.
And I played it up in the press.
In retrospect, I'm not so sure
it was a good idea.
I don't think we'd be wise
to push for an election.
Thomas, I haven't decided yet.
But I won't give it all up to the Opposition
before thinking it over.
Your grandfather fought
in the Danish resistance...
The Prime Minister
did the right thing.
He gave the Minister of Defense
the boot the moment he knew the truth.
Did you spill the beans? I told you, and,
you went straight to the Prime Minister
because you were terrified
of those ridiculous polls.
What are you talking about?
I was at a party meeting all day.
You are the only one I told,
apart from people in my trust.
Do you know what, Thomas?
There is nobody here you can trust.
It won't be the first time
your staff lead you up the garden path.
I'll call you.
The Prime Minister's office
wants to call a meeting. I declined.
Good. Who prepared
the documents yesterday?
- Plough.
- Who else? Any secretaries?
No. Why?
Could anyone have warned
the Prime Minister?
No. I had the documents
while Plough popped over
to the Prime Minister's office.
It was about that post in Skopje.
Ask him when he gets back.
But I don't know where he is.
On my first day, I received
a file on the killing of Dragsholm.
Monberg's Special Branch memo.
Who leaked it?
Plough said it couldn't be traced.
Where is the information
on the military squad?
Thomas... What's going on?
Did Plough say anything about
the soldiers or the Minister of Defense?
No. Why?
What's going on?
I know Plough was angry
with the Minister of Defense.
He didn't want you
to go for the Prime Minister.
But it couldn't have been Plough!
- Does Plough have a son?
- He did. He died last year.
In a traffic accident?
If I still have a driver,
then tell him I'm on my way.
- In there! He has my daughter.
- Where's Raben?
- He ran after him.
- Is he armed?
Cover all exits.
Tell Brix nobody is to enter.
Louise!
Step forward,
so I can see you!
or I'll shoot her head off.
Put down your weapon.
Where's the Colonel?
I told you not to look for me.
Let her go.
You have me now.
If only you'd kept
your big mouth shut!
There were no civilian killings.
They were informers to the Taliban.
Bilal! Easy now. Put down the gun.
Let's talk this over. Put it down.
Put the gun down.
We'll walk out of here and talk it over.
- I merely did my duty.
- She has nothing to do with it.
She's not guilty.
I can't help you
unless you let her go.
Go.
- I merely did my duty.
- What exactly did you do?
You erased some radio recordings.
Who was the officer? What were they?
Good...
- Lund, something is wrong.
- Come on. Let's leave.
Get out!
For God, king and country!
Plough...
Plough?
His name was Hans Christian.
Hans Christian Plough Vedel.
Vedel was my wife's name.
In the army he was called HC.
He was the only one in the squad
who got out unharmed. A miracle.
But we realised
he came home with a problem.
He too claimed there had been
an incident in the village.
Involving an officer
and the killing of civilians.
We followed the investigation.
It couldn't have happened.
My son changed his statement.
But he got increasingly ill.
A year ago, he drove
in the wrong direction on the motorway
and he was killed.
My marriage broke up,
and I buried myself in guilt.
But then Dragsholm turned up
to see my Minister.
She'd had
a breakthrough in the case.
She'd found the officer.
I suddenly realised
my son had been telling the truth.
I believed Monberg when he promised
to do something about it.
But Dragsholm was killed,
and he did nothing.
Instead, he tried to take
his own cowardly life.
I had to lead you to the case.
I leaked the Special Branch memo.
I made sure Karina found
Monberg's private diary.
So you'd help me find out
what had happened.
You could have helped
the investigation by informing the police.
I had no choice. I was convinced
the Minister of Defense was behind it.
But I had no proof, until yesterday.
I was relieved to give it
to the Prime Minister.
He reacted resolutely. Without hesitation.
The opposite of you.
- How could you be so sure?
- Monberg told me so.
He had a meeting
with the Minister of Defense.
When he returned,
the case was shut down.
Thanks for lending me this book.
Not exactly my taste.
I'm sorry about the course of events,
but you and Karina will do all right.
That meeting was cancelled
and moved to the Prime Minister's office.
- It was about the terrorism package.
- You're the crown prince.
Karina will take over the Ministry.
I'll be Consul General in New York.
It's in Monberg's private diary,
damn it!
If anyone shut down the case,
it was the Prime Minister.
No. Monberg said
it was the Minister of Defense.
He was fucking with you!
Do you know anything else?
- What do you know, damn it?
- I'd like you to go now.
You have been helping
the wrong man.
You helped the man
who caused your son's death.
The right people have been punished.
I owed that to my son.
Now leave, goddamn it!
The judge advocates
will believe you this time.
Drop your accusations
against the police officer.
Your other allegations were correct.
So you've served two years
in custody on the wrong grounds.
Whatever penalty
you may be given for your crimes
you've already served so much time
that you are covered.
You can look forward
to being released very soon.
And I advise you
to sue for damages.
- May we have a moment's privacy?
- Yes, of course.
I have more good news.
You're to be moved to Horserød
where you'll have a family room,
so that you may be together.
See you later.
- I will do anything.
- You don't need to.
As long as you come home.
Every stone must be turned in that village,
and keep me informed.
- Any news about General Arild?
- No. The new team arrives tonight.
- I'd like to bid them welcome.
- Thanks, but I'll do it myself.
- Your daughter wants to see you.
- Show her in.
She's in the house,
packing her things.
- We're leaving now.
- Where are you going?
To visit Jens. They let us spend
the evening with him.
- We have to get away from here.
- Where are you going to stay?
We'll work that out with Daddy,
won't we, Jonas?
- See you soon, Dad.
- Right...
I'll call you.
Come along, dear.
Hello, old sport.
I'm so glad
Louise came to no harm.
What a business! Bilal made sure
none of us knew about the incident.
- Not even you?
- No.
If you know anything,
now's the time to speak up.
I'll do everything I can
to clear up this mess.
- It's more complicated than that.
- What's so complicated about it?
Either you lied to me, the police
and the whole world, or you didn't.
The police didn't need
to get all the information
so long as we didn't believe
civilians had been killed.
- What are you saying?
- The police suspected one officer.
I confirmed
that he'd been sent home.
But that was not entirely true.
He was sent back, shortly after.
But that mission was secret.
That's why
the radio messages were deleted.
There was no evidence of his guilt.
I checked his CV when the police
were asking questions.
The guy went AWOL
for a couple of days.
But that doesn't make him
a war criminal.
We received intelligence
that the father was pro-Taliban.
Get out.
Never show your face here again!
And don't come near my men!
Understood?
I'll put in a word for you, so that
you can stay on at the barracks.
We need you.
We expect you to make the next team
as strong as the last one.
- May we take the case files?
- Yes, of course.
Did the doctor at Lashkar Gar
get my message?
Yes, he got your number.
Shall I follow up on it?
No. Never mind.
But there is one other thing.
We searched the barracks
a few days ago.
- Why didn't we find anything?
- There was nothing there.
Bilal must have put
those things there later.
- And the room and the locker?
- We searched the whole lot.
Did you find out
how Dragsholm found that officer?
No. We went through her case files.
Nothing but meetings with clients,
lawyers, and the police.
- Meetings with the police?
- Yes. At the magistrate's office.
Is that how she contacted us
before she was killed?
- She didn't contact us.
- She must have contacted the police.
She hired her own security people.
May I take that box too?
Who was in charge of the first search
at the barracks, around the lockers?
- I don't remember.
- Are you sure it wasn't Strange?
That's right. It was Strange.
Why?
- Can I take that box?
- Yes...
Lund? My superiors want
me to say "well done" to you.
I admit I had my doubts
when Brix sent for you.
And no less so when I met you.
But now there is a good chance
you won't be sent back to Gedser.
- Congratulations!
- Brix?
That day Strange visited
the refugee centre in Helsingør...
The day I chased the killer.
Did they check his alibi?
Yes. They had split up,
but it was checked.
- Where is he?
- Escorting Raben to Horserød.
Lennart... Come and
say hello to my husband.
He's ready with a glass of wine.
Won't you come?
I'll take care of it.
Go and have a beer.
- You sure?
- He won't make any more trouble.
- Save one for me!
- No way!
- I'm coming with you.
- OK.
- We need to talk. Let me drive.
- What's happened?
- Give me the key.
- All right.
How about some music?
- What do you want to talk about?
- I'll get to that.
- I want to show you something.
- OK.
- Horserød is straight ahead.
- My wife and son are waiting for me.
What's going on?
Something is wrong.
I think Brix is hiding something.
- Brix?
- Come here.
Bloody hell, Lund!
Now what? Lund!
I'd love to be alone with you,
but this is not very cosy.
This is a memorial park
for the Danish resistance.
War heroes
for whom Bilal felt great respect.
Yes. And?
He'd never place Dragsholm here.
He regarded her as a traitor.
But whoever killed Dragsholm and
the others doesn't care about that.
It means nothing to him.
What has that got to do with Brix?
Brix is protecting the killer.
What?
Dragsholm was scared before
she was killed. She lived just over here.
Her house was full of alarms.
She ordered sensors for her garden
and hired her own security guards.
But she never called the police.
- Maybe she felt she was covered.
- No.
I think it was because
she found the officer.
She discovered he was working
at our police station.
It sounds crazy,
but it explains her silence
and why, suddenly, we found
those things at the barracks
even though we'd already searched
the place once. Don't you see?
The killer planted the things
during the search.
But, Lund...
I was in charge of the search.
- I didn't plant anything.
- No, all right.
It must be someone else
on the team.
I don't know what to say.
- Have you talked to Brix about it?
- No. Not yet.
He's going to send me back
to Gedser.
Right. You and I
should have a talk with Brix.
You're not going back to Gedser!
But, for now, we'll stick
to the official version.
Bilal dragged Dragsholm across
the railway tracks and strung her up.
Come on. Let's drive on.
How do you know that?
That she was dragged
across the tracks.
We never discovered that.
Give it a rest!
What do you mean?
Why?
At an unimportant court sitting,
last summer.
It was hot.
She caught sight of my tattoo.
I don't know why,
but she started asking questions.
Just like you.
- Yes?
- Holst. Is Sarah Lund there?
No. She just popped out.
What is it?
I'm calling from Afghanistan.
I'm an army surgeon at ISAF.
I was asked to inquire
into a certain dog tag.
- I found out nothing.
- I'll pass it on.
But I can confirm that
a Special Forces officer was here.
- He was treated for a cut.
- That's fine.
- OK.
- Thank you.
It can't be true.
I was with him every single day.
Don't you see? All Plough
could think of was revenge.
He must have said something
that proves it.
No! Plough believes
he did the right thing.
Thomas, we know
it was the Prime Minister.
He mustn't get away with it.
I don't care about my future career.
- I'm not giving up!
- Good! What do we do?
- Just a moment.
- The press will be waiting.
Tell them we're on our way,
and get all the microphones you can.
Hi, Thomas. Come right in.
We're busy. We want to present
the cabinet reshuffle this evening.
I'm glad to have
a chance to talk to you.
I'm sorry about
your night with Special Branch.
- I owe you an explanation.
- I don't want to hear it.
You can keep
your ministerial offices.
Plough told me about my predecessor
and the Minister of Defense.
I'm going to disclose it all
at a press conference.
And then I'll tell Parliament,
the police and Special Branch.
I'll give them every single
confidential document I've seen.
You've been covering up murder.
People were killed because of you.
I know you were behind it.
And I'll prove it.
We weren't covering up
the killing of civilians.
Things like that happen,
and people can forgive that.
The officer was the problem.
The officer wasn't there.
The incident took place
during a secret mission.
We hadn't cleared it
with the Parliament.
Special Forces missions
must be passed by Parliament.
That is practically impossible.
Secret decisions made
in the Foreign Policy Committee
quickly reach the streets of Kabul.
You knew it all along.
You knew who that officer was.
I had to make a choice.
It wasn't difficult.
At the time, we were
short of money and troops.
You could have done
something to stop it.
Get real! We are at war!
What could we have done?
Do you think round table discussions
are any use in the war on terror?
Would a scandal comfort the families
whose sons return in coffins?
The Taliban are gaining strength.
Sometimes we have
to put aside democracy
in order to fight for democracy.
You should be
the first to appreciate that.
I took you for being harmless.
But I'd like to keep you on.
If you think I've made mistakes
you could help
preventing me making more.
You're out of your mind.
When I tell this to Krabbe and the world,
you'll be finished.
Go ahead.
But there is nothing to tell.
You are not the only one I have
chosen to initiate this evening.
Meet the people
who have all agreed
that it is of utmost importance
to continue the fight.
You killed them all.
Better to kill an innocent person
than to hesitate to kill the enemy.
Didn't they teach you that too?
- You won't get away with this.
- I got away with worse.
And you were the one
who shot the little girl.
You left that bit out
in your statement.
- You've forgotten!
- You're lying!
You shot her.
Suddenly, you started sniveling.
Don't you remember?
Don't you?
Strange here. Raben escaped.
He shot Lund. I'm following him.
Raben, take the gun.
Don't move!
Stay down!