Ten days ago, a woman was killed
in strange circumstances
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
- What does Special Branch say?
- Raben was their squad leader.
- There wasn't anyone called Perk.
- Perk...
Put the gun down.
- I had to shoot.
- Strange was in Special Forces.
I think he was an officer.
We're wasting time.
He has a tattoo on his shoulder.
- He couldn't know about it.
- Was he with you during the murders?
- You and Jonas are my world.
- I'm seeing Søgaard.
You never told me
about that message.
Special Forces were only 150km
from Raben's group.
Søgaard isn't the problem. Did you
help Raben evade Special Branch?
You've been in office seven days.
God created the Earth in seven days.
Unlike him, you're destroying it,
so you have to step down.
- We can't give up.
- What was my predecessor doing?
- And you slept with him!
- Check the dates on the reports.
The Prime Minister
was preparing extra funding
for our effort in Afghanistan.
Tighten up the terrorism package
and the wrong people will suffer.
According to military records,
the man you pointed out
wasn't in Afghanistan at the time.
- I'm sorry.
- It was Raben's fault they died.
Sebastian sent a video diary home.
Raben sees the Taliban everywhere.
All he thinks of is killing.
- It doesn't matter.
- There couldn't have been a Perk.
His big brother is in Afghanistan.
They found this.
You have 36 hours.
THE KILLING
The drama around the Minister of Justice
took a new turn
when the passing of the terrorism
package was postponed.
The Prime Minister has made
no comment, but sources say
that the Minister of Justice
was stepping down.
However, he has called party
leaders to an emergency meeting.
No comment,
but I'm still a Minister. Goodbye.
Were we to overthrow
the Government?
Is everyone coming?
Get hold of the others. Tell Plough
I want an update from the police.
Tell them we can't spin our way out
of this. It's the worst scandal ever.
- I can't believe it!
- You've done the right thing.
I hope so. Get back to me
when the meeting is over.
I said I'm on my way.
I want to talk to you about
the agenda you sent the group.
It sounds like
you're out to get the Prime Minister.
I am. You and Karina said
to be prepared to go all the way.
But not on such shaky grounds.
Every time he went straight
to the Minister of Defense.
If everything points
to the Minister of Defense...
If the Prime Minister is screwing us over,
people have to know.
- What did the police say?
- Nothing new from Raben.
Last night they got an investigative trip
to Helmand cleared.
I don't know what it's about, and
neither did the Deputy Commissioner.
Keep me informed about that.
And get someone to move these chairs.
I just talked to Gitta Spalding.
The meeting might not be held.
Where is everybody?
The Prime Minister
hasn't said he'd come.
Then get hold of him!
The meeting is about him.
As I just told the Minister
calling a meeting at such short
notice is completely inexcusable.
We'll hold the meeting. I have an item
for the agenda. Have a seat.
Let's hear what Thomas
has to say in his defense.
Talk to everyone who's been
in contact with Frederik Holst
while he was home on leave.
Check his phone records, etc.
Track his movements
from day to day.
Where was he
at the time of the murders?
The Ministry called
asking for an explanation
for a trip to Afghanistan.
We had to act quickly. But Strange
has been cleared, and Lund found...
I don't give a shit about
Lund and Strange right now.
We found out that a suspect
had been to Afghanistan.
- Why wasn't I informed?
- Frederik Holst.
A doctor at ISAF's hospital
in Lashkar Gah.
- And brother of one of the dead men.
- You know this has to go through me.
- I don't understand why...
- Because you'd have said no!
You would have had to push
papers around, and I couldn't wait.
We're pretty sure he's our man.
At any rate, it's too late now.
They've already left.
The Ministry of Justice
wants an update.
Frederik Holst...
- What's your relationship to him?
- None. He's not important.
Just tell me what you know.
How's it going?
He's sticking to his old story.
I talked to the prison. Frederik Holst
wanted to visit you there.
Five times.
You refused to see him every time.
I want to see my wife.
We found several letters in his home
that were addressed to you.
You returned them.
He wanted to express his anger
about your responsibility
for his brother's death.
- Ask him yourself.
- We plan to.
- It's in your interest to help us.
- I have.
An officer executed that family
and killed the others.
You claim it was one of our Chief
Inspectors, but he wasn't there.
- I want to talk to my wife.
- Reconsider your testimony.
As it is, it won't do you any good
as we move forward.
Talk to Colonel Jarnvig.
He believes me.
He's being questioned by the military
because he helped you get away.
Your preliminary hearing
is tomorrow.
Why did Jarnvig check
the old messages?
I don't know.
He didn't seem to be himself.
- Just a minute.
- Wait while I talk to Søgaard.
Hi.
- Isn't he back yet?
- No.
Your father has been taken in
for questioning.
He talked to Jens at the ball and
helped him evade Special Branch.
But that's nonsense.
We were there.
They were seen.
Someone told General Arild.
- Who?
- I don't know. Your father confessed.
Your father doesn't seem
to be himself.
Tonight he accused me
of various things.
- He's preoccupied by the murders.
- What did he accuse you of?
Of concealing radio messages
from Special Forces.
It was as if he believed
all the things Jens made up.
He'll be held accountable,
but I'll do what I can to help him.
- Did he suddenly believe Jens?
- Yes, but it seemed far-fetched.
- But what about you?
- I want to see my father.
If you hear anything,
let me know right away.
Louise, you don't think
I'm involved, do you?
No. Why?
For two months, the Minister
did nothing about the hand
and the suspected killing of civilians,
which I find incredible.
However, that allowed
the Prime Minister enough time
to get the deployment of 200 troops
passed in Parliament.
The investigation just took
longer than expected.
How can we believe you?
You should have spoken up long ago.
Instead, five people are dead,
and we've wasted time on scare tactics.
We have to get to the bottom of this,
even if it's within our own ranks.
You keep carping on the same thing...
...and now you're smearing
the Prime Minister.
The People's Party would also like the
Prime Minister's responsibility assessed.
There's no proof.
Let's see, if there's any proof.
If I messed up, I will step down.
You have stepped down. I'll be glad
to repeat that in front of witnesses.
Please tell Thomas
what this meeting is actually about.
Many of us believe
you're damaging the party.
We'd like to vote on excluding you
from the parliamentary group.
I refer you to party statutes, section 12a.
Here's a copy for you.
As you can see, we already have
the necessary signatures.
If that's all for today,
let's resolve the matter now.
Would you please take part
in the meeting you've called?
Before we go on, you should know
the civilian casualties are confirmed.
The police have sent people
to Helmand to investigate.
They'll talk to the doctor
who can comment on the extra hand.
- Excuse me, I haven't been informed.
- Investigators are sent for a reason.
I think we should
get the vote over with.
- When will we know the results?
- They'll fly back tomorrow evening.
Have a preliminary conclusion ready
tomorrow afternoon. Then we'll vote.
I'm going to a memorial service for
the fallen soldiers, so I'm not coming.
Right. Let's get it over with now.
We'll have to wait.
They won't find anything
but it could be misunderstood
if we take action tonight.
Thank you.
Will you cancel my appointment
with Her Majesty?
Did the police know what the doctor
might say about the hand?
- No. He's a murder suspect.
- Will they ask him about the reports?
We need all communication between
the military and the Ministry on this.
- Don't we have right of access?
- Yes, but the system is slow.
The Minister of Defense is the only
one who can give us the Prime Minister.
Why would he talk to us?
Unless we can drive a wedge
between the two of them.
- When will we hear from the police?
- They'll land there in the morning.
- There are two officers...
- One of them must be Lund.
If we can be of help,
let me know. Buch here.
Stop calling me, you little bitch!
WEDNESDAY, 23 NOVEMBER
7:10AM
DAY 10
This is a bad time for us.
This morning we had
two suicide bombers.
The hospital is very busy.
Buckle your helmet.
And your vest.
Otherwise it's useless.
Do you want to freshen up
at the base first?
No, take us to the hospital.
We want to talk to Frederik Holst.
Frederik Holst.
I'm going home soon.
In a week.
I went home on leave
for three weeks.
None of your friends saw you
and you didn't visit your parents.
- Where were you?
- Why do you want to know?
- Korselitze.
- It's in Falster.
- Who was with you?
- I was alone.
Could you tell me
who you think I killed?
They all stopped breathing
while you were on leave.
I spend my life saving people.
Will that be all?
Two years ago, you tried
to save your brother Sebastian.
We saw his video diary.
We found this in your home.
Your interpretation is that Raben
was responsible for his death.
You tried to contact Raben,
but your letters were returned.
Then what did you do?
You're wasting your time.
- I didn't kill anybody.
- Don't give me that shit!
- You didn't cross them out for fun.
- Call it a pastime.
You were on duty
when your brother came in.
You saw him lying there
among the dead and wounded.
It must have been a shock to find out
that Raben and others were to blame.
Yes.
They should have been on the slab,
not your brother.
Yes. And I hope they burn in hell.
I couldn't touch them.
There's no law that can sentence
them for taking him to that village.
So instead, I discovered that
there was an extra body part. A hand.
I tried to get them suspected
of murdering civilians.
No one believed their explanation
about an officer.
I thought they'd all go to prison.
But the judge advocate dismissed it.
The hand belonged
to a suicide bomber.
- That must have pissed you off.
- There wasn't any DNA, but...
You sent the medical report. You wanted
to ruin the squad's reputation.
My brother died of a punctured lung.
That's curable.
He could have survived.
So am I angry
at that psychopath
who forced him
to go to that village
and the lawyer
who got them off scot-free?
You can damn well bet I am. Yes!
But that won't bring Sebastian back.
So what else can I do,
but try to save him
every single day
on that damn operating table?
He can't account for his movements
at the time of the murders...
- I'm asking you if he did it.
- No, he didn't.
- Has Raben said anything new?
- He's sticking to his story.
Major Søgaard's name
keeps turning up.
His testimony wasn't very useful.
Pack your sunglasses and come home.
I assume it was worth it.
Hopefully it wasn't a shot in the dark.
Special Branch and Parliament
are constantly calling me.
Someone thinks
we've made a break in the case.
- I'm sure the Minister of Justice...
- He's hanging by a thread.
Don't count on him.
The brass will look into this.
Do nothing till you've heard from me.
- What do we have?
- No officers.
If it's not this big brother,
we are left with Raben.
The perpetrator bought things
on the web using Per K's name.
Most of the things
were purchased from civilians
and paid in cash
and sent by mail.
A video camera, a laptop,
"The Anarchist's Cookbook".
It was all sent to a PO box
at the same place
where the perpetrator
had Kodmani rent a box.
Hasn't the alias been used
to rent a flat
or storage?
Not as yet.
But there is news.
The third victim was set on fire
by a stolen mobile.
This morning,
the phone was active again.
- There's one answered call.
- From where?
A payphone. The weak signal seems
to come from around Ryvang.
- The barracks?
- It's impossible to say.
Why would the perpetrator use a phone
he knows we're looking for?
Christ, the guy must be human.
Let's get out there right away.
- Isn't the memorial service today?
- We're doing this for their sake.
Maybe we should go by the base.
They might tell us about Søgaard.
We have some hours to kill.
What goes on when Special Forces
are on a mission?
How do you operate?
Five men behind enemy lines.
We track his movements. Why?
Were you in radio contact
with the other units?
No, we shot at anything that moved
and hoped for the best.
Didn't the General say that
no Special Forces were involved?
Stop the car, please. Stop.
What's up?
- How far is the village from here?
- Not now, Lund.
- I just want to see it.
- We're not tourists here.
- Can you take us there?
- You don't have authorisation.
- What are you on about?
- You can't leave the military zone.
Nonsense. Our authorisation
was faxed last night.
Not as far as I can see.
Get your act together. We wouldn't
come without authorisation.
- We have special permission.
- Give me your phone.
What was your name?
Siegler.
If I'm the one who fucked up,
I'm really sorry.
That's OK.
Shall we?
Get hold of the local head of police.
His name is
in the judge advocate's report.
You'll be charged with burglary,
car theft, possession of arms
false imprisonment, violence
and threatening someone's life.
How will you plead?
- Guilty on all counts?
- Has my wife contacted you?
No.
What about the police officers
who went to Afghanistan?
I advise you to forget
the story about the officer.
It can only hurt your case.
There's no need to provoke people.
Your sentence will be harsh.
You might be deemed dangerous
and get an indeterminate
sentence, so...
Do you know if my wife
has tried to visit me?
No, but someone else has.
The police have allowed it.
Hello, Raben.
I've heard so much about you.
I hope you don't mind this little visit.
I'm on official business.
You feel that we've let you down.
And I'm very sorry you feel that way.
- I want you to know that.
- And now I do.
If you stick to your testimony,
you're hurting yourself and the military.
Part of it is up to you,
but the other part is my business.
Perhaps we can help each other.
I'm not withdrawing my statement.
On behalf of the military,
I'd like to offer you compensation
by adjusting the insurance policy
you took out in your contract.
Fuck off.
I'm not thinking so much about you,
but about your wife and son
who were entitled to a pension
if you died.
We've managed to change
the premise
so it also applies
in the case of long-term illness.
I hope it can make life easier
for Louise and Jonas.
And all you have to do in return...
You know perfectly well,
but it's up to you.
My father has been with you
since yesterday.
Can you give him a message?
I see. Thanks.
For nothing.
- What is going on?
- Lennart Brix. Head of homicide.
We have reason to believe there
is evidence here. Here's the warrant.
What do you expect to find?
You've been here many times.
I hear that you're in charge now.
If you don't want trouble,
you'll let us do our job.
Don't let anyone leave.
Send someone to get the keys we need.
- What's up?
- Get hold of General Arild.
Get hold of him,
for fuck's sake.
Krabbe is being pressured
by his support base.
I'll talk to him. Are the police
coming home without any evidence?
- Plough has the details.
- Where the hell is he?
Take that cart first
and then the other one.
The press gave up on you.
Three members
have accused you of treason.
We need evidence that the Prime Minister
shelved the first medical report.
We haven't found a reason
why he would do that.
The doctor was content
with the revised report.
He hasn't murdered civilians. Your
accusations against the Prime Minister
seem more and more extreme.
I think we should spend our time
on the Minister of Defense.
I think I have something here.
The Prime Minister has a secret abroad.
I'm afraid we'll have to postpone
the memorial service for a while.
- What's wrong?
- The relatives are on their way.
But the barracks are being
searched. If it takes too long
we'll have to continue without
the personnel from the barracks.
What are you doing here?
Were you invited?
I know you don't trust me, but we
have more in common than you think.
I certainly hope not.
I hear your investigators' efforts
in Afghanistan were fruitless.
So no wonder you're stressed.
You think you've served
a greater purpose.
I have.
Every coffin reminds me...
...that we have to continue
until no death is in vain.
For the Prime Minister this was not
about fighting, but about the UN.
He hopes to be the next
Secretary General.
All he needed
was the support of the Americans.
That's why we deployed
more soldiers to Afghanistan.
A French news agency has confirmed
that he was offered the position.
Look at those coffins
and tell me that it was worth it.
The Prime Minister
turned the offer down.
He was encouraged to apply,
but he declined. Goodbye, Buch.
That doesn't change anything. I refuse
to believe you did this on your own.
The death of the soldiers is linked
to what happened back then.
You have a responsibility,
for fuck's sake.
Would you please leave?
Your behaviour is inappropriate.
- We haven't found a thing.
- What about the phone?
We keep trying.
The battery seems to be dead.
What about the underground areas?
The practice grounds?
- The area around the lecture hall?
- We don't have the manpower.
We'll stay till we're finished.
We'll go through the whole lot.
Wait a moment.
I know what you want to say.
You have nothing to do with this.
And you have no idea what's going on.
Good. That's all squared.
It's for you.
- I don't understand you either.
- This isn't a good time.
Pack your things
and get out of there. Now!
I will take full responsibility for
the situation, but we must continue.
I've talked to management.
You have no authority any more.
Lennart...
We have five minutes
to get out of here.
Brix, come in.
There's something in the basement.
What's in the box?
Open it.
The squad apparently entrenched
themselves on the second floor.
Calibre 5.56. They're used
in the Danish M-95s.
The soldiers slept in shifts.
In here.
- Is this where they were killed?
- According to Raben.
And he said that the bodies
were moved in here.
The soldiers who came
to their rescue found nothing.
- Did they drag the bodies outside?
- They would have been shot.
Aren't we all done here?
Some people thought he was
a drug lord who financed the Taliban.
Does he think the family
was killed by Danish soldiers?
No, there was no sign of them.
All right. Sorry to bother you.
What is this?
- It was a family of bakers.
- Where is the oven?
- He says everything was destroyed.
- I just want to see that oven.
I don't care. Just get it ready
before the meeting!
Rossing had his chance,
but now we're going after him.
- The lawyers are waiting for you.
- We have a problem.
The police have extended
their investigation in Afghanistan.
They've left the military zone
without authorisation.
Get them a visa.
It's against all international rules.
Operational Command is furious.
Where have you been? The Minister
of Defense is in your office.
- Help them, if you can.
- That's easy for you to say.
If this is about some trivial clearance
for my people there, forget it.
I've always been loyal
to the Prime Minister.
Congratulations.
Even when I've had to compromise
on my principles.
When we heard about
the death of civilians
we were in the middle
of a decision process.
We needed more money,
more soldiers.
The Prime Minister and I agreed
to put off the investigation of the hand.
I had no idea where it could lead.
Monberg... and all the murders...
Perhaps some of it
should have rung some bells.
- What bells?
- I'm not sure.
The examination of the hand
resulted in inconsistencies.
We felt it was inconclusive.
But in the meantime
military intelligence concluded that
none of the victims were civilians.
What inconsistencies?
There was something about
a special henna tattoo.
We consulted experts who said
it was typical of the Hazara people.
The Hazara hate the Taliban.
But the key factor is the gold ring.
The Taliban don't wear gold.
Therefore, it couldn't possibly
be a suicide bomber.
Did the Prime Minister
know about this?
- It's not on record.
- But did he know?
Gert knows everything.
He's the man in charge.
- What's going on?
- We're changing our strategy.
You and Rossing against
the Prime Minister?
Read this.
- You're sure he's not lying?
- I'll let Krabbe know.
Yes, it's my locker, but I haven't used
it for ages. I've said so many times.
The phone is linked with the murder
of Grüner last week.
That may be, but it's not mine.
I have nothing to do
with those murders.
Take a look.
The lab has examined the halves.
Each matches a half
found on one of the five victims.
I see.
- I haven't seen them before.
- What is this a key to?
- No idea.
- You're charged with all five murders.
- I'm innocent.
- So you never met the first victim?
Dragsholm?
And you had no idea
she was reopening the old case?
You'll be put in isolation pending
the investigation. Take him away.
I have met Anne Dragsholm.
She called me
and requested a meeting.
I thought it was best
to keep an open mind.
But she stuck to her accusations,
so I told her to go to hell.
Why would I kill my own people?
And be dumb enough to leave
a switched-on phone in my locker?
I bet you regret it,
but the judge won't care.
We didn't care about Dragsholm.
You know I have a watertight alibi.
- We?
- Yes.
Bilal was at that meeting.
He was my second-in-command
and can confirm my statement.
How did Bilal react
to the accusations?
He was angry and afraid
that it would ruin our cause.
Bilal is a Muslim, but he hates
the obscurants more than we do.
And that's understandable.
Does Bilal have access
to the basement?
- Knock it off. Bilal is a boy scout.
- Does he have access?
Yes, but he said not to go down there
because the ceiling might cave in.
The prosecutor will state the charges
and you'll plead guilty on all counts.
You'll withdraw your statement about
the officer and civilian casualties.
Afterwards, you'll probably
be taken back to prison.
At least until...
Excuse me a minute.
The hearing has been postponed.
They think they have the perpetrator.
They've found evidence
pointing to Major Søgaard.
You've claimed someone
at the barracks was involved.
OK. Let's go.
Don't let them question you
without me.
Søgaard might cover something up,
but no way is he the perpetrator.
It's not Søgaard.
All the ID halves were found
in his locker. Move it!
You have the wrong man.
My wife and son are at the barracks.
- Relax.
- My wife and son...
What the hell are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Get him in the car.
The investigators still won't tell me
when my father will be released.
- Any news from the police?
- The last one just left.
My father found out that someone
concealed the radio messages.
Who here would have done that?
Don't you see that it's important?
It indicates that Jens was right.
There were no messages,
and no one concealed anything.
But my father thinks so.
It must be the same person
who planted those things
in Søgaard's locker.
In his locker?
Then it must be Søgaard.
Who was the radio operator?
There's a log
that registers radio calls.
Let's say someone figured out
how to delete messages.
Who apart from Søgaard
could have done that?
- I have to inform the other officers.
- Call General Arild.
Find out who ratted on my father.
It must be the same guy.
My father was digging something up
and suddenly he was ratted on.
Make the call. Or call the police.
They have to be told.
What are you waiting for?
Lund... I talked to my superior.
We have to leave right now.
- There's nothing there.
- I want to see that oven.
I could get reported for this.
Yes? Hello? This is Strange.
There must be another one.
We have to remove all the debris
and check this out.
- He says you're crazy. I agree.
- What happened here led to murders.
If you know anything about it,
tell me now.
A family lived here.
Two adults and two children.
I have to know
if they were murdered.
People around here die every day,
in case you haven't noticed.
What the hell is that supposed
to mean? Hey...
Hey! Hey!
When people get killed, it's important.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Translate, damn it!
Tell me what happened here.
Is that uniform just a joke?
What happened to the bodies?
You must've seen or heard something.
Were they buried? Cremated?
Taken somewhere?
You don't care!
You don't give a...
Easy now.
We've been through everything.
There's no oven. No bodies. OK?
It's Brix. They think they know
who the perpetrator is.
Yes?
Get on a plane now. The Ministry
and the army are all over us.
- What's up?
- Bilal might be our man.
He knew Dragsholm
was opening the case
and we found the other halves
of the IDs at the barracks.
- We're going to arrest him now.
- At the barracks? Why would Bilal...?
We found out what the key is for.
It's not at the barracks.
The locksmith says it's to a rented place
in the name of Per K.
Let's start. Will all of you
have a seat, please?
Item one is the Minister of Justice's
summary of the Helmand investigation.
Next is the Prime Minister's
comment before we vote.
He'll have plenty to comment on.
As you've heard
nothing new has come to light
in the investigation in Afghanistan.
However, I've been made aware
of a scandal of historic proportions.
A stain on the history of the party
and on the Government.
That's it?
Haven't the police found anything?
No, but if I may continue...
Any further items will have to wait.
The Prime Minister has the floor.
His words are immaterial
if I am not allowed to continue.
The voting has been postponed.
This is not an easy thing to say.
I have just been given information
that clearly indicates that the
Minister of Defense has deceived us.
The Minister of Defense has withheld
a certain expert's testimony
which concluded that
the hand found in Afghanistan
possibly did not belong
to a Taliban suicide bomber.
It was suppressed to avoid
the suspicion of civilian casualties.
- This is incorrect...
- It's shocking.
We'll see if that changes
our conclusions
but the Minister of Defense
is dismissed immediately.
His actions will be investigated
by Special Branch.
Tell them. The Prime Minister
told you to hide those papers.
The Minister of Justice
will have to wait.
Let me speak.
He just told me all about it.
With regard to the Minister of Justice,
the situation is equally grave.
He could have used his knowledge
to benefit his country
but instead he has abused
his office to raise doubts about me.
Listen! The Prime Minister instructed
the Minister of Defense to do that.
His motive is dubious.
He has conducted a smear campaign
and been very careless in his
handling of confidential information.
Special Branch will investigate
if he has committed acts of treason.
This is ridiculous!
What the hell is this?
Leave the building immediately.
You cannot take anything with you.
I assume it's evident
that you've stepped down now.
Take it easy!
I can walk on my own.
Are you under arrest?
Has the Minister of Defense
deceived Parliament?
Did they find everything
in Søgaard's locker?
But his alibis do check out.
Brix thinks that Bilal used
the locker or planted the stuff.
If there were no civilian casualties,
why commit the murders?
Ask Brix. That's all I heard
before you let that Afghan have it.
The main thing is we've got him,
whether it's Bilal or Søgaard.
Yes. I don't know...
It's a good thing you're going home
to solve the whole thing.
Shit!
Do as they say.