Ten days ago, a woman was
killed in strange circumstances.
The Muslim League will avenge
the suffering Denmark has caused...
My blood will be shed.
And many will die along with me.
Brix thinks
you can give us a new angle.
David Grüner, 28-year-old veteran.
- What do you know about the squad?
- 3-2-AIpha. Raben was squad leader.
- Do we know where the rest are?
- Raben and Lisbeth Thomsen.
- She's living on a Swedish island.
- Raben may turn up.
- The Probation Service turned you down.
- Why?
- Why can't I visit him?
- Raben lied, and now he's escaped.
- He turned up.
- Have you agreed to meet?
- Something happened in that village.
- They can't just vanish.
- What happened?
- He called himself Perk.
Thomsen!
Don't start it! Stop!
The Government has put a lot of work
into the terrorism package.
- Will you be Minister of Justice?
- I had an affair with Monberg.
This is a report
on an incident in Afghanistan.
- I realise I must resign.
- The victims' names!
You leave me no choice
but to tell the media
that the Government is incapable
of taking action against terrorism.
- Buch?
- We'll have to stop this.
- These are merely allegations.
- I have written evidence.
Monberg didn't have a heart attack.
He took some pills.
What if it's all a set-up?
The video, Faith Fellow, Kodmani?
- The army doesn't kill its own.
- Someone in the army.
- Rubbish!
- Lund and Strange stay on the case.
- No officer Perk, no bodies.
- And you checked all this?
- My second-in-command briefed me.
- Who was he?
War is dirty. Innocent people die.
That's why the politicians send us.
I need your help.
Why did he try to kill himself?
What?
- It is not the right time.
- Monberg is involved in the case.
The lawyer asked for his help
to reopen the case.
The Defense Ministry called a meeting
with the Minister of Justice.
Concerning squad leader Raben.
He was in a mental institution.
- That won't buy you a gas pistol!
- I need it!
My father knows about this phone.
Are you all right?
You'd better take this.
You are right to turn yourself in.
Let me change, before we go.
Some recruits were trained by
a first lieutenant they called Perk.
Per K. Møller.
He was on Team Ægir.
He got the funeral he wanted.
Is this to do with the investigation?
A lawyer was here,
asking the same questions.
He died,
three months before the incident.
Søgaard wouldn't
let them see the body.
We must get her permission to dig
up the coffin, to see if it's empty.
THE KILLING
- Something came up.
- You promised to give me a hand.
- I'll come tomorrow morning.
- Tomorrow? It's my wedding!
Mum, I can't talk now.
I'll call you. Bye.
- How deep must we dig?
- About my height.
- Is the coffin still intact?
- I've never dug one up before.
- Mind the hedge!
- Lund? We have a problem.
We can't get a warrant now.
The judge wants to know more.
Let's hear what the field chaplain
and Major Søgaard say.
And the mother of the deceased
just turned up.
I can't agree to this.
- We're on thin ice.
- Where is she?
Get those people out.
I won't have anybody digging there.
- May I have a word with you?
- No. I won't change my mind. Leave!
There may have been a mistake
at your son's funeral.
You have no right! Leave!
We must be quite certain
that your son is in the coffin.
And we need your permission.
- I promise we'll do it with care.
- Why wouldn't he be in the coffin?
He is believed to have been seen
three months after his presumed death.
Some soldiers witnessed
something in Afghanistan.
Your son may have been involved
with the killing of civilians.
With your permission,
we can start immediately.
Otherwise, I'm forced to get
permission from someone else.
- What kind of a person are you?
- I realise it may seem...
Lund? Brix wants to see you.
- We didn't talk of exhumations.
- The family never saw the body.
- The chaplain and Søgaard said...
- It's not enough!
- Not without the mother's consent.
- There is no body in that coffin.
- If the coffin is empty...
- Send these people home!
Brix, wait a moment!
I know I'm right.
Trust me, goddamn it!
- Søgaard refuses to be questioned.
- Bring him in to HQ now.
- And the chaplain?
- We're still looking for him.
We can't wait for more killings.
We must do something!
Did you see the chaplain
about your husband?
Yes, he said he wasn't well.
Can we go now?
Was your husband angry
with the chaplain?
No. He knows he only wants to help.
They are friends.
- Would your husband harm him?
- Not so loud!
The chaplain left in a hurry.
He forgot a parish council meeting.
He was seen leaving with someone
who looked like your husband.
- Any idea where they were heading?
- No.
He'd never dream
of harming the vicar.
Thank you.
- The pizza is getting cold.
- We'll buy another on the way home.
- Where are we going?
- Drive on!
What did Dragsholm say?
Why did she contact you?
- Was she reopening the case?
- Turn left here. Here!
Leave the keys in the ignition.
Move away from the car.
Further away!
What are you planning to do, Priest?
It won't do you any good.
The police will find out.
Yes. Hello? Is that the police?
My name is Gunnar Torp.
I'm in Hareskoven Forest.
I want to report an assault.
It concerns a former soldier,
Jens Peter Raben.
He drove me into the woods
and threatened me with a pistol.
No, I don't know where he is.
I'll wait at the main path.
Thank you.
I want no part in it. If you contact
me again, I'll shoot you.
- What did Dragsholm want?
- Run!
- I know nothing. Stay put!
- She saw Myg, Grüner, Thomsen.
She wanted them to testify
against the officer.
I buried that officer,
three months before the incident!
Now, get lost!
What had Dragsholm uncovered?
Why reopen the case?
She wanted me to testify.
I heard them talk about the officer.
- You knew something was amiss.
- No. I didn't understand.
- I asked Søgaard about it.
- And what did Søgaard say?
That there was no case.
As the judge advocate's report said.
I was locked up for two years,
drugged, cut off from my family.
Talk to Søgaard, the Colonel
and the others at the barracks.
No!
Raben...
Forgive me.
Think of your wife!
Think of your son!
People are shocked. Four killings!
Why don't we do something?
The investigation is complicated.
It's fundamentalism.
We are under terrorist attack.
- It isn't as simple as that.
- What's so bloody complicated?
Even though this meeting
is off the record
the Home Secretary
should refrain from swearing.
Yes, of course. I'm sorry.
But we're in this together.
There has been no breakthrough.
The Opposition is gloating
and the People's Party is impatient
because the Minister of Justice
won't pass the terrorism package.
- We must look into it.
- Into what?
I know these Islamist organisations,
these people you are protecting.
They'd replace democracy
with Sharia if you let them.
None of my colleagues abroad
understand that we're doing nothing.
What if these organisations
are mixed up in it?
That is why
I've called this meeting.
Thomas wishes to present us
with something to explain himself.
That part is no longer relevant.
It was a misunderstanding.
- What the hell is going on?
- Listen to me.
We all know
it was no easy start for Buch.
But he's sure to pass the terrorism
package if he can work in peace.
Let's focus on our common enemy,
and refrain from blaming each other.
Any one of us
could be in Buch's shoes.
Excuse me.
Rossing here.
Protecting those organisations
is not the way to show tolerance.
Could I talk this over with you,
in private?
- What's that?
- It won't take a moment. Please.
Put the police
and Special Branch to work.
The police seem to be too busy.
The Ministry of Defense
has been informed
that a dead soldier
is about to be exhumed.
- What are you saying?
- The bereaved are very upset.
Buch... Do you have an explanation?
I'm not quite up-to-date on that,
but let us...
You may be newly appointed,
but I can't protect you
You seem to have changed
your mind about Monberg.
- Why this exhumation?
- I need time.
Tell me what is going on.
It's best the Prime Minister
is not informed about such matters.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
But it must not be said later on
that the Prime Minister was informed.
- It would compromise you.
- What are you on about?
Perhaps I was wrong about Monberg
being the only one at fault.
Call a meeting
with the People's Party.
Ease their mind,
say we'll pass the terror package
but we need to investigate
the organisations one more time.
- For how long?
- A couple of days.
Blame me and my amateurism.
Krabbe will understand that.
We all have a tight schedule.
Could we come to a decision?
I'll talk to Krabbe.
I'm giving Thomas 24 hours
to investigate
certain circumstances.
- Might I ask which circumstances?
- No. Please inform the others.
You claimed you didn't know
any officer by the name of Perk.
I still don't.
Officer Per K. Møller's
nickname was Perk
and he was on Team Ægir,
as were you.
Correct. Some officers
gave him that nickname.
- Did you drag me in here for that?
- Just answer the questions.
You and the field chaplain
attended his funeral. Why?
We escorted the coffin on the flight
home and wanted to pay our respects.
Why wasn't his family
allowed to see his body?
- He died in an explosion.
- Tell me about it.
His head was severed from what was
left of his body. What is this about?
With a dead officer called Perk,
it must have surprised you
when Raben and the others claimed
to have met an officer of that name.
No. It made their report even more
unbelievable. I'd buried him!
- Did you alone declare him dead?
- This is ridiculous!
- Why was there no autopsy?
- I saw what was left of the man!
We feared
his death was self-inflicted.
- Do you claim he took his own life?
- We'll never know.
- But for the sake of the family...
- Rubbish!
We are about to open an empty coffin,
so don't give me that!
Don't tell me you're digging him up!
Lund...
- The coffin has been dug up.
- And?
Hi, Lund.
Nice to see you again.
I only get this kind of work
when you're around.
Well...
Caucasian, late twenties.
The femur indicates
that he was about six foot tall.
He's had a very rough treatment.
I'd say an explosion.
It's rather a mess. It reminds me
of one time in the Balkans...
It can't be him.
You can't be sure it's Per K. Møller.
- We'll need to take him in...
- You can't be sure!
It could be someone else. They could
have put another body in its place.
- It's not necessarily Per K. Møller.
- What is that?
We'll have to take a DNA test.
What about his teeth?
It just can't be right.
It can't be him.
Søgaard and the chaplain
wouldn't let them see the body.
Something is amiss.
I know...
Wrap it up and close it.
Hey. What's going on?
- Got anyone buried here?
- No.
Some crazy cop thought
an empty coffin was buried here.
You'd think
they had better things to do.
"The dragon curled up around
the town, bit his tail, and fell asleep."
So should you.
Tomorrow we'll make your room nice.
Why are they chasing Daddy?
Has he gone?
He's playing hide-and-seek,
just like you do at nursery.
Now lie down and sleep.
- Are they angry with Daddy?
- No. They just want to find him.
When they do,
we can go visit him again.
Shall we try out
your new scooter tomorrow?
Sleep tight, darling.
Yes, of course. I understand.
Thank you. Goodbye.
They found the Priest.
He says Jens took him
to some woods at gunpoint.
He's all right,
apart from being slightly bruised.
I wanted to check that you were OK.
You'd better not leave the barracks.
I'd like to know
what the hell is going on.
Explosives have been found here.
You and Søgaard were questioned.
- And now the Priest tells this tale.
- It's a routine investigation.
Nonsense! Jens said something
bad happened in Afghanistan.
He's right about that.
Three soldiers
from this squad were killed.
- That wasn't it. What was it?
- There's a simple explanation.
As a squad leader, Jens made
a wrong decision. I'd feel bad too.
So you think
he's acting out of guilt?
It's time you realised there are sides
to Jens you don't know.
Right. I'd like you to leave now.
Why did he go to war
when Jonas was born?
- He was sent to Iraq.
- No. He was not on a contract.
He volunteered.
He wanted to go!
- Jens is not the man you think...
- Leave!
Get out of here!
Rossing called a meeting
with Monberg
and Raben was on the agenda.
The official reason is "prevention
of crime among demobilised soldiers".
Raben is not the only soldier
to be named as an example.
Eat, Plough. It's delicious.
The Ministry of Defense didn't want
to disclose Raben's name.
- Why are there no minutes?
- The Ministers were alone.
I was busy with a bill.
Monberg promised his constituents
to cut expenses in the Probation Service.
Is there any dessert?
If Monberg knew then
about this military case
and failed to inform the police
when Dragsholm was killed...
What do the police
and Special Branch say?
At the moment, they are arguing
about the exhumation of that soldier.
Special Branch was against it.
I want to be briefed about it.
Find out what Monberg was told.
- Did Monberg keep a diary?
- I could call and ask his wife.
No. Let me. Meanwhile,
you can talk to Karina.
I ask her to pop in, to thank her,
and get her to resume her work.
She can't. There are disciplinary
proceedings. She's being replaced.
Dial the number
of Monberg's wife.
We can't ignore what she's done.
She even used her password
after she was fired.
- Talk to her.
- No! I won't talk to Karina.
Good evening. Thomas Buch.
Sorry to disturb you at this hour.
Can I talk to Hanne Monberg?
- Thomas said you wanted to see me.
- Yes...
No. It was his idea.
I wasn't informed.
OK.
I want you to know,
I enjoyed working here.
I admire your expertise.
But you can be a pain in the arse.
I've worn out three nannies
because I had to be here every day
to meet your impossible demands.
But it was never good enough.
- Everything must be done properly.
- Evidently it wasn't, anyway.
You're so uptight! My sleeping
with Monberg really disappointed you!
I'd just gone through a divorce.
But we don't talk of such matters!
When did you ever ask me
about my personal life?
Never! But you are so prudish
whenever something happens
which doesn't involve
rules and regulations.
You deserve better!
Karina! How could you
ruin your career like that?
After all we've worked for,
all I've taught you. For a moment of...
How are you doing?
Monberg's wife said
he didn't keep a diary.
But he's regained consciousness.
His condition is stable.
We must talk with him
as soon as possible.
- I'll call the hospital.
- We must get to him before Rossing.
Get me an update on Raben
from our system.
And find out where the police
and Special Branch stand. Hurry up!
- Do you have a nanny?
- It's been seen to.
The coroner has checked his teeth.
There is no doubt
about the soldier's identity.
This is either going to be
Lund's funeral or yours.
Do you get my drift?
I will protect you,
but the matter must be cleared up.
Special Branch has found something.
They have tracked down Raben.
He abandoned the chaplain's car
and continued on foot.
- Have they caught him?
- König will inform us tomorrow.
Could you ask him
if there is anything we can do?
To think that
you could be so wrong.
And your pass, please?
I'll inform Gedser.
You can resume your work there.
Send Major Søgaard home.
I'll talk to Special Branch.
Let me have a word with you
in a couple of minutes.
Do you want me to drive you home?
- Thank you for...
- Lund, I'm sorry, it...
I'll call you tomorrow.
Give your mother
my best wishes for...
Raben abandoned the chaplain's car.
A Volvo was stolen nearby.
We found him at around 2:00am.
He slept for three hours,
then drove on.
He's near the barracks
- Why don't we get him in here?
- Raben is the last one of the squad.
- He is the next potential victim.
- So you want to use him as bait?
I could keep chasing fundamentalists.
But, sooner or later,
the killers will get to Raben.
- Our men can assist you.
- Thank you.
Our men are better equipped for it.
You need to regroup, since Lund...
We have dealt
with this lack of cooperation.
We're up and running.
That will please
the Ministry of Justice immensely.
I'd like you to look at these.
Refugees from Helmand, living in
Denmark for the last couple of years.
- They might be seeking revenge.
- Take a look.
Some to be watched, others questioned,
none to be exhumed!
Do you have a moment?
Lennart, we'll talk.
Why did Raben
take you to the woods at gunpoint?
I don't know.
Maybe because he's not well.
He is under enormous pressure.
I tried to reason with him.
War does strange things to people.
We found this in your church.
Anne Dragsholm's calling card.
- What was it doing there?
- Raben must have had it.
- Did you know her?
- No. Raben talked about her.
But I never met her.
Nor have I seen that card.
Can I go now?
It's Sunday. I have a church service.
Yes, all right.
- Special Branch is watching Raben.
- Why don't they bring him in?
- We do as they say. Take a look.
- We should check the chaplain.
Afghan refugees in Denmark.
Go see them.
- Lund suspected the chaplain...
- Lund is no longer here.
No more nonsense. Get moving.
What do we say, if anyone calls up
and wants to speak to Lund?
Say that she's attending a wedding.
I spoke to Møller's mother.
The family is suing for damages
for the pain and suffering
the police caused her.
I spoke to our former field chaplain.
He is shocked.
The question is
what Raben will do next.
He seems desperate.
He's the only one left of the squad.
He must be under extreme pressure.
It's best to keep your eyes and ears
open when leaving the barracks.
- Have you informed Louise?
- He was one of the best.
When others gave up,
Raben had 10% more to give.
A pity he didn't hold out
in the long run.
Did we get to the bottom of it,
the things Raben and his squad claimed?
- How certain were we?
- 100% certain. Why?
These past few days have been tough.
I could relieve you.
That won't be necessary,
Thanks all the same.
Are you hungry?
Do you want a sandwich?
Here.
We only have a couple of minutes.
You must leave the barracks!
- What did you do to the Priest?
- Nothing. They're lying to you.
About what? My father told me
about the incident. You feel guilty.
- It's not that.
- Then what?
They are covering up
for something an officer did.
- Who?
- I don't know. Søgaard.
- Maybe others. Your father.
- My father?
I don't believe it!
Get hold of Sarah Lund of the police.
Tell her to check...
Is it true you volunteered
when Jonas was born?
- Who told you that?
- Just tell me the truth.
Yes, it's true. Can't you see
they are trying to separate us?
It's not what you think.
After what I'd seen and done
I didn't deserve him.
- He was so pure. And I wasn't.
- Let go of me!
I've changed. I just want
to come home and be with you.
Let go of Mummy!
Let her go!
How you've grown!
It's me. Daddy.
- May I see? Smashing!
- Mummy, let's go now.
Don't try to see us.
Ever again.
- Would you rather wait here?
- No. It's OK.
- There he is.
- It's good to see you.
- How are you?
- All right.
It seems quite a storm
has been brewing.
Hello, Karina.
I'm glad you could take over from me.
Now, I can take better care
of this old heart.
I doubt I'm allowed
to eat chocolate any more.
Well... Evidently,
you have been informed.
I've been unwell for some time.
I don't want my family to suffer,
unnecessarily.
Of course not. We just want
to talk about that old military case.
The one you circulated,
just before you...
There's not much to tell.
I passed it on for Anne Dragsholm,
who I knew some few years back.
We had a meeting. She was getting
divorced. We talked about old times.
She gave me the folder as I was leaving.
The case meant a lot to her.
But I never got to look at it.
- Why?
- You already knew about the case.
The Defense Minister had called
a meeting with you about a soldier.
A certain Jens Peter Raben.
I... I'm not sure I understand.
Just tell me what you spoke about
with Rossing at that meeting.
But that's several years ago.
I can't remember...
Frode! You withheld information
about that military case
from the police, Special Branch,
and the rest of the world. Why?
- What are you hiding?
- Karina, what's the idea?
Why have a meeting about the soldier?
- What did Rossing say?
- What are you on about?
You met with the Minister of Defense.
Later, Dragsholm brings the case up.
But you never let on.
Not even when she was killed.
If you've come to blame me for
your mistakes, I must ask you to leave.
What did Rossing say at that meeting?
Visitors again? That won't do.
I appreciate your concern
but the doctor needs
to examine my husband.
- It isn't good for him.
- My wife is right. I should rest.
And I do believe
the Minister was about to leave.
Right.
Thanks, Plough.
Krabbe is impatient.
He wants to talk to you.
I've been given 24 hours. Send him
back to the Prime Minister's office.
I suggest you issue an apology
for the exhumation of the soldier.
- Who organised that exhumation?
- The person in question was fired.
And not for the first time. As a chief
inspector, she solved a murder
and kept digging into
the involvement of local politicians.
I suggest you mention she's been
fired and that we expect to...
I'd like to talk to her.
You said she solved that case.
Maybe she knows something.
You can't. It will compromise
your relations with the police.
If Monberg won't talk, we'll have to try
something else. Get hold of her.
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
- You may kiss the bride.
- May I?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's have something to eat
and a drink, and another, and another!
You can tell
he was in the Home Guard!
- Congratulations, Granny.
- Thank you.
- About my being toastmaster...
- Yes! Keep the speeches short.
- There must be time for dancing.
- We must have our picture taken.
Here's the bell.
We've put the presents on the table.
Including the flowers for you.
Yes. The red bouquet.
- OK. Thanks.
- Everybody, take your places.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. Say cheese!
- Do you still work at police HQ?
- No, not for a long time.
I read in the morning paper
that they dug up a dead soldier.
I'm sorry, someone's here to see you.
She says it's important.
I've been looking
forward to making this speech
so I will get down to it,
straight away.
That's all right.
I'll wait a minute.
- Karina Munch, Ministry of Justice.
- A toast? Cheers!
This conversation
is purely coincidental.
What conversation, with whom?
Come this way.
Hi. Thomas Buch.
Karina suggests
we have met by coincidence.
But in truth
I'm in dire need of some answers.
If it's about the exhumation,
I'm really sorry.
Do you know about the accusations
against Danish troops in Afghanistan?
I'm not...
Are there any indications
of the killings of civilians?
You had better call
Lennart Brix or Ruth Hedeby.
Focus is on a certain officer.
Could there be a cover-up?
No. And there probably
wasn't any officer.
- Why did you dig up that man?
- That was a mistake.
I don't know anything.
I have to get back to the wedding.
What do you know about
the squad leader, Jens Peter Raben?
Nothing.
I thought he knew something, but...
They claim he is mentally ill.
He had good reason to escape.
He'd just been turned down.
- By whom?
- The Probation Service.
The doctors had given him
a clean bill of health
but the Probation Service turned
down his requests for parole.
And once again, recently.
He was probably disappointed.
Just a moment.
Monberg was working on a bill
concerning the Probation Service.
When was that abandoned?
Shortly after the meeting between
Monberg and the Minister of Defense.
We must get hold of Plough.
Thank you. And congratulations
on your mother's wedding.
You make me so happy.
I just want to sing and make speeches,
all the time.
Sometimes I wish we had met
earlier in life.
But I'm sure we needed to have
some corners rubbed off first.
I'm so glad I walked into
the second-hand shop that day...
Long live the bride!
- Who brought these flowers?
- They were delivered by courier.
CHECK THE DOG TAG - RABEN
Now that we are all gathered,
I would like to continue what I started.
Dear Bjørn...
What's this?
You can't walk out
on your mother's speech!
Yes, that's exactly
what she's doing. And it's OK!
Get used to it, Bjørn!
The women of this family
are very busy.
- You'll just have to keep up!
- Now you tell me!
Where was I?
My dear, wonderful Bjørn...
I want to apologise.
I know I can't put it right.
I hope you understand
it was important to be certain.
I understand you won't speak to me.
But there is something I need to know.
No one else can help.
It's about your son's dog tag.
The chain with the metal name tag.
Do you know where it is?
No. They said they never found it.
They said it was lost, when he...
And it wasn't brought back
with his other belongings?
Why do you ask?
I think someone found his dog tag
and misused it.
Somebody who needed
to take on another identity.
I won't disturb you any longer.
Wait a moment.
I have something to show you.
Yes?
I thought it was a mistake.
Now and then things turn up,
as if Per were still alive.
For instance,
bills for various purchases.
The latest one
is from two months ago.
I must ask you to come
during visiting hours.
- I have no more to say.
- You needn't say much.
You were preparing a bill.
You promised your constituents
to cut Probation Service expenses.
- No more overcrowded prisons.
- We have no more to talk about.
And fewer mentally ill criminals
in the prisons.
Some of them were to be reassessed
and given parole.
One of them was Jens Peter Raben.
That's what Rossing
wished to discuss with you.
Strangely enough,
you withdrew your proposal.
- Nothing came of it.
- No...
- There were other reasons for that.
- I won't disturb you any longer.
I'll leave it to Plough
and the legal experts.
Wait.
- What do you plan to do now?
- That depends on you.
- But it doesn't look good.
- It wasn't my decision.
- What?
- I just wanted to do my job.
Rossing didn't want Raben released.
He was a security risk.
It was in the national interest
to keep him locked up.
- The national interest?
- He didn't elaborate on it.
- Raben knew something was amiss.
- I can't make head nor tail of it.
- Rossing told me what to do.
- But you found the reason.
When Anne Dragsholm
wanted to reopen the case.
What did Dragsholm say?
What had she discovered?
- I can't...
- Damn it! Tell me!
People are dying out there!
You're the one to take the blame,
not Rossing.
She had found proof that
the soldiers were speaking the truth.
Civilians had been killed.
It was an injustice
that Raben had been locked away.
- What had she found?
- The officer.
She had found the officer who did it.
That's all I know!
What happens now?
- Who was that officer?
- She didn't say.
- What am I to do?
- It will be all right.
You did right to tell me.
Excuse me, but I must talk to you.
It's important.
- Two minutes.
- Rossing won't say a word.
You can't make him.
You don't know him.
I got Monberg to talk. We must get
Special Branch over here.
- Krabbe demands your resignation
- Do you know that for sure, or...?
He gave the Prime Minister
an ultimatum.
Either you go or the Government falls.
Monberg is giving
an official explanation.
We'll take it from there.
It will all work out.
- Where is Monberg?
- He wanted a bit of exercise.
- Is it hanging straight now?
- Lift up the corner. And the other.
- Like that?
- Yes, that's it.
Right. There we go.
It looks great, doesn't it?
- I'll leave you to it now.
- Thanks for helping, Dad.
I'm sorry about
the things I said yesterday.
It's all right.
I've been a fool.
Join us at the cadets' ball.
I'd like you to come.
- It would do you good.
- I'm not in the mood.
- And I want to be with Jonas.
- Jonas is all right.
It's you I'm worried about.
Come on. It'll do you good.
I'll call the nanny.
It's just for a couple of hours.
We can leave when you like.
Of course, it's up to you.
See you.
What time are you going?
- Aren't you at the wedding?
- You must check something.
I'm standing here with an interpreter
at a refugee centre.
- I'll just step outside.
- Right.
What's up?
Someone used Per K. Møller's identity.
His dog tag is missing.
Purchases were made
in his name, recently.
Talk to the chaplain
or Major Søgaard.
Run his name through a computer
and see if anything else turns up.
I'm in Helsingør. What's up?
- When will you be back?
- In a couple of hours.
- Have you talked to Brix?
- No. Not yet.
I will. Of course.
I'm sorry. Bye.
Strange and the team
are still interviewing refugees.
- Any joy?
- They've run up some mileage.
What does Special Branch
say about Raben?
He was at the barracks until 11:00
and then approached his wife and son.
They argued.
Now he's back at the barracks.
- No trace of any perpetrators?
- No. Strangely enough.
König is right to focus on Raben,
him being the last man of the squad.
It won't be in vain.
Do you want to come for a bite?
Or are you going to sit here
and brood all day?
This came back from Forensics.
Strange had it checked.
- What is it?
- The calling card.
The one the chaplain
didn't know about.
- I'm done with the chaplain.
- It's full of his fingerprints.
Strange, seeing as he claims
to know nothing of it.
Hello?
Anybody there?
Sarah Lund. Send an ambulance
to St Simon's Church, Vesterbro.
I just found the vicar.
He's still breathing, but...