Ten days ago
a woman was murdered in unusual circumstances
.
How many will follow me in death?
What does PET have on the group?
Raben was the squad leader.
There was no one named Perk.
A lieutenant was called Perk.
There may be nothing in the coffin.
I informed Gedser you'll be returning to them.
I'm sorry that that...
We're up to four deaths.
Why don't we do something?
It's best that the Prime Minister
doesn't know.
I've given Thomas 24 hours to
investigate certain leads.
May I enquire as to what investigations?
No..
He couldn't do the priest thing.
Of course I was  in the camp.
They talked about him, captain..officer.
Volunteered...you voluntarily joined
just before Jonas was born?
Don't try to contact us again.
Why haven't we caught him?
Raben is the last survivor.
You didn't know Anne Dragsholm?
I haven't seen the report.
Check with the priest. Lund said...
Lund...She isn't here anymore.
Karina, what were you thinking?
To ruin your career.
Monberg's woken up. We need to
talk with him before Rossing does.
I need to rest, I'm asking you to leave..
What did Rossing mean?
I need to get some rest.
Who was in charge of the exhumation?
You mean Jens Peter Raben?
He had just been denied
release from prison.
You'll get blamed!
Not Rossing.
She found the captain...the officer
Either you or he
betrayed the government.
Who sent the flowers?
Per K. Møller's dog tags
were never found.
It's obvious, talking to the priest.
Her business card is covered
with the priest's fingerprints.
Send an ambulance immediately
to Simon Church.
Interview the chaplain
He said he didn't know the lawyer.
He's swamped us with lies from the beginning.
Lund, I don't have time...
The priest is seriously injured.
I've followed the suspect.
I'm located in the meatpacking district.
Send all the manpower
that you have available here.
Stay where you are. We're on our way.
Talk with the priest. He's seen him.
Lund stay where you are.
Don't do any more. Lund do you understand?
Yes.
No, wait.
Don't do anything else.
Lund!
Reports are coming in that ormer Justice Minister
Frode Monberg died earlier this evening.
He suffered a heart attack last week and has
been being treated in hospital since then.
Frode Monberg had served as a Government Attorney for
nine years before becoming Justice Minister.
He was replaced by Thomas Buch, who was believed to have
been his last visitor at the hospital before he died.
The PM has reconvened Parliament because of
the recent threats and deaths of military personnel..
If you hadn't pressed Monberg, he
would never have admitted anything.
How much did you push him?
It was necessary to do it.
You weren't there.
Buch, what exactly happened?
In Monberg's case,
he certainly was complicit.
If we don't do anything,
the Defense Ministry is off the hook.
Monberg is dead now straight after he was 'pressed'
I want to know what happened.
We need to focus on
what we do at the meeting.
Krabbe and the Defense Ministry will decide the
anti-terrorism package. You're on very dodgy ground.
If the Liberal Party gets anything
on you now, you're done.
You've got to stay focussed and alert, the knives
are out for you now..
The meeting started five minutes ago.
We're awaiting your instructions.
We need to stop the meeting.
I'd like to know more about Monberg.
this was a statesman, a loyal friend and not someone who
would act this way..
Why did you leave him?
What did you tell him?
I am deeply shocked by the loss
of a good colleague...
...and a great political figure,
but above all, a very dear friend.
It's an unbelievable loss in light of
the difficulties our country is in.
Don't defend him like he could do no wrong how dare you..
I need to know..want to know what happened!
What happened was he was up to his neck in deceit
and if he wasn't now dead he'd be facing impeachment!
Get the press over here!
Right now!
With all due respect: I have
far better candidates than him.
I expect and hope that when Buch is gone the
Liberal Party will stop taking shots at us.
He has proved to be a liability in our partnership, expect
a smoother relationship from now on..
We are prepared to finalise the
anti-terrorism legislation.
Once Buch is out of the way.
How will he be got rid of...
We'll fire him.
Buch admitted to irregularities...
..and stepped outside of what were his duties
when pursuing these delicate matters...
Particularly the situation with Frode Monberg.
No..I think there is somthing to all of that..
Regardless of what happened tonight..in recent weeks..
I mean...
Frode had lost his focus, allowed his emotions
to get in the way of political judgement..
I'll just say that I'm being
a little bit cautious...
This whole matter has been beset with
problems and dare I say it..surprises
...when new surprises continue
to emerge almost daily..
It's difficult to reach agreement with these distractions..
The last one about an old military file
was somewhat of a shock
Have you been listening to such nonsense?
That's just what I wanted to hear.
Glad you are listening..
Once we've completed and announced the anti-
terrorism deal, things will quieten down.
There are clearly now some very critical
questions for The Defence Ministry.
There has been a systomatic cover up reaching
top levels regarding the military.
The Minister of Defence will have to explain
surpressing a two year old military file...
...that's possibly connected to the recent murders.
Despite the contents of the file there is..
Evidence to suggest that the Defense
Ministry deliberately failed to disclose
...information in order to cover-up
its own negligence.
Shortly before his death, Frode Monberg confirmed
my fears..we must now have a meeting about this.
You will be kept informed
during the process.  Thank you.
If fundamentalists aren't behind
the killings, then who is?
Is this what you mean that...
'things will quieten down'?
Lund surprised him in the church,
followed him and they ended up here.
Ready for you now..
Did the priest say anything?
No.
He died on his way to the hospital.
He was beaten to death.
And what did Lund say?
That we should check the dog tags
on the exhumed soldier.
I wish we'd checked earlier.
Get it done.
Call his mother. Find out
if there were dog tags or not.
Where is she?
She's back at the station by now..
We need to have a talk.
Right now.
But you didn't see his face?
Nothing distinguishable?
No. nothing that would help us..
Why didn't you call in before that?
You should have waited for back-up.
Are you okay?
I'll drive you home.
Is there anyone I should call?
No, I'm not going home.
My mom still has some wedding
guests staying at home.
Come
My place..
The Exhumation was risky,
but we had to close a line of enquiry
On the say so of a flawed detective's hunch..is that
all you needed to agree to it..
His dog tags were never found.
His identity has been compromised...
Lets get this straight regarding Lund and this case..
She is gone, history and made you look a fool..
...PET has been proven wrong. We
need to have a meeting with König.
König has no time. The Minister of
Justice has reached a verdict
And our problem with Raben..he is being monitored
by PET surveillance teams
Why can't you trust me for once, show some faith..
I'm not saying our information is flawless,
or that she has the answer
But if you could show
more confidence in me... other than
... at night-time meetings
in random hotel rooms...
I'll even forget the
conversation with König.
Yes. Okay. I'll see
what I can do about it.
Are there problems with the other men?
Yes, but we'll get a handle on it.
The only survivor from the group left now
is your son.
Your former son in law.
What do the police know?
Are they saying much?
I don't know much about it. How
is the deer hunting this year?
Don't know...haven't been..
..If he attacked an army chaplain,
he must be very sick.
Yes.
Good evening.
Sorry, I came so late.
Søgaard, you came.
I'm glad you came.
There's not much time left.
I think Søgaard needs me to
offer myself up for a dance.
Yes...I would like to..
Excuse my directness..The point that I'm
trying to make is...
...that it won't be very long
before they get to Raben.
According to intelligence,
Raben's been found.
PET has him under surveillance
hoping to find the perpetrators.
Excuse me.... This is Jarnvig.
What do the police know?
Okay. Thanks, Bilal.
If you tell me the truth, you'll
be back at the ball in two minutes.
The officer I took over from,
said he was called Perk.
He had a dog tag with that name,
but it couldn't have been his.
There was no other officer..
There was, you or Søgaard covered it up.
You need to know this..
The priest was found murdered tonight.
Beaten to death at his church.
You need help.
I want to see the personnel files I need
to know who was there
That information is classified...and stored at Human
Resources you have no access there..
Incidentally,
you are being monitored by PET.
Turn yourself in, now.
Are they watching me now?
PET think they can find
the perpetrators through you.
You're just making it much worse.
Now we're just talking, I am on your side. Ok?
We'll talk quietly.
Keep your mouth shut. On my side?
I was on my way home.
I had fourteen days remaining.
Now it's been two years.
You could have done something, spoken up.
There was nothing to say that could help you.
It was you who destroyed
everything. For Louise, for Jonas.
What the hell are you thinking?
Why would I lie?
Why would the others lie?
I tried to stop him.
Killing was as easy for him
as blowing out candles.
He had the officer school logo
tattooed on his shoulder.
Ingenio et Armis
I just need to see him again...
I'll recognize him.
There's a way out the back.
The road leads out to the garden.
The Khazi's are that way,
down at the end of the hall.
My options were limited. it was
the only thing I could do.
I had no doubt that it should be you when
I asked you to become my minister.
I knew I could trust you.
There was nothing in your political past...
that suggested that you would stab
your own government in the back.
Your accusations against the Defence Minister
can't be withdrawn.
I'm not interested in a witch hunt..this needs
investigating and cleaning up..
Thomas..without documentary proof there is
nothing. Rossing is a trusted minister.
Give me the opportunity to
question the safety committee.
I've no choice, after you went ahead and
shared the documents with the press.
If there's proof of any of it, I want to know before
you ever pull a stunt like that again.
If there's no evidence...you're time is done.
I'll earn your trust. Thing's willl
be better from now on.
He was found in his church.
He died on the way to hospital.
Former army chaplain. Counting him,
the number of dead is now five.
Unless we count Monberg too..
But no dog tags?
No, The killer was disturbed by a police
woman. The priest was dying on the floor.
You mean Lund?
Yes..The priest was also on team Aegir
and had contact with Dragsholm.
All the victims may have had knowledge
about the incident in Afghanistan.
Everything was documented
and processed according to regulations.
Nothing suggests the killing of civilians.
Maybe there's a reason, after all they've made
a big effort to surpress the case..
No more of that. I have a pear.
We'll need to go through this carefully.
Karina do we know anyone who knows
the Defense Ministry from the inside?
I also want to know what Lund has found out
with respect to the mystery officer.
Lund isn't on the case anymore. She was removed
after the exhumation
PET manages the investigations.
What's PET say?
They looked into what Monberg said.
They aren't convinced that it has
any significance to the investigation.
It's noteworthy that the soldier's
dog tag was never found.
Not really. And why should we be trying
to criminalise people in the army?
Not a damn thing suggests that
fundamentalists are behind it.
No...Aside from the connection with Kodmani...
Or connected with their beliefs.
This is Ruth Hedeby..
Yes?
Why aren't we investigating the army?
Lennert..Stop. I don't want to
argue with you.
So, at least let's get Raben in for questioning.
Let us do our job.
That will have to wait.
He might have escaped.
Escaped..!
We're looking for him now...
...We'll find him.
We're still working on various theories.
You need to have a little confidence.
Lennart, dammit... If I knew there
was something being hidden..
...do you think I'd sit here
and lie to you?
That was the Justice Department.
letting us know some detail..
...about the conversation
Buch had with his predecessor.
Monberg had spoken to Anne Dragsholm.
She had found the officer
that the group had referred to.
Nothing's changed. We don't know
if anything happened then, the case is closed
The Ministry of Justice directive is
clear: Everything must be revealed.
If we encounter obstacles, the Minister
wants to be notified immediately.
You forgot your...
Thank you.
Then there's just one point.
No. Lund's not coming back.
Have you tried..a...38?
Yes. 38....
...And with extra cheese.
And a 38 with extra cheese.
Yes.
Si, si.
How's the head?
I took some aspirin.
I've got it.
You can't see anything.
It looks fine.
Yes, it stings a little.
I don't understand.
What don't you understand?
Why he didn't pull the trigger.
It doesn't matter now... No.
He could have killed me easily
It won't happen again...
That was bloody fast.
It's for you.
For me?
Excuse me for interrupting.
I'll be brief.
I've had a meeting with Lennart...
Brix listened and we decided
We moved a little too fast.
You are reinstated to your temporary job...
..effective immediately.
This is only possible because of
a significant change in attitude...
...within the Ministry of Justice.
Thanks.  See you tomorrow.
I want to stay on
until the case is closed.
I'll want to lead the investigation
together with Strange.
What else will you need?
We need to get all the officers from
Team Aegir in for questioning.
Fine. We'll do that.
Oh..Hey...Stop monitoring Raben, so we can
bring him in for questioning.
Raben's escaped.
It's regrettable but
that's where we are..
I'm tired and really need to sleep
The food's on its way.
It'll keep until tomorrow.
Okay.
Lund never saw his face and so
we are working on a theory
...that we think he is an officer or former
officer with Team Aegir.
The unit was led by 28 officers before it
was disbanded. All are potential suspects.
Track them down.Get them all in for
questioning wherever they are.
Per K. Møller's ID tags
were never found.
Someone has been using his identity.
We need to check through these receipts
for things bought in his name.
we need to carefully work backwards to when
Anne Dragsholm found the officer
who called himself Perk.
We have to find out
how she located him.
Intelligence recorded the details of
everyone who attended the cadet ball.
What did they say about Raben?
He left the car there.
He entered the building where they lost him
After the party, he disappeared.
His wife and the Colonel stayed there.
Nothing suggests that they made contact.
He's doing the same as us. investigating.
What does it have to do with
the ministers of Justice and Defense?
We need to ask..there are lot's of unans.....
Don't get ahead of yourself..
Have you checked Søgaard's background?
Yes it's very interesting...
We're about to send a new team to
Afghanistan. This is very inconvenient.
Where were you yesterday between 17:00
and 21;00 before you went to the cadet ball?
One of my officers wanted to talk to me
before the redeployment begins.
Who was the officer you saw?
Call me immediately if you find a problem.
Otherwise it'll be half a year.
Yesterday you also spoke with
the chaplain. Why did you call him?
Is it now illegal to call an old friend?
Were you afraid he would talk?
About what? Raben had attacked him.
I wanted to make sure he was ok.
Dragsholm had contacted the chaplain...
...because she wanted to reopen
an old military case.
If you say so.
Back then you said that Raben was
unpatriotic and cowardly.
It's true. Raben's behavior harmed us all.
Put safety and care at risk.
What's your relationship with Raben's
wife? You drove her home yesterday.
How long have you actually
known her?
Five years ago
you gave you the order ...
...for some cadets to be tied to a tree.
For some minor breach of rules...
A minor breach of rules..the service without
rules and discipline is worthless..
Civilians don't understand what it means
to put your lives in the hands of others.
In war you need to trust each other.
Raben's group failed because they were
accusing a Danish officer of killing civilians?
That would give you and your fellow officers
a good motive to cover up..
I won't say anything more
without a lawyer.
Get to the back of the line. There are
30 of your colleagues waiting to be seen.
So you left the military college together?
Søgaard gave me a lift home.
Did you notice anything unusual? There
were armoured vehicles everywhere.
Pressure Dressings,
painkillers, morphine, etc.
What about the day Gruner was killed?
I've already said.
We met Søgaard by accident, and he
gave us a lift back to the barracks.
Anything unusual in his behaviour lately?
I don't know if he's been
in Sweden with explosives...
...but I don't think he was.
He helped me to paint and then
we went to my dad's place.
Good. Thank you. You'll hear from us
if there are developments.
Could you check my innoculations..
Sorry. Just two seconds.
I need the key to the store room
to pick up the rest of our kit.
Yes of course, no problem..
I'll handle it later.
We're busy right now.
I want everything to be ready
before Jonas comes home.
That idiot from yesterday has come to visit..
Police have focused their attention
on officers from Team Aegir.
Tell me what they say...what they think..
They seem to think that there's a
military connection with the murders.
Madness. They're our best people.
Not determined terrorists.
We'll do what we can to help the police.
No point in impeding their work.
Only the police? Jens Peter Raben
was at the military college last night.
Did you know?  No. Why?
What did he want?
He's also interested in the officers
who made up the unit
Raben succeeded in shaking off
the Intelligence tail.
Early this morning we had
a break-in at Human Resources.
Raben was detected on the surveillance
camera.No doubt it was him.
All officer records from
Team Aegir are missing.
Report: Captain Torben Skåning
mentally unstable, tantrums
Three soldiers died during the mission.
The Ministry of Defence was informed.
Reportedly, a local family was executed
by Danish soldiers.
Is there any evidence?
No.  Only the provost report.
The soldiers all claimed that the officer
they came to the rescue killed civilians.
The story was dismissed as Taliban
propaganda and the unit was withdrawn.
What caused them to change their minds?
They didn't answer that question.
They're all dead.  So be it.
Any news about Raben?
No. They keep us informed when there is anything.
The Minister of Defence knew there
was something wrong with the case.
Connie Vemmer, a journalist, wants
to see you.  She can join the queue.
She knows something about Rossing.
She used to worked for Defence.
Come
I worked for the press service at the
Ministry of Defense...
...when the case came up two years ago.
On the day the soldiers were buried,
the minister gave a speech...
I was at work and received a fax...
Anonymously, from Afghanistan.
Is it okay if I smoke?
No.  But go ahead.
Thank you.
Where was I?
There was a fax.
It was a medical report from the
field hospital where the casualties were.
There was a mismatch between the
collected limbs and body parts.
Mismatched, how?
They had one hand too many.
A hand?
It wasn't a soldier's hand.
The hand of a dead civilian?
A logical conclusion.
I gave the fax to the secretary and
thought the matter would be investigated...
...because it supported the soldiers'
allegations. But nothing was done..
There was no response.
The fax isn't in the case file.
You need to come and explain this
to the Security Committee.
I can't. I'm subject to the
Official Secrets Act.
I risk being charged with treason.
Otherwise, I'd have written about it.
If you want to make a deal...
I've been waiting for someone
to take up the matter.
If you will not testify,
I can't use a damn thing.
What's this?
The Fax.
I made a photocopy,
before I gave it to the secretary.
Thank you.
We don't know her. I've got a
very bad feeling about this.
Sorry for the delay. I apologise.
We're here to consider the allegations
made by the Minister of Justice...
....against the Minister of Defence in
connection with the military matter.
Present are the Ministers of Interior,
Foreign Affairs and Defense...
and now finally the Justice Minister
In August, two years ago, an incident
was reported in Afghanistan.
It was alleged that civilians had been
brutally killed by Danish troops
while serving in Afghanistan.
Hereinafter referred to
as the 'Helmand' matter.
Raben stole information about
the officers in Team Aegir.
He's clearly trying to track someone down
We need to get hold of him.
He must have a car again. Find out
which cars have been reported stolen.
Trace as many as possible
Sorry.
Excuse me.
There's something you should look at.
Lund... look here.
They had to go and find him. He didn't
appear for questioning. Lund...
Yes. Who is he?
Lieutenant Peter Lænkholm.
He was kicked out a few years ago.
Thank you.
I'm not in the army anymore
so I can't really help you.
You were in Team Aegir? What do you
think about Major Søgaard?
Super.
He taught me at the military college.
I thought he was great.
I chose to serve under him.
You didn't serve very long.
I went to Afghanistan.
It says here that you were uncooperative
and had disciplinary problems.
I'm not saying anything about Søgaard.
The thing is, he is my friend.
I'll tell you something friend..
You have enough marijuana at home for an
extended vacation in prison. Get me? Huh?
But I'm not a dealer.
Tell us about Søgaard.
What went wrong?
As long as you follow the rules,
there's no problem. He's cool.
But you didn't follow the rules.
I smoked a small joint. I wasn't more
of a problem than the damn Taliban.
And then they kicked you out?
No. Søgaard kicking people out
was not his style of doing things.
It was a serious challenge to his command.
What then?
They pick you up at night
when you're asleep.
They tie you down
with zip ties and gaffa tape.
So, they hang you up
with a flare in your ass.
A flare?
Yes. And that's not nice, I can tell you.
Did anyone help you?
Søgaard is God. Nobody does anything
without his say-so there.
What about Raben and his group?
How did Søgaard treat them?
Not particularly well.
They were in deep shit.
How did you know that?
We heard the rumours.
And an officer was sent home.
Søgaard simply had the officer
flown home early.
He did something worse than smoke
marijuana.  What was his name?
His name was Skåninge.
Okay. What else?
I don't know.
Is this him?
Fine.
He's not answering. It sounds like
his phone's turned off. Come on.
Why wasn't parliament informed
of the allegations?
We are fighting a war, we don't bring
to parliament every piece of Taliban propoganda
No-one at your ministry suggested that the
claimed civilian deaths should be investigated?
Come on, Buch. The Minister of Defence
has already answered the question..
Can we now finally find out
what this is all about?
What's this?
A report from the field hospital.
It was faxed to your ministry, on the
same day the soldiers state funeral.
There was one hand too many
among the body parts.
Apparently from an Afghan civilian.
How do you know that?
The doctor concluded that the alleged...
...civilian deaths should be investigated.
The case was investigated and the truth is Buch...
there were no grounds to do anything
You didn't do a damn thing, you failed your duty..
You saw the report. but did nothing...
..and you kept Monberg quiet with nonsense
and flim flam about national security.
And when the first victim was found,
you still didn't do a damn thing.
Five people have been killed.
And perhaps they didn't have to die.
Does the Minister have an explanation?
Yes, of course.
The fax wasn't included in the file
because there was an inaccuracy.
Nonsense. Time, date place are
indicated on the fax. Everything is there..
If you'll get of your high horse
and allow me to finish..
A closer examination revealed that
hand belonged to a suicide bomber...
...who tried to blow up
the besieged building.
The evidence in the fax should have been investigated..
But still... There is the corrected
medical report that we received later.
I don't want to waste your time.
You may read the report.
I think it's been a bit of an ordeal.
How did you know
I'd talk about the fax?
You ignored the experts. You forced
police and Intelligence ...
... into a smear campaign against our brave soldiers
serving in Afghanistan.
You pressured Monberg when he didn't feel well!
God knows what you did to him.
And now you push responsibility
for your own ineptitude on me.
Your husband isn't answering
his mobile. He's not home.
Then try...
No, why?
When was that?
Okay, good. She doesn't know
why he's not answering.
Skåninge is studying Afghan
and went to the library today.
And later?  Two hours ago,
someone called. She didn't know him.
Hello.  I thought you were never coming back.
Ah I was held up, traffic.
I'll get going then
Good luck. Bye.
The Minister of Defence
refutes all your allegations.
Will there be an official apology
from your side, Buch?
More embarrassment for the government
are emerging about Thomas Buch
Political commentators describe Justice
Minister Buchs future as highly uncertain...
...after what is seen as a massive political
blunder that has seriously damaged his future
Analysts expect the People's Party
will insist on the Minister's departure...
...and use the political situation
to defeat the anti-terrorism package.
It was the journalist for sure.
Yes yes, you were right..
The Minister of Defence stuffed us.
Nobody was really slandered,
I'm happy and relieved that...
...the Minister of Justice has been
asked to withdraw his accusations.
It's my own fault.
The Defence Minister was right.
I pressured Monberg too much.
I continued to pressure him.
I didn't think for a moment about
his condition. Not a single moment.
You had good reason.
You were onto something.
Apparently not.
Sorry. Can I just talk
to you for two minutes?
I hope that you won't gloat. It's a bad
time.
I don't want to...
May I smoke?
...talk about the anti-terrorism package.
And I don't want to suck up to you.
I know I'll get my anti-terrorism package
through and I still want you out.
But how confident are you about
the charges against Rossing?
Why'd you ask?
Surely, it is not something
that you'll lose sleep over?
You still believe there's something to it?
Why are you asking?
I saw that the Minister of Defence
was exceptionally well-prepared.
Maybe even a little too well-prepared.
Yeah..
He was very well prepared.
I got a tip about an important fax. It
was probably arranged by Rossing.
And I went in with both feet.
Satisfied?
Did you tell anybody about the fax before the
meeting? I imagine you kept it all quiet..
Yes of course I wanted to
catch him off balance..
So only you and your staff knew.
Krabbe It was a set up..
Was the Prime Minister aware?
Of course The Prime Minister knew
I didn't realise the full extent...
Excuse me, the Prime Minister would like
to see you in his offices straight away..
Sorry.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Good luck and.......Thanks for listening.
It's fantastic. Come on.
Come along.
No filming, I'm too fat.
Nonsense, you're beautiful.
Hi. Sorry, I'm late.
They've kept me quite busy.
I'll come back later.
No,  stay here.
Is your son home?
No, he's with my dad.
You haven't failed him, Louise.
You've held out longer than most.
There's something
I'd like your help with.
We'll try his house again.
Shut up. You said he was called Perk.
You had the ID tags. It was you.
Not true. Admit it, damn it.
I know it was you.
I came to your rescue.
Leave me alone. I was sent home
with a nervous breakdown.
I flew back with the wounded soldiers.
What soldiers?
Those from the 3-2-Alpha.
The survivors who were beseiged
for two days in a village.
You were on the plane?
Now leave me alone.
Raben...
Put the gun down.
You're the only one remaining.
Raben, think twice.
Put the gun down and come
over here....Come..
It's okay. He's my colleague.
Just put the gun down.
Raben, put the gun down.
Put it down, damn it.
Put the gun on the floor.
Perk...
Put the gun down, I said.
Put the gun down, now.
Do as he says.
No!
Subtitles re-edited by DG