Ten days ago a woman was killed
in unusual circumstances
How many will follow me in death?
What does PET have on the group?
Raben was the squad leader.
There was no officer named Perk.
There were no civilian bodies.
Why was he depressed?
He escaped.
It doesn't matter now..
He could have killed me easily.
The Minister of Defence needs to
explain the circumstances...
...of the Afghan military isssue
that may be related to the killings.
If there's any truth to it,
we have to know the details.
..No evidence..
and your time is done
We received a fax from
the camp in Afghanistan.
There was a mismatch
in the number of body parts.
They had one hand too many...
...it belonged to a suicide bomber.
Who tried to blow up the beseiged building.
It appears in
the adjusted medical report.
The Minister of Defence was unusually
well-prepared for the meeting.
Did the prime minister know?
Of course he knew...
I didn't know the extent..
There was no other officer
Why would I lie?
He had a officer school logo tattoo on
his shoulder, If I saw him, I'd recognize him.
You haven't failed him.
You've stayed longer than most do.
I need your help with something.
You'll temporarily have your job back.
How did Søgaard treat Raben?
Not well. They were in deep shit
There was the officer
who was sent away...
...I know it was you. We came to your
rescue. Do you think I'm crazy?
I was sent home because of
a nervous breakdown.
Raben... Put the gun down.
Perk...
Put the gun down now.
No!
On the left side of the chest...
...the bullet pierced his lung.
Has he eaten recently?
He's lost a lot of blood.
Is he allergic to any medication?
They have his medical records.
He needs to have his lung drained.
Prepare him for the operation.
You can't come in here...
They need to question the officer Raben was holding,
see if we can find out what happened..
He'll be okay in there
I had to shoot. He was standing there
and waving a gun.
Why didn't he run? What happened?
He was putting it down.
I'd calmed him down, he was coming..
Then you came in.
He thought you were Perk.
Perk!
Where is he now?
On the operating table.
What the hell happened?
He took the officer hostage.
He had a gun. He ran away.
He wouldn't drop the weapon.
Who shot?  I aimed at his arm.
Put guards on Raben.  No one is to
see him without our authorisation.
How's his condition now?
Why didn't he put the gun down?
I don't know. But we have
the officer in custody.
Raben also found him.
I think he was right.
Saturation?
Blood pressure dropping.
Ventricular fibrillation.
More oxygen
Put the gun down now!
Perk...
Raben said the officer they were
sent to rescue, was called Perk.
Søgaard helped bury a soldier with
that nickname, three months earlier.
Wasn't it strange?
He couldn't be Perk.
What about the radio call that Raben and
the group claimed they received...
...of a unit in difficuty? Nothing like
that was reported
We have a tight schedule for
the redeployment tomorrow.
I suggest we address
these questions later.
There was no officer.
We had no people in the area.
No. not officially
I want a transcript of all radio
communications in that area from that time
Ask HQ to send it over.
Bilal!
Just between us.
Something happened to Jens.
The police tried to reach you.
I'll stay with Jonas. You go ahead.
What happened?
Does he have an alibi?
Skåning had a nervous breakdown.
He was flown home with Raben
and the wounded soldiers.
Check again.
I'm on my way.
The surgery just finished, he's stable now.
What happened?
He took an officer hostage.
He had a gun and tried to escape.
Why was he shot?
Because there was an...
...an emergency. He wanted to commit
suicide. Then he changed his mind.
But he wouldn't put his weapon down.
Sorry... Just a moment.
These are his personal belongings.
They're questioning the officer now.
I'll check the officer's explanation.
His ststement is ready.
It must be him. We've checked
all other officers thoroughly.
We can talk to Raben tomorrow.
We've got a problem. Raben said
something before he went under.
He was rambling but nonetheless
He said repeatedly, that the
policeman who shot him was Perk.
The doctor said it was delirium,
but it'll be included in the report.
Did we describe the event accurately?
We did.
What did the doctor mean, exactly?
Something was wrong. When Raben
saw Strange, he called him 'Perk'.
Anyway...Two seconds before, he was
threatening to take his own life.
He was confused...
He was definitely not himself.
What did Strange say?
What could he say? I'm going to HQ.
We need to take this seriously.
When Strange was hired a year
ago, I read his resumé.
He served in the army.
I know...in Vordingborg.
He had back problems.
That doesn't make him suspect.
Strange was not only posted
in Vordingborg.
At some point Strange was in the
commando division. As an officer.
What are we going to do next?
Raben is the last survivor
from that soldiers group.
The Minister of Justice Buch accused
the Minister of Defence ...
... of withholding information about
civilian casualties in Afghanistan.
The Prime Minister held a meeting
with Buch.
Krabbe call me back.
I don't have any excuses.
I regret the delay,
but there's a lot of work to do.
I know...do take a seat..
Would you like something to drink?
No thanks.
I want to clear things with the Minister of Defence.
This matter is causing turbulence
Go on..
Of course I am aware I was a bit rushed.
hasty in my actions..
I am sorry for the misunderstanding.
I'll offer him my apologies ...
...so we can continue our work.
Likewise with Krabbe.  We're under
pressure with the anti-terrorism package.
If I could just talk to him, I'm sure ...
You've been a minister for 7 days.
In that time God created the Earth.
You have come close to ruining everything.
Politics is a team sport.
Don't go on a solo tour leaving turmoil in your wake
as you try to make your name
You've been damaged
by all the allegations.
I listened to you, but you didn't
listen to me. You'll have to resign.
I'm not ready or going to resign.
There are too many loose ends.
How did the Minister of Defence
know I would bring up the fax?
What fax?
The fax about the medical report
and the extra hand!
I didn't tell him anything.
Who did then?
Should I call Rossing over here
so he can answer?
No.
No. It's nothing.
Are you coming to the reception?
No thanks. I don't have time.
Here's what we'll do: Tomorrow we finalise
the anti-terrorism package.
You hold your resignation press conference
and come out with half a victory.
You have the skills. Keep low for a
couple of years, then you'll come back.
See you tomorrow.
Say 'Hi' to your family from me.
How long were you a commando?
Come on, Brix I can't tell you that.
You have to answer. There'll be
an investigation into the shooting.
We need to know where we stand.
I spent several years in the army.
They asked if I wanted to join
the commandos.  I said yes.
I got tired of it... fed up...
and entered the Police Academy.
But you went back in again, why?
After September 11, 2001, I was
invited to rejoin the commandos.
I was bored working on the Drug
Squad, so I took another rotation.
I quit six months ago.
Were you in Afghanistan?
Yes. Three times. But, I had nothing
to do with Team Aegir.
I was back home half a year
before they deployed.
I've never met Jens Peter Raben.
If I had known anything about
this case,  I'd have told you.
Why didn't you say something?
I wanted to put it all behind me.
My life fell apart while I was there.
My marriage, my children.
I suffered from depression,
which took me a long time to get over.
Raben was very interested in a tattoo that the
officer had on his shoulder.
'Ingenio et Armis'.
'With wisdom and weapons'
We're wasting time. Why aren't we
interrogating the officer?
He's not here.
We sent him home.
There must be something we overlooked.
Just show us your shoulder
then we'll get this over with.
Find out how many people
have this tattoo.
Turn in your gun and police ID card.
We need to investigate this.
You'll be questioned about the shooting,
Go home now.
Strange is temporarily suspended.
You'll take over his duties.
Okay.
You'll get a briefing from Lund.
I've asked the commandos for a list
of their officers.
I don't see any involvement.
The case is linked to Afghanistan
He didn't say a damn thing.
Not even in his resumé.
That doesn't make him a suspect..
No..We have to consider him a suspect.
When he shot Raben...
..was there no other way?
No..
It was justified.
Were  you with Strange when
all the killings occurred?
Either Raben is crazy or...
Strange is lying.  I prefer the former.
Think hard.
How is he?
He's out of danger now. He'll sleep until tomorrow.
He's fine. You can see him.
I'll wait until tomorrow.
It's important that he feels
that someone is there for him.
The doctor says
I need to speak with you.
I don't know what to say.
I watched an old video tonight.
We were on the beach, just before
Jonas was born. Do you remember?
We couldn't decide
what he should be called.
We had made
a long list of names.
After a while you wanted
to go swimming.
Not me, because I felt
I looked like a whale.
But you picked me up and carried me
to the sea. And you kissed me.
And you said that you now knew
what he should be called.
We called him Jonas...
...because he was inside a whale.
I'm going home.
No comment. We have no statement
for the press until we know more. Bye
We need to find him...any joy?
His driver hasn't seen him. He left the Prime Minister
over an hour ago in some distress..
He's not answering his mobile. I'm hearing
lots of rumours.
Let's wait to hear from him.
Maybe he agreed to meet with that
journalist without telling us..
Is this the Secretariat? Plough.
We can't find our minister.
Could he be at a committee meeting?
What do you think?
Where do you think...? How long?
It doesn't matter. Thank you.
Where is he?
He's at the Ministry of Integration.
Hello...This is done..I need another one...
Connie Vemmer wants to talk to you.
Have a glass of champagne.
The Minister of Defence knew we
had the medical report.
Did Krabbe tell him?
They have Raben. He's hurt, but ...
It's over!
I'll resign tomorrow.
We can't just give up.
Something's not right.
Buch..We have to stand together on this.
We need to keep cool heads.
You don't know what you're talking about.
and it's all your fault
Now I think you've crossed the line.
We didn't have enough info!
You had no idea what Monberg
was going to do...
...You slept with him!
Why don't you check the dates? Goddamn it!
Don't go. Come back!
Come here..
Please leave now.
Yes.
Yes! I'm coming, damn it.
Stop your banging now
Hello?
Buch, what the hell are you doing here?
We need to talk...it's important..
Go ahead.
We have to talk about it.
What?
To get an au pair.
It's my wife ...
...and my children.
What do you want?
I'm sorry if I confused you when
I came to see you at your office
Then, why did you come?
There was nothing.
I had the confidence of the Prime Minister.
What were you talking about before?
After your TV appearance, I was angry.
The anti-terrorism package was ruined.
I hastily called a meeting of
the party executive committee.
But you weren't there.
I was in the car when I received
a message from the Prime Minister.
The Minister of Defence
would be exhonerated ...
and the anti-terrorism package
will be back on track tomorrow.
How did they know that before the
meeting of the Security Committee?
I don't understand, but...
...I've been thinking about that
and I think I understand it.
Who cares if the prime minister had
advance knowledge?
They knew that your allegations
would be rejected. So they called me.
It's possible they just don't
have confidence in you anymore.
Or the defense minister just
wanted to made a fool out of you.
But it doesn't appear that the
Prime Minister is the villain.
I spoke with him this evening.
Everything was fine.
I'm pleased that he's given
you the boot, I fought for it.
You were not good for the job at hand
Now I'll call you a cab.
When was Strange sent home?
He claimed, six months ago. The
commandos won't give that information.
General Arild is coming to see us
tomorrow morning.
Good. Can you send Strange's CV
to me? Thanks.
Lund...
These are documents on the soldiers
who died during Raben's last mission.
I had them in the car.
It's best that you take them.
I don't care what Brix thinks...
...or what crazy Raben thinks.
It's late for this..
What do you think?
You should have said something.
Why?
Why didn't you tell anyone
about your partner who was shot?
A detective told me you were biased
and guilty in Jan Meyers death.
I've always backed you up, even
when you have been wrong..
I've told my children about you.
They asked me why I was happy.
I said that I'd met someone.
We have been very cooperative.
Your interrogations at the officers'
barracks. And now the commandos.
Were there commandos in that
area two years ago?
Yes they were there.
While Team Aegir was there?
Was Ulrik Strange
sent home six months earlier?
I can't confirm that.
I want a list of the commandos who were there.
I can't give you that information.
It's classified and not for your eyes.
But no commandos were involved
in the incident.
Brix...
The Danish commandos are brave men who
don't randomly kill civilians.
We have to send off our team, I hope
this is at an end now
They were deployed and now they're dead,
we need info.
The ravings of a traumatized soldier are not enough
to warrant this witch hunt
Answer me this..How could Jens Peter Raben
have slipped away from Intelligence?
It's like this. Either you give me
what I need...
...or I'll call the press and ask why ...
you are being obstructive and not trying to help us
resolve this matter? Do you understand...?
...or should I find someone higher up who
can give us the information we need?
I understand that the information is
important. I'll do whatever I can.
Jens Peter Raben just woke up.
He's asked to speak to you..... immediately.
You've had arterial surgery.  Careful.
It could be fatal.
Wait... Wait a minute. I'll get someone
to help you get ready.
I'm sorry if I've put you in
an embarrassing position.
I've been happy to be here. I hope my
successor will be more successful...
...regardless of who it is.
Thank you.
Today's program:
The Prime Minister expects you
to give the usual resignation speech.
Then there's Jens Peter Raben...
It doesn't matter.
I want to say sorry for my behavior last night.
It was wrong of me to treat you like that
You've always supported me.
I'm the one who blew it.
It's the best solution for both the
government and the ministry.
I wish you all the best.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
I'll just have to take this call..
Was it the wrong brandy?
No, it is fine.
Plough has his own concerns.
He's been summoned to a meeting
with the Prime Minister.
Rumour is they'll appoint him as the
EU advisor in Skopje and banish him
If Plough goes, I'll probably go too.
But it doesn't matter.
The journalist told me that she can
explain everything and make it all clear
But only to you. It might be worthwhile..
I really think that you ...
I'll talk to prime minister about your future.
I'm sure there's a place for you here
See you down the hall.
We should've never backed him up.
It's Skopje. EU advisor.
After 23 years, I end up in Skopje.
Skopje isn't the end of the earth
What the hell do I tell my wife?
And where is it? Do we have an atlas?
Listen... Maybe your wife
will want to stay in Denmark.
At 09:32, we received a message
that a Danish unit was under fire.
We crossed the river, then it went wrong.
Thomsen told you what happened.
We fought our way into the building.
There was no sign of any Danish unit.
Only one officer who had barricaded
himself in with a local family.
Why did you think his name was Perk?
That's what was on his ID tag.
I assumed, that he was
from another Danish camp.
How did he get there?
He said he was separated from his group.
The Taliban chased him.
He sought refuge in the building.
There were only four of us.
Myg, HC, Sebastian and myself...
...and Perk. Dolmer was killed when
he went inside. Grüner was shot...
...in the leg. He needed help but,
we were under attack. Thomsen had...
...the radio. What about Perk's radio?
He said it was shot to pieces.
He decided it was better
to wait, than to fight it out.
The shooting continued.
The next day it began to heat up.
We had very little water. The stench
was unbearable. No one came to help.
Perk became irritated and angry
He wanted to try to get away.
He wanted the father of the family
to help obtain a radio.
The father said he knew nothing
about where to get a radio .
Perk took a child, a girl, and...
...held a gun to her head.
He asked the father whether he
would help the Taliban or us.
And then he shot her.
He took the mother and shot her too.
The father was holding the youngest,
a boy, and begged for their lives.
Perk shot them both.
What did you do?
I held the first child... the girl.
I didn't think he would shoot her.
What did the others do?
They all shouted at once.
Sebastian shouted.
Was that Sebastian Holst?
The youngest. He was more interested
in his camera than his gun.
I threw my arms around him. I
managed to get him calmed down.
When it got dark, we suddenly
heard an engine noise.
A man drove his motorcycle into the
courtyard and blew himself up.
So I don't remember much after that.
Help may have arrived shortly after.
Where was Perk at that time?
I don't know.
He must've found a way out,
just before help arrived.
And the bodies of the family?
He must've got rid of them.
You can ask him yourself. The
policeman who shot me...was Perk.
Where is he?
Why do you think it was him?
It's him. He's killed all the others.
He has the tattoo on his shoulder.
You were also convinced that the
officer you took as hostage was Perk.
I want you to look at these.
Just take your time.
Raben needed to tell us that story.
He's the accused, but he's also the victim.
Strange may have been there?
That hasn't been confirmed.
But Raben is mentally unstable,
of that we have documentary evidence.
He may have confused Strange with
another commando officer.
We're checking into that now. Strange
investigated the matter with Lund.
We've never identified any other trace
of war with the muslim league
Unfortunately there are
holes in his alibi.
It was more than an hour before we met
and went out to see Myg Poulsen.
Grüner was set on fire by a call from a
mobile, and we don't know the owner.
And I met Strange shortly before we
went to the parking garage.
He was away when I interviewed
Lisbeth Thomsen in Sweden.
And he was in the barracks the
evening the explosives were stolen.
But when you found the chaplain in the
church Strange was in Elsinore.
Has that been checked into?
I saw him come back but
of course I'll check into it.
I have to meet Sebastian Holst's
parents and tell them what Raben said.
It's already been checked
We saw his pictures.There was no officer.
He always had his camera with him, but...
...it wasn't found.What do we do with
Strange?  Get him in for questioning.
Our superiors will want to know
why you employed him this time.
I didn't hire him.
Strange came as part of a reshuffle
for police reform.
If anyone's hands have to be washed
in public, it's our superiors.
Thank you. Bye. He's asked
to see me, so I'm going now.
He's been interrogated.
Don't forget to pack those.
Tell me if I can help.
Why?
He's accused of a lot of crap.
Wasn't that what you wanted?
Here's the program for the ceremony.
I'll leave it to you. I'll come, But...
...you can make the speech.
Was there anything else?  Yes.
HQ asked if you wanted the radio traffic
text as a hard copy or computer file.
I said in view of the enquiry
you probably wanted both.
May I ask why?
Jus take care of the ceremony.
In a moment, there'll be a short break,
just before the vote.
At the press conference afterwards,
Buch will resign.
Let's see if we can get a comment.
A quick comment?
Got a minute?
There's been a stupid mistake. Plough's been
asked to resign from his office..
That was no mistake.
We need a new beginning.
..a new broom to sweep
everything clean until all
The fossils have gone.
But I'm the one ...
Buch you had apologised to the Prime Minister
yesterday. I'm glad there are no bad feelings.
We'll figure it out. It's politics.. We've said
A, but then we must also say B.
Have you seen the draft of your speech
for the press conference?
I have yes, glanced through it...
Yeah, thanks.
Sorry, I need to see him.
Plough here. Everything's ready for your
press conference in about a half hour.
Your wife has just arrived. Karina's
gone down to meet her.
My wife?
I said you'd met her out front.
Where is she?
We have to talk about the medical reports, educate
yourself........ get in. We're going.
You think I was the errand-boy
for the Minister of Defence.
I was kicked out.
He knew everything in advance...
Must have been one of your people
who tipped him off. Okay
The whole time it was right in front of you.
Why didn't you check the dates
of the two medical reports?
What dates?
I understand Sebastian always had
his camera with him.
He always took pictures. There's
a whole box of photos down there.
Did they offer an explanation two years
ago, why his camera was missing?
It wasn't missing..He'd sent it home.
He'd sent the camera back here?
Yes..It was broken.
He asked me to get it repaired
Why are you asking?
Just something I was following up..it's nothing now.
I heard on the radio
that you'd found Raben.
Now the whole story will be
dredged up again.
What do you know about it?
I don't think there was an officer.
They invented him as an excuse
to go to that building.
It was Raben's fault that Sebastian
and the others were killed.
Why do you think that?
Sebastian predicted that himself.
I lost both my sons to a war,
I don't understand.
One came home in a coffin.
The other simply returned.
I don't know what we've done wrong.
Is there anything you haven't told us?
A video diary.
I would like to see it please.
If you agree with the conditions
Please sign it.
I want to see my wife.
She's waiting outside.
You'll be driven back to the hospital.
You can have five minutes with her.
Can we have some privacy?
Sorry.
Come on.
Sit down.
They've probably told you what
happened yesterday. I wasn't myself.
It will never happen again.
We can talk about it another time.
I've disappointed you.
I was really a bad friend,
a bad father.
If I could only turn back the clock.
But there.s one bright spot.
Now they're listening to me.
You and Jonas
mean everything to me.
We'll work it out.
I've started to see Søgaard.
This has nothing to do with him.
I've missed you every single day.
I just don't think anymore that
I...
...can't you see it?
It's no good.
We have to take you in for questioning
again...We're not finished.
Sorry.
I want to talk to my wife again.
You want a lawyer?
No I want to talk to my wife.
Sebastian Holst sent a video diary
home shortly before his death.
Don't be scared, but something
isn't right in our group.
Why should I look at it?
Raben is the worst of all.
He sees Taliban everywhere
and only thinks about killing.
He takes too many chances and asks
us to do things we're not supposed to..
He invents messages for us to go out
and kick ass.
This morning we went out to search
a house for the third time in a week...
...because Raben believes that
it's a Taliban safe house.
We searched. Raben accused the
father of being an informant. ...
He placed his weapon
against his head....for no reason
The children cried. The mother
and the old women wept.
Raben will do it again.
When I talk with others, they say
it'll be okay. They don't want to
fall out with him.
But he's the best person to be with...
...once the shit starts to rain
down on your head.
And in a few weeks we'll come
home, so it'll probably be fine.
I miss you. See you soon. I'll pass on
your greetings to my brother. Bye.
Is what he says true?
Sebastian joined up, just to
compete with his older brother.
It's not about Sebastian, but the officer.
The family, he talks about...
Is this the same family,
you claim was killed?
Yes, the same family.
So you and the group had been
with the family many times before?
You were convinced that they were Taliban.
Found nothing, but you kept going there.
It doesn't matter.
No.
There's no evidence
you received the message.
So there was no officer called Perk.
I've explained everything.
Look at these..
There are five people killed.
I've done everything to find the officer you describe.
If you lied to me and he doesn't exist,
you need to admit it to me right now.
It was my decision to go into
in the village. The others disagreed.
I should've listened to them.
But there was an officer.
I saw him yesterday.
Papers from Defense say...
...that the person you identified
as the officer...
...wasn't in Afghanistan then.
And Sebastian's older brother?
Do you know him?
He's a doctor. He was in the camp.
A military doctor? What's his name?
Frederik. Frederik Holst.
Frederik Holst, army  physician.
We need to see him here.
Ask the father what the older
brother said about Raben's unit.
The minister's just arrived..
He's back.
What did she say?
Sorry, I tricked you.
You'll have to talk to Vemmer.
We know there are things
you can't tell us about.
Even if you do nothing with it
you should have the information.
I've resigned and I'll go to Skopje.
If you decide to do something,
you have to finish it.
How is the bill coming along?
The vote is in about ten minutes.
Is Krabbe there?
Yes.
But he has nothing to do with it.
Krabbe?
Krabbe? Is this you?
Damn, even here..?
Call my secretary if
you want to speak to me.
The medical report about the extra hand
was faxed to Defence in mid-August.
The revised medical report
appeared in early October.
First, a report which suggests
that civilians were killed.
And which you maintain is a
pathetic cover-up attempt.
Everything was clear, but nothing
was done for two months...
There was no reason. The hand
belonged to a suicide bomber.
Why did they said nothing?
What were they up to?
When the first report came, the Prime
Minister was proposing funding...
...to increase our military
deployment effort in Afghanistan.
It was adopted when parliament
opened in October.
You and your party voted for it.
This proves nothing. Pure speculation.
What would the Prime Minister gain from it...
That's how it happened, dammit!
Vote for a draconian anti-terrorism
package if you want.
But it will target the wrong people.
The question is whether you will
help me do something about it.
They're on the road
and in good spirits.
You never said anything
about a notice, five days before.
There was an announcement.
in August, two years ago.
Five days before the incident.
An message from the commandos.
I don't understand.
The commandos were only 150 km
from Raben's group at the village.
I've never seen that message.
You had command.
What do you mean? I've never seen this before..
Raben and his group said someone
was there. We didn't believe them.
We said they saw ghosts.
Yes, and they did. This proves nothing.
Why didn't you check it out?
I had no knowledge of that.
If an official complaint is submitted,
I want to see it.
I'm going to the airport.
No stay in the barracks until further notice.
Is that understood?
I'm glad you're here. I was going to call.
You were gone all day.
There is a possibility that Raben
may have been right.
There was radio contact with a Danish
commando unit five days before.
We have to call the police.
The police will need to focus on the commandos.
But why are you so interested?
Søgaard withheld the information. When
I was in Kabul, he was in command.
Something's wrong, but
Søgaard's not the problem.
Did you help Raben
escape from Intelligence?
I see from your reaction and silence that you
did help him slip away..
I gave you confidential information
about his security. You tipped him off later.
This is important information which
we need to investigate further.
Just answer me, damn it!
Did you help Raben, or not?
When?
Yes. That's good. Thank you.
The older brother's in Afghanistan.
He just left yesterday.
He's been home on leave for
three weeks. We found this...here.
We'll have to go and interrogate him.
There's a military flight tonight.
What the hell are you talking about?
We're wasting our time.
Frederik Holst has a motive.
He's seen his brother's video.
He was at the field hospital when
his brother's body was brought in.
We'll need to ask for permission.
I'll ask Hedeby...
It may take several days.
We can't wait.
I need a copy of the medical report
from the Ministry of Justice.
Do you want to travel as a tourist?
This needs to be done if you want to solve this
You have connections.
Didn't you tell me that Ruth Hedeby
runs the whole place.
Yes, damn it. TNT, tetryl, RDX.
You name it?
I also buy rockets for
New Years' celebrations.
My buddy... Jan Meyer.
We arrived at a warehouse.
And I went inside. I didn't think
that anyone was in the building.
Meyer went inside.
I should've stopped him.
It was my fault.
We found the perpetrator,
but it seemed... unimportant.
They pulled the plug...
I got the job in Gedser
which suited me fine.
I just wanted to hide.
If you hadn't come with the request
from Brix, I'd still be sitting there.
So sorry.
And what now?
We gotta go.
Uh, where? I didn't have a chance to
get my jacket when they took me.
We'll get it
Are you coming?
Here's the CV for Frederik Holst.
An arrest warrant. Contacts.
Strange, you'll be the point man.
You're going to Istanbul.
I'll send visas and documents
to you by fax.
You'll travel on a military aircraft
to Afghanistan under their command.
Just do as they say.
Got that, Lund?
I'll see you two back here
in 36 hours.
Take care of yourselves.
Subtitles re-edited by DG