Ten days ago a woman was murdered
under strange circumstances.
You've probably read about
it in the newspapers.
Brix thinks you can offer new insight.
Tell him it's no use.
It's Sarah. I'll be coming by train
in a couple of hours.
And I can only stay until tomorrow.
Minister of Justice Monberg is in the
emergency ward after a heart attack..
Hi Thomas. The government has worked
hard on the terrorism package.
Someone must lead the negotiations.
Would you like to be the new Minister of Justice?
We are at war.
The challenge is to find unity.
We must pursue a broad national reconciliation.
The package doesn't consider
the current terrorist threat.
The People's Party stance is too rigid.
We cannot support it.
I'm having an interview with them.
The lawyer is optimistic.
They can't say no this time.
Soon we'll be together so much,
that we'll miss being alone.
Is Dad coming home?
Oh yes.
You think he'll get out?
He seems to have a good chance.
And if not?
She was attacked and stabbed 21 times.
Here is where she was found.
She had nothing to do with the park.
What did she do for the army? She was a military
legal advisor in the Balkans, Iraq, Cyprus, Afghanistan.
There are pictures here of a dead woman
in the Memorial Grove.
Your predecessor wanted them to stay.
Memorial Grove is a national monument.
We'd like to dispell any speculation.
If we're to bring charges today...we'll need more.
You think he stabbed her...
to get her to talk. About what?
Military ID.
An army buddy doesn't feel well.
I can help you, Myg.
You don't know a damn thing.
The probation board has rejected
your application. I'm sorry.
Calm down, calm down...
Let me go!
The killer filmed everything.
I just opened the link.
"I accuse the hypocritical Danish Government.
The Muslim League punishes Denmark
for the suffering it has inflicted on our brothers
...in Palestine, Iraq and Afghanistan."
Where's the veterans association located?
The local Secretary is Allan Myg Poulsen.
The Killing II
In additional news. A few hours ago,
a terror threat was issued against Denmark.
Sources confirm
that there is a real threat.
The threat is a 45-second long
video recording, streamed online...
via an Islamic website at 17:03.
The Justice Department
is aware of the video ...
but wouldn't comment before
hearing from the police and PET.
The victim is Allan Myg Poulsen, 36,
an unmarried, professional soldier.
He's been a soldier for a number of years
and was stationed at the Ryvangen Barracks.
He was active in the veterans' association.
"The Black Berets". Which has an office here.
We chased the man who ran away.
But Lund didn't get a good look at him.
Are there any more witnesses? A neighbor
across the way saw the victim come home.
The back door was broken in.
The killer had been waiting for him.
The coroner says the victim defecated
himself and had thrown up.
The murderer was alone
with the victim for a long time.
He must have known that the
building was abandoned at that time.
Have you found the murder weapon?
It's around his neck.
Lund found him.
And what about PET?
Where is she?
We need people over on the railway area.
He climbed over the barbed wire ...
and may have cut himself.
I saw only him, but there
may well have been more.
Has PET said anything?
They were clearly taken by surprise.
We have to start from scratch.
Can I get a copy of the video?
Lund, you're not actually on the case.
What do you mean?
You sent a man down to see me.
In order for me to review the case.
You knew something was wrong,
otherwise you wouldn't have asked me ...
The situation's changed now,
but it's not your paperwork.
There are disciplinary problems ...topped by
threatening a colleague with a loaded weapon.
They haven't forgotten that in the yard.
Your failures are believed to have
contributed to Jan Meyers death.
Why should I trust you?
Give me one reason to reconsider it.
I know that I've made mistakes.
I wish I could change that ...
But I can't.
This is what I do best.
I'll contact your office in Gedser.
We'll borrow you for a while,
first just for a few days...
Then we'll see.
Do we understand each other?
The video is ready for you at the office.
They're here.
Give the girls a kiss for me.
I told the press that your
response will come later.
The Prime Minister needs to be
briefed regularly on the matter.
Eric Koenig, head of PET.
Deputy Commissioner Hedeby.
The link was activated at 5:03 pm.
It's the end of Ramadan.
We traced the site to a host server in London.
We contacted local authorities
which closed the site at 7:23 pm.
The video was sent via Hotmail to
key ministries and the media.
Surely the email can be traced?
No. It went through an unsecured network.
The website is a forum for fundamentalists.
The lP address was created in this country.
By whom and when?
Half a year ago.
We're looking for the owner.
And the Muslim League?
We know almost nothing about them.
It could be a new group...
or a offshoot of an existing one.
What do we know about
the woman in the video?
She was identified as the victim
from the Memorial Grove.
Anne Dragsholm, 35, a lawyer.
There's also a second victim.
When did that happen?
He was found when the video was activated.
The victim is a 36 year old man,
Allan Myg Poulsen, a soldier.
He had been on foreign missions to
lraq and Afghanistan.
It also seems relevant that...
the woman was also sent abroad
in military service as a legal advisor.
They are both symbolic targets
with military backgrounds.
Yes, It's clearly an act of revenge.
How can this be a surprise?
It's an unusual case. There was no indication
of terrorism in the Memorial Grove murder.
If we had known about ID tags sooner ...
We just found out about that tonight.
It's nobodys fault, no one is pointing fingers.
How do we solve this?
We'll coordinate with the police.
Send a warning to all the barracks.
But not a word to the media
about the second victim.
No way. Two people are dead,
we are under threat.
People have a right to know
what is happening.
The Prime Minister has agreed to a press release.
Good. I'll talk to him later.
Have the next of kin been informed?
Yes, they have.
Got a minute?
Don't forget your tie.
Thank you.
I'd like to point out that the ministry
has followed procedure in this situation.
But questions must still be asked.
The former Minister was aware of it.
But neither we nor PET could have foreseen
that it would come to this.
We must know where you stand.
This is a very serious matter ...
Further spontaneous reactions
from you have to stop.
It won't happen again.
Thank you.
The settlement with the People's Party
should be published tomorrow.
We need to signal that we stand together.
Yes, that we stand together.
Is everything ready out there?
Why shouldn't we stand together?
This is it. The press is waiting.
We need to search the railway area
and interview the train crew.
Check the surveillance footage.
The guy couldn't have just disappeared.
PET can't give us a list of suspects?
We'll hear from them when they're ready.
We need everything on the victims' past
and military backgrounds.
The "Black Berets" may be a link.
See if their database has been hacked and
whether the victims are on their member list.
Both sets of dog tags were cut in half.
Find out where they're made
and who ordered them.
Sarah Lund is on board and helping us.
Some of you already know her,
some do not.
Make her feel at home.
Okay, let's get to work.
You'll partner with Strange.
The Muslim League? Isn't it strange
that you haven't heard of them?
It is very typical. Groups often arise
spontaneously in a given case.
And what about that website?
Still nothing new yet.
The PET will keep us informed.
I think we should go
to Allan Poulsen's barracks.
They were his only family.
Good idea.
I am just ...
I'm sorry.
Go ahead and take the desk opposite me.
Okay. Over there?
I like to keep it neat, but you go ahead.
Here.
Strange can show you where your locker is.
Shall we get going?
Yes.
Both victims had been sent to
the Middle East by the army.
This might be revenge for our
role in the fight against terrorism.
This is Jarnvig.
Are you watching the news?
Yes. I've spoken to the Defense Command.
Put extra guards and triple the men
in areas surrounding the the sites...
... as soon as possible. I can't say more.
Why didn't you say something?
It started 14 days ago.
Okay, I'm on my way.
... We are still investigating.
And what about the terror package?
Louise, I have to go now.
Jonas is asleep.
I've put a tin animal from the
tooth fairy under his pillow.
Thanks, Dad.
I'd like to hear what happened out there.
The prison rejected his request.
I couldn't see him because he
has a history of angry outbursts.
How much does Jonas know?
Nothing.
The Superintendent has delayed
all discussions until tomorrow.
I've asked the lawyer for a meeting.
About what?
We need to appeal the decision.
The lawyer was very optimistic.
So this is nonsense.
We can apply again in six months.
Why did you take Jonah there?
Because he wanted to go.
If it takes another six months,
we can remodel the basement ...
...so Jonas could have his own room.
I'll talk to you more about it tomorrow.
You don't really care
whether Jens is released.
I have a message for the Colonel.
Come in.
Do they know who did it?
Thanks.
What's the matter?
Have you seen Myg Poulsen today?
How are you doing?
I don't know what came over me.
Can I talk to Louise?
She came to visit you.
You didn't get the message?
I told her why you couldn't come.
I didn't tell your son.
Are you ready to come back to your cell,
do you think?
Was Jonas there too?
Yes.
I would like to talk with Louise.
One thing at a time.
We need to resume your treatment with medication.
I don't need medication.
Then you can't leave.
There is nothing wrong with me.
If you do not cooperate,
you'll have to stay here.
The police want to question you
about Allan Myg Poulsen.
But based on this conversation,
that'll have to wait.
Interrogate me. Why?
Your number was in his cell phone.
And he's been here on visits.
He was found dead tonight.
Murdered... I'm sorry.
I'll tell them to come back tomorrow.
Murdered?
I don't know any more.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Call the guard if you need anything.
Okay, thanks.
Bye.
The pamphlets with the body
have been translated.
"Battle for God's sake. Kill those
who defile God." Koran exerpts.
Do we know who made the pamphlets?
They're looking for the printer.
Okay, my name is Ulrik.
I've been with the department
for about a year.
I'm recently divorced and fine with it.
I have two wonderful kids.
It has been hard, but ultimately
it's better for everyone.
I like soccer... and opera, without the screaming.
You have to make a left next time.
Allan Myg Poulsen had been decorated.
And what about you?
I haven't been decorated.
There is not much else to tell.
You've been in Gedser.
And the rest you've probably heard.
I don't listen to gossip.
I'd rather not talk about it.
But we can talk about everything else.
It's not that I don't want to talk to you...
Was it left next time?
Yes.
Thank you.
Colonel Torsten Jarnvig.
Ulrick Strange.
Sarah Lund.
And this is Major Christian Sogaard.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
As you know, one of your people
has been found murdered.
How was he affiliated with the barracks?
Corporal Myg Poulsen was a good
soldier with many years of service.
We're very shocked by his death and
the manner of it
How long has he been in the army?
He was first drafted into the army
but has been on contract since then.
He had been to the Balkans,
Iraq and Afghanistan
When did you last see him?
At the morning roll call.
He had one week to go before
being deployed to Helmand.
How was he murdered?
We can't go into detail.
Does it have to do with the terrorist threat?
Is he one of the two victims?
As it looks now, yes.
Has he received threats?
Not to my knowledge.
Has the barracks received threats?
We receive them constantly.
Phone calls and emails every day.
But not from the Muslim League.
Can you give us copies of those e-mails and calls?
And Allan Myg Poulsen's personnel file.
Sogaard will take care of all that.
If there's nothing else,
I would personally like to inform my staff.
Do you know this woman?
Anne Dragsholm.
No, I don't know her.
She was a legal advisor for
the Defense Department.
We'd like to talk to people who knew
Myg Poulsen well.
His company commander
will show you around.
I should emphasize that this case
will create uncertainty and concern ...
...my people cannot have that when
they are so close to leaving on a mission.
It's important that all communications
go through me or Major Sogaard.
Can we agree on that?
Of course.
Most of the guys are at home right now,
just before departure.
This was his bunk.
And this was his locker.
How well did you know him?
Not so well. Nobody knew him very well.
He was a loner.
When did you last see him?
At the 6:30 am morning roll call.
And later in the day?
No, they came back after FUT.
FUT?
Physical Education and Training.
Do you know when he put in for deployment?
Last week.
Last week?
Wasn't that a bit sudden?
He was already planning for a while.
This is Strange.
Who is Raben?
I don't know.
Okay, thanks.
They found the printer.
The pamphlets were delivered to
Aisha Oman's bookstore in Norrebro.
Anything else?
No, thanks for your help.
The People's Party and the opposition
support the government unconditionally.
They want an update in the case before
they'll sign the settlement.
So they don't have a letter of agreement?
Not without your update.
Plough was right.
They'll look for any excuse to criticise us.
When we have nothing to go by,
it becomes easier for them.
Why don't you go home? There's nothing
more you can do right now.
Still no news from the police or PET?
No.
I promise that we'll call you
as soon as we hear anything.
Write down the phone numbers
of Krabbe and Agger.
Then I can get it over with immediately.
I've looked at your calendar
for tomorrow.
Maybe you should have a talk
with your family.
My wife would probably prefer that I
be here to get a grip on things.
See you tomorrow.
Should I call the driver?
No, I'll find him. Thank you.
Thank you for your help today.
Hi Buch, did you get my message?
Yes, hi Krabbe. Thank you.
Of course you should be informed.
How bad is it?
As things stand right now...
Thomas?
PET found the person who created
the website with the video.
One moment... I'm just checking my calendar.
I'll catch up with you tomorrow morning.
Why not now?
There's something new that just come up
and I want to have Agger there. See you 8:00?
That's fine.
Okay, see you.
Yes, this is Thomas Buch.
No one by that name lives here.
Are you sure it was a bookstore?
Hi. We're looking for Aisha Oman.
Who lives here?
She has a bookstore.
It could be his room.
Kodmani. He sells books.
But I haven't seen him today.
Thanks. We'll check it out.
Maybe you're looking for his wife.
But she died a two or three years ago.
Thanks.
You knocked on the door?
Yes.
Open up!
Police.
Police!  Hands where I can see them.
Why didn't you open the door?
My children were sleeping.
What do you want?
Is there anyone else here?
No. Who are you looking for?
Don't be afraid.
Go back to bed.
It's okay.
Three months ago you ordered
pamphlets in your deceased wife's name.
Why?
I want to see a warrant?
Where were you earlier today?
I want a lawyer.
I know my rights.
You can not just do this.
I want to see your search warrant.
Would you mind moving aside? Move over.
That's my basement.
I want to see the search warrant.
Stay where you are.
Wednesday, November 16th 7:43
His name is Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
A Fundamentalist and widower.
A Moroccan, who has lived in Denmark for 16 years.
Engineers say it's his website with the video.
But he's used a number of aliases to hide it.
That was the good news.
And the bad?
The PET will confirm.
Kodmani served time for inciting terrorism.
They've been watching him
and are angry over the arrest.
Why?
You shouldn't stay at the hotel.
I've prepared a bed for you.
No Mom, I don't want to bother you.
You can have the key.
I'm still with Bjorn most of the time.
We'll figure it out on Sunday.
What's happening Sunday?
Our wedding. Borjn's family
can sleep here at the hotel.
There are over thirty people.
I can get the rooms here.
I hope you have time to
eat with me and Bjorn.
I want him to get to
know him, but I get so busy.
And I would also like to see Mark.
You must surely have time to eat.
Bjorn has a nice friend
that I want you to meet.
It doesn't have to be right now.
That's for me. I have to go.
I want to eat with you and Bjorn.
Who is that?
Did you get the key for me?
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
Sarah?
See you, Mom.
Perhaps it would have gone differently,
if we had heard from you.
You have jeopardized the investigation.
The investigation is stalled.
There are two bodies in the morgue.
What are we doing here?
We regret that we have disturbed your operation.
The main thing is that we have the man.
No.
It's not just him we're looking for.
Kodmani has an alibi.
And since we were watching him,
his alibi is pretty airtight.
It could be part of a larger plan.
He's had time to prepare.
We need to intensify the investigation.
Do you have any other suspects?
We need to focus on Kodmani
and his deciples. Agreed?
Shall we?
Any more news on the suspect?
They haven't interviewed him yet.
We'll release the news of our agreement today and
show the perpetrators that we won't be intimidated.
What are you surprised about?
The first murder seemed
like a marital crime of passion.
The foreign minister had no way of
knowing that it was terrorist-related.
And do we know any more?
No. What's your postion.
Heaven knows that we're against this war.
These things will make no difference.
But we need to stick together.
It's important that we act together.
The most important thing is that you realize this is
exactly what the Popular Party warned us about.
You can't make policy based on current affairs.
Two killed and a fundamentalist arrested.
We'll vote no on this package if the
crime involves groups we have warned about.
You don't know yet.
No. But it's not inconceivable.
But if the suspect is guilty,
I can't defend it to the voters.
I have a suggestion.
Let's try to find out more about the suspect,
then meet later.
If everything is clear,
we can issue a statement tonight.
That's an excellent proposal.
Good. We'll be back.
Just so we understand each other ...
If they find so much as a parenthesis,
we are pulling out.
That won't happen. I'll see you later.
Must we now negotiate with Krabbe?
He's under pressure from his people.
We need to give him the impression
that we're meeting him half way.
The agreement is important.
Let's wait for PET and the police.
That's not going to be an issue, waiting for
PET could take a while
Hopefully, the discussion
with Krabbe won't be necessary.
We're up against it..
The arrest last night wasn't
coordinated between PET and the police.
The suspect isn't just anybody.
My client is willing to cooperate.
We're looking forward to that.
Tell us about the Muslim League.
I first heard about it yesterday.
The video was on your website.
My client would like to clear up some things:
He runs a publishing house and a bookstore
with the aim of spreading the message of Koran.
On the basis of his civil liberties ...
he uses his literary platform to
make a discussion forum available.
He knew nothing of the video
and has not turned to terrorism.
You are clever ...
..and maybe you run a good business
but there were execution videos
and militant material at your residence.
Only material that falls within the law.
Your pamphlets were at the crime scene,
Your web site is used as a tool.
You can choose between solitary confinement
or cooperation. No one believes you.
I've been contacted over the last few weeks
by someone who calls himself a fellow believer.
Faith-mates who seem to share my ideals.
He wrote that he wanted to upload a religious video.
It appeared suddenly on my website last night.
Do you still have the messages?
Oh.. no, unfortunately I deleted them.
If he is a faith mate,
then you know who he is.
No, if my pamphlets were
used in a criminal context ...
he could have gotten them from a library.
Can we have a list of libraries?
Sure... if you think that will help.
Thank you. That's it for today.
Why shouldn't it help?
We are all in Allah's hands.
Allahu akbar.
We're running out of time.
We need to find this faith mate.
Here's a list of Kodmani's
religious contacts, customers ...
and a printout of names
of people in this country...
...who've visited his website.
These should all be checked.
We found blood on the barbed wire,
the person cut himself on it ...
...but the DNA does n't match anyone known.
Okay.
I'm going to be gone for an hour.
Okay. Where?
Raben is an Army buddy that
Poulsen visited yesterday ...
...in the Herstedvester prison.
He should have been questioned last night,
but it got postponed.
We should concentrate on Kodmani.
Why would Kodmani put
the video on his own site?
Why question an Army buddy?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
See you later.
Sogaard?
Have the police found out anything?
Not that we've heard.
We hope that they'll find something soon.
Did you know him well?
Not very.
But I spoke with him yesterday.
He was Jens' old friend.
I'm sorry to hear that he was turned down again.
Your dad said he was renovating the basement.
So you'll stay?
For now, yes.
I'm going to see him.
Your list of vaccinations is in the hospital.
Thanks.
Let me know if your father needs
help moving anything.
Why can't I see him?
Because of his..
...anger and his refusal
to go back on medication.
He hasn't taken any
medication for a long time.
Hopefully it's not a relapse.
But he must cooperate.
He usually cooperates.
Let's wait a week or so.
We have a meeting with our lawyer
to discuss many things. The case and the decision.
I understand that.
But your husband needs rest.
The only thing my husband needs right now,
is to see me.
I'll see what I can do.
But he needs to begin to cooperate.
It's a bad time to interrogate him.
Can't it wait?
It won't take long.
Why is he here?
Kidnap and death threats.
What happened?
He was wounded and sent home
from military service.
He suffered from delusions.
He took a nurse hostage and
threatened her life.
He was sentenced to be in custody
and to indefinite solitary confinement.
He came to visit you?
I had invited him.
He had gotten me a job.
But I don't need it now.
How did he seem? Was he nervous?
As if he was afraid of something?
Myg did not scare easily.
But he was very restless.
Maybe he was in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
I don't know.
How did he die?
He was suspended from his legs,
upside down ...
...and cut with his dog tags.
Does this mean anything to you?
No.
He hadn't been deployed for years.
Why would he leave again?
He didn't feel comfortable at home.
If that's all, I would like to get some rest.
Fine. There is actually ...
...one more thing.
Do you know this woman?
Anne Dragsholm, former military counselor.
Did she know Allan Myg Poulsen?
Why is that important?
She was killed two weeks ago.
We think there may be a connection.
I don't know her.
And Myg never said anything about her.
Are you sure you don't know her?
I'm sure, I don't know her.
Well, thank you for your help. Goodbye.
I want to cooperate.
Tell the superintendent.
Did you find anything?
I don't know.
Okay, we have a lot of Kodmanis
disciples here for questioning.
But none of them seem like a suspect to me.
But there is something else. Do you remember
Bilal, from back in the barracks?
Who?
Said Bilal, the company commander.
He is in Kodmani's customer database.
What?
He is apparently a big customer
of rabid Islamist literature.
I'm on my way.
He's a member of several Islamist organizations.
He claims that the website has been
misused to disseminate the video.
But he was previously convicted. Right?
Yes.
But we won't know what that means
until the investigation is complete.
We don't make laws based on
current affairs, but we have an offer.
We can set up a committee ...
...which examines the need for a ban on
the unions the Popular Party has mentioned.
Buch ...
I'm not interested in
ending up in pickle jar.
The credit for this committee
should go to the People's Party.
And the minister is prepared to provide
concrete data for your decisions.
You can look your voters in the eye.
The problem's solved.
Thanks, but we don't make
decisions based on current events.
Discuss it with your people...
please let us know tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Try never, it's not going to happen
The vote on the package is next week.
That may be too soon.
We have to discuss how
we'll tackle fundamentalism.
What next?
Should I ban lslam?
We'll leave it here for today.
He wants to gain votes from this situation.
I won't stand for it.
The prime minister needs to intervene.
It is your supporting party.
You have to figure it out.
No. We agree with the opposition.
Tell Birgitte we want a press conference tonight
to announce the ageement failure.
They're having their own news conference.
What press conference?
There's no press conference planned.
Be clear with the press.
Give me two minutes.
I was just about to call you.
You should know about it before it happens.
What's the problem?
We're cutting ties.
You'll have to make do with People's Party.
The group no longer has confidence in you.
But you'd agreed with the proposal to Krabbe.
Buch, you tricked me.
Can we talk about this?
I've been informed about the memo.
What memo?
The note, from PET to your predecessor...
...when they warned of a terror
connection with the first killing.
Someone in your ministry's been asleep.
The Audit investigation showed
it's been known for sometime.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Buch, I've seen the memo.
If I were you, I wouldn't have made
so many promises.
Do you have a minute?
The Colonel is in a meeting.
It's you we need to talk to.
Take over.
Do you know Abdel Hussein Kodmani?
No.
You bought a few books from him.
Al Jihad and Radical lslam.
ls that your taste?
I bought them online.
Why?
What's this about?
Just answer the question.
The books help my officers understand
the mentality of the enemy.
They need to know what they are dealing
with, so they can come home again.
Are you a Muslim, or ...
I was asked to buy these books.
You're welcome to ask.
If that is all, I have work to do.
I think you're bleeding.
Where were you last night
before we arrived?
In my office.
Can anyone confirm that?
You're wasting your time.
Wait, we're not done yet.
Are you willing to give us a blood sample?
Not unless the Colonel orders it.
We can apply again in six months,
but it requires your cooperation.
He has at all times,
other than this episode.
What happened yesterday,
can't happen again.
Can you promise?
Of course.
Can we be alone for a moment?
Yes.
I'm so sorry for what happened to Myg...
...but I need you now.
How is Jonas?
He's fine.
But you need to focus on this.
It's important.
I want a plan.
Should we find another lawyer?
Should we appeal the decision?
What should we do?
We only have a minute.
I need to see the chief of staff now
about my medication.
We have all kinds of practical issues
we need to discuss...
...like, which school should Jonas go to?
Where should we live?
First, I need to clean up my own mess.
This is urgent.
I'll see you again, baby.
How's it going?
I missed you.
Raben?
If you must change clothes,
please hurry.
Can I shower?
Yes. You have two minutes.
Raben?
Here I am.
Let Raben through.
Jens Peter Raben is on his way to psychiatry.
He should be there in about four minutes.
Raben. Dinner in about a half hour?
Okay, about a half hour.
I assure you that Bilal had nothing
to do with the murder.
Either he talks to us here,
or he comes along to the station.
All communication must go
through me or Major Sorgaard.
So I think that you should
make sure he tells us the truth then.
Corporal Myg was under my command.
I went to visit him to clear some things up.
The door was open, so I went inside.
Then I saw him hanging from the ceiling.
I saw no one else.
Then you came...
and I took off back to the barracks.
Nice story.
What had Myg done?
There had been a serious breach of security.
How?
Our security chief had reported ...
...that someone hacked the firewall
and accessed our database.
The logs showed that Myg Poulsen
had downloaded confidential information.
What's in the database?
He had downloaded a PDF file.
What file?
A list of a team of soldiers.
It was his team from Afghanistan.
He probably used the list in his
work with the veterans association.
You need to submit your DNA.
So that story you told us yesterday was false.
It's been reported. When you left,
Bilal told me everything.
I contacted PET and Bilal's
explanation has been accepted.
You'd have known that if you had
contacted me first as we had agreed.
It was Brix. PET has arrested three
people associated with Kodmani.
May I borrow that picture?
The arrangement with PET is clearly one way.
Okay. This is Lund, send two deputies to
the Herstedvester prison.
Yes. Look at the bottom left corner.
What am I looking at?
Besides Myg Poulsen. That's Raben,
his friend who I visited today.
So what?
Anne Dragsholm?
He said he didn't know her.
It's about inmate Jens Peter Raben.
He must be transferred for questioning
at the prison immediately.
He disappeared behind the MRI building.
There is a blind spot.
He didn't come out the other side.
Over here.
Subtitles re-edited by DG