Ten days ago a woman was killed in
unusual circumstances.
The Muslim League will punish Denmark.
Brix says you offer a different perspective.
Kodmani should be interviewed again.
Jens Peter Raben knew both victims.
Now he's escaped.
I have respect for your work,
but sometimes it's a disaster
The government has put much effort
into the anti-terrorism package.
Do you want to be the Minister of Justice?
The link was activated a 17:03.
The woman was also
sent on military service.
Buchs attempt to create a broad
agreement has suffered a severe blow.
There was a confidential memo.
Is it true what they say?
Yes. The memo suggested a possible
terrorism link to the first murder.
Your predecessor, Monberg, and I
removed the note from the record
The note was removed from the record.
Why?
Why did Monberg fear a threat
to national security?
The Directorate of Prisons has
rejected your application.
Why can't I see him?
-He refuses his medication.
He would never just run away.
There has to be a reason.
Hi, Chaplain. There are some people
I need to talk to.
Myg and the lawyer are dead.
Myg visited me.
Why did you rent the post box?
'Faith Brother' told me to
What language did he write in?
Just shut up for a minute!
Lund is..
I know all about Lund.
She was kicked out of here, for many
good reasons.
what we witnessed today is the most talentless
interview I have witnessed in many years
Monberg has requested material
about Anne Dragsholm.
Why did your predecessor supress
information about the warning on terrorism?
There was a risk of compromising
strategy in Afghanistan.
Frode had an agenda. He knew
Anne Dragsholm personally.
She felt that the army didn't take the
group's explanation seriously.
She argued the case for a group of soldiers.
The lawyer contacted me two days
before she was killed.
Do you have the list of Team Aegir members?
We need to talk to someone in Raben's group.
Can't you stop that racket?
We're doing our best.
He was attacked in his car and
wheeled down here in his wheelchair.
We saw the smoke,
but we couldn't put the fire out.
Are there Sprinklers?
They've been turned off.
The same with the security cameras.
Shortly before 17:00.
The victim was doused with petrol.
The fire was ignited by a call
to a mobile phone. There.
The victim was handcuffed and the
wheelchair was chained.
Must have just sat there waiting for the
phone to ring...
for all hell to break loose.
What do we know about him?
David Grüner, 28 a former soldier.
He's been employed here as a guard
for about a year.
He lost his legs in Afghanistan.
He was in Raben's unit.
He may have been burned alive.
Is that a car tyre? - Yes
I've got to make a call.
No image recognition?
We're checking that now
Everything points to the same perpetrator.
It would have been nice to get
a briefing before the press conference.
Lund knows nothing.
We came out here and then ...
I should have known.
I should have...
I should have done something.
If we'd arrived half an hour sooner.
Just a quarter hour.
Lund...
I'm okay.
The tyre around the neck is favoured
against informants in South Africa.
And against U.S. security personnel in Iraq.
They saw him run away I hear?
Raben? No idea what he was doing here.
Because everything indicates it's the same
perpetrator as before.
And Sarah Lund has it all figured out?
She's smart, I didn't know they
were coming here
Would have been nice if you had.
Kodmani may still be involved.
I'm going to take Lund off
the case for several days.
Why?
I know what I said yesterday.
But there are two good reasons
to keep her now.
What she thinks about 'Faith Brother',
that Kodmani keeps talking about?
We need to have a broader view, she gives it to us.
And what's the other reason?
Kodmani has agreed to an interrogation.
On one condition.
You must meet Bjørn before the wedding.
It's a bad time now.
How about a cup of coffee?
We could get together
Any news about Raben?
No.
What about the rest of his group?
They should be questioned.
Lund!
It's fine for coffee this evening.
I'll buy some cake.
I'm glad. I'll see you.
The cake should be without nuts.
Bjørn can't tolerate nuts.
Kodmani wants to talk. The condition is
that you conduct the interrogation.
You saw him.
You don't know if it was him.
It was him.
Maybe he...
Chaplain! He's dead, damn it.
Face it..it's fact
He had a wife and child.
Have you found the others?
There's only one of you left.
It's Thomsen.
What about the HC?
I have heard from the veterans' club
Hans died in a traffic accident last year.
I've checked and Thomsen no longer lives
at the address in Copenhagen.
It's your wife.
She said you'd not contacted her
I said I didn't know where you were,
but she wanted to stay.
Jonas, listen to her. Go to sleep.
Sleep well, darling.
Does anyone know you're here?
No, no one.
I said I was going to a friend's place.
Are you sure you were'nt followed?
Why did you run away?
Myg and Grüner have been killed.
I don't know what this is about.
They knew something. They were afraid.
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
There was something that happened
in Afghanistan our last time out.
I've never told you.
I thought it was over, maybe I imagined it
or I had invented it.
Perhaps I was crazy, maybe not...
I have to find out what happened or rot in
that Institution.
What is it you haven't told me?
Jens, give yourself up I'm sure we can explain it.
We can make it clear, they'll understand
Then maybe theres a chance for us
I can't do that..
Why not? We've waited two years!
We've talked to doctors and lawyers.
Now you can destroy it all.
What do you want me to do?
Should I wait ten years until
my son has forgotten me?
And you're out there with Søgaard?
Sorry.
I need time to get a handle on it.
I know what to do. Okay?
I need your help to find Thomsen.
Search the files in the barracks.
I need to speak with her.
She's the last one of the group.
Bring it here. It's safe.
I'll call you tomorrow morning.
I have to go now. They'll be coming here.
Give Jonas a kiss from me.
The war in Afghanistan is a fiasco. It
leads to terrorism here as a consequence of it.
It's shameless, exploiting a national crisis.
Would you prefer to abolish the law?
And democratic rights?
The People's Party supports the Government,
but these anti-terrorism measures are too soft.
The government has the country in a crisis.
The government tries to keep a cool head,
unlike my colleagues at the table
Constitutional experts have worked hard
to re-shape the present package.
Personal pettiness should not get in the way
of solving these problems.
The Ministry of Justice
is trying to withhold information.
The Minister of Justice has already given an
explanation about the Intelligence memo.
We aren't convinced what role
the Department of Justice plays in this.
Buchs' predecessor withheld
information about the first killing.
That was a security decision as we have explained
Regardless of the security situation
it's stupid not to inform anyone.
There is clearly still a distance between
the parties on this issue
We are working on a broad compromise.
And if that fails?
There is no doubt about what I
think of the People's Party proposal.
We are confident that the minister
will come to his senses.
Thank you all for a lively debate
It went very well. Shall we put our
heads together tomorrow morning?
We've found out something about Monberg.
I just want this resolved.
I'll be there.  Or do you want to keep
quiet about it? What is it.
There's Nothing suggested that Monberg
and Dragsholm knew each other privately.
Intelligence knew nothing and
König was surprised.
We know they had a meeting at a hotel
the weekend before she was killed.
It could have been completely innocent
The weekend Monberg spoke at
a seminar on human rights...
...organized by Amnesty
and Dragsholm sat on the board.
Do we know if they stayed the night?
The Minister did.
I left in the afternoon.
What do you think they were doing?
I know what you're asking....If they had an affair.
I'm sure I would have noticed.
What's Plough doing here?
He was found this evening.
Everything indicates
it's the same perpetrator.
Intelligence now doubts that
we have the right suspect.
The Prime Minister wants to meet you
and the Minister of Defence.
What was the connection
between Monberg and the first victim?
If Monberg has withheld information
on personal grounds, we need to find out.
There's something I have to tell you about him.
In the last few months
Monberg sometimes cancelled meetings.
Always with a plausible explanation.
Come to the point, Plough.
He wasn't always able to be the places...
I felt that he had someone ...
It wasn't necessarily something
his family was informed about.
He had it both ways?
You think it was with Dragsholm?
The day he canceled the meetings
He stayed at the Hotel Hammershøj.
Where he recently met with Dragsholm.
The Intelligence Service knows nothing.
And if it affected the investigation,
he ordered it.
Don't mention it at the meeting.
We have to get some more information.
Moreover Monberg knew the Minister of Defence
really well.
Good evening. I'm sorry that you
had to wait. Go ahead take a seat.
It's my colleague. Sit down.
Do you have something to tell us?
I'll tell everything
I know about 'Faith Brother'.
I tell you this to protect my members
None of the people you've arrested,
had anything to do with him.
We're not going to make a deal on that.
We decide who we pick up not you.
I realise that I will have
to pay for my mistake.
but it is my mistake alone you understand
No one else was involved is that clear..
What kind of a mistake?
My first contact with 'Faith Brother'
was an on-line chat two months ago.
We haven't found anything.
I can see now that he pressed
all the right buttons.
My religion, my political beliefs,
my hatred...
Come on get to the point.
I was sure I could trust him, he was so plausible.
He asked me to rent a post box
because he wanted to donate money.
He asked for guidance on how to put
a video on my website.
Did you commit murder for him?
No, there was nothing...
There was nothing of the sort like that.
It initially gave me a pleasant feeling.
Finally, I got what I'd worked for.
A sense of justice.
Until you showed me those photos.
Until I understood there was a price to pay.
What do you mean?
You see only what you want.
It's not fundamentalists who did this here.
It was those who hate us.
Who are they?
You need to find that out for yourself.
What language did 'Faith Brother'
write in?
English, with some Arabic.
So he was an Arab?
No. That was just to placate me.
His grammer was all wrong... out of context.
Did  'Faith Brother' write about the
soldiers' group? About Anne Dragsholm?
You must know more than that.
The words he used...
He was very precise and concise.
I'm sure that  'Faith Brother' is a soldier.
...Or was.
Kodmani remains suspicious,
but what do we know about  'Faith Brother'?
He's probably the person
behind the Muslim League.
The video, military lists, ID tags.
We need to focus on Raben's group
and keep an open mind on the subject.
What would the motive be if
Kodmani didn't do it?
What does Intelligence say about that unit?
It's a highly decorated group.
It was operating under the name 3-2-Alpha.
It consisted of eight people
with Raben as squad leader since 2001.
The unit did good work in Afghanistan.
as part of Team Aegir.
It received the highest praise.
But just before their repatriation...
the group lost three men and was disbanded
And what of the rest of the group?
There are only two left.
Jens Peter Raben and Lisbeth Thomsen.
Raben is a fugitive and
we're looking for Lisbeth Thomsen
Was the first victim in contact
with the group, or...?
She represented the group
in connection with an investigation.
About what?
From the last mission.
Contravention of the Geneva Convention.
What does that mean?
Accusations of civilian killings.
Thanks to Dragsholm and
the prosecutor's report, the unit was acquitted.
Dragholm's husband believed
there was a controversy.
Therefore, she was fired by the army.
Maybe she harbored a grudge.
But the fact remains that she resigned.
This is her resignation letter.
Do you have a moment?
Yes.
Kodmani said he thought he was a soldier.
Maybe when he was in Afghanistan.
Maybe it's someone who was involved
there and is now seeking revenge.
What's a provost report?
Judge Advocate General Corps can try
military criminal cases.
I'd like to have the report
as soon as possible.
Let's get ahold of Lisbeth Thomsen
before it's too late. We'll call her.
Thank you. Do you know where there
is a bakery that's still open now?
Yes, it...
Well.
I'm calling.
What then?
You've decided to keep Lund on the case?
Is this a problem?
No.
But it's perhaps wise
if you consider your future.
Surely my future can't be affected by König?
I mean that the Minister
of Justice is under pressure.
Ruth, what is it?
I'd like to stay fully informed.
If König and you know something ...
In due course you'll be informed.
You have enough on your plate.
Including Lund, they're all your responsibility.
Do we agree on that?
We didn't talk about anything important.
See you later?
Good.
See you then. Bye.
Another ex Danish soldier has fallen to terrorism
28-year-old David  Grüner was once
stationed in the barracks at Ryvangen.
His body was found in a car park.
Like the previous victims
He had been brutally murdered.
Police and Intelligence still have in custody
group members connected to the slayings
Well, Buch... Good to see you.
Thanks, you too.
Did I just miss something?
We had a chat.
Can you keep going?
I do what I can.
It'll be alright.
You're doing fine.
Monberg would be happy if
He knew that you had taken over.
Let's get started.
It doesn't look good, but the police and Intelligence
are working round the clock
But it may take time?
I 'm afraid so.
The terrorists have chosen an unfortunate
moment for us to begin their campaign.
We have to get an agreement at all costs
on the anti-terrorism measures.
And Gert, we can't get Agger
and the opposition to wait.
We'll agree with the People's Party
to ban certain organizations.
The investigation doesn't show
a link to those associations.
Nothing at all..
It's not right to ban them
because of this matter.
I understand your objections.
If the situation was peaceful ..
I would probably share your opinion.
The Defence Minister is right.
Damn right I am on that basis!
There are other issues connected to it.
Monberg may have had personal
knowledge of the first victim.
He hasn't said anything to anyone.
How did he know her?
What does Intelligence say?
They weren't even aware of a connection...
So they're just rumours?
There's just something wrong.
If Intelligence finds nothing,
Then there is nothing going on?
Thomas, do you know something?
No, I don't know anything.
So I think we should
concentrate on our own work.
It seems premature
to prohibit an organisation.
But these Muslim organisations
have made statements ...
...which are objectionable and hostile.
We have to take action.
I want you to finalise the anti-terrorism
package with the People's Party.
Understood?
With regard to the deployment of the next
army team there may be trouble.
We're telling everyone the procedures.
But if they face risk when they come home ...
Will some soldiers want to reconsider
going there.
We've invited soldiers
and their relatives to a briefing.
Bilal will have a word with them.
It won't be easy after what happened to Grüner.
You must explain to them that the situation is
temporary and completely untypical.
Do it dammit
It's high time to do this job.
One more thing.
Grüner was in 3-2-Alfa like Myg Poulsen.
The first victim, the lawyer,
was associated with the group.
There may be some speculation
in that context.
We have nothing to hide.
Give the police everything they want.
And then there's Raben.
His escape could be linked to here. Raben is heavily linked here
Why would he come here..
It's obvious he'd seek out his contacts
in the military, come looking for help
So he gets arrested immediately.
It is a safety issue.
If it's my daughter's loyalty,
you worry about, Bilal...
...then we're not going to get along.
Is that understood?
Søgaard, come with me
to see Grüner's wife.
Bilal, set up an agenda
for a discussion with families.
Do you have time?
Later..I'll probably move my stuff tomorrow.
I'm sure we can do it with not much upheaval
I have heard about Grüner.
He and Myg were in Jens' group together.
Really, but Jens was seen at the
scene of the murder.
The police will be watching
you and Jonas from now on.
Louise...
If Jens contacts you
it's important that you call me..
Do you agree?
Yes.
Good. When will the forensic
report be ready? Okay.
Thank you. Sorry. So am I.
Now you'll see.
The seating arrangement is
traditional horseshoe shape.
We're trying to fit personalities all together..
These are good cakes.
You're there.
Shouldn't I sit next to Mark?
Bjorn's cousin is also alone
because his wife is sick.
It's okay to bring someone.
Not necessarily.
Do you not have a partner?
No. Sarah's had enough of that.
I also put everything on hold
but then I came up with other ideas.
Do you know how we met?
Ah..excuse me please..
That's fine.
I'll get them as soon as possible.
Thank you.
How do you know each other?
Yesterday...
It's a thrift store...where you find
used stuff.
But good quality. Famous brands.
I was looking for a jacket.
That's for me.
Maybe we should have talked to
her when she was down in Gedser.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes.
Hello. Here's the provost's report
and a folder on Thomsen.
Anything useful for us?
She rented her flat out and comes
every three months for rent and mail.
That's all we have.
Why can't we find her?
She's making an effort not to be found.
We'll have to go.
Bjørn feels so bad.
Are you sure that there were
no nuts in the cake?
I get that from gluten also.
And you are?
Ulrik Strange. From work.
Vibeke. Sarah's mother.
We'll have to run.
He doesn't feel well. We'll call you.
Bue, bye.
- Bye.
I've asked Colonel Jarnvig
to come in and talk to us.
There is still no news about Raben?
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Unless I eat some cake.
See you tomorrow.
Yes.
The police have stepped up the search
for the escapee from Herstedvester.
Jens Peter Raben is 37 years old,
1.90 cm tall and has dark hair.
Police say he is dangerous and should
not be approached.
Hello?
It's me. Where are you?
I'm on my way now
Are you being followed?
I don't think so.
I'll be back in the barracks in half an hour.
Did you find anything?
I have some papers for you.
Have you seen her file?
Yes. It doesn't say anything.
Only her address in Copenhagen
Is there anything about Hirtshals?
Thomsen comes from Hirtshals.
Who is her next of kin? She has an uncle.
In Sweden...on an island.
She used to go there on vacation
when she was on leave.
Yes. That's here.
But the uncle is dead.
There is nothing after that.
Now I'm here.
Where are you?
Stay where you are.
They're watching you.
I don't want you to get involved.
Thanks for the help, honey.
I'll call as often as possible.
Jens...
I love you.
But I can't do this anymore.
I'll stay at the barracks.
They want me to stay on at the hospital.
I have to think about Jonas.
He needs me.
Louise...
I have to run now.
Wait...
Take care of yourself.
This involved the killing of civilians.
It's an allegation we often hear.
The Opposition are trying
to whip up public indignation.
It may well be true.
The Taliban often hide behind civilians.
The case was thoroughly investigated
and the unit has been acquitted.
So you don't believe those allegations.
No, they were totally unfounded.
But the report ...
I haven't come to be accountable.
Three men from my barracks were
killed on that mission.
That's stated in the report.
Could it be an act of revenge
in response to those allegations?
Could be.
The case damaged our reputation.
It might someone with a grudge.
Are there any soldiers in the army
who might be linked to Afghanistan?
No. Not that I know of.
Do you think a Danish military unit
commits attrocities? That's crazy.
Thank you. That was all.
Lisbeth Thomsen lives
on a Swedish island, Skogö ...
in the home of her deceased uncle.
The local police have gotten hold of her.
How long does it take to go to Skogö?
A couple of hours.
Lisbeth Thomsen volunteered
for military service.
And you didn't?
No, I can damn well assure you.
I pretended to have back pain, but
I landed in a foxhole.
How was it?
I stuck it out for a couple of years.
The army was okay.
Shouldn't we turn here?
No, we take E6, it's faster.
How the hell do you know?
Do you have a summer cottage?
I used to have a Swedish boyfriend.
Mr. Nilsson?
Why 'used to have'?
Long story..
It was understood that I'd move up
here, but it didn't work out.
It's a little hard to imagine you
holding hands in a Swedish forest.
Have the local police been informed
that Raben might show up?
Yeah yeah yeah
It's pretty unlikely all the same
We've accommodated all the
People's Party's demands.
That's far too hasty.
You wanted this agreement.
But now there are too many loose ends.
You've always been against the ban.
I don't like it.
It's politically motivated
These are flimsy associations
with  nothing to suggest...
...that Monberg and Anne Dragsholm
had anything going on.
Am I too early?
No, come inside.
Karina, do you want to prepare for
our press conference?
To justify a ban on certain associations.
We've reworded it
Yes. I can see that you have been
talking to the Prime Minister.
Everyone want's to get this through
There is one small detail that concerns us
"'Associations which incite terrorism..."
What is the objection
Just words..It should read:
"... encourage terrorism or other
subversive activities..."
Let's get it right this time
We're almost there
When i was negotiating with Monberg. He worked
tirelessly. Too bad he couldn't finish.
he was dedicated to finding a solution
We all are..
Despite his heart problems
he worked hard for it..
I think that he only cancelled once.
That day, the Minister of Integration...
...was assaulted in front of her home.
That gave us a topic of conversation
for our next meeting.
I'm sending the text over, right?
See you at the press conference.
This letter has been returned.
Thanks.
Monberg canceled a meeting on October 7.
Is there anything about
where he went later that day?
I'll check and see..
It's one of those days when he
was booked into the hotel.
He went to the doctor.
Call the head of Intelligence.
That day Intelligence increased security
for certain ministers...
...among them Justice.
Did Monberg take Dragsholm to a hotel?
It must be in the Intelligence report
for that day.
Welcome.
Lisbeth Thomsen lives on the other side
of the island. We'll pick her up for you.
You haven't picked her up yet..
We have a couple of men out there.
But she can handle herself.
Do you know her?
Yes, but she keeps to herself.
What does she do?
What does she do? She works in the woods,
...felling, hunting.  She can do everything.
We'll drive to the police station.
Raben will probably visit her.
If he does, we'll take care of him.
Up here on the left.
The Danish police called.
They want to question you.
Where are you going?
You want me to come with you holding this?
You've been briefed?
Yes.
Can you explain what happened?
Nothing more than what I've heard.
Have you ever received threats?  No.
Have you seen Myg Poulsen,
David Grüner or Jens Peter Raben?
No, I haven't seen them for two years.
Besides the members of your unit,
the lawyer was also murdered.
Anne Dragsholm.
Has she contacted you?
What happened in August,
two years ago?
Three men were killed.
It's in the report.
We want to hear your version.
We need to ask these questions.
It's very important to us, and for you.
We were........we were out on patrol.
After a while ...
...we got a radio message.
A Danish group had come under fire.
They were in an area by a river.
In the Green Zone,
the area controlled by the enemy.
At first we wanted to cross the river
using the bridge...
...but there were explosives.
The bridge was blown to pieces.
We called for an armoured vehicle.
Bo sat next to me and got hit in the throat.
The gun barrel shattered and shrapnel pierced him....
In the throat..
We were cut off from the rest,
but they said help was coming.
Raben ordered the rest of the unit
to go to the village ...
...to help those under fire there.
What then?
It was the last time I saw them.
They were found two days later
and brought back to the camp.
Why weren't you there?
My job was to
stay until help came for the wounded.
He died before the helicopter arrived.
The others have probably told you
what happened in the village.
You know what the report says.
They were ambushed. Two were killed.
Raben and Grüner were injured.
Subsequently there were allegations of
civilian deaths and atrocities..war crimes.
I know nothing about that.
Can you explain the anger against...
..the unit,something must have
happened that wasn't...
I don't want to hear anymore about
the accusations. We lost three men.
The group was fully exonerated.
Raben, Myg and others risked their lives.
You shouldn't slander them.
We risked our lives down there.
Sorry, but according to the report from the
enquiry no Danish patrol was under fire.
We received a call.
It may seem strange...
Are we finished?
We're here for your own good.
Why are you hiding here?
I'm not. I'm just here to get a little peace. It was
before you two arrived. Are we finished?
No, we have some photos we'd
like you to take a look at.
Maybe you can help us.
God...
That's Krabbe calling. What can I say?
First I want to speak to Intelligence.
We have a press conference to prepare for
What did König say?
I haven't spoken to him.
We have to go now.
Give me the number.
Listen to me
Just give me the bloody number
It was not Dragsholm who had
an affair with Monberg. It was me.
I didn't think it played any role.
The weekend before the assassination
I was in the same hotel.
Frode ..
Monberg had to talk that afternoon.
He had asked me to come and work
there in the evening.
I had just broken off the affair and
thought that it was a pretext.
I met him at the hotel bar, shortly after his
meeting with Dragsholm. He was quiet.
But he drank way too fast and I began
to worry. He had a file with him.
Shortly after that I left.
So, did you see Dragsholm?
No. And he said nothing about her.
I knew nothing about their connection.
But, he behaved differently.
How?
I thought it was because I had
ended our relationship.
He avoided me.
Until the night before his heart attack.
He wanted my help to
post something for him.
I gave him an envelope,
and he put it in the out tray.
That was the last time I saw him.
Now, the envelope came back with the
file from the evening with Dragsholm.
He wanted to be absolutely sure
that envelope and folder came back.
It is an auditor's report. And CVs
of the soldiers from a particular group.
There are names of those killed.
Why did Dragsholm give him this file?
There is other documentation at the back
There is an accompanying letter from
Monberg..a request to reopen the case.
I realise that I have to resign.
I deeply regret that.
I'll go immediately
It's Krabbe again.
What should we do?
How was the meeting with the families?
We've lost some, Five have resigned.
Some family members were upset
by Grüner's death.
They'll have time for reflection
until 9:00 tomorrow morning.
Give Søgaard the message
to come tomorrow morning.
Bilal, did you touch the Lisbeth
Thomsen file last night?
No.
Do you know if Søgaard did?
No, I can ask him when I give him the message
No no, Thanks, that's fine.
The Colonel is to see the security officer...
There is no need for him.
I've just spoken to security.
What I said was uncalled for.
There's not much furniture.
My stuff is in storage.
What next?
Now it's fine.
Jonas will sleep over with a friend.
I need to paint his new room.
Shall I help you?
Thank you. That's nice of you...
...but painting is good therapy.
You got just a little...
There is still just a little...
I'm really glad that you...
Give me a shout if you want me
to come and help.
Thanks.
When did you talk to him?
Is he here?
I'm leaving.
You stay here. It also concerns you.
He wanted to know where Thomsen was.
I looked in your computer.
Sorry, but he said it was important.
Did you take him to the barracks?
No.
I said he should give himself up
or leave us alone.
Satisfied?
Where is he now?
I don't know. Why?
There've been burglaries at the depot.
Someone, who knows security procedures,
has taken some plastic explosives.
5 kilograms.
You may be able to tell me
something more.  I want to go home.
Lund...
What?
No one has seen Dragsholm over here.
She knows something.
And Raben?
We haven't seen him.
Should we drive Thomsen home?
We'll take her to Copenhagen.
I'm not going to Copenhagen.
It's in your own interest to go, you are in danger
while you are here
Why the hell would I want to?
Come on, the ferry goes in three minutes.
If you're responsible for the roads,
I have some complaints.
Lund speaking. Brix here, any news?
We're taking her home.
We've spoken with a neighbour
He was called a week ago by the tax office.
They asked him to call them
the next time Thomsen appeared.
So they could talk to her.
Why is that important?
We talked to the tax office.
No one there want's to talk to her
You may not be alone on the island.
Okay. Thank you.
Does this happen a lot out here?
Let's go back.
I'll just check.
No, Strange...
Turn around. Let's go, damn it.
You're a sitting target
I think something happened at the village.
I don't know more, just talk and gossip
What do you think happened then?
They said something happened and now they're all dead.
Did they talk about civilian casualties?
They didn't do anything.
The whole thing was fucked up by a Danish officer.
The report says nothing about an officer,
all personnel were accounted for
They talked about an officer named Perk.
No one believed them.
The case was closed.
The lawyer believed them.
She asked if I wanted to testify.
Draagsholm..
Police!
Come out or I'll shoot!
What is it?
Go back to Thomsen.
Now!
That was me who stopped you.
Have you opened this?
Get out!