Ten days ago a woman was murdered
under unusual circumstances.
The Muslim League will punish Denmark
for the suffering caused in Palestine and Iraq.
Brix thinks you might help.
There's no point..
I could use your help.
The victim'm name is Myg Allan Poulsen.
Have you found murder weapon?
It's around his neck
You're not officially on the case.
This is what I do best.
We will borrow you for a while.
His name is Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
The video was on his website.
Police! Hands up.
The government has worked hard
on the terrorism package.
Someone needs to lead
the negotiations.
Do ypu want to be Minister of Justice?
The link was activated at 17:03.
The woman was also in military service.
How can it surprise us?
We were aware of the case.
But neither we, nor Intelligence had
reason to believe how it would end up.
The three of us'll go out with our agreement
and show that we won't be intimidated.
We'll make no commitment.
The package will be voted on.
I'll get the memo
Intelligence sent to your predecessor...
...when they warned of terrorism
connected to the first killing.
The Directorate of Prisons has
refused your application.
Why can't I see him?
Because of his outburst yesterday.
He won't take his medicine.
We have a meeting with the lawyer.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Police want to interrogate you about Poulsen.
I've been contacted by someone
who calls himself a 'Faith Brother'.
He described a religious video
that he wanted to upload.
We'll focus only on Kodmani and his
disciples. Do we agree on that?
I like football and opera.
Follow the links.
Myg Poulsen was a good soldier.
Has he received any threats?
We receive threats constantly.
That was his bunk. His locker.
Who is Raben?
He was injured some years ago.
He suffered from delusions.
He took a nurse hostage.
He is here indefinitely.
Do you know Anne Dragsholm?
She's been murdered.
I don't know her.
I'm sorry about Myg.
See you, honey.
What am I looking for?
Him, beside Poulsen. It's Raben.
Anne Dragsholm?
He said he didn't know her.
He left his room to go to an interview,
but never showed up.
He bypassed security
and escaped through the sewers.
Any idea how far he could be?
-No.
He can't be that far.
It's pitch black down there.
The sewer ends at the water treatment plant.
Be like winning the lottery
to find the path.
All procedures were followed.
We're checking on how it could happen.
He'll soon become tired of the stench.
Yes, this is Strange.
They're searching the sewer.
He's probably smarter than they think.
What are you looking for?
Anything.
Brix is asking for us.
Is the superintendant here?
Yes, but Brix wants a report.
Intelligence has arrested three people ...
We'll interview the superintendant first.
Raben had expected that his application
would be approved.
He's had a relapse.
Relapse into what?
PTSD, brought on by his experiences
he had as a soldier.
What experiences?
He was committed for psychiatric treatment .
He displayed aggressive behavior
when he returned to Denmark.
What had he experienced?
Our conversations are confidential.
You have no confidentiality
when others' lives may be in jeopardy.
You claimed the man could be dangerous.
Some of his comrades died in battle
and he felt guilty.
However, he suffered from amnesia.
He spoke of an army buddy
named Myg Allan Poulsen?
Not until yesterday after he had visited
..he was worried about him.
How worried?
He was afraid that he would harm himself.
Why do you ask?
What about the military legal advisor
Anne Dragsholm ...
Raben spoke very little about war and soldiers.
He was preoccupied with his family
Has he had contact with her?
No. I'd have known. Why?
We're trying to get an overview.
How can you be sure?
This is a record of his telephone calls and visits.
We're not trying to hide anything.
What has happened is unfortunate...
...and maybe we should have
anticipated it from the diagnosis.
Here's the visitation record,
since Raben arrived here two years ago.
Just so you have an idea.
We held him for nearly three weeks in
solitary, until he calmed down.
They've found where He's broken out of the sewer.
He's 5 km away. Should we hurry?
We have teams out in the area...
...and we must advise his wife and family.
He's a fugitive, but there's
no need for a manhunt.
He's on a photo with the two murder victims
but that doesn't say much.
But he knows them both.
He lied about it and now he's gone.
Is he connected to the Muslim League?
I don't know.
Intelligence is more interested in Kodmani
Brix agrees. Kodmani must be questioned.
Raben could have bolted long ago.
He could have escaped any time.
But he chooses now.
Let's go.
I'll admit that it's weird ...
I have respect for your work,
but sometimes it's a disaster
Are you now listening to gossip?
No. I'm just saying ...
Fine. I'll take it up with Brix.
I'm going. Give me the key.
No, he has no criminal record.
I have his file.
I sent you everything
so you could look at it. Thanks. Bye.
Hello.
I just talked with another lawyer.
Louise, do you have a moment?
He thinks we can appeal.
I've promised to send him all the material.
Everything indicates that he was planning
his escape for some time.
When did it happen?
After your daughter's visit.
If you have any idea where he'll go,
then tell us.
We have no clue.
Does he have contacts abroad?
Yes, he served in the army.
He's been deployed overseas
So yes, it is a possibility.
And you?
Has he said anything to you ...
If my daughter knew something,
she would say so.
I think I understand why he
is upset by this situation.
But .. here's my card if he contacts you.
He is dangerous.
Yes.
We understand the situation
Do you want a hand with that?
There must have been something.
He said he wanted to resume reading.
Whatever he has done,
there must be a reason.
He would say something to me.
He would never just run away.
Mom ...
Can't you sleep, Jonas?
Come on, baby.
Excuse me, can I get a lift?
Just hop into.
Remember to belt up, right?
I just have to go across the bridge.
I'm not crossing the bridge.
Can you give me a short ride?
My car is full.
Excuse me, are you going over the bridge?
Can I get a ride? I'll behave myself.
Minister of Justice Buch's attempt to create
broad consensus on the terrorism package -
is failing tonight. The Opposition
accuses the government of -
withholding information about two
possible terrorism-related killings.
There is an Intelligence service memo
which warned the Ministry of Justice -
of the possibility they were possibly
linked to terrorism.
I don't know anything about this memo
she is talking about.
And the government has done nothing.
-Yes. I'll call the Prime Minister if I know.
Krabbe.
I must first speak with Plough.
Where the hell is he?
He doesn't answer his mobile.
Plough can probably explain.
Yes, but where is he?
I can have him called.
I apologise for the delay. Shall we?
Our lawyers have investigated if
Agger leaked state secrets.
But is what she says true?
Nobody knows what's gone wrong.
Is what she says true?
That's my question.
Yes. There was a memo
and yes, it warned about terrorism.
No one can explain
how she got hold of it.
I don't give a shit about how she
got it. Why didn't I get it?
Lets be calm ...
I'd like to see the memo right now.
The memo came to me directly.
I gave it to your predecessor.
It's true you should have seen it
unfortunately it has been hectic
It outlines the circumstances about the
killing in Mindelunden Park.
The Intelligence service had concerns due
to the location and the woman's past.
Is the word 'terrorism' mentioned?
Yes.
You knew that I should have known?
Yes, in hindsight.
Your predecessor, Monberg, and I
removed the note from the record.
We didn't want it to get into circulation.
Information in it
could compromise national security.
What is this information?
Information about the victim's past.
The victim's past.
Monberg didn't elaborate and got ill.
So you do not know.
Monberg wanted to speak to Intelligence
about it. He knew what he was talking about.
Monberg was a very thorough Minister.
Then we need that information.
Set up a meeting with Kønig in Intelligence.
Yes. The Prime Minister will see you now.
You've done nothing about that memo.
The note was removed from the record.
Why?
It's still a little unclear.
Monberg fell ill. The case could
compromise national security.
How so?
I had actually hoped
you could answer, how.
Did Monberg say ...?
No, I can assure you.
Then it was not so out of hand.
No, it is clear.
Agger wants to discredit us.
Drop it and focus on the terrorism agreement.
Do you have the People's Party in hand?
Not really.
It's important that you deny Agger's allegation.
I spoke to the hospital.
Monberg is unconscious...
...so I need to wait instead for a report
by Intelligence. - Fine.
What has happened shocked everyone.
Instead of standing together...
...we quarrel. It will continue to grow
while the case is unsolved.
I'll get a handle on it.
I'm counting on that.
You have a tedious job on your plate
but my door is always open...
...when you need it.
Excuse me a moment.
I'll find out for myself.
Agger is more difficult than expected.
Why?
You'll have to appear at my committee
room tomorrow. About that memo.
They're hoping that you don't have
any answers and the dust will settle.
I have no answers.
Find them.
Find out what Monberg's national
security concerns were.  Okay.
Hello, darling. Well thanks.
Are the girls asleep?
I'm sorry I didn't call them to say goodnight.
Something came up.
Raben said he didn't know the first
victim. But then we found this.
Team Aegir consisted of approximately
500 soldiers deployed to Afghanistan.
including Jens Peter Raben, Myg Allan
Poulsen and Anne Dragsholm.
I don't know what it has to do
with the Muslim League.
The perpetrator obtained the list of names
of the entire Team Aegir.
So, we need to get Raben.
He knows what this is all about.
Intelligence printed the roster,
of those you're talking about.
They've arrested three suspects
linked to Kodmani's association.
During the raid on the Association's premises...
...they found a key to a post box in Vesterbro.
The box is registered in Kodmani's name.
The content speaks for itself.
Lennart.
Shall we get started?
You sympathise with the Taliban's battle
against international forces.
The Afghan people
have the right to defend themselves.
Is it okay to beat Danish soldiers to death?
What do you expect?
You are at war. You kill people too.
Do you save your photos for recognition?
This is ridiculous. I have an alibi.
This was in your box.
We also found a list of Team Aegir.
The post box was rented
just over a month ago.
It's not ours.
The photos made at the crime scenes are.
But they're not ours.
They were in your box.
Why did you rent the box?
Did you order these?
I didn't give any order.
Look straight at the photos.
'Faith Brother' wrote,
I had to rent a post box.
What bullshit. You preached to the
young members about injustice.
Why did you rent the box?
You let others do the dirty work.
What language did he write to you in?
You have to confess.
In what language did he write. English?
Shut up a minute.
Who wrote 'Faith Brother'?
What about Raben?
Did 'Faith Brother' write about a Team
Aegir member named Jens Peter Raben?
I won't say more.
So tell me something.
Who is 'Faith Brother'?
What do you know?
We'll have no problem holding him
and the three others in custody.
And we'll continue the same course.
Yes.
Lund is employed as a consultant ...
Thanks. I know who she is.
She has been with the Passport Police
for a few years.
Lennart, I wont interfere in your
investigation, but dammit ...
She was kicked out of here, for many
good reasons.
She was probably competent
but what we witnessed today -
is the most talentless interview
I have witnessed in many years.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my intention ...
...Give us a moment.
Yes. Okay.
Maybe I should just say that
I stand behind Lund.
I find it hard to see how evidence
against Kodmani could be planted.
But we'd never have reached it,
if it were not for Lund.
If she feels so strongly about Raben, as
far as I'm concerned..it's worth checking.
Okay. Well, thanks.
Aside from his wife and son,
virtually no one visited Raben.
No friends?
Myg Poulsen and his lawyer.
Someone from Team Aegir may be
able to tell us something.
There are over 500 names.
We can begin at the barracks in the morning.
I'll check up on Raben before then.
I'll see about Team Aegir.
And thanks for ...
You're welcome.
But you'd have gone ahead with it whatever,
right?
Is this a problem?
Quite the contrary.
Strange, there is someone here for you.
I'm comimg. See you tomorrow.
Call if there is anything, okay?
Lund, I have to give you this.
Raben was seen at a gas station
south of Copenhagen.
He tried to hitch a ride.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
The church is closed.
You must come again tomorrow.
Hey! The church is closed.
Hi, Pastor.
Long time no see.
Is there anything that fits?
That's all I could find.
Besides wafers, the altar wine is just fine.
What in the world are you doing?
Have you been here since then?
Yes.
I found a nice little church here.
It suits me perfectly.
Do you ever see anyone from back then?
Not really.
But I've heard about Myg.
I don't know what you're planning...
...but think twice about it.
Think of your wife and your son.
I need your help, Reverend.
I gotta talk to someone.
This is important.
I don't know who else to ask.
Will you help me?
Raben has come over the bridge.
We're about to check his contacts.
The three suspects have been
remanded into custody.
I've got search warrants
for more of Kodmanis associates.
Yes. And what about Team Aegir?
I was out yesterday evening
so it was a little late.
Hold this for me please?
Team Aegis was deployed two
and a half years ago.
It seems that Raben and Myg Poulsen
were in the same group.
That's all?
Do you have any paracetamol.
No, I do not have any paracetamol
There's no reason to be jealous.
She's just a friend.
I'm not jealous.
Okay. What do you know about Raben?
Raben is 37 years old. He's been
in the army for most of his adult life.
He's a Staff Sergeant.
Trained in Sønderborg.
He's assigned to the barracks
and has been deployed several times.
Okay.
He was decorated several times,
but was wounded and sent home.
When he was recovering, he snapped.
You know the rest.
He's also married to Louise Raben,
and they have a son together.
Why is that important?
Louise is the daughter of Colonel Jarnvig.
Jens Peter Raben is his son-in-law.
Okay. Then it's damn small world.
The colonel was also with team Aegir.
He was the battalion commander.
He didn't know Anne Dragsholm.
Why didn't you say that before?
I had no chance, because you were
so jealous. Shall we go?
You claim you haven't met her?
I've never met her.
She is in a photo of Team Aegir and
was listed as a member of Team Aegir.
The photo was taken in Oksbøl shortly
before their redeployment.
Maybe she was there to lecture the men
on the legal aspects of war before they left.
She was not part of Team Aegir.
You surely can't remember all 500 of them.
If you don't believe me, check with HQ.
She was never one of my advisors.
So if theres nothing else ...
There is actually, tell me a little
about your son in law, Jens Peter Raben.
Why?
He was sent home.
What happened?
What are you saying here exactly?
There appear to be some coincidences.
I don't give a shit.
Two soldiers have been killed.
My people ask me what happened
and then you ask about Raben.
You do your own work,
and we'll look after ours.
Okay. Thank you. Bye.
Army Command confirms that Dragsholm
was there for a legal seminar.
She appears on the team list.
They said she jumped in.
If she has known to Raben and Myg,
it was very peripherally.
Is there anything new about Raben?
No. We need to move on Kodmani.
The search has paid off. Let's
round up the whole gang. Strange here.
Just drive. I'll come later.
What now? What are you doing now?
Yes, yes. But we're underway.
At least one of us. Bye.
It's a network related to Ahl Al-Kahf...
...founded by Abdel Hussein Kodmani.
We've arrested three more suspects.
There are more to come.
So the issue is almost resolved?
-Yes. There is incriminating evidence.
We will announce later today when
we have all the perpetrators.
Nice, but how did Agger get his hands on
a confidential Intelligence memo?
It didn't come from us.
But right now it's important that
we find out how.
What did my predecessor do?
What was done and why?
It's very simple.
We investigated the Mindelunden killing.
The victim was a former soldier, so we
advised the Minister by memo.
But you said nothing in our first conversation.
You weren't briefed...
...besides, we weren't alone in the room.
How did my predecessor get your note?
Can't he tell you this himself?
I shall, in consultation with the committee,
deal with this matter later.
My predecessor would appreciate it
if you could help us along the road.
Yes, of course.
The minister was very concerned.
Why didn't Intelligence inform the
police?
There's a good reason. Intelligence
investigated the possibility of a terrorist act.
But why would they  not inform the police
if it was terrorism related?
We weren't sure of anything.
It was the Minister who considered...
...it was too risky to inform the police.
Monberg thought...
...that certain information could
compromise national security.
What information? I'd like to hear more.
So would I.
Especially since it was my department.
He could have come back with a
explanation, but he didn't.
So you don't know?
No, Sorry.
There were two folders from last year.
There must be something somewhere.
Agger's right. We haven't
taken the terrorism threat seriously.
I was Monberg's Permanent Secretary
for nine years.
It wasn't his fault.
He told no one here about it.
He had his reasons.
Buch, the whole thing is unravelling.
I found something. I spent last week
reviewing the records.
Monberg requested material
about Anne Dragsholm.
What kind of material?
It came from the Department of Defence.
It only says that it was requested from
Defence and then returned.
I don't understand. The Minister shouldn't
have done that without going through me.
Maybe you've not been privy to it, Plough.
We're busy. What can you do?
I'll get hold of the permanent secretary.
Karina prepare for the Minister.
Take your questions up with him.
Hurry, though, damn.
Grüner ...
Hi, Reverend. Where's the choir?
The choir's been cancelled.
I know I said to come for the choir, but ...
I brought my own music with me.
There's someone who wants to see you.
It's an okay job.
It's not very interesting.
I'm still a little picky.
How's Marie?
We're doing fine. We're good.
And the little one?
Grown up, now.
She's everything to me.
She wants a wheelchair
when she's as big as dad.
And then I started making music again.
When the hell were you released?
I wasn't released.
Not the normal way, anyway.
Have you talked with anyone recently?
Have you seen Myg?
You escaped?..why?
Because he is dead. So is the lawyer.
Don't you watch the news?
Yes, but I don't exactly exchange
Christmas cards with them.
What's happening?
I don't know a damn thing.
Maybe it was God's will.
Myg visited me the day he was killed.
I don't know anything! I don't want you
stirring this shit up again.
What are you talking about?
Let me go, damn it.
I don't know a damn thing.
You know nothing!
Come here.
Let me go!
Bye, Raben. And good luck.
Grüner, if you want to talk to me
call the chaplain. Okay?
I need to get hold of the others.
I don't know where they are.
You have connections.
You can find out.
Can I borrow your phone?
What are you doing?
I have to explain to Louise why I ran away.
I don't think I get it.
Take care.
I've told the police what I know.
Can't you leave me alone?
The woman was named Anne Dragsholm.
Your husband must have known her.
I don't know who she is.
Was there something bothering him ...?
His friend had just died.
His request for release was rejected.
Do you think he escaped because of the rejection?
How long have you been married?
We've known each other for 14 years.
We married four years ago. Why?
How did you meet?
I was at the barracks to visit my dad.
Jens gave me a lift into town.
He had just started.
And so it was you?
No.
He wanted to see the world
and make a difference.
I didn't want a relationship with a soldier.
So it shouldn't have lasted.
It was the last time he was deployed.
What happened?
They were ambushed and were cut off
from the rest of the force.
He was at a field hospital until he could be
moved to a hospital at home.
It took several weeks before they knew
if he would survive.
Do you know anything that could explain
why he escaped?
No.
Do you know where he is?
Did he leave a message for us?
I have to go and pick up my boy.
Of course.
If he contacts you, please call me.
Gedser passport control?
My number is on the back.
The woman in the photo ...
...visited Jens in hospital.
She had a different surname.
Many people interviewed him about
what had happened.
It's Lund.
I've been trying to reach you.
Theres an e-mail urging Kodmani
to continue the war on Danish soil.
We've arrested all suspects
related to his association.
Anne Dragsholm visited Raben in hospital.
Louise Raben recognized her.
Dragsholm questioned Raben about
what happened in Afghanistan.
Okay. Why would she interview him?
You'll have to ask someone in the military.
Lund I've talked to them enough.
Go back there.
We need to know what Dragsholm did
in the army when Raben was in hospital.
Okay.
I'll ask her husband.
Bad idea.
The man has sued us for unlawful arrest.
Intelligence will give a Press Conference
about the arrests.
If you learn anything new,
please let me know right away, okay?
Lund, try just to listen here.
Lund?
Louise ...
Would you like a ride?
Yes.
I was just dropping someone off,
so that's okay
Yes?
It's Grüner.
Her lawyer contacted me
a few weeks before she was killed.
About what Grüner?
Can we meet?
Sarah Lund, police.
Please accept our condolences.
I need to ask you a few questions.
Look, I don't like doing this,
but it is important.
I'm afraid that others will suffer
the same fate as your wife ...
Why did you confess?
Eventually I didn't care what I said.
The easiest thing was to confess.
The most important thing was that
she knew it wasn't me.
Did she talk about her time in the army?
Not particularly.
She never mentioned Myg Poulsen?
No. They've already asked me.
How about a Jens Peter Raben?
No.
Did she leave the army because you met?
No. We knew each other many years
before we got married.
I wanted her to quit but she liked her job.
Why did she leave?
She was fired.
Why was she fired?
She got into a conflict.
Some soldiers in Afghanistan or something.
What incident?
I don't know.
I have to go for the guests.
But the army got her to investigate.
That was part of the problem.
She did it on her own initiative.
She didn't believe the army took the
group's explanation seriously.
The group of soldiers.
She argued their case.
She was their lawyer?
Yes.
Thank you.
Okay.
I've inquired at Defence.
They're looking into it.
It doesn't matter now.
Did you get the list of Team Aegir members?
We need to speak to someone from Raben's unit.
The opposition claims the memo
wasn't taken seriously.
That's not true. Intelligence had
the matter under investigation...
...and had the group under surveillance.
Fine. But why was your predecessor
so sparse with information...
...that terrorists were behind it?
There were certain matters
related to national security.
I'd like to hear about that.
Exercise a little patience.
Karina will bring the documents.
Have all the suspects been arrested
Indeed, members of Ahl Al-Kahf?
That is correct. But ...
Ahl Al-Kahf, is one of the associations
the People's Party wants banned.
If your predecessor believed
there was no terrorism, explain...
...why the police held the murdered woman's
husband for ten days for interrogation.
Because Intelligence was
focusing on the trail of terrorists.
And police were obviously informed
about Intelligence's theory on terrorism?
No, not the police.
Who was responsible for that?
Intelligence was investigating.
So, your predecessor put the entire
operation at risk?
My predecessor can't answer, but
I've told the committee everything.
Yes, and national security.
But what about it?
The People's Party wasn't
briefed about that here.
We must conclude that the Ministry of Justice
deliberately concealed information...
...and thus misled parliament.
We understand the Minister is confused.
Can someone explain the rules to him.
Even though he'll hardly need it
for very long.
I regret that little interruption.
Where were we?
... the government's responsibility
in this tragedy ...
...the Intelligence memo was classified as secret.
Publication would have created dissension
at a time when we need to stand united.
The government has created mistrust.
We want a thorough Investigation.
There it is, but first
you need to view this document.
It outlines the risks of publication of
information about the slain woman.
In a public inquiry
information could get out...
...that could compromise our strategy,
for example in Afghanistan...
thus placing Danish soldiers' lives in danger.
We must investigate further.
It's secret information.
Please treat it with utmost confidentiality.
Then the media may not have access
to it, for good reasons.
Unless others want to question
my predecessor's motives...
I'll go back and do my job.
Thank you.
Damn,  were we good.
You got that settled nicely.
We weren't too much?
No. She asked for it herself.
Now we've got her to reveal
how she got hold of the memo.
It's the prime minister.
There will be a press release.
Hi, Thomas. Congratulations.
It went quite well, I understand.
They prepared me very well.
Now, that terrorism package.
There's still a lot of work to do, it's your priority
Tomorrow I'll talk with the People's Party.
Okay. Good luck.
Come, I'll pour some for you.
Krabbe is pushing for you to
ban that association.
Now they know who they're up against.
Karina come in. Have a drink with us.
I'll send Monberg's papers to his
residence, then join you
Send anything you need to
Cheers and thanks for the help.
Plough, Frode had a private agenda I knew
nothing about, it's here in his diary
He knew Anne Dragsholm
personally. I don't understand it...
...but he met with her
on at least two occasions.
I also have confirmation that
he also had her mobile number.
The last time they met was in a hotel
the weekend before the murder.
Check it out.
Yes.
Shall we eat now?
Just a minute, honey.
I cut off the head of the dragon
but his blood is acidic.
That's good. Then you must be hungry.
What would you say to
getting your own room?
Grandpa says you can have his.
I think we could do it up
really nice with all your stuff.
Shall we?
I also found a school,
we'll have to go and check it out.
Could I start this summer?
- Yes, indeed.
Hello.
Should Dad have his own room?
Yes. But ...
We'll find out.
May I draw?
Yes, of course.
Someone found Jonas' glove.
I must have dropped it on the way home.
Luckily, his name was in it.
There's no name in it.
And we haven't lost it.
We drove with Søgaard.
In any case he was at the gate.
Hi there, Jonas.
Grüner?
Was Dragsholm the lawyer for the group?
That's what we should try to confirm.
But it was several years ago.
What's his name?
David Grüner.
He's on duty this evening.
Are you sure he's here?
Yes. You go in here, and I'll go
around to look for an entrance.
Hey!
Subtitles Re-edited by DG