Ten days ago a woman was
killed in unusual circumstances
The Muslim League
will punish Denmark.
My blood will flow.
How many will follow me?
Brix Thinks you will contribute a new angle.
David Gruner, 28 a former soldier.
What does Intelligence know of the group?
Raben was the squad leader.
And the rest?
Raben is a fugitive.
Thomsen lives on an island in Sweden.
Raben may show up.
The Directorate of Prisons
has rejected your application.
Why can't I see him?
Raben has escaped.
He suddenly showed up.
I have no documents?
Something happened in the village.
There was an officer who fucked-up.
They can't just disappear.
What happened in the village?
He was called 'Perk'.
Thomsen - don't start it!  Stop!
The government's put a lot of effort
into the anti-terrorism package.
Do you want to be Minister of Justice?
I had an affair with Monberg.
The report of an incident in Afghanistan.
I have to resign.
The names of the victims.
I demand an explanation.
...or I'll tell the press that the
Government doesn't dare tackle terrorism.
Buch...
We need to stop.
Are you starting rumours again
It's available in print.
Monberg took pills.
What if everything is pre-arranged...staged?
The video, 'Faith Brother' , Kodmani?
The Army doesn't kill its own people.
Someone in the army does.
Lund and Strange continue with the investigation.
There was no officer 'Perk', no bodies.
Have you checked everything personally?
My deputy briefed me. stop stop stop
Who was that?.
Innocents die too We do the dirty work.
The polititions don't want blood on their hands
I need your help.
Why did he try to kill himself?
Things need to come to light;
But now, just now. Monberg is involved.
The lawyer wanted the case reopened.
It was a Defence case but
the Minister of Justice was called in.
One of the soldiers interviewed was
Jens Peter Raben.
You can't get an air gun for 600.
I'll use it....
My father knows about the phone.
The chaplain says something is very wrong.
You better take this from me
I'll change as we go.
I don't know what I was thinking..
They were trained by a lieutenant
they called 'Perk'.
His real name is Per K. Møller.
He was with Team Aegir.
It was a nice funeral.
Did you have contact with the investigators?
A lawyer was out here asking
the same questions.
The man died three months
before the incident.
Søgaard didn't want them to see the corpse.
...If he's actually dead.
We need to dig up the coffin
to see what's inside.
Something came up.
You could help decorate tables.
I'll come and help tomorrow morning.
That's when I'm getting married.
Mom, I can't talk now.
I'll call you later.  Bye.
How deep do we need to dig?
About my own height.
Is the coffin still intact?
It's the first time, so...
Beware of the hedge.
Lund, there's a problem.
We can't do it before getting a warrant.
Most judges won't allow it.
We're about to speak to
the army chaplain and Major Søgaard.
The mother of the deceased will have to be there.
I can't support you on this
We don't have reason enough.
Get those people away.
I don't want any digging.
Can we just talk?
I've changed my mind... no.
There may have been a mistake
in connection with the funeral.
You have no right.
We want to be absolutely sure that
it's your son who's in the coffin.
We need your permission.
We will proceed with reverence.
why do you think he's not in the coffin?
There's evidence that he was seen
alive after his death.
Some soldiers in Afghanistan
saw something.
Your son could be involved in
the killing of civilians.
If you give us your permission,
We can start now.
Otherwise I'll get the permit
through other channels.
Are you, human?
I understand...
Lund, Brix wants to speak with you.
We talked about a suspect.
They weren't allowed to see the body.
The chaplain and Søgaard said...
It's not enough.
Not without the consent of the mother.
There is no one in the coffin.
If we are faced with an empty coffin...
Send these workers home.
Brix, wait a minute!
I know I'm right!
Trust me about this, dammit!
Søgaard refuses to
come in for questioning.
We need to talk with him.
What about the chaplain?
We're still looking for him.
We can't wait for more murders.
We have to do something!
You were restless and
went over to the church.
You wanted to talk to the chaplain about
your husband? He said things weren't good.
Can we go home now?
Was your husband angry with the chaplain?
He knows he was just trying to help.
They're friends.
Could your husband have hurt the chaplain?
I told you they are friends..
The chaplain never showed up for a meeting.
A witness saw the chaplain leave with
someone who looks like your husband.
Do you have an idea
where he would go?
He would never do anything to the chaplain.
Thank you.
The pizza's cold.
We'll buy another one on the way home..
Where are we going?
Just drive.
What did Dragsholm want?
Why did she contact you?
She wanted the case reopened.
Turn in here... Here.
Leave the key in the ignition.
Move away from the car...
...Farther away....
What are you doing?
You'll get no help out here.
The police will find out.
Yes, hello. Is this the police?
My name is Gunnar Torp.
I'm in Hareskoven
and want to report an assault.
A former soldier, Jens Raben,
threatened me with a gun.
I don't know where he is.
I'll wait by the main path. Thank you.
Leave me out of this. If you ever come back, I'll shoot you
What did Dragsholm want?
Go now, damn.
Chaplain, what did she say?
Just go...the police are on their way
She visited Myg, Grüner, Thomsen.
She wanted them to testify
about the officer.
I buried that officer, three months before
it happened. Go away now.
What had Dragsholm found out?
Why should the case be reopened?
She wanted me to testify.
I heard the others talk about the officer.
What did they say...?
Søgaard told the family that
they shouldn't see the body.
What did Søgaard say?
That it was all blown up
I've been imprisoned for two years
without my family and stuffed with drugs.
You need to talk to
Søgaard and the colonel.
No! No.
Raben...
Forgive me.
Think of your wife.
Think of your son.
I don't understand. Four murders.
Why don't we do something?
The investigation is complicated.
Everything points to fundamentalists.
We're being attacked by terrorists.
What is so damn complicated?
This meeting is 'off the record'...
Feelings are running high, we're all affected by it..
...but please lets keep calm
Yes, of course. Sorry.
But we're in the same boat.
There is no breakthrough.
The People's Party members
are sharpening their knives ...
...because the Minister of Justice
is delaying the anti-terrorism package.
We need to examine some things.
What things, perhaps you'll tell us?
I know the Muslim organisations that you're protecting.
While you fanny around they get stronger
They wouldn't hesitate for a moment
to introduce Sharia law.
My foreign colleagues don't understand
why we're doing nothing.
And if these organizations
are involved with the killings?
That's why I have convened
this meeting.
Thomas is going to show us something
that will explain it.
That part is no longer relevant.
It proved to be a misunderstanding.
What the hell is going on here?
Listen...
...We all know Buch had a difficult start.
But Buch would have finalized the package
if we let him work in peace.
We shouldn't beat each other
over the head about it.
Anyone of us could be in Buch's situation.
Sorry.
Rossing, here.
Protecting those organisations
is misguided 'pc' tolerance.
May I speak to you in private?
Nothing you can share here?
It'll only take a minute.
You should've informed the
police and Intelligence.
The police were apparently
busy with other things.
The Ministry of Defence just learned
you're about to exhume a dead soldier.
Tell us  about that?
The families are upset.
Buch... Will you try to explain?
I'm not on aware of that.
If we could just...
You're new, but I can't protect you.
Yesterday you said something about Monberg,
you didn't follow up on that.
I need time.
Thomas tell me what it's about.
It's better if the Prime Minister
isn't aware of it.
Then no one can later say that
the prime minister was aware.
You'll be compromised.
What're you talking about?
Maybe I was mistaken about Monberg.
Maybe he hasn't been alone.
Meet with the People's Party.
Iron out the details with them.
Say that we will investigate those
associations a second time.
How long?
A couple of days.
Blame me and my amateurism.
Krabbe will understand.
We're all very busy
Can we finish up?
I'll have a word with Krabbe.
I'm giving Thomas 24 hours to verify some facts.
May I ask which facts?
No, considering everything, not for now..
Earlier, you said that you didn't know
an officer called 'Perk'. True
Per K. Møller was nicknamed
'Perk' and was on Team Aegir.
Some of the men gave him that name.
Is that why I was brought in?
You were brought in to answer our questions..
Why were you and the chaplain
at his funeral?
We escorted the coffin home and
we wanted pay our respects
Respect...Why couldn't the family see the body?
He was killed in an explosion..ever seen one?
No, can't say I have..
His head was separated from the
rest of the body.
What's this about?
You must have worried when the others said
they'd came across an officer of that name.
Their explanation was even more unreliable
I had buried him.
Did you declare him dead?
He was dead..
Why was there no autopsy
performed in Denmark?
Operational reasons
We were careful with information because
it may have looked like a suicide.
He might have taken his own life?
We'll never know that.
he may have intentionally detonated the device
What an absurd statement.
At this moment the coffin is being exhumed
we'll see what it contains..
I'm not scared because you're
exhuming the body..
Lund...
They've called from the cemetery.
The coffin's out.
..and whats inside?
Hello, Lund.
Good to see you again.
I get these type of jobs only
when you're in the neighborhood.
Well?
White male, late twenties.
Femur bone indicates
a height of 180-182 cm.
He's had a rough ride.
I would guess an explosion.
It's quite a mess.
Like that time in the Balkans ...
You can't know for sure if he was
Per K. Møller.
All the evidence...
You can't be sure.
It may be someone else. They could've
swapped one body for another.
It doesn't have to be Per K. Møller.
What's that?
We need a DNA test. Or his teeth?
It just doesn't fit.
It can't be him.
Søgaard and the chaplain
didn't want them to see the corpse.
There's something wrong.
I know there is...
Wrap up and get it shut down.
Hey! What's happening?
Do you have someone buried around here?
Some deranged detective thought that...
...we had buried an empty coffin.
I thought they had better things to do.
"The dragon curled around the village,
grabbed its tail and fell asleep. "
Now you must sleep.
Tomorrow we'll make your room beautiful.
Why are they after Daddy?
Is he gone?
Daddy's playing hide and seek,
just like you do in kindergarten.
Go to sleep.
Are they mad at Dad?
No. They just want to find him.
And if they find him,
we can go to visit him.
Do you want to try your new scooter tomorrow?
Sleep well, darling.
Yes, yes, of course. I understand.
Thank you. Goodbye.
They've found the chaplain.
He says Jens threatened him with a gun.
Nothing wrong with him, only some bruising.
I was just checking if everything's okay.
Don't go leaving the barracks.
I'd like to know what the hell is going on.
Explosives were found at the barracks.
You and Søgaard were interviewed.
Now the chaplain claims
Jens threatened him.
None of us know what's going on in his mind..
he is capable of anything
Something happened in Afghanistan,
which shouldn't have happened.
That's right.
Three soldiers from his group were killed.
Something else happened, it doesnt make
sense..
There is a simple explanation for his behaviour
...it's not unknown
Jens was squad leader. He made
a wrong decision. I too feel guilty.
So he's acting out of guilt?
You are his wife and know him well but..
There are certain sides of Jens
you don't know.
I want you to go.
Why do you think he went into service
when Jonas was born?
He wanted to serve his country
He volunteered for Iraq.
No
He simply had to leave, Louise..he had
no choice...
Jens isn't the man you think...
Go ..
Get out of here!
Rossing attended important meetings
with Monberg ...
...including one
where Raben was on the agenda.
Officially called, "the Prevention of
crimes among returning soldiers."
Raben is not the only soldier
mentioned as an example.
Eat. It's delicious.
My guess is that they have taken pains
to tarnish Raben's reputation.
Why aren't there any minutes?
Only Ministers were there.
I was working on a bill.
Monberg had promised his voters
cuts in the prison system.
Isn't there any dessert?
If Monberg had been aware of the
Afghan military case...
...and failed to inform the police
when Dragsholm was killed...
...what are the police and Intelligence doing?
They quarrel among themselves.
They disagree about the exhumation.
Intelligence thought it was a bad idea.
Keep me informed...
...and they need a kick in the ass.
What was Monberg told?
Did Monberg keep a diary?
I can call his wife.
Let me, then you can discuss it with Karina.
I have asked if we can start again.
But there'll be a disciplinary matter.
Her replacement is coming from personnel.
Make the call to Monberg's wife.
We can't just turn a blind eye to what she did.
Talk with her now.
No.
I won't speak to Karina.
Good evening. It's Thomas Buch.
Excuse me for disturbing you so late.
May I speak with Hannah Monberg?
Thomas said you wanted to talk to me.
No, it was his idea.
I knew nothing about it.
Okay.
I've enjoyed working here.
I admired you for your expertise.
But you can also be pretty annoying.
I've worn out three nannies, I'm...
...here all the time to meet your demands.
It was never good enough.
Everything must be done correctly.
But it all changed, huh?
When you learned I had gone to bed with
Monberg, you were really disappointed.
I was recently divorced...
But it's not something we talk about.
When have you asked about my private life?
I don't know.
Never. But you're on moral high ground
if something happens ...
...that falls within the rules and regulations.
I just think you're worth more!
What were you thinking...to destroy
your career in that way?
After everything I've taught you.
How's it going?
According to Monberg's wife he left
no diary, but now he's conscious.
His condition is stable.
We need to speak with him
as soon as possible.
We have to speak with him
before Rossing does.
Give me a status update on Raben...
...and find out how the police and
Intelligence investgations are going...get on it.
Do you have a nanny?
It's under control.
The pathologist has examined the teeth.
There's no doubt about the soldier's identity.
Either it will be your funeral or Lund's.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I'll hand over your head if this isn't solved.
Intelligence have traced Jens Peter Raben.
He abandoned the chaplain's car
and continued on foot.
Have they been in touch with him?
König will tell us tomorrow.
Could you ask if we can do something?
Hard to think that you could
handle so much failure.
And your admission.
I'll give Gedser a message.
You can resume your work there.
Send Major Søgaard home.
I want to talk to you later.
Shall I take you home?
Thanks for...
Lund, I'm sorry that it...
I'll call tomorrow and then...
Say hi to your mom and
say congratulations...
Raben left the chaplain's car in Valby
and stole another car nearby.
We found that around 2.00.
He slept three hours, and drove further.
He's near the barracks.
Why don't we arrest him?
Raben is the last of the group.
He's the next potential victim.
You'll use him as bait?
At some point the perpetrators
will come after Raben.
Our people can assist.
Thanks.
We're better equipped for that.
You still have Lund ...
Our cooperation problems are over.
We can get back to normal.
The Ministry of Justice
will be very happy with that.
I'd like to show you this. Refugees from Helmand
who spent years in Denmark.
Maybe they're out for revenge.
They need to be monitored or interrogated.
They're alive, so they don't need to be dug up.
Got a minute? Lennart, we need to talk.
Why didn't Raben kill you into the woods?
No idea.
Perhaps because he know's he's wrong.
He must be under enormous pressure.
I tried to talk some reason into him.
War does strange things to people.
This was in your church.
Anne Dragsholm's card.
Why was it there?
Raben had it with him.
Did you know her?
No, Raben began talking about her..seemed obsessed
Can I go now?
It's Sunday and there's a service.
Yes, yes..ok
Intelligence has a lead on Raben.
They'll try to monitor him.
Why aren't we arresting him?
We do what they say.
Go through this list
We need to check the chaplain.
You check out the Afghan refugees.
Get on it immediately.
Lund also thought...
Lund..not here now.
My quota for hernias is used up.
Get going.
What do we say if anyone calls for Lund?
That she's gone to a wedding.
I've spoken with Møller's mother.
We support the need for compensation...
...because of the pain and suffering
the police actions have caused.
The chaplain is clearly shaken.
The question is what to do about Raben.
He must feel very pressured.
He's the last one left.
It's a good idea
if we keep our eyes and ears open.
Have you informed Louise?
He was one of the best.
Raben always did 10% extra.
But he couldn't handle it in the long run.
We found out the whole thing?
What Raben and others spoke about.
How safe are we?
We are 100% safe.
Why?
These last few days have been intense.
I can just take over.
That's not necessary.
Otherwise, thank you.
Are you hungry?
Would you like a sandwich?
Go ahead.
We only have a few minutes.
I have to get away from the barracks.
What did you do with the chaplain?
Nothing. They lied.
About what?
My dad says you feel guilty.
I want to know what happened.
An officer did something.
They're covering it up.
Who?
Søgaard, maybe more.
Maybe your dad.
It's simply a lie.
You need to talk to Sarah Lund.
Tell her she should consider ...
Is it true that you joined voluntarily,
right before Jonas was born?
Who says so?
Just answer me honestly.
Yes it's true. Can't you see
they're trying to separate us?
It's not what you think.
After all I had seen and done...
I didn't deserve him.
He was so pure. I wasn't.
Let me go!
I just want to go home and be with you.
Let mom go! Let her go!
You've grown.
It's me. Daddy.
May I see?
It's nice.
Mom, let's go now.
Don't look for us again.
Ever.
Would you rather wait here?
It's okay.
There' a future for you after all.
It's good to see you.
How are you?
Fine.
I understand that everything
has developed into something of a storm.
Hi, Karina.
I'll be taking better care of this old heart.
I'm not even sure that
I can eat these anymore.
Okay, you're obviously aware.
I haven't had it good for a while.
I don't want to cause my family
any unnecessary misery.
We understand. But we are here
because of that old military issue.
The one where you sent in
the information before you...
There isn't so much to tell.
I forwarded it as a gesture
to Anne Dragsholm.
I had a meeting with her,
shortly before she was killed.
She gave me the folder when I left.
She was very committed to the case.
I couldn't help, unfortunately.
Why?  You already knew about the case
The Defence Minister called you to
a meeting about a soldier from that time,...
...Jens Peter Raben.
I... I don't quite understand.
Just tell me what you discussed with Rossing.
It was several years ago.
I can't remember all the details.
Ohh For Fuc...
Frode, you withheld information from
Police and Intelligence. Why?
What are you hiding, I need to know?
Karina, what's this?
Why would you have a chat about a soldier?
What did Rossing say?
How can I remember..
You spoke with the Defense Minister...
...two years earlier than Dragsholm.
You didn't say a damn thing...
...not even when she was killed.
It wasn't the first thing in my mind..
What did Rossing say at the meeting?
Will you come and visit again?
That's great.
Thanks for your sympathy, but the doctor
says my husband needs to rest.
This isn't very good for him.
My wife is right. I need to rest.
Yes.
Plough says Krabbe is still impatient.
He wants to talk to you.
I've got 24 hours.
Send him back to the Prime Minister. .
There's a complaint that the police have
had a soldier dug up for no reason.
Who was in charge of the exhumation?
It's academic, She's off the case
Some years ago she solved
a manslaughter case and she  ...
...broadened her investigation
into the role of local politicians.
I suggest you say that
they fired her and that we ...
I'd like to speak to her.
Maybe she knows something...she can't always
be wrong.
It'll compromise your relationship
with the police.
If Monberg won't tell us what's going on
we'll try something else...get hold of her for me
I hereby pronounce you man and wife,
for better or worse..
You may kiss the bride.
May I?
Thank you.
Much obliged.
Now, let's have something to eat and drink.
And another, and another.
He's good enough and was a soldier.
Congratulations, Grandma.
Thanks.
I'm the master of ceremonies ...
so, keep the speeches short.
We need time to dance.
We should do the photo-shoot.
Sorry. There's call.
We've put all the presents there.
Even the flowers for you.
The red bouquet.
Okay. Thank you.
We need to have you here with us
Congratulations!
Thank you. And now we'll smile.
Are you still at Police Headquarters?
No, no longer.
I just read that they had
exhumed a dead soldier.
Someone is looking for you.
She says it's important.
I'm quite tired waiting to make this speech ...
...so I'll jump right into it.
That's fine. Wait a minute.
Karina Munch, Justice.
Shall we toast? Cheers.
You need to have a confidential conversation,
it's important
A conversation... with whom?
It's this way.
Hello. Thomas Buch. Karina has briefed you
that what we say here is confidential..
I desperately need some answers.
If it's about the exhumation...
I'm sorry.
Are you familiar with the allegations
against Danish soldiers in Afghanistan?
Er..yes..well..a little about it.
Yes, but maybe more than me...
Is there any evidence of civilian killings?
It's best if you call
Lennart Brix or Ruth Hedeby.
Their focus is on a certain officer.
Is it a coverup?
No. And there was probably no officer.
Why did you have the body exhumed?
It was a mistake.
I'll have to go in again.
What about  the squad leader,
Jens Peter Raben?
I thought maybe he knew something,
but...
They say he's mentally ill and
he'd just been denied release.
Denied release..how?
Doctors had given the green light...
but for some unknown reason
.. the Directorate of Prisons refused
his application several times.
He was just disappointed.
Just a moment.
Monberg was working on a bill
about the prison system.
When exactly was  it dropped?
Shortly after the meeting between
Monberg and the Defence Minister.
Get me exact details
Thank you...
...and congratulations to your mom.
You make me so happy.
I just want to...
...break out in speeches and song.
Sometimes I wish that
we had met earlier.
But I think we first had to
grind down our sharp edges.
I'm so glad about the day I
went down to the thrift store...
Who came with the flowers?
A courier. Look at the card,
Now we're all together.
So I think...
It's what I was doing.
Dear Bjørn...
What is it?
"You're going now your mother is speaking"?
Yes, that's just what she does.
You'll probably get used to it, Bjørn.
The women in this family are very
busy, so tighten your buttocks.
And you're showing up just now?
Where was I?
Dear lovely Bjørn...
I want to apologise.
I know I can't make amends.
I hope you understand that
it was important to be certain.
I understand that you don't want to talk
to me. But I must know something.
It's about your son's ID tag.
Chain... Metal plate with his name.
Do you know where it is?
No. They said they never found it.
They said it was gone when he...
It didn't come home
with his other belongings?
Why you ask?
I think someone found his ID tag
...and used it.
Somebody who needed
to have a different identity.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Wait a minute.
There is something I need to show you.
I thought it might be a mistake.
Occasionally things crop up,
as if Per was still alive.
For example, bills for purchase
of different things.
This one from two months ago.
You should only come
during visiting hours.
I have nothing more to say.
You don't have much to say.
According to Plough,
you promised your constituents...
to reduce the number of prisoners
and overcrowded prisons...
We have nothing to discuss.
...and fewer people
in preventive detention.
Some inmates would be reviewed
and given conditional release.
One of them was Jens Peter Raben.
That's what Rossing wanted to discuss.
Oddly enough, you withdrew the bill.
It ended up in a drawer.
No. There were other reasons.
I'll leave you alone. Plough and the legal experts
are examining all the files..they'll find out..
Wait!
What are you going to do now?
That depends on you.
But it doesn't look good.
It wasn't my decision.
I was just been doing my job.
Rossing didn't want Raben released, he was insistant
and didn't go into detail
It was in the national interest to keep him locked-up.
He didn't explain further?
national interests like what?
He didn't explain it to me, just insisted..
Raben knew something had happened.
I don't understand it.
Rossing told me what I should do.
But you found out ...
...then Anne Dragsholm wanted
to have the case reopened.
What did Dragsholm discover?
nay nay nay nay nay
There isn't time for this Now, tell me!
There are people dying out there!
And you'll be blamed for it,
not Rossing.
She found proof that the soldiers
were telling the truth.
That there had been civilian killings.
That Raben had been wrongly imprisoned.
What else did she find out?
The officer...
...she found the officer who did it.
That's all I know.
What'll happen now?
Who was it?
She didn't say.
What am I going to do?
It'll be alright.
It was right to tell me.
I need to talk to you.
This is important.
Two minutes.
Rossing won't say anything.
You'll never get him to say anything.
You don't know him.
Monberg starts talking. Intelligence
comes and informs the Prime Minister.
Krabbe demands your resignation.
Is this something you know or...
He's told the prime minister.
You're out, or the government falls.
Monberg gives an official explanation
and then we take it from there.
Things will fall into place.
Where's Monberg?
He's gone out to stretch his legs.
Is it hanging ok now?
Just move the right corner up.
How's this?
Yes, that's good.
Good. How's that?
It's nice, huh?
I'm going to be on my way.
Thanks for your help, Dad.
Sorry for what I said yesterday.
It's okay. I've been a fool.
Are you coming to the cadets' ball?
I'd like you to. It'll do you good.
It could be good for you.
I'm not really in the mood.
Jonas is okay.
It's you I'm worried about.
Come on.
You'll benefit from it.
I'll call the babysitter.
It's only for a couple hours.
Ok...I can't force you
Bye.
What time are you going?
Why aren't you at the wedding?
You need to check something.
I'm here with an interpreter
at the refugee center.
I'll walk outside.
OK.
What is it now?
Someone used Per K. Møller's identity.
His ID tags are gone and someone
recently bought stuff online in his name.
Run his name through the computer
and see if anything more pops up.
I'm in Elsinore.
When will you be back?
In a few hours.
Have you talked to Brix?
No, not yet.
That's what I'll do. Of course.
Sorry. Bye.
Strange and the others are
still out talking to refugees.
Anything come out of it?
They've traveled a lot.
What does Intelligence know about
Raben?  He followed his wife and son.
It ended up in a quarrel.
Now he's back at the barracks.
There was no trace of the perpetrators?
It's true that König is focusing
on Raben, last survivor of the unit.
He'll probably get something out of it.
Are you going to eat?
...or are you going to sulk all day?
This is from Technical Investigation.
Strange sent it in to be checked out.
The business card, the chaplain said,
he didn't know about.
I'm done with that pastor.
It's covered with
the chaplain's fingerprints.
Odd he said he didn't know about it.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Sarah Lund. Send an ambulance
to Simon Church in Vesterbro.
I've found the pastor.
He's still breathing, but ...
Subtitles re-edited by DG.