Ten days ago a woman was killed
In unusual circumstances
How many will follow me in death?
What does Intelligence have on the group?
Raben was the squad leader.
There was no officer called Perk.
Perk...
Put the gun down now.
I had to shoot.
Strange was a commando.
I think he was an officer.
He had a tattoo on his shoulder.
He couldn't know.
Were you together at all times?
You and Jonas mean everything to me.
I'm starting to see Søgaard.
You never told us
about the announcement.
The Danish commandos were only
150 km from Raben's Group.
I do not think Søgaard's the problem.
Did you help Raben escape?
You've been a minister for seven days.
In the same time God created the Earth.
You have come close to ruining everything.
You'll have to resign.
We can't give up.
What did my predecessor know?
You slept with him!
Why don't you check the dates?
The Prime Minister was preparing
appropriations for Afghanistan.
If you extend the anti-terrorism
package, innocent people will suffer.
The man you identified, wasn't
in Afghanistan at the time.
Sorry. They were killed by Raben.
Sebastian sent his video diary home.
Raben sees Taliban everywhere.
He thinks only of killing.
It doesn't matter.
So there was no Perk.
His older brother is in Afghanistan.
They found this.
You have 36 hours.
The drama surrounding Minister of
Justice, Buch, took a sensational twist...
...when the vote on the anti-terrorism
package was postponed.
The Prime Minister had no comment
but others say the Minister of Justice...
...should resign.  Party leaders are
meeting to discuss the crisis.
Of course I'm still the minister.
Goodbye.
We have to defeat the government..
Does everyone know?
Not everyone has reported in yet.
So get themall in then...and I need to
have an update from the police.
If we don't resolve it. This will be
the biggest scandal of all time.
It's incredible.
You've done the right thing.
I hope so. I'll make an announcement
as soon as the meeting is over.
I'm going.
Let me talk to you about the agenda.
It seems like you're going
after the prime minister.
Damn right we're going after the Prime Minister
Karina told you the plan don't change now..
Yes I know..but are you convinced the Prime Minister
would jeopardise his position by playing these games...
Each time he went directly to the
aid of the Minister of Defence.
Buch, everything points toward the Minister
of Defence and his department
If the Prime Minister is playing games,
then the people have a right to  know.
What's the news from the police?
Nothing new on Raben.
Last night they authorised a
research trip to Helmand.
I don't know why. Neither did the
Deputy Police Commissioner.
Keep me informed. And get someone
to remove these chairs.
I just spoke with Gitta Spalding.
There'll be no meeting.
Where is everybody?
The Prime Minister hasn't heard.
So get hold of the prime minister.
The meeting's about him.
I told the Minister of Justice a meeting
at such short notice is unacceptable.
We're holding the meeting. I have
an item for the agenda. Sit down.
Let's find out what Thomas
has to say in his defense.
Talk to anyone who's had contact
with Frederik Holst...
...in the few weeks that he was home
on leave. Phone, credit cards etc.
Map his whereabouts from day to day.
Where was he sleeping...
...where he was
at the time of the murders?
The ministry called.
They want an explanation ...
...about a police trip to Afghanistan.
We had to act quickly...... Strange is
innocent and Lund found out...
Right now I don't give a damn about
Lund and Strange..
We know that the suspect is in Afghanistan now...
He was here but redeployed two days ago
..and who is the suspect now?
...Frederik Holst. Doctor at ISAF
military hospital in Lashkar Gah, and...
...brother of soldier killed in Raben's unit.
This should have been approved by me.
I don't understand why you
keep trying to undermine....
Because you would have said no. It
would have taken too much time...
...to arrange documents and I had no
time to wait. We're pretty confident...
...that it's him.In any event, it's
too late now. They have left.
The Ministry of Justice
wants an update.
Frederik Holst...What's your relationship to him?
Do you know him?
Yes, I know him
No relationship. It's not important.
Answer the question..he was a colleague of yours.
How's it going here?
Just the same old excuses.
I've talked to the Institution.
Frederik Holst wanted to visit you.
Five times.
Every time you rejected him.
I want to see my wife.
We found letters at his residence,
addressed to you at the Institution.
You returned them.
He wanted to express his anger...
...about your responsibility for
his little brother's death.
You can ask him yourself.
We've also thought about that.
It's in your interest to help us.
I will.
The officer executed the family
and beat the others to death.
You said it was one of our police
inspectors, but he wasn't there.
I want to talk to my wife.
Think about your testimony
None of this will be beneficial in
the future of your cause
Talk to Colonel Jarnvig.
He believes me.
Colonel Jarnvig is being questioned because he
helped you escape from the PET.
You'll be charged and arraigned tomorrow.
Why are you examing
Jarnvig's old files?
No idea. It seemed as if
he wasn't himself.
Just a moment.
I'm going to talk to Søgaard.
Hello.
He hasn't come back yet?
No.
Your father has been pulled in
for questioning.
He talked to Jens at the ball and
helped him get away from there.
What is this nonsense?
You were there yourself.
They were seen together.
Someone informed General Arild.
By whom? No idea.
Your father's well-known.
I don't think he's feeling
so well at the moment.
Tonight he came in with
some accusations against me.
The murders keep him very busy.
What were the accusations?
That I hid radio messages we received
from the commandos.
It was as if he believed everything
Jens had invented.
He is responsible for this situation,
but I am loyal and try to help him.
Suddenly he believed Jens?
Yes. It seemed pretty far-fetched.
What about you?
I need to talk to my dad.
If you hear something, I want to
know about it immediately.
Yes of course.
Louise... Do you think
I had something to do with it?
No, why?
For two months, the Minister of Defence
did nothing to investigate the hand...
...and the alleged killing of civilians.
I find that incredible.
But this gave the Prime Minister
enough time to work ...
...to get parliamentary approval
for an additional 200 soldiers.
The study took longer than expected.
How can we believe it? I could have
dealt with this long ago.
Instead, five people have been murdered
and we've been wasting..
..time chasing shadows, fake muslim groups
and invisible terrorists
We have to get to the bottom of this
within our own ranks.
This is a complete mess with grave consequences,
and the public will never forgive or forget
You're accusing the government of being
involved in a cover up, wheres the proof Buch..
It's a serious allegation against the
Prime Minister himself.
The People's Party wants to examine
the Prime Minister's role in this.
It needs a full investigation..
There is no case..
We'll see if there's evidence for a case.
If I've made mistakes, I'll resign.
You've already resigned. I'd like
repeat it in the presence of witnesses.
Tell Thomas why we're meeting.
Some think you'll damage the party.
We want a vote on
your expulsion from our caucus.
You can't do...
May I refer you to the party statutes,
Section 12A. Here's a copy.
As you can see, we already have
the required signatures.
That's it, all correctly done, so lets get started..
with an outline of the matter
When you're ready we'd all like to participate
in the meeting you've called Thomas.
The allegation of civilian murders is not
something I am standing alone on.
The police have sent officers
to Helmand to investigate and...
...to speak with the doctor who had
reported the anomily of the extra hand.
Where did the authority to do this come from?
I know nothing ... The police
investigators were sent for a reason.
They will let us know their findings
I think we should take the vote. This is clearly
a delaying tactic..
When will we hear about the findings?
They'll fly back tomorrow and deliver their..
Get the preliminary findings tomorrow
afternoon. Then we'll vote.
I can't attend because I'll be at
a military memorial ceremony.
I think we should get it over with.
We'll have to wait. They have not
found anything yet ...
But it could be misunderstood if we took action tonight
before we have the report from the police..
Thanks.
You say my appointment
with Her Majesty is still on?
Excuse me Plough, do they expect the doctor
to help with regard to the hand?
No. He's also accused of murder so it's unclear
what the outcome could be..
Yes Yes..but they'll still have to ask him about the reports
he sent back about the hand..we need
We need to be able to see all the communications
about the reports to and from the ministry.
That won't be easy with the controls in place
Can't we just see the reports?
Yes, but the system is slow.
..and it's not going to be easy working with defence..
I'm sure the Prime Minister will burn the Minister of Defence
He'll give him up..
It's obvious that of the two the Prime Minister has the most power
maybe we could speak to the Defence Minister...
Why would he talk to us? and what could
be achieved from such a strategy
Perhaps we'll be able to
drive a wedge between them.
Look, heres what we do..lets examine every scrap
of paper and find something we can use against him.
When will we hear from the police?
They're due to return tomorrow morning with their report
The two detectives, a man and a woman...
One of them must be Lund.
If we can help them let me know.
Yes, it's Buch.
Don't ever call me, you stupid fucking bitch..
Calm down there.
You've arrived at a bad time.
We had two suicide bombings
this morning..
It's very busy in the hospital.
Tighten the chin strap on your helmet...
...and your bulletproof vest.
Otherwise it's pointless wearing it
Come here..
Would you like to go out to
the base first to freshen up?
No, we want to go to the hospital.
We need to talk with Frederik Holst.
Frederik Holst.
I'll be home soon.
I'm going home in a week.
I was home on leave for three weeks.
Your friends and acquaintances didn't
see you. You didn't visit your parents.
Where were you?
Why do you want to know?
That's an easy question.
Korselitze. It's on Falster.
Who were you with?
I was alone.
Who is it that you think I've killed?
They were murdered,
while you were home.
I spend my life trying to save
human lives. Was that all?
Two years ago you tried
to save your brother, Sebastian.
We've seen his video diary and
we found this in your house.
You hold Raben responsible for your brothers death.
You think that he was a maverick that lead his unit
into an impossible situation which killed your brother
You tried to get in touch with Raben,
but your letters were returned unopened.
What did you do?
You're wasting your time.
I didn't kill anyone.
What incredible bullshit!
You haven't crossed these faces out for fun.
Let's just call it a pastime then.
You were on duty when your brother was brought in.
weren't you.
You stood and looked at him
amongst all those killed and wounded.
It must have been quite a shock to
discover that is was Raben's fault.
Yes....quite a sight..
They were his colleagues alive on the operating
table.... but not your brother.
Yes. And I hope they all burn in hell.
I couldn't touch them.
No law can try them for taking
my brother out to that village.
Instead, I found out that there was amongst all
the body parts a surplus limb. A hand.
I tried to raise suspicions that civilians were murdered.
There was clear evidence..
Maybe it was the phantom officer..
Nobody believed the group's story about the officer.
Just covering for themselves
I thought all of them would be charged, but the military provost
let them go..and nothing was done..
Are you sure the hand could not have been from
a suicide bomber, was a check not done for DNA.
I was furious that it wasn't done
There was no DNA taken for matching.
Did you send the first medical report to the defence
ministry so You could damage the group.
My brother died from a punctured lung.
It was nothing.
He could have survived.
I'm angry at the psychopath...
..who forced him to
go out to the village...
...and the lawyer who got them
acquitted of everything.
So the answer is yes!  YES!
But it can't bring Sebastian back.
So... What can I do,
other than to try to save him...
...every day,
on the damn operating table?
He can't say where he was
during the murders.
So did he do it?  No, it's not him.
Damn!  After all that effort.
Has Raben said anything new?
He's saying the same story over again.
Major Søgaard's name is
popping up again and again..
We brought him in.  He didn't give much.
Pack your sunglasses and come home.
So we got nothing..hopefully it was worth
going and it wasn't just a wild guess.
Now I've got to grovellingly call Intelligence and
parliament and tell them it's all been for nothing..
There is one minister who thinks we made
a break through. I'm sure the...
It's this minister who dangles by a thread.
I hope you're not counting on him...
I'll have to try to smooth this over with our superiors.
Don't do anything else unless I give the order.
What do we have?
Nothing on the fundamentalists, all dead end's,
and if it isn't big brother, that leaves only Raben.
The offender's bought stuff all over
the internet in Perk's name.
Mostly second-hand things
from civilians...
...paid in cash sent by post.
We've already looked into it all, it's difficult to trace
done online, sent to an anonymous post box
A camcorder, a laptop "The Anarchist Cookbook '
..other bits and pieces..
...all sent to a PO box, at the same place...
where the offender had Kodmani rent a postbox.
That doesn't make any sense to me at all..
Why not use an alias to rent an
apartment or storage space?
We don't know yet. But there is something new.
Telecom let us know..
The third victim was set on fire using a
call from a stolen mobile phone.
It has been switched off since the killing
This morning the phone
was activated again.
There's an unanswered call.
From where?
A phone booth...They are not on the digital network
so only a rough area can be given
Unlike the mobile network...
somewhere around Ryvang.
The barracks?
That's impossible to confirm with the information we have
Why would he turn on the mobile
that he knows we're looking for?
We all make mistakes..
We'll go back there right now.
Is there a memoria lservice today?
We'll do it for their sake.
Maybe we should drive past the base.
Maybe someone will tell Søgaard.
We have some time to kill.
How did it work when the commandos
were out on missions?
How did you operate then?
Five men behind enemy lines. We'd identify a
target and monitor their movements. Why?
Did you have radio contact
with the other forces?
No. We shot everything that moved
and hoped for the best.
Didn't the General say that the
commandos weren't involved?
Would you please stop the car?
Stop!
What is it?
How far is it to the village from here?
Not now, Lund.
I just want to see the place where it happened.
We're not tourists on a sightseeing trip...
Can you take us there?
You don't have permission to go there.
What're you talking about?
You can't leave the military zone.
Nonsense.
Consent to do this was faxed last night.
Not as far as I can see.
Take a better look..what is it with all this..we come
on a special top level mission and get this.
We have dispensation direct from the Defence Minister.
Give me the phone.
What's your name?
Siegler.
If I've made a mistake, I'm sorry.
That's alright.
Shall we get going?
Call the local police chief.
His name appears in the provost's report.
You're charged with burglary, car theft,
illegal weapons possession...
...kidnap, violence and death threats.
How do you plead to the charges?
Guilty on all points?
Has my wife contacted you?
No.
What about the police
who went to Afghanistan?
I don't know...
I'd advise you to drop the
story about the officer.
It's only harmful to your case.
There's no reason to make it worse.
The verdict will be harsher than last time.
You're dangerous.You might be placed...
...under indefinite detention. So...
Do you know if my wife has tried
to come to visit me?
No, but someone else did. Not the police. Someone from
the military and you should really listen to what he offers
Hello, Raben.
I've heard a lot about you. I hope
you'll allow me this little visit.
I'm on an official mission.
You feel that we've failed you.
I sincerely regret that.
I just wanted to say it.
You've done that now.
If you continue with your statement,
you'll hurt yourself and the army.
The first is your own affair,
but the second concerns me.
Maybe we can help each other out.
I'm not going to retract my statement.
On behalf of the defense, I would like
to offer you compensation...
...by adjusting the pension benefits
in your contract.
Go to Hell.
I don't like you much, I don't really care what happens
to you, but your wife and your son ...
...are entitled to a pension...
in case you die.
We've altered the wording slightly to change
the proviso's.. so that it...
... also applies to prolonged illness.
Hopefully that'll make life easier for
Louise and Jonas.
All you need to do for me in return...
You know very well.
But you have to decide yourself.
My dad was with you yesterday.
Can you give him a message?
No.  Okay. Thank you.
For nothing.
What's going on here?
Lennart Brix. Chief of Homicide.
We have reason to believe that there
is crucial evidence at this location
What do you expect to find here?
You can't just waltz into a barracks..
I understand that you're the new guy,
in charge with your shiny cap on.
If you don't want too much trouble,
just do as I say.
No one is to leave the area. Send
someone for the necessary keys.
What now?
Contact General Arild.
Go directly to see him, damn it.
Krabbe's being pressured by his supporters to
commit to the vote, will he come through?
I'll take care of him. Have the police come back
with anything? There must be some news soon..
They'll be flying back tomorrow
Plough has the details.
Where the hell is he when he is needed...?
They have to go over there with that lot..
and then we need to start there..
The press report is out. Three members see your
stance as terrible and are accusing you of treason.
Probably a little over the top but
they don't know the full picture
We have evidence that the Prime Minister covered
up the story to help him manouvre defence...
The first medical report. We can't find a reason
in there that would make him complicit.
And the doctor was satisfied with the revised report.
He could find nothing at all to suggest a cover up..
Nothing points to the murder of civilians or wrongdoing.
Thomas your allegations about ...
...the prime minister
are becoming more and more extreme.
Thomas, maybe we should spend more
time on the Minister of Defense.
I think I've found something.
The Prime Minister has a secret.
We need to wait a little longer for the memorial service.
What's wrong?
The relatives are coming and there's been a problem.
There's been a search at the barracks.
If it takes too long ...
...we can't start before anyone from
the Barracks is here to take part.
What are you doing here?
You don't have much faith in me,
but we have more in common
than you think.
I hope not.
Your two investigators are on their way
back from Afghanistan with empty pockets.
No wonder you're under pressure.
Can you defend yourself because
there is a greater cause.
Yes..I can, The greater cause is real,
I can never forget that...
Each coffin reminds me that we must
continue, so no one has died in vain.
For the Prime Minister it wasn't
about the war, but about the UN.
The prime minister wanted to run for
the office of the UN Secretary General.
He lacked U.S. backing, and without that
he would never even be considered..
Therefore, we had to send more troops
to Afghanistan...
A French news agency confirmed
he had been offered the post.
It's all been about that post..
Look at those coffins and
tell me it was worth it.
The prime minister rejected the offer.
He was invited to apply, but said
no thanks. Goodbye, Buch.
It changes nothing. I refuse to
believe that you did this on your own.
The soldiers' deaths are linked
with what happened then.
You have a responsibility!
Would you please leave? this is a chapel..
Your behavior is inappropriate.
There is nothing, we keep coming up with nothing.
What about the phone?
We keep trying a trace
but the battery is running low.
How far are they with the search of the
underground plants? Training course?
The whole area down at the auditorium?
We have no manpower.
We'll stay here until we're finished.
We'll search everything.
Hold on one second..
I know what you're going to say..Haven't you got anything
better to do , shouldn't you be catching criminals...
I don't know what you're doing here wasting your time.
Good. Then you said it.
It's for you.
...And I don't understand what you're doing either.
Doing what should have been done a long time ago..
You listen to me, get your pack of hounds
together and get out of there. Now!
I'll take full responsibility. We have to continue.
I'll telephone you with an update
This has to be done.
I've spoken with the military,
You have no authority anymore.
Lennart...
Allow me to help you with that..
I'll give you exactly five minutes to
get packed up and out of here.
Brix, come in. Brix, come in...
We found something in the basement.
What's in the box?
Get it open.
The group had based themselves
here on the first floor.
5.56 calibre. The bullets used by
Danish soldiers in their assault rifles.
The soldiers slept in shifts.
Here in this area.
Was it here that they were killed?
According to Raben.
And the corpses
were brought in here afterwards.
The soldiers, who came to
rescue the group, found nothing.
They couldn't drag the bodies outside?
Not without being shot....pretty open out there..
Are we done here?
Some people thought the father was a drug lord,
who financed the Taliban by selling opium.
Does he believe that the family
were killed by Danish soldiers?
No, there was no trace of them, no
trace of them has ever been found.
Good. Excuse us for disturbing you.
What's this?
The family had a bakery.
Where's the oven?
He says that everything was destroyed.
I just want to see the oven.
I don't care! Look, get it cleared
before the meeting!
Rossing took the bait, he wants
to meet Now, we'll get him.
He's up there waiting...tell him I'm coming..
yes yes, he'll be waiting for you.
We have a problem.
The police have expanded their
investigation in Afghanistan.
What do you mean expanded?
I'm not sure of the details yet..
They've left the Militarised Zone without permission.
Without authority their findings are flawed
So give them authority.
It's against international rules. Military HQ is furious.
Their safety is not guaranteed
Where have you been? The Minister
of Defence is still waiting in your office.
Help them over there, if you can.
Easy for you to talk.
If it's not a pressing matter,
come back later.
I've always been loyal to the
Prime Minister.  Congratulations
Even when I had to
compromise my own principles.
When the civilian killings were reported
we had to make a difficult decision.
We needed more money
and more soldiers.
The prime minister and I agreed to
delay the examination of the extra hand.
I had no idea where it would lead.
With Monberg...
...and all those killings.
Alarm bells should have gone off
in the process.
What about?
Irregularities were found when
the hand was properly examined
We were very hesitant about it.
The prosecutor concluded that the only
civilian among those killed was a bomber.
What was the problem?
There was a henna tattoo on the
hand, a special henna tattoo.
Experts believed that it was
typical of the Hazara people.
Hazara people are sworn enemies of the Taliban.
But the crucial point was...
...the gold ring.
The Taliban never wear gold.
Therefore, it couldn't possibly
have been from a suicide bomber.
Did the prime minister know all this?
Officially, no.
But did he ..?
Gert knows everything. He's in charge.
What happens now?
We'll change our strategy again.
You and Rossing against the Prime Minister?
Read it here.
Are you sure he isn't lying?
I'll inform Krabbe before the meeting.
It's my locker, but I haven't used it
in ages. I've always said so.
The phone was used in connection
with the murder of Grüner.
It's possible, but it's not mine.
I had nothing to do with the killings.
Look at these. Our technicians
examined the broken parts.
They matched the ID tag that
we've found on the five victims.
Yes.
I've never seen any of this before.
What is that key for?
No idea.
You are going to be charged
with all five murders.
That's ridiculous..
I'm innocent.
You claim that you never met the victim of
the first murder, the lawyer Dragsholm?
And you didn't know know that
she wanted to reopen the case?
Pending our investigation, you'll be
kept in solitary. Take him away.
You're right, I did meet Anne Dragsholm.
She asked for a meeting. I thought
it was best to remain open-minded.
But she kept making accusations,
so I told her to go to hell.
Why should I kill my own people...
...and be stupid enough to leave
a mobile inside my locker?
You've now established regret,
but that won't sway the judge.
We didn't care about Anne Dragsholm.
You can damn-well check my alibi.
We?
Yes.
Bilal was involved in the meeting.
He was deputy commander
of the camp at the time.
How did Bilal feel about the accusations?
He was angry. He was afraid that
it would destroy our reputation.
Bilal is a Muslim, but he hates
dark men more than we do.
And that's understandable.
Bilal has access to the basement?
Bilal is a boy scout.
Does he have access?
Yes, but he said it was dangerous
because the ceiling could collapse.
The prosecutor will read the indictment
before you enter your plea.
Are you sticking by your statement
about the officer and civilian victims?
You'll probably go back to the
Institution again.
ln any case ... Excuse me?
The session has been postponed. They
think they've found the perpetrator.
They've found evidence
pointing to General Søgaard.
You've insisted someone from
the barracks was involved.
Now maybe they'll find some truth
Okay. Come on.
They must not question you
without me being there.
Søgaard may be hiding something,
but he's definitely not the culprit.
It isn't Søgaard.
The other half of all ID tags
were in his locker. Hurry.
You've got the wrong man.
My wife and son are in the barracks.
Quiet.
My wife and son ...
What are you doing?
Are you completely mad?
Put him in the car....Now...hurry.
I still can't get information about
when my father will be released.
Any news from the police?
The last one just left.
My dad found out that someone
had hidden some radio messages.
Who here could have done that?
Do you understand that it's important?
Everything Jens said may be true.
There were no messages and
no one is hiding anything.
My dad thinks otherwise. They must've
been placed in Søgaard's locker.
So it must be Søgaard.
Who operated the radio?
All radio calls are recorded in a log.
So, is there a way to delete
the messages from it.
Who could have done it,
if it wasn't Søgaard?
I have to see the other officers.
Call General Arild. Find out
who accused my dad.
This must be the same guy...
someone who attended the ball.
My father was on to something
and suddenly he was betrayed.
Call him. Or call the police.
They need to know.
What are you waiting for?
Lund... I've talked to my superiors.
We have to get out of here, right now.
There's nothing here, right?
I want to see the oven.
You'll be sent home to answer
a criminal charge.
Yes? Hello, Strange here.
There must be another.
We have to remove all this
rubble and take a look.
He says you're crazy. Agreed...
five people were killed.
If you know anything about it
please tell us about it now.
A family used to live here.
Two adults and two children.
I need to know whether
they were killed or not.
Around here, every day people die,
in case you haven't noticed.
What the hell does he mean by that?
Hey...
Hey! Hey!
When people get killed, it means
something. What's wrong with you?
Translate, dammit.
Tell me what happened. Do you have
the uniform on just for decoration?
What happened to the corpses? You
must've heard or seen something.
They were buried outside? Were they
burned? Did they run away?
You should care, all of you..
That concerns you...
Relax, relax.
We've been through it all.
There is no oven. No bodies. Okay?
It's Brix. They think they know
who the perpetrator is.
Yes?
Fly back immediately. We're in the
shit with the ministry and the army
You have caused a stink by
stepping out of the zone
No choice..
Evidence suggests that it is Bilal.
He knew Dragsholm.  It started to...
..make sense when we found the five
halves of the ID tags at the barracks.
How come?
Yes, so..come home now..
At the barracks?
Why would Bilal...
Come home Lund.
We know where this key is for.
Good, back to the barracks.
It's not the barracks. According to
the locksmith it's a lease...
in the name of Per K. Møller.
The meeting's started. Would
everyone take their seats.
The Minister of Justice has a report
about the investigation in Helmand.
The Prime Minister wants it heard before the vote.
Let's start now
As you know the investigation carried out in
Afghanistan has yielded no new information.
...but I've discovered a scandal
of historic proportions.
A stain on the history of the party
and the government.
Is that it?
That's all..?
The police found nothing?
No, but if I may continue ...
...other issues will have to wait.
The prime minister has the floor.
His words aren't important If I can't continue. What I have
to expose, it's scandalous, I must be allowed to speak.
You can wait, I will speak now, and I find
this a hard thing to say...
I've just received information ...
...which more than suggests that
the Minister of Defence misled us.
The Minister of Defence
withheld a statement ...
...indicating that the hand
found in Afghanistan ...
...didn't belong to
a Taliban suicide bomber.
This information was concealed to
avoid the question of killing civilians.
That's totally wrong...It's shocking.
Yes...I was shocked..
With immediate effect The Minister Of Defence is
dismissed for gross misconduct in office,
His actions will be investigated
by the Intelligence service.
Say it. The Prime Minister told you
to withhold those documents.
The Minister of Justice must wait.
Let me finish. The Minister of Defence
has told me everything.
The situation regarding the Minister
of Justice is equally serious.
He should be acting for the benefit
of the nation...
...but instead he misused his office
to cast doubt on the Prime Minister.
The Prime Minister instructed
the Minister of Defense ...
His motives are questionable.
He's leading a smear campaign...
...and is very careless
with confidential information.
Intelligence will investigate
whether he has committed treason.
That's ludicrous!
What the hell is going on?
If it is discovered you have broken
the law I cannot help you here
I need no help from you..
It goes without saying, that you have
hereby resigned as minister.
Relax, relax.
I'll go myself. Relax!
Have you been arrested?
Has the Minister of Defense tried to
mislead parliament?
They found it in Søgaards locker?
Søgaard's alibis are all in order.
Brix thinks Bilal used the locker
to plant evidence.
If there were no civilian deaths,
then why the murders?
I didn't get to hear more after
you went at his Afghan driver.
The main thing is that we have him
now...whether it's Bilal or Søgaard.
Yes. you're right
So it's good you're on your way home
to clean everything up, right?
Shit.
Do as they say.
Subtitles re-edited by DG