You're through to the alarm center.
I think something's happened.
Yes? What's your name?
There's blood everywhere..
I can't find her.
Okay. Where are you calling from?
Oh God!
Hello? I need your name & address.
Anne?   Anne?
There's no one at home.
I can't find my wife.
Is anyone hurt?
I don't know.
Tell me what happened
so I can help you. Hello?
What did I do?
Hello? Stay on the line.
Anne?
Hello?
Where are you?
Anne!
She has 15-20 stab wounds
to the torso and throat.
Looks like she was killed elsewhere
and then brought here
It also appears that she was dead
when she was strung up.
Get the dog to shut up.
Brix ...
Her husband was found in his car
down by the highway.
He was covered in blood.
Take him in for questioning.
If he's covered with blood,
we're already halfway there.
It's seven a.m Monday,
November 14. Here is the news.
The Minister of Justice, Frode Monberg
has been admitted to hospital after
a suspected heart attack.
His condition is uncertain.
Parliament will sit to consider
the new anti-terrorism package.
The Prime Minister states Monberg's
absence won't affect negotiations.
This anti-terrorism package is needed.
The threat to Denmark has increased.
The fight against terrorism must be fought
both here and in Afghanistan.
In other news a suspect in the Mindelunden Park
murder is in custody.
Police so far have released few details
about the murder which took place ten days
ago
The suspect must be charged or
released by tomorrow
Anything happen Lund?
No.
Good night.
Thanks.
Hello. My name is Ulrich Strange.
I left a message for you...
...but I don't think
your voice-mail is working.
There's coffee in the pot if you'd like some
Yes, please.
I'm an inspector at Police HQ ...
You mean sergeant, right?
No, the title changed
after the last reorganisation.
There's something that we want to
talk to you about.
Ten days ago
a woman was murdered...
Under strange circumstances.
I'll just wait until you're done.
I can hear you.
We've withheld information...
We imagine that you've already
read about it.
Who is 'we'?
Brix, your former boss.
He believes that you can contribute
a new angle.
Lennart Brix?
Yes, He wants you to review the file.
Brix thinks you can offer new insight
we can discuss it.
As you can see, I'm no longer dealing
with files and suspects.
We think the murderer is the victim's
husband, who we're holding...
In another 32 hours we
charge him or let him go.
You'll be paid for the inconvenience.
Yes, that's fine.
Tell him it's no use
Why not?
Brix said I should stress to you most
strongly that he needs your help.
And you've done it, right?
I have to go.
It's been a long night.
Close the door when you're done
Okay.
How is his condition?
Will the minister come back?
I have no comment.
We hope his condition improves.
Thanks for your concern.
Won't you sit down.
The Prime Minister won't be a moment.
Hi, Thomas. How are you?
Fine, thank you.
How's the family?
Good, everything's fine.
Is there any news?
He's doing well.
But he's not coming back,
either now or later.
We're relieved that he survived,
but it comes at an unfortunate time.
That's clear.
So, I have chosen you...
..to get our anti-terrorism
package through Parliament.
There'll be a vote next week.
Right now it's a mad house.
Our coalition partners are flexing their
muscles, and the opposition ...
Sorry. There's something
I have to say first.
I'm truly honored by your offer...
Really...
But I have to say, no thanks.
Why?
I don't feel ready.
I'm not a lawyer. There must be
others who are much better suited.
But maybe in a few years,
when I've been here a little longer.
The government has worked
hard on the terrorism package
Someone must lead the negotiations.
Would you like to be that person?
For me it's very simple.  You have the skills.
So you have to do it.
I can nominate anyone from our party,
but it's you I need.
If you have no other reasons to
reject me, then I'll ask you again:
Will you be our new Justice Minister?
Raben, you have a visitor.
He wanted to be here, but there's "Colors
and Shapes Day" in kindergarten.
All the others will be there.
I understand.
I've brought some of his new drawings.
Would you like to see them?
Everything has to do with adventures
and role playing for the time being.
It's a very important dragon...
I can't remember its name...
...but it's huge and very dangerous.
He's good at it.
Yesterday we bought the shield and sword.
It was a gift from grandpa.
Otherwise, not much has happened.
Shall we ...?
Let's just wait a little while.
When is it?  soon.
I'll be nice and calm.
I'm having an interview with them,
and then they'll decide.
The lawyer is optimistic.
They can't say no this time.
The superintendent says
I've made great progress.
They can't say no this time.
What's up?
He's not here because..
Jonas doesn't want to come anymore.
I know you wanted to see him,
so I tried, but he won't come.
It's okay.
It's important not to push him.
I don't push him.
But he isn't a small child anymore.
He won't talk about you.
I think it's because someone has teased
him in kindergarten, you know..kids..
Sorry, honey. Just forget it.
I'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out..
It'll be fine. I promise you.
Soon we'll be together so much,
that we'll miss being alone.
Even If I snore and slurp...
...and put toothpaste on my upper lip.
This is Vibeke Lund. I'm not home,
please leave a message.
Hi, Mom. It's Sarah. I'll be coming by
train in a couple of hours.
And I can only stay until tomorrow,
so ... Yes. See you.
She said no. I think she had
a busy night with ferry traffic.
Brix.
It's Strange.
Sarah Lund. Is Brix there?
He's busy right now. Can I help?
I'm going to visit my family today.
It's not certain that I'll have time...
...but if he really thinks
I can help, then ...
Then what?
I need to run. I'll call you later.
Hello?
38-year-old Thomas Buch has today been
sworn in as the new justice minister.
Buch's appointment was seen as a surprise in
political circles.
His first task will be to create consensus to
push through the anti-terrorism package.
yes yes we shook hands and she put
her congratulations on record.
I have to run.
I'll talk to you later.
Karina Munk Jørgensen,
secretary. Congratulations.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
We fill the second and third floor,
and we have 170 employees.
This is yours, the office of the
Minister of Justice.
The rest of his stuff will be moved soon.
That's good.
My predecessor left it?
No. I brought it here.
So the Minister can just read it.
Carsten Plough, Permanent Secretary.
The reception's ready to begin.
That's good.
Can I have an update on the
progress of the negotiations?
It'll be a settlement between the
Government and the People's Party.
The opposition's rejected it, but you
can check the details in the file.
Yes. But first I'll tell you about my
position. We're at war.
Whether we like it or not,
The challenge is to find unity.
We must pursue a broad national
reconciliation.
That's also been tried.
Your predecessor had to admit ...
... I understand. But it's very
important that this succeeds.
Unless there's a problem?
No, of course not.
Let me show you the welcome
gift from the People's Party.
''Never again 9th April.'' I'm not
an expert on political messages...
...but I don't think they've given up .
Well, we'll see.
Yes.
But you can discuss it
with your personal advisor.
I don't need a lawyer. The three of us
can handle it together.
Okay. I'll call the parties together
to meet as soon as possible.
That sounds wonderful.
Great..lets get going then
Stop fretting, things have changed now,
everything will be fine
They can't keep you here forever
Why don't they just give a sign?
Don't make a fuss, too much and you'll get
it in the ass. Do you understand?
Yes, I understand. See you later.
Superintendant Toft!
Raben! Stop there!
Away from the fence....
Away from the fence...It's okay.
How did it go?
I can't say anything about that.
You need to talk to your lawyer.
I don't have his number.
Then wait.
It's not my fault.
I need to call my wife. If it's
bad news, I want to hear it now.
We made a positive recommendation..
But it's not up to us.
The Directorate of Prisons will
make the final decision.
So, nothing is certain.
Raben, come now!
What did she say exactly?
The doctors think I'm ready.
When's the answer due?
In about a week or so.
It depends on the Directorate of Prisons.
You need to get hold of Myg.
Wait I need to move..
Myg? Why?
He can get me work.
It will help the decision, say it's urgent.
Ok I will
Jonas is there? Yes he's going to
show my father something.
I'll call you as soon as I can. Say
goodnight for me and remember Myg.
I will.
Hi. There's still some food.
That sounds good.
How did it go?
We need to send 200 men.
They can't understand that logistical
Services works so slow
Usually you're good at
explaining things to them.
Jonas, you have to get into your pyjamas.
No, I need to fence with grandpa.
Hurry. Maybe he'll read a bedtime
story if you're quick.
I've looked at schools, Louise.
Sion Street sounds the best.
And it's not so far away.
That's good. Gravy?
Just a little bit.  Be sure
to register on time.
I'll check it out, Dad.
I'm not sure we're staying here.
Why not? The Infirmary wants you
to continue.
I need that personnel list with numbers,
do you know where it is?
It's over in the bureau.
I've said, I can move down to
the basement. I'll get it decorated.
That's fine, Dad.
We'll see, right?
You think he'll get out?
He seems to have a good chance.
And what if they're wrong?
You've waited over two years.
Two years in which both Jonas and you are suffering...
...he is his father and I love him.
If you have a problem with that
we'll pack our bags right away.
Sorry. The major said that the colonel
wanted an update on the armoured cars.
Yes, Bilal. Later.
I want to speak to the colonel.
Yes. Thank you. Later.
Yes.
We know she came home at 19:32 and
disabled the alarm system.
She spoke with her husband
Maybe I should wait outside until Brix gets here.
Brix is delayed.
He asked me to bring you up to speed
They were in the middle of a divorce
after he had an affair with his secretary.
She found out and threw him out a month ago.
She refused to talk to him..
even on the phone.
Where was his daughter?
With her grandparents.
At 19:41 she logged onto her laptop
here in the kitchen and went online.
She got a glass of wine, checked some
housing sites and went to the bathroom.
So she didn't hear the
basement window being broken.
She took a long bath, then came
back in her bathrobe to cook.
Was it her routine? Arriving home late,
taking a bath and eating alone in the kitchen?
It's a hard to know. She lived alone.
Yes.
Looks like she was assaulted in
the middle of cooking.
They struggled and ended up in this room
where he went crazy with a sword.
She was stabbed 21 times. The fatal
wound passed through the heart.
She was forcibly put in the chair.
This shows the amount of blood.
The plastic wrap, did you find cigarette butts?
It's not from a cigarette package.
Chewing gum?
Yes, maybe.
The husband claims he arrived
here a little after midnight.
Does he have an alibi?
...His girlfriend.
...backs up his story as far as times etc.
He drank a lot, then came to talk to
his wife to bring her to her senses.
When he found the broken basement
window he went back to the road.
He got blood on himself.
Didn't he have a key?
His wife had the locks and alarms
replaced a few weeks ago.
She was very concerned about security.
She fired the previous alarm company
because they weren't good enough.
Under the new one, she  ordered
sensors installed throughout the garden.
Good to see you.
Can we look at the rest?
Yes, this way.
The victim was entitled to half
of her husband's fortune.
So we aren't lacking a motive.
Here is where she was found.
She had nothing to do with
Mindelunden Park.
But she was dragged over the fence.
There are photos at the back of the file.
Thank you.
The husband isn't stupid, we think most
of it is an elaborate diversion.
Everything points to him.
What are you thinking?
I think there's a mistake here.
I think I'm wasting your time.
I just want to hear your opinion.
Can't we sleep on it?
So we'll have a chat tomorrow...
I don't know if I have anything.
If you do,  let me know...
..if not, that's fine too.
Still, I could use your help...
...otherwise I'll let the guy go free
tomorrow morning.
It's Buch.  Karina speaking.
I've spoken to the opposition.
They can meet you and the People's
Party in the morning.
Fine. I need to read 700-800
pages, so I'll be up to speed.
Well, we'll see you tomorrow.
Wait a minute...
...I have a folder with some photos of a
dead woman. in the Memorial Grove
It's a mistake. I'm sorry.
What's it got to do with the Ministry?
Your predecessor wanted to be
updated, the Memorial Grove is a
national monument
The police don't believe
there's a political motive.
Yes, thanks. See you tomorrow.
Yes.
Hello.
Yes. Good night.
One Islamist association
pops up after another.
It's pure scaremongering.They're
determined to overthrow democracy.
They'll re-introduce the Middle Ages.
What about free speech?
The package doesn't consider
the current terrorist threat.
The People's Party stance is too rigid.
We cannot support it
I've got to go... But now
you have an insight into the problem.
Congratulations on your appointment.
Good luck with your task.
Bye, Agger.
Good day to you, Krabbe.
Nice try. I'll regret the outcome, but
some things have to be said.
We need to protect ourselves...
Think of London and Madrid.
The opposition is right. Intelligence
Service Reports don't support you.
Did you get our little gift yesterday?
Yes, thanks.
Since your drop in the polls ...
would a "scare campaign" help to
improve your ratings, put you in a safe place?
My grandfather was in the Resistance.
He ended up in Neuengamme.
Make no mistake. What I say is true...
That doesn't change anything.
Your proposal is problematic.
Who says it's only a proposal?
What do you mean?
We need each other to get
a majority vote. And right now...
As I see it, you have more need of
us than we have of you.
My party supporters want
an answer later today.
Is a couple of hours enough time,
to clear it with the prime minister?
...and thanks for coffee.
We'll take a five minute break...
then we'll start again.
Hello.
Give him something to eat,
then continue the interrogation.
The clock's ticking.
We need something more.
Hello.
Yes, that's fine. I'm right in
the middle of something ... Yes.
So, I'll get back to you later, okay?
That's good. Bye.
Go ahead.
Deputy Commissioner Director,
Ruth Hedeby, wants to be here.
Sarah Lund. I've heard a lot about you.
Please sit down.
Mindelunden Park is
a national monument.
We'd like to dispell any speculation.
Despite the fact the suspect has an alibi.
We're laying charges today...
...If we're to bring charges today
...we'll need more.
I'd like to know if
you can help in this matter.
I don't know if I can.
I see no weak points
in the investigation.
The forensic evidence
is conclusive, so ...
But do you have any thoughts?
Yes ...
I don't think it's him...
...the husband, I mean.
Of course, it could have been him,
but I don't think so.
I don't think he has anything to do with it.
The report says that the offence
was a crime of passion..
yet he dragged the body to Mindelunden Park..
yes to hinder the investigation. According
to forensics, he was covered with blood.
I just want to hear what Lund
has to say, if that's okay.
The victim was afraid of the suspect.
She had been for some time.
Her husband had a motive
and was manipulative ...
but he wasn't violent.
There are no previous reported incidents.
And I think...
...that whoever did this wanted to say
something about where he left the body.
Yes.
What did he want to say?
What did she do before she was married?
A lot.
Partly educated in the U.S...
...NGO's in Africa and Asia.
During certain periods she was
employed by the Army and Amnesty.
What did she do in the Army?
Military Legal Adviser...
...sent to the Balkans, Iraq, Cyprus,
Afghanistan. It was several years ago.
Did she have military contacts?
No.
Aside from a monthly contribution
to a veterans' Association.
It was paid by automatic transfer
and ... Sorry, excuse me..
I don't know if I'm right in this...
...but if so, then there is something
you haven't found...
...or something's missing.
Yes ?...
The husband has just confessed.
He confessed to the killing
and the removal of the corpse.
Well then...
Good. Yes.
Prosecutors must have a detailed
confession to prepare the charge...
...so we can close this case.
Sorry. Thanks for your effort.
For a moment there,
I was getting worried.
I'm sorry ...
It's fine.
I would gladly pay for your costs...
No. I wanted to come anyway.
Congratulations.
He will live; he must live... Hurrah!
Time to blow out the candles. Ready?
I need a breath...
Really. Here we go...
Go ahead.
It was nice.
While we're all here, Bjørn and I
want to share something with you.
It's good news... In a moment of madness,
Bjørn asked me to marry him...
...and I said "yes", so you're all invited.
Congratulations!
It'll be a simple ceremony.
I'm not wearing white.
So that's out. Sit down.
Here, Mom. Thanks for the sweater.
- I'm sorry about the size.
It doesn't matter.
I'm just glad you're here.
When do you plan to leave?
Later, I'm not here for long
Weren't you here for an interview?
Grandma said you had a job.
No, no..She misunderstood.
How are you?
Fine, Dad. Ulla and the girls are in
Spain for a few days...
...so I have the house all to myself.
Mark.
Come on, Sarah.
Strange here.
Lund speaking..I can't get hold of Brix.
He's in the middle of an interrogation.
I think I have something about the case.
He is just explaining it all..
The plastic wrap..remember?
I think the killer filmed everything
So..unless you believe...
...the husband filmed the assault on
his wife, you have the wrong guy.
I just want to see the murder scene
again, if that's okay.
Raben, you have a visitor.
Raben, you old wanker.
Myg. How are you?
I'm doing fine. Yes, how about you?
Well thanks.
I have some books to read as they say.
Please, sit down.
OK.
I'm bloody sorry I didn't come
more often, but I've been busy.
It's okay.
You talked to Louise?
Yes. She called me yesterday.
I don't know if you can use it.
A job with a master carpenter.
An ex-sergeant.
He talks about the good old days.
He needs a man for a few months.
Does he know where I am? Yes,
he helps out Association members.
I'll get someone to call him,
so he can send a letter here.
Thanks, Myg.
Hey, we always help each other.
The Association can help
with an apartment.
I'll speak to Louise before I head off..
Where you going?
I'm being transferred next week.
Louise can call them herself.
Barracks life is not for me, right?
Too damn boring.
It's time for a change.
Where?
In Helmand. Maybe up north.
It all happened so fast.
I gotta go.
The last time you said you wanted out.
I have to go now.
What did you do? No matter what
it is, I can help you, Myg.
You don't know a damn thing.
When we got home,
I thought it was all over.
It's not over.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Take care of yourself.
Guard! let me out.
Hello.
Hello, darling.
He seems okay.
They dropped him off from kindergarten,
and I brought him up here.
Thanks, Søgaard.
Let me know if I can help.
See you, kid.
Come here.
I know the other kids can be idiots...
...but it's not good to fight with them.
You can only fight dragons...
...and grandfather.
They said things about my dad.
I'll talk to them.
Is dad coming home?
Yes, he will.
I just don't quite know
when that will be.
I've lost a tooth.
Really? That's a good one.
Can I see?
Did it hurt?
Let me give it to dad.
I would even give it to him.
Yes. I'll try to call and see
if they have a time today.
Intelligence's latest threat assessment?
It's still with the Prime Minister.
They just got him talking sense.
He's only been here for 24 hours.
That's enough to undermine our
government's parliamentary base.
This link can only be opened at 17.03.
The Ministry of Finance.
It's their turn to host the
Interdepartmental Friday Get-together.
I thought so too, but they deny it.
Am I disturbing you? No,
The Intelligence Assessment.
What did the prime minister say?
He wasn't there.
What about the People's Party?
Krabbe is on his way up.
Let's go inside.
Did you decide?
We did, yes.
That sounds good.
I'm sorry if my tone was a little ...
...but it's obviously very important.
Certainly, I agree.
But our position is quite clear...
...we refuse to compromise ...
...on the constitutional protection
of democratic principles.
No threat or intimidation by you or
by terrorists can change that.
Yes ... If the government wants
us to leave the coalition...
...then we'll have to think about it.
I need to tell the press, of course,
that the coalition has ended.
I'm not a historian,
but I think that only once before...
...a Danish government has prohibited
an otherwise lawful union.
In 1941 with the communist party.
Back then, however, we were
under pressure from the Wehrmacht.
This can't be compared with that.
I've spoken to constitutional experts.
I've enclosed their opinions...
...if you're interested.
Will you be part of a settlement
or stand alone with your views...
...which haven't been heard since
the Nazis were in the country?
Lund, I haven't got all night.
Why would he film it?
You said the victim was put
in the chair after the stabbing.
Yes, but the volume of blood suggests ...
...she was placed in the chair ...
..and then stabbed?
That doesn't fit a crime of passion.
Who said it was?
Only one stab wound was deep
enough to strike a vital organ.
Why didn't she defend herself?
She had no defensive wounds on her hands.
You think she was bound...
...he wanted to talk to her...
...and only the last stab was fatal.
You think he stabbed her...
to get her to talk. About what?
What is it?
A military dog tag.
One half is sheared off.
Do you have the address of the Veterans'
Association she was a member of?
Did you speak to the Director of Prisons?
I've completed your assessment.
You'll get an answer tomorrow.
I can't wait until tomorrow.
Relax now, dammit.
Hello. I asked for a phone call.
Has the Director seen it?
I don't know.
Raben!
An army buddy visited me.
He isn't feeling well.
I need to call him.
I'll say that it is urgent.
Thank you.
We should talk about something else.
Can I just call first?
No. Let's get started.
The Directorate of Prisons has
rejected your application. I'm sorry..
Normally it takes a long time and
they follow our advice, but ....
I haven't received an explanation.
You'll get it as soon as possible.
I'm sorry.
Why?
As I said...
I've followed the treatment..all that was asked.
You may apply again in six months.
You should value your progress.
Listen to me.. I have a young son.
Not so close to the director.
I just have to ...
Fuck off!
Raben... quiet, quiet.
You should take it easy.
I am calm. You don't understand.
I'm not a psychopath.
Raben, come on now...Now!
Calm down, calm down...
Let me go!
Calm, calm.
Yes. I'll tell him. Thank you.
The People's Party accepts the
revised text with minor modifications.
That sounds good.
You don't seem very happy.
The Law of 1941 can't be compared
to the People's Party proposal.
Next time you come to see me,
and not my lawyers.
You're right. Sorry.
There's something you have to see.
It's Karina Munk Jorgensen.
The Justice minister is delayed..Thanks.
I just opened that link.
What link?
Hang on for a minute.
It's just re-loading.
It says it's from hotmail.
Come on, what is it?
It's interesting, but ...
...wait a minute. Here it is.
"I accuse the hypocritical
Danish Government and...
...the infidel Danish people of crimes
against humanity. The time has...
come for Allah's revenge. The Muslim
League punishes Denmark for the suffering...
...Denmark has inflicted on our brothers
in Palestine, Iraq and Afghanistan.
I declare myself guilty.
My blood will flow, and
many will follow me in death."
I haven't done anything...
I have a little girl ...
The veterans' Association has
about 10,000 members.
The secretary of the local one is called
Myg Allan Poulsen. He lives at #46
Wait here. I don't want the hassle
of having to make a report.
Hello?  Is anyone home?
Hello?
Hey!
Myg Allan Poulsen. Get a description
and put out an APB right away.
Get a team out here.
I want the house searched. Hey!
Hello!
I told you to stay outside!
Are you deaf or what?
Subtitles By DG