Ten days ago a woman was killed in
unusual circumstances.
The Muslim League
will punish Denmark.
"My blood will flow.
Many shall follow me in death."
He called Kodmani.
The video was on his site.
Brix wants to hear your views on the case.
David Gruner 28, a former soldier.
What does Intelligence know about the unit?
3-2-Alpha had eight members ..
.. with Raben as squad leader.
There were allegations of civilian casualties.
The report exhonerated them.
And the rest of the unit?
Raben is a fugitive and
we're looking for Lisbeth Thomsen.
A third died last year
in a traffic accident.
The government has put a lot of effort
into the anti-terrorism package.
Do you want to be
the Minister of Justice.?
Neither we nor Intelligence
had reason to foresee this.
Do you want to try negotiating an
agreement with the People's Party alone?
We're working on a broad compromise.
The Prime Minister wants consensus.
Monberg possibly had
knowledge of the first victim.
We have to intervene. Agree to
the demands of the People's Party.
The Directorate of Prisons
has rejected your application.
Why can't I see him?
Myg Allan Poulsen was found murdered.
Raben knew both victims.
He lied about it and has escaped.
I need to get in touch with Thomsen
She is the last of the group.
If Jens contacts you
it's important that you tell me.
She had an uncle somewhere.
Sweden...an island.
Has he been at the barracks?
Someone took 5 kg. of plastic explosives.
Lisbeth Thomsen lives on an island
in southern Sweden...Skogö.
Raben may show up.
That's pretty unlikely.
We're looking for something
which may explain the anger...
Raben and Myg risked their lives.
You shouldn't slander them.
You're not alone on the island.
Please have a seat.
Something happened in the village.
The others said so. Now they are dead.
There was an officer who fucked-up...
He's called Perk.
The lawyer believed them.
Come out or I'll shoot!
Krabbe is getting impatient.
We have to hold a press conference.
It wasn't Dragsholm who had
an affair with Monberg... It was me.
So you saw Dragsholm?
No.
It's a report about an incident in Afghanistan.
I'll have to resign.
The names of those killed.
What happens?
Go back to Thomsen. Now!
It was me who stopped you.
Have you been in here?
They can't just disappear.
What's that?
Nothing, just woods.
It is all the same.
8000 hectares of forest...
...and Thomsen knows it
like the back of her hand.
Bertil and Ralle have driven down
the road to cut him off.
Where the hell are they?
About a half hour away, they said.
But it'll probably be longer.
But my brother-in-law is on his way.
Your brother-in-law?
If we had known that they'd escaped,
we'd have been better prepared.
We could have prepared better.
It wasn't a problem to enter the house.
The kitchen window was unlocked.
No trace of the perpetrator?
Only Raben.
We're not sure that he isn't the only
one who was involved. He's former military.
It's a booby-trap with a kilo of explosives.
If Thomsen had touched the rifle,
the hut would have blown to hell.
The checkpoint could have been Raben,
but not this.
We have to find Thomsen and Raben.
Why can't they find out...
This is my brother and his friends.
Thomsen's car was found on the north side.
They must have headed out on foot.
Come on!
What happened?
I  can't...
Come here.
How far is it?
A good distance yet.
Be careful.
Someone's been in your house.
Who do you think it could be?
I haven't used the rifle in days.
What's going on?
The lawyer who came to ask
if I wanted to testify.
She wanted to have the case re-opened.
She found some new information.
What information?
She wouldn't say anything about it.
What happened in the village?
I don't know. Where did she go?
I don't know.
Did you do anything? What happened?
I can't remember.
I remember the screams.
The stench of death. The children who tried to...
He said the officer was called Perk.
Is it a survivor seeking revenge?
They've found the car. Come on!
Why did he need the explosives?
He didn't. I've said that already
Your father has the codes for the
ammunition depot in his computer.
Jens hasn't been here.
I checked on the computer.
He knew nothing about explosives.
He wanted to find Thomsen.
I found an address
of an uncle in Sweden...
How did you? It doesn't matter.
He's a fugitive.
You're an accomplice.
In a parking lot.
He just popped up.
I have no contact? No deals?
You know where he is now?
No.
Come in.
The investigators have searched the depot.
The codes used weren't the Colonel's.
They've found explosives from the same
lot-number we've lost.
The explosives were used in a
house belonging Lisbeth Thomsen.
Where was Jens going?
He didn't say...
But he asked about Thomsen's house
in Sweden...right?
As long as the explosives have been found,
there's no danger.
Will you let me know,
if the police say anything about Jens?
The police will want speak to you.
But that's not as bad as this.
"The number you are trying to call
is currently unavailable."
They were here not so long ago.
They may have taken the path.
Where does it go?
It leads to the harbour and the ferry.
What is that way?
There's a campsite, but it is closed.
There's a harbour?
There's only one jetty.
Thomsen has a boat.
Call the Coast Guard.
We need the area searched.
We're on the west side. Come on.
They have my car and they know where
I moor my boat.
Then they'll contact the coastguard.
Okay. Come on...No, here.
They're sailing northward. I'll sail the other way.
The Coast Guard will follow.
We'll stay together.
It'll give you a head start.
The police will let me go.
It's the only chance we have.
We'll stay together. Come on.
We have no fuel.
There's a reserve canister in my boat-house.
You can't miss seeing it.
There really are no monsters.
Come on. We're stuck.
Thomsen!
Stop!
Don't start it!
Take the kayak. See you.
Stop!
The Minister will come when he's ready.
Time is running out.
The prime minister is on the plane.
TV news goes live.
What's happening here?
Keep him on hold. I'm sorry.
There's something that I must discuss
with the prime minister.
What happened?
It's confidential, but very important.
I'm not sure the prime minister will
be happy with the delay.
The investigation may have an impact
on the banning of associations.
Buch...
Stop now, what... damn it.
The country's waiting for us to take action.
Don't start your humanitarian nonsense.
Krabbe, I'm tired ...
I'm 100 % sure the prime minister is.
I demand an immediate explanation.
Should I go in there and say that
the government is paralysed?
I'm sorry, but it's your problem.
I won't be held responsible for your decision.
If you don't go on now,
then it'll be too late for the news broadcast.
Nervousness is normal during such a crisis.
But let's announce what we've decided.
Good evening and welcome. The Government
announces the new anti-terrorism law agreement...
...reached with the People's Party. Terrorism
has unfortunately become part of our everyday lives...
so we must be continually vigilent
to improve the safety of the public.
The threat must not encroach
on our democratic values.
But we must safeguard our freedom
against the dark forces...
Since the recent murders of former
military personnel ...
...have tragically brought this issue into focus
we have all worked together on this bill.
Before we go into details of the package,
Erling Krabbe will say a few words.
Thank you.
There has been lengthy and tough negotiations...
...but we've now succeeded in reaching an agreement.
I want to commend the government
on good political work...
...and for having the courage to
take the bull by the horns...
...although the opposition has thrown in the towel.
For the People's Party,
defense of our freedom is the highest priority.
We won't be bullied by medieval fanatics...
...who repeatedly emerge from
Koranic schools and associations...
..funded by Danish tax payers.
We must crack down...
...on groups that try to undermine our society.
Otherwise we squander our identity as Danes.
This must not happen.
Therefore, the Peoples Party
is proud to support the new law...
.. that the Minister of Justice will
now outline in detail.
Buch...
This won't do.
We need to stop.
Yes...Sorry.
I can't go into details. I apologise.
What's this?
The announcement of the anti-terrorism package
took a surprising twist.
Justice Minister Thomas Buch walked away from
a press conference with the People's Party.
The Minister of Justice has so far
refused to comment on the situation.
I can't reach König in Intelligence.
Ask Karina to find out what's available
on the military action in question.
I'll take care of it myself.
It's possible that it'll raised ...
I haven't been here...since Monberg turned 50.
These portraits remind the minister
that he has some responsibility.
It seems strange, but ...
Did you hear the reactions.
Do you realise the magnitude of the crisis?
Terrorism is a mistake .. Monberg
Don't blame Monberg.
You started those rumors?
I understand that you're still flinging
around lots of accusations.
They're not just accusations.
It's in black and white.
Monberg knew the first victim...
She was a lawyer who wanted Monberg
to reopen an old military criminal case.
The case is about the soldiers
who have now been murdered.
A group of soldiers accused
of killing Afghan civilians.
The group was exonerated,
but the lawyer wanted to reopen the case.
She gave Monberg a file...
Five days later she was murdered
How did you get this?
Monberg sent it to himself in the post.
We opened it when it was delivered to the office
and saw what it contained
Monberg should have taken this up long ago.
We can ask him when he wakes up,
but we have to decide here and now.
Monberg didn't have a heart attack.
According to his wife, he swallowed pills.
He was depressed.
We gave the press a cover story.
It doesn't make the situation better.
What did Monberg have to hide?
Why was he worried about an old
military matter? I don't understand.
Get to the bottom of it.
But, keep these cards close to your chest.
We need to know what's going on
as soon as possible...
...Especially considering the latest rumours.
Rumours?
Something happened in Sweden.
They've found another dead soldier.
We couldn't know she would run away.
There's no trace of Raben.
He may have escaped on another boat
The Coast Guard and the Swedish Navy
are conducting a manhunt
We'll do our best. Okay?
Bye
Explosives were stolen in a burglary
at the barracks.
They're investigating, whether
they came from the same batch.
We couldn't prevent it.
We wanted to help, but she ran away.
Let's go and check the boathouse for traces.
It may be...
Where you going?
Lund!
Okay. Thank you.
Sources suggest the Danish Citizen
murdered in Sweden...
...was directly connected to other recent
terrorist-related killings.
The woman was formerly
a member of the armed forces.
In this case, we are now talking
about a fourth victim.
Neither Intelligence nor the police have...
What the hell are they talking about?
Hedeby is there too.
We can't give up now.
We're onto something.
We don't have anything at all.
We're the ones who found the bodies.
We're not sure what happened in Afghanistan.
In fundamentalist circles...
...the soldiers are guilty despite the
findings of the official enquiry.
We've found fatwas against the
military on websites and against ...
...the system that acquitted them.
That's what we are concentrating on.
The investigation hasn't brought us
any closer to a solution.
I've asked Brix to reorganise his team,
effective from today.
What does that mean?
You're still on the case.
But first you need to take some days off.
We're just ...
You let your witness escape
with the suspect in the area.
We couldn't tie her down!
You knew that religious fanatics
had their eyes on that unit.
So, shouldn't we have lunch.
Or could someone else disappear from that unit?
has everything been arranged...staged?
The flyers, video 'Faith Brother',
Kodmani, Muslim League.
What are you talking about?
What is she talking about?
Dragsholm wanted Thomsen to testify
if the case was reopened.
What if someone isn't interested
in having the case reopened?
Who could it be?
They're all dead.
The last one has
a pretty good alibi in Herstedvester.
Consider the army.
Explosives were stolen from the barracks.
And the detonators they needed.
We don't know if the incident is closed,
or if the case will be re-opened.
The case is about to be re-opened.
I've just heard.
It's a political issue now.
But it has no connection to the killings.
It would explain a lot.
The army doesn't kill its own people.
Someone in the army has a motive.
Insane speculation.
I suppose I'll get a briefing,
when you've restructured the team.
It's already been done. Lund and
Strange continue to investigate the matter.
It's in everyone's interest that this
case is concluded. Understand.
Otherwise, we're going to end up with more bodies
filling the refridgerators in the morgue
Don't make any mistakes.
Are we completely agreed?
The team has to go through everything
related to the old Afghan case.
And we need to find that officer, Perk.
that Thomsen told us about
As long as it's discreet.
What's she doing here?
She's had no contact with her husband.
How do you know? We're having her followed.
She told him about Thomsen's house in Sweden.
I have a search warrant.
Shall we go?
The police have been here twice,
and Louise called.
A fourth Danish soldier's been killed
I need money.
Can you lend me some?
For what?
Just a few thousand.
This has to stop now.
You're the last person left.
Can I get the money or not?
Turn yourself in.
Thomsen said the lawyer
wanted to reopen the case.
Which case?
What happened out there.
She must have found something new.
If I give up now, they died for nothing.
Did Dragsholm ever contact you?
Who?
The lawyer who was killed in Mindelunden Park.
I've never met her.
You think I'm crazy.
I was in the camp.
There was no officer...
Someone might have put a lid on it.
It'll be the same people behind this.
You can't just think about yourself.
You have a wife, a son.
Give me the money now.
We can drive to the police now.
I can tell them that you are innocent.
Trust me.
I saw Thompsen blown into thin air.
Don't tell me to turn the other cheek.
Give me the money.
Don't you have a debit card?
Bloody hell, don't you have a debit card?
We've tried to explain away your behavior
at the press conference...
...about the need to discuss the matter,
with the safety committee...
...but speaking after the latest killing
was an enormous press blunder.
Some colleagues are distancing themselves from you.
Not the least of which is Erling Krabbe.
What about the prime minister?
He expects a lengthy statement this evening.
There's nothing that connects
Monberg to the Afghan military matter.
But I've been wrong before.
Did you notice anything about him?
No.
It dawned on me that
I really might not have known him.
It's probably best you go in alone.
If there is a disciplinary matter,
shouldn't we talk about this in private.
As it stands Plough,
she just had an affair with the minister.
We're not sure if there's more to it.
You won't hear about his sex life.
It would be nice to avoid that.
Hello?
Hello.
Please sit here, darling?
Go and read a book.
I'll just help the babysitter discard it.
Just a moment.
Hello. What's your name?
Merle.
Come on baby, Lotte's helping
to get you dressed.
I need to go to the post office.
Remember, she has to pee.
If it's about my resignation,
I'll go by the Ministry's wishes.
You have a daughter.
It's not the first thing I expected the ministry to care about
And her father is a musician?
No, it's mine.
His father is a lawyer.
He went to earn tons of money. In Dubai.
I want you to come back.
I have unintentionally misled
both you and my secretary.
Plough believes you've done nothing wrong.
He would jump at a chance for a "roll
in the hay". Sorry, but I need your help.
Before this evening, I need to find out
what Monberg's role was in this.
Don't you have any idea why
Monberg wanted to keep it hidden?
If I did, then I'd have told you.
Why all the secrecy?
Something that could explain why he
tried to kill himself. What?
He took pills.
Apparently he had a guilty conscience...
...but I want facts.
I don't know what to say.
If you remember anything, please call.
Bye.
The Minister of Defence Minister
has requested a meeting...
...if possible in the afternoon.
Tell him that I don't have time.
Major Søgaard isn't answering his phone.
He is busy sending off the officers today on deployment.
Myg Poulsen was responsible for
his platoon's ammunition.
The access code and password
that were used, were his.
The murderer must have
tortured him to get it.
Aren't those codes cancelled
when the person dies?
The technicians hadn't yet
reset the passwords
When I downloaded the auditors report
Thursday evening, there was no guard.
The depot is electronically locked.
Only seven people have the password.
Normally, monitoring isn't necessary.
What time was the burglary?
According to system logs, the lock
was opened at 0:39 Thursday night.
And again at 01:04...
25 minutes later.
The thief took his time..
I presume that your technicians
can explain how ...
... the explosives were taken
off the shelf over here.
We made a list of people
with knowledge of the barracks area.
How did Lisbeth Thomsen die? Might it be
from the same explosive as this one?
Nobody noticed anything because
Intelligence is often here.
A hole was cut in the fence.
Perhaps to distract us.
This looks like an inside job made
to look like a burglary
Who else has access?
Three platoon leaders.
And two officers.
What about yourself?
You have to come with us to the office.
We still need to talk to you.
Why?
So we can ask you more questions.
That'll have to wait.
Do it voluntarily...
...or else we'll arrest you.
Yesterday you said that
no civilians were killed at the village.
According to Thomsen, 3-2-Alpha
reported otherwise.
Yes, but that turned out to be wrong.
You'd lost three of your unit members.
Maybe your focus was somewhere else.
What was the soldiers' explanation?
They had received a message from a
patrol in distress behind enemy lines.
They said it came from a Danish officer,
Perk.
He was under fire.
And they were coming to his rescue.
Go on...explain.
They sought refuge in a building,
but were under siege for two days.
During this siege
something happened to a family.
They claimed that the Danish officer
had killed them.
How did you feel about that?
The story was pure fabrication.
Nobody could confirm the distress call
that group claimed they had received.
There was no officer named Perk.
There were no corpses.
Why would they lie?
The mission had cost three lives.
It was an attempt to shift the focus
from the tragedy they had caused.
Do you think it was Raben
who was to blame for the tragedy?
Nothing was ever established
What about the family in the house?
They all fled.
It was a very dangerous area.
We had done everything we could...
Have you checked all of this out personally?
Yes, It's part of my job.
I wasn't in the camp at that time,
but I'm familiar ...
Just a moment...
You weren't in the camp?
I was in a consultation meeting
with the Afghan government in Kabul.
My second in command kept me informed.
Who was your deputy?
Captain Søgaard.
Today, he's Gen. Søgaard.
Søgaard was in command?
I came back two days later.
Thank you.
Jarnvig here.
Yes, hello. Just a moment.
Has Søgaard reported back?
No, but I have called him on his mobile
He's not answering.
Intelligence has identified
the Islamist groups...
...who have alleged that Danish soldiers
committed atrocities in Afghanistan
Is there any concrete evidence?
I don't know.
König will brief you later.
They've nothing on Monberg and the military issue.
They complain about lack of cooperation from
the police.  Why?  I'll check into it.
I'll have the job-posting for the
new secretary distributed internally.
I know that there are two ...
Do you have a moment?
Now isn't a good time.
See you later.
Two minutes.
I was just talking to the Prime Minister.
It's best that we have this chat.
Rossing, I know that Monberg is your friend.
This has been an unpleasant experience,
but we have to investigate.
I remember the time when I was just appointed.
You're nervous.
You want to make a good impression
on the Prime Minister... Like back at school.
I'm a little busy, so...
You'll ruin the whole country.
I don't know of any connection between
Monberg and the military issue.
Fine... If you say so.
There is one thing you must understand.
Frode has been under a lot of pressure
for a long time.
Anti-Terrorism Package Negotiations.
A very unhappy marriage.
Can I?
In this situation, he was approached by
Anne Dragsholm, his great love.
They met at university.
He was a guest teacher... she a student.
He had a wife and children,
and broke-off their relationship.
I really don't think that
they've had any contact since...
...not until recently, when she decided
to use their old connection.
Is there a point to all of this?
Monberg wasn't interested in this case,
but in Dragsholm.
When she was killed a few days later,
he collapsed.
I ate lunch with him a few days before he...
..he talked about the mistakes
he had committed in his life.
I had other things on my mind.
But he talked about his breakup
with Anne Dragsholm.
So I need to put the matter to rest.
No, I'm not saying that.
Things need to come to light;
but not just yet.
If the scandal only concerns
Monberg's privacy ...
...you might as well make everything public.
It's your choice.
Better think twice about it.
Thanks for the coffee.
Is this your address book?
Yes. But he's not in there.
We'll have to borrow it.
You'll get it back as soon as we finish.
Mama...
Hello, darling.
Hello.
Did you have fun?
They were helping mom clean up.
But now they're going.
Was the museum interesting?
Please sign here.
Hello. Jonas. Nice bag.
Did you get it from Daddy?
Where are they taking the computer?
Goodbye again.
It's okay, honey.
They're just borrowing it.
We'll buy a new Play Station on Monday,
right?
Louise... Hello?
It's me.
Come right over to my office.
Come in.
He's really not well.
He needs to be helped,
before it's too late.
Call him and tell him you'll meet him.
The police will arrange the rest.
He isn't there...
...Try again.
Try this one
It's smaller
How much will you pay?
Just 600.
You can't get an air pistol for 600
I'll take it.
I'll use it. OK?
Get out.
Louise?
Dad knows I have the phone number.
Did he find out from the chaplain?
They're worried about you.
Are you okay?
Are the police still there do they know about the phone?
Not yet. Are you okay?
The chaplain says something's very wrong.
I know what I'm doing..
We can't talk now.
I'm looking for Major Søgaard.
Has anyone seen him?
No just looking for my wallet?
..and the bloke looks at him coldly and says..
"Oh..I thought you might have been the
bastard that shit on my tortoise."
Hello.
I've left messages all day.
This is the last day with the soldiers.
We run a fairly tight schedule.
I have a few questions about your
deployment with Team Aegir.
My deployment again..
Should we talk about it here?
I have to go to the toilet. You can come
if you want. Or We'll meet outside after.
Go ahead. Ask away.
But I know nothing more than the Colonel.
You must have heard the
soldiers' explanation.
I can't tell you anything
you don't already know.
The soldiers spoke of an officer Perk.
There was no officer.
Nobody called Perk.
And there was no distress signal.
The leader sent the group into action
without receiving confirmation.
You don't like Raben?
I didn't say that. He was a good soldier
How can you be sure nothing happened?
I led the operation to extract
Raben's group out of that shit.
So you were one of the first
to arrive at the village?
That's right.
And you didn't see anything?
I wouldn't say that..I saw..
three dead soldiers... The rest wounded.
But I didn't see any civilians...
...dead or alive.
You were decorated and promoted.
Did it have anything to do with that?
We saved the rest of the group.
If something happened in the village,
does it fall under your responsibility?
If something had happened,
it was no big deal.
War is dirty.
Innocents die.
The politicians sent us off to the front
to avoid blood on their hands.
Yes.
Lund here.
You should have checked Søgaards alibi.
Where was he at the time of the killings.
We have checked all the officers,
commissioned since 1996.
There's no one called Perk.
But some recruits were trained by
a lieutenant they called 'Perk'.
Okay.
His real name is Per K. Moller.
He was with the Aegir Team.
Do you have his address?
Thank you very much.
Monberg was a guest lecturer
when Dragsholm was going to university.
They may have had a relationship
before she applied for the army position.
I hope you were'nt too rough
on the Minister of Defense?
I've been trying to call you.
Where is he?... He's inside.
We can't talk about the case.
No, I need to see him.
This is important.
Thank you.
I want to talk to you.
Got a minute? ...Yes of course.
I just want to say thanks.
We have to see everything
as part of a greater cause.
I will suggest to the Prime Minister
that he makes a clean breast of it all.
Good to know that you are on-side.
Buch...
Karina.
You should take it up with Plough.
There's a connection between Monberg
and the old military issue in Afghanistan.
The lawyer complained to him that the
soldiers' version of events was ignored.
Monberg knew about it.
We've already discussed that.
I used the computer
to cross check the names on the list...
...that was provided by the ministry.
You shouldn't use that computer.
You don't have authority to access that data.
It was a Defence case, but the Minister
of Justice talked to some of the soldiers.
One of the soldiers he met was
Jens Peter Raben.
There's no record of that meeting.
But the Minister of Defence Minister
did convene the meeting.
Buch, we're waiting for you.
Come on, baby.
They were Per Kristian sunglasses,
his favorite. They were...
Please have a seat.
My husband is overseas, but maybe I can help.
When did your son die?
In May, about two years ago.
In May?
Yes.
It was a blasting accident.
He died three months before the others.
I tried to persuade him
to find another profession.
But he liked the army. He wanted to
travel and make a difference.
For a time, we heard
almost nothing from him.
Not until they phoned
and told us what had happened.
But he got the funeral he wanted.
Thanks for your time.
Do you have anything to do
with the investigation?
A lawyer came out here some time
ago and asked the same question.
A lawyer..?
We still have his stuff.
Sometimes we think of throwing it out
but then we change our minds.
The lawyer only wanted to examine his
documents about the accident.
But when I came back, she was
rummaging through his things.
She asked all sorts of questions.
About the funeral and stuff.
About the funeral?
She was very concerned...
that we hadn't seen him.
Seen him where?
In the coffin.
We would liked to have seen him,
but they said it was best not to.
Who said that?
Captain Søgaard and the chaplain.
They said that you couldn't
see your son in the coffin?
Where is he buried?
Down here in the cemetery.
I have a picture of the grave...
...if you want to see it.
Yes please..
Dragsholm was on the same trail as us.
Søgaard claimed he didn't know Perk.
I think he's covering for him.
Lund he died three months before
the Raben platoon incident.
Søgaard didn't let them see the corpse...
...If he's actually dead.
He was blown to pieces of course
they shouldn't see the corpse
There's only one way to find out for sure..
We need to dig up the coffin
to see if anyone is in it.
You'd better leave.
Jens?
I never really did believe in God.
It always seemed very strange.
If God exists, what's the point
with everything that's happened?
I'd quite like to believe.
But it's not easy. Do you understand?
Let's go to the police.
You better take this from me.
I don't know what I was thinking.
You're doing the right thing.
I just have to get dressed.
Chaplain?
K. Møller
Rest in Peace
Subtitles re-edited by DG