Ten days ago a woman was
killed in unusual circumstances
How many will follow me in death?
What does Intelligence have on the
group? Raben was the squad leader.
They were praised for their work there.
I want to see that place.
There was no officer.
There were no corpses.
The Taliban don't wear gold.
It couldn't possibly have
been a suicide bomber.
This is nonsense.
I understand that you've resigned.
You've got the wrong man.
My wife and son are in the barracks.
Someone hid the radio messages.
Who?
We've searched everywhere.
There are no bodies.
Denmark woke up to the biggest
government crisis in recent history.
The Prime Minister sacked
the Minister of Defence because...
... he was the chief architect behind the
cover-up of civilian killings in Afghanistan.
These killings appear to be linked
to the terrorism-related murders.
We're on our way. Bye.
Bilal has fled in a jeep. There's increased
surveillance at all border crossings
Raben's wife has disappeared
from the barracks along with Bilal.
There's no trace of Raben, but in his
condition he can't interfere very much.
That's certainly true. Where's Brix?
Bilal rented the apartment where
he planned the five murders.
Brix is waiting for us.
See you there.
Lund... What gives? You haven't
said a word all the way home.
What's wrong?
Hello, hello.
How sweet of you
to come and pick us up.
Where have you been?
Prague. It was bang on.
What did you do?
I had a horrible dream.
I dreamed you were lying dead
somewhere. I couldn't revive you.
I cried and Mark cried.
I'll get the car.
I'll be glad when you finish work.
Bjørn and I will come to visit you
in Gedser.
It's Lund.
Where did that nice man go?
We found the remains of two adults
and two children in an oven...
...which was hidden under debris, well
concealed, clearly not wanting to be found
Well done, Lund.
I've forwarded your fax.
Each skull had a bullet hole.
Everything points to murder.
Did you find anything on Bilal?
Not too much, he wasn't the focus..
We found Per K. Møller's ID tags
...also hidden in the oven..
...the officer Raben saw.
Did you ask if anyone had seen him?
Did we get a list of the commandos?
That's not our concern anymore.
The civilian killings will be
investigated by the army.
We're not finished with that
officer. I saw what he did.
There was something ritualistic about it,
that resembled the killings here at home.
That's not now the focus Lund.
The suspect may still be a commando.
In theory it may still be Strange.
Check Bilal.
Brix...I think we should leave.
Mama... It was a nightmare, right?
Everything is okay.
We found the key to the apartment
together with a mobile...
...and the five broken ID tags.
There are no other tenants in
the building.
It's only used as a garage for storage
and stuff.
Maybe we should wait for Strange.
No, let's just move on it.
Camera, disks, computer, explosives
..evidence connected with the murders.
We found the murder weapon used on
Dragsholm and the chaplain.
It's their DNA.
Bilal is a Muslim.
His hatred of the Islamists is greater
than anyone ever imagined.
He hates Islamists more than anyone.
He saw Raben's unit as traitors because...
...they wanted to reveal the civilian killings.
Bilal came up with the Moslem League...
and tried to wipe out Kodmani's group.
He was inspired by military history.
Dragsholm was the first victim,
because she wanted to reopen the case.
They met a few months ago, and
he rented this place shortly after.
He arranged everything and used
hotmail and the name Per K. Møller.
He rented a post-box
with the same name.
How did Bilal know Per K. Møller?
From Team Aegir.
Has anyone seen Bilal coming and going?
Do we have his fingerprints, DNA?
He was very careful. It's very clean that way
The key is the only evidence
that links the murders to Bilal.
He got the colonel arrested because he
wanted to examine and destroy radio logs.
Afterwards, he left with Louise Raben.
Radio messages? The officer?
Isn't getting Bilal important enough for you?
He can lead us to the officer.
He doesn't have to be the murderer.
Why would Bilal hide the key and
the mobile at the barracks?
Who tipped you off and got you to do
a search?  You were in Afghanistan.
We still don't know who 'Faith brother'
was. Dragsholm said she found the officer.
We can't get the list of commandos.
Lund..all the evidence we need is all here
This proves nothing. Raben was right.
He accused Strange.
Lund! Because you went away, I
double-checked on Strange.
All the military authorities confirmed
independently that Strange was...
...demobilized a long time before.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
Perhaps because I haven't slept.
Jet lag.
I have a feeling that there's
something about me you like.
But you have a strange way
of showing  it.
Now we've cleared the air, so...
Of course I'm sorry if...
Where do we go from here?
We need to find Bilal?
Yes. We must also question Søgaard
about the radio messages.
If it's Bilal, it must be
because he hates the Islamists.
The video was posted
exactly as Ramadan ended.
The man must be an extremist
in the opposite direction.
If it is Bilal, he didn't have to go very far
to get the idea...
The Muslim league.
His jeep was seen on the bridge,
heading towards Fynen.
Any clues? No. She was focussed
on the same thing as you.
My daughter is missing.
What are you doing to find her?
Bilal may be hiding more?
Ask military HQ.
Do you know where Bilal is?
No, otherwise I'd go there.
Are we ready?
Did you know he hates Islamists?
We fought the same enemy.
He seemed to be the perfect soldier.
Look! It seems to look different now.
Let us know if you hear anything...
...also about Jens Peter Raben.
Well, Jonas...get your coat.
Are you going outside to play.
Go with Joakimand and his parents...
...to take a trip to the zoo.
When you get back, mom will be here.
I know. Dad says that too.
It's a secret.
He's waiting for you outside at the gate.
Did the police find anything?
The police don't know a damn thing.
Bilal isn't in any of the buildings.
You must have an idea.
It's Jarnvig. Hold on.
Have you contacted the barracks?
Stay away.
We need to help each other.
It's your fault!
She tried to help you.
Stay away.
You've caused enough misery. Hello?
We have to fight the enemy.
The enemy isn't us.
Where are you?
I've only done my duty.
Where is Louise?
I'm not to blame.
Bilal, come back.
Why did you betray me?
No. The police found evidence.
Someone is trying to frame me make
it look like it was me.
You need to come in and we can deal..
Call General Arild and say he needs to
get me out of here, right now.
Give up now..
Let me talk to Louise.
Let me talk to the general
We won't do a damn thing until we hear her voice.
Louise...
We drove three or four hours.
Somewhere remote..
You fucking pig..
I'll call you tonight. If you
contact the police, she dies.
She said they drove 3 - 4 hours.
Somewhere remote..
Where can that be?
Maybe a military facility.
There are a number in Zealand,
but they're only an hour away.
Bilal, let me go.
Bilal What's wrong with you?
The prime minister knew I had something
on him. The Minister of Defence...
...wanted to reveal everything at the
meeting, but the Prime Minister blamed us.
He will stop at nothing to avert blame
from himself and push it on me and  Rossing
The Minister of Defence refuses
to speak about any of it
How could the Prime Minister know?
He was warned.
You detained me overnight for no reason.
Is national security not reason enough?
I haven't compromised national security..
Let's take the key points one by one.
A confidential Intelligence memo
was leaked from your office.
That has never been proved..
You talked to a suspended police officer.
Sarah Lund.  About what?
It was her mothers wedding..
You visited Frode Monberg, who
subsequently took his own life.
Your secretary accessed information illegally from
another department at your behest...
You undermined Intelligence
investigations.
You even had König fired.
You defended Islamist associations.
You had contact with a person
inside the PFLP...
Who..when?
...a journalist, formerly employed by
Ministry of Defence, Connie Vemmer.
Everything indicates that during
war-time you have undermined...
the elected Government
and our democracy.
Whether Afghan civilians were slain,
has nothing to do with it.
Do you maintain your accusations
against the prime minister?
No. I'll go even further.
He's the traitor.
What's going on here?
Tell me what's going on...
Are you okay?
Yes. What happened?
We've been informed of a discovery
in Afghanistan, as you shall see.
Found by Sarah Lund. The police are
currently looking for a Danish soldier.
He committed the murders, to prevent
the investigation of civilian killings.
And the officer who did this?
The military is working on it.
It's going to come out now..Why
didn't they find the bodies at first?
I'll arrange a meeting
without the Prime Minister.
I think right now we have something solid
You can get what you want
if you play your cards right.
The Prime Minister is fireproof and in a strong
position.The Minister of Defence withheld ...
I heard that yesterday.
It was the Prime Minister who
ordered you out of here.
Well let's get his wishes followed quickly.
So..let's meet with the group.
Are you back in parliament?
Do you support the government?
Will you continue your accusations?
What did Intelligence say?
Hello, Buch. Good to see you.
Yes, thanks. Good to see you too.
Excuse the mess. I've been busy
I've been away.
Yesterday, we had our problems.
But the need to protect the party was paramount.
At the expense of truth?
lndeed. But now we know a lot more.
We want to give you
an unreserved apology.
Excellent. We must look forward
and act to do something quickly.
There are two possibilities. Either
the Prime Minister resigns...
in the face of this unacceptable cover
up and does the right thing
and he falls on his sword, or we
gather up enough support..
...and we force him to do so.
Start the process, Gita ring round and find out how
many party MP's want to get rid of him.
There will have to be a dissolvement and elections
Yes, of course that's how it works..
It's not necessary.
The Minister of Defence said
Gert is the architect behind this.
I am right to do demand..
Don't you understand that nothing is
going to stick to the Prime Minister
The way it stands is that Rossing is prepared to take
all the blame and not say a word about it
...and your predecessor, Monberg,
is also to blame 100% all the way
Minister..you can't win on this,
we can't defeat him.
The Prime Minister wants to talk to you.
He's planning a cabinet shuffle.
Rumour has it that you'll get
a nice promotion.
You don't want to dissolve this corrupt
parliament. Get out of here.
Buch..listen.
I understand you're happy with your job.
An election now would shatter the party.
Buch, I'll have a word with Krabbe.
Yes, you seem to side with Krabbe a lot..
Is he the best hope we have as a
guardian of our democracy?
Krabbe is fully in line with the Prime
Minister.  Until I've talked to him.
Thank you very much. Good luck. Bye.
Thank's for coming..come come come come.
It can't be Bilal, I've known
him since training school
Do you know any contacts?
Friends, family?
None outside the military. It can't
possibly be Bilal.
Our technicians have examined all the logs and
confirmed that some messages were deleted.
So someone who knew their way around
the system could have done it
Who was responsible?
Yes, Bilal. But...
...there were civilian killings.
And there was an officer.
Bilal covered up reports.
Tell us what you know.
I didn't know about the messages.
Like you never knew or
talked to Dragsholm.
You'll have to ask Bilal.
You must've known about the
message five days earlier.
No, wasn't my remit
Commandos went into that village for a reason
Who were those people, why were they killed
No idea. Did Dragsholm
mention commandos?
Did they withdraw? Was someone left at the village?
I don't know, dammit.
The killer called himself Per K. Møller and
used that identity. Did Bilal know him?
Not personally.
Was Bilal there when he died?
No.
Was anyone there from the commandos?
I don't think so.
He was alone when the incident happened,
and was brought to the ISAF hospital.
The Military Hospital in Lashkar Gar?
Yes. I think so.
And if he had ID tags on?
It's usual they would..
...be taken off and sent to
relatives or placed in the coffin.
Lund...
Hey, what's happening? Hello!
They've found the jeep on Fynen.
Bilal switched license plates on the jeeps.
We've bugged Jarnvig's phone.
Bilal called him from north of Copenhagen,
we're working on a precise location now..
What did Bilal say?
The Colonel had to find the
solution to the situation.
The Colonel and Raben are
working together on this now
We'll try to stop them.
Bilal will have a place to hide.
What military bases are in that area?
Look for something remote, out of the way
There's a deserted military
facility from the Cold War era.
Has it been checked?
Get in touch with Fred Holst. He's a
doctor at the ISAF hospital in Lashkar Gar.
Ask if he can find out what
happened to Per K's ID tags.
We need to know if they
were with the body
Lund..come on now.
Oh, ask him to check if there were any commandos
hospitalised the same time or before the incident
Yes, I'm on it..
We can't keep looking. Call the police.
Drive on.
Arild may negotiate
something with Bilal.
We're going through.
He's not here, damn.
Stop!
Get the police.
The People's Party won't support
the government at any price.
We always go for the truth.
You're welcome. What now?
I've already spoken with you.
I wanted to call you,
but I have a meeting.
Tell me you'll join the opposition
and overthrow the government.
Krabbe, We had an agreement. The Prime
Minister can't be allowed to stay on.
They've found evidence of civilian killings which
the Prime Minister must have known about..
The Minister of Defence has already accepted
responsibility and he takes the blame, ok.
Krabbe...Krabbe..
Hey. Hello...Krabbe wait..
What's going on?
The polls were favourable when Muslims
were thought to be the killers.
I had lots of discussions
with the press about it.
In retrospect, perhaps it wasn't
such a good idea.
I don't think resorting to elections
is the wisest course right now.
Thomas, I don't know yet.
I refuse to give it all to the opposition
without thinking about it first.
Your grandfather was in the Resistance.
You said he fought for rights and freedoms..
The Prime Minister did what?
He dismissed the Minister of Defense....
...once he knew the truth.
Did you brief him? I informed you,
then you went to the Prime Minister...
...because you were scared to death
of those idiotic polls.
What are you talking about?
I was at a party meeting all day.
You're the only one I told, beside
my confidants.
You know, Thomas?
You can't trust anyone.
It's not the first time your personnel
have been led down the garden path.
I'll call you.
The Prime Minister wants to meet.
I said no.
Who prepared the papers yesterday?
Plough.
What about here, any secretaries?
No, why?
So nobody here who may have alerted
the prime minister about the papers?
No, I had the documents while Plough
was over in the Cabinet Office.
It was about the post in Skopje.
Ask him when he returns, he'll be back soon
On my first day here I found a file in my
papers about the Dragsholm murder.
Monberg's Intelligence memo...
Could anyone have leaked it?
No..no..Plough said it had
vanished into thin air.
Where's the information on the
group of soldiers?
Thomas, what's going on?
Did Plough say anything to you about the
soldiers or the Minister of Defense?
No. Why?
What's going on?
Thomas..Plough was angry at the Minister of Defence.
He didn't care if you went after the Prime Minister.
Plough couldn't have done it.
Does Plough have a son?
Yes. But he died last year.
In a car accident?
I still have a chauffeur,
so call and say that I'm coming.
They're down there. He has my daughter.
Where is Raben?
He went after him.
Is he armed?
Monitor all the exits.
Tell Brix that nobody should go in.
Louise!
Step forward, so I can see you.
Step forward, or I'll put
a bullet in her head.
Put the gun down
Where's the colonel?
He said you wouldn't look for me.
Let her go. Now you have me.
Just kept your mouth shut.
There were no civilian casualties.
They were Taliban collaborators.
Bilal, calm down. Put the gun away.
We're going to talk about it.
Put the gun down. We'll go outside
and talk about it.
I've only done my duty.
She has nothing to do with it.
She's innocent.
I can only help you,
if you let her go now.
Go.
I've only done my duty.
What exactly did you do?
You hid radio messages.
Do you know who the officer was?
Put it down now..
Good.
Lund, something's wrong.
Come. Now we'll walk out of here.
Lund!
For God, king and country.
Plough...
Plough?
His name was Hans Christian.
Hans Christian Vedel Plough.
Vedel after my wife.
In the army he was called HC.
He was one from the group who got out.
He escaped with superficial wounds.
But when he came home, we discovered
he had a problem.
He said there had been
an episode in the village.
Something about an officer
and civilian killings.
We supported the investigation which
concluded that it didn't happen.
My son's demeanor changed.
And he became increasingly ill.
A year ago, he drove into
oncoming traffic on the highway...
...and was killed.
My marriage broke down,
and I buried myself in debt.
Until the lawyer Dragsholm reappeared...
...to meet with my minister.
She had a breakthrough in the case.
She identified the officer.
I suddenly realised...
...that my son had told the truth.
I trusted Monberg, when he said
he would do something about it.
But Dragsholm was killed
and nothing happened.
Instead, he tried to end his life.
I put you on the track of the cover-up.
I leaked the Intelligence memo.
I made sure Karina took Monberg's private calendar.
Made sure that you found it out and would act.
Dammit Plough, you should have given
the information to the police.
I had no choice. The Minister
of Defence pulled strings.
I had no proof until yesterday.
It was a relief for me...
...to give it to the Prime Minister.
He responded decisively.
Very different from you.
Why were you so sure?
Monberg told me that....
...he had discussed it
with the Minister of Defense.
When he returned,
the case was closed.
Thanks for the loan.
It wasn't exactly my taste.
Too bad it's over for me,
but you and Karina will do fine.
The meeting about the anti-terrorism
package will be in the cabinet office .
You'll be the crown prince. Karina will take over
the Ministry. I'll go to the New York consulate.
It was in Monberg's private calendar.
If someone put a lid on the matter,
it was the Prime Minister.
Monberg said it was the Minister
of Defence. He had you fooled.
Do you want to know more?
What are you doing?
Now ,I think you should go.
You've helped the wrong way.
You helped the man who caused
your son's death.
The right people were punished
That was what I owed my son.
Go now, damn it!
The military prosecutor will believe
you this time.
You should drop all the accusations
against the policeman.
Your other accusations were true.
You were imprisoned for two years,
on false grounds.
Whatever punishment you get for your crimes ...
...any time that you have already served
falsely will be taken into consideration
...you've served too long
because of a mistake.
You can look forward to
being released very soon.
I encourage you to sue for damages.
Can we have some privacy here?
Of course.
I have more good news. You will
be transferred to Horserød...
...where you'll have a family home,
so you can be together.
We'll talk.
I'll do anything.
Not necessarily.
I just want you to come home.
Every stone in that village must be
turned over. Keep me informed.
Any news about General Arild?
No. The new team is meeting tonight.
They'd like to welcome you back General.
Thanks, but I'll do ok by myself.
Your daughter wants to talk to you.
She's over at the house, packing.
We're leaving now.
Where to?
Up to Jens. We've been allowed
to be with him tonight.
We need to get away from here.
Where are you staying then?
We'll arrange that with his dad,
Jonas huh?
See you, Dad.
Be good.
I'm going.
Come on, baby.
Hello there..
I'm glad that nothing happened
to Louise.
What a story. Bilal made sure
that none of us knew anything.
Not even you?
No.
If you know something,
you need to tell me now.
I'll do everything I can
to get this mess cleared up.
It's a bit more complicated than that.
What's so complicated
Either you lied to me, the police and the
whole world. Or not.
The police didn't get any information...
...until we thought there had been
civilian killings.
What are you saying?
The police suspected a single commando.
I confirmed that
he had been sent home.
But it wasn't the whole truth.
He was sent there again shortly after.
But the mission was top secret.
Therefore, all the radio messages were
deleted. There's no evidence of his existence.
I checked his CV
when the police asked questions.
The guy was missing for a few days...
...but that doesn't
make him a war criminal.
We had received intelligence that the
father was a Taliban sympathizer.
Stop
You should've never shown up here
again. Stay away from my people.
Is that understood?
I'll put in a good word for you so you
can continue to stay at the barracks.
Make sure the next team
is as strong as the last one was.
The lawyers would like to see the
files. Can we take them? Of course.
Did the doctor in Lashkar Gar get
my message?
He has your number.
Should I contact him again?
No. It doesn't matter. But there
actually was something else.
When we searched the barracks
the first time, a few days ago.
Why didn't we find anything there?
There was nothing. Bilal planted it later
Did you check the room and the locker?
Yes, we searched everywhere.
Did you find out how
Dragsholm located the officer?
No. We've reviewed her records.
Meetings with clients, lawyers and police.
Meetings with the police?
Yes. With the prosecutors office.
So she had contacted us
before she was murdered?
Not about any of this.
She didn't want contact with the police.
She had a private security service.
Hmm..yes I guess so..
Can I have the box?
Who led the first search in the barracks,
near the lockers?
I don't know anymore.
Wasn't it Strange? Think now..
Yes, it was Strange. Why?
Can I have that box?
Yes.
Lund...The powers that be told me that
I should commend you. Well done!
I had my doubts when Brix sent for you.
And that continued after I met you.
Chances are that you won't be sent
back to Gedser. Congratulations.
Brix...
The day Strange was at the refugee
center in Elsinore...
Was it checked?
When I ran after the offender.
Yes. we were busy..
but it was checked.
Where is he?
He's driving Raben to Horserød...What now?
Lennart... are you going to say goodbye
to my husband? He has to leave early
Don't look disappointed.
I'll take him back.
Go up and get yourself a beer.
Are you sure?
He's no longer difficult. Just save one for me.
I'm going.
Okay.
We need to talk. Let me drive.
What?
Give me the key.
Yes, yes.
Shall we hear some music?
You have something to talk about?
Later.
I'll show you something.
Okay.
Horserød is straight ahead.
My wife and son are waiting for me.
What is it?
There's something wrong.
I think Brix is hiding something.
Brix?
Come on, let's go.
Lund, dammit. What now?
Lund!
I want to be alone with you,
but it's not very romantic.
This is a memorial for resistance
fighters. War Heroes...
...for whom Bilal had great respect.
Yes?
He would never put Dragsholm here.
He saw her as a traitor. Whoever beat...
...Dragsholm and the others to death
wouldn't care about such things.
What does Brix have to do with that?
Brix is protecting the murderer.
What?
Dragsholm was scared before she
was killed. She lived right over there.
The house was packed with alarms.
She had sensors installed in the garden.
She had her own private security.
But she didn't call the police
a single time.
Maybe she was under protection.
No.
She found the captain, the officer...
...and found out he worked for us.
That explains her silence.
That explains why we found the mobile at the barracks
when the search was conducted by him
Although we had searched just a few days earlier
and it wasn't found. Can't you see it?
The perpetrator planted
those things during the search.
But Lund ... I led the search.
I didn't plant anything.
Good. Then it must be someone
on the other team.
I don't know what to say.
Have you talked to Brix about this?
No. Not yet.
He'll send me back to Gedser.
Okay, so I think we have to talk with Brix.
You'll definitely not go back to Gedser.
But until then we'll maintain...
...that Bilal dragged her over the
railway yard and hung her up.
Ok, Come on. Let's get going.
How do you know...?
...that she was dragged over the track?
We never found that out.
Come on, that's...
What do you mean?
Why?
I was at a minor court in summer.
It was hot.
She saw my tattoo.
I don't know why,
but she started asking questions.
Like you...
Yes? Holst here.
Is Sarah Lund there?
She is just away for a moment.
What's it about
I'm calling from Afghanistan. I am a
physician at the ISAF military hospital.
I haven't found out anything about the ID tags.
I'll let her know.
However,  a commando was hospitalised...
at the same time from a different unit...
...with some wound's but he was soon flown back home.
Fine. Thank you.
It may not be true.
I was with him every day.
Plough was only thinking of revenge.
He must have said something...
Not a damn thing.
No, Plough believes
he did the right thing.
Thomas, we know it was the Prime Minister.
After all you've been through
you can't give it up now
I do give a damn what Plough
is arranging for my future.
I won't give up.
Good. What do we do?
Just a moment.
The press is ready and the ministers
are arriving for the meeting.
Say we're coming. Line up as many
microphones as possible.
Hi, Thomas. Come inside.
We'd like to present the Ministerial
re-shuffle this evening.
I'm just glad I can talk to you.
I'm sorry for that night with Intelligence.
I owe you an explanation.
I won't listen to your explanation.
Keep your ministerial post.
Plough has told me.
He also talked about my predecessor
and the Minister of Defence.
I'll unveil it at the press conference.
The turn of parliament, the police
and Intelligence comes later.
I'm going to give them
every confidential document.
You covered up the murders.
People were killed because
of your political ambitions.
I know you're behind it.
And I'm going to prove it.
We haven't covered up civilian killings.
We could probably survive if we had...
The public can forgive anything..
The officer was the problem.
The officer wasn't there.
The incident occurred during a top secret mission.
We didn't have
parliamentary approval.
Commando missions require
Reality is, it's impossible.
It's not five minutes before the info
is on the streets in Kabul.
You've always known.
You knew who the officer was.
I had to choose. It wasn't difficult.
At that time, we lacked
money and troops.
You could have stopped it
there and then...Get real!
We're at war!
What could we do?
Can discussions and a show of hands
make inroads in the fight against terrorism?
Will a scandal console families whose
sons have come home in coffins?
The Taliban is getting stronger.
At times we need to ignore democracy...
...to carry on the struggle
FOR democracy.
You ought to be the first
to appreciate that.
I appointed you because I figured you were
harmless. But now I want to keep you.
If you think I've made mistakes,
help me so it doesn't happen again.
You're insane.
When I tell this to Krabbe
and the public, you're finished.
Go ahead.
But there's nothing to tell.
And you won't be alone this evening
when the new cabinet is sworn in.
Say hello to the MPs who agree
the most important thing is...
...that we continue the fight.
You beat them all to death.
Killing an innocent is better than
having doubts about killing the enemy.
Haven't you learned that yet?
You can't get away with it here.
I've escaped from worse things.
And it was you who shot the little girl.
You left that out of your statement.
You forgot it.
You're lying.
You shot her.
Suddenly you began to snivel.
Don't you remember it? Well?
What? What?
It's Strange. Raben has escaped.
He's shot Lund.
Raben, take the gun.
Don't move.
Stay down.
Subtitles re-edited by DG