yeah
what's the hang-up Beltran's well this
here Cal worth of the niner you can
search me
hello Mac Mac this is kelly coming I
want to talk to you
hey Mac beautiful sure
Buckingham Palace you know this place
used to be a refueling station during
World War two but there hasn't been
anybody here since i can't imagine why
Dutch six square miles of lush tropical
garden spot
Hey look what I expect we are only 200
miles off the coast of africa right all
right let's go get you some help
Veronica Lake
what what man who this is Veronica Lake
did you ever hear of Veronica Lake
I want to taste them this check was cool
before they invented the word
come on let's get out of here kill is
gonna be on channels are supposed to be
fixing up you know what I better small
life magazines around here
all right fellows what's the story a
coach , save I that used to be in all
Explorer Scout ya can't seem to break
the habit
yeah where you follows were being paid
to hack out of base camp Warburton's
drilling crews not rummaging around you
see if you can find the side of that
benign
ok ok don't get uptight hire the best
look at your job done on schedule only
got five days left
good point out
go wrap up my big yellow baby you do
that
come on Dutch let's go Veronica Lake
careful
yeah
I want you to get Beltran hand on the
access road
ok
yeah
ok sweet on destroy
ok
yeah
what's the matter want to come out funny
like a rock here
yeah but telling that's much of
geological formation
maybe we've uncovered Captain Kidd's
treasure well whatever it is it's gonna
have to come out
you sound like the dentist show you how
it's done kid
yeah
get back
hey what's the matter boy
hey man what happened
back
yeah
how could I don't get it
what was Kelly doing anyway haul was
pushing for driving the d9 this max job
not Kelly's I got the guys going to die
you want me to hear you but somebody's
gotta do something
kelly's on the radio calling who look
the supply ship is four days out and
besides too slow
listen to a guy
he's a doctor in a hospital maybe the
company can arrange for mercy flight
land where will you shut up
we can refine this trip as quick as they
can fly
we'll catch a patch me through to a
doctor
I don't care ghana library anywhere as
long as he speaks English
many ships in the area will call me back
when you do know what will be on the
moon
any chance of a plane still can't figure
it happened
our wire
yeah
how's it going -
are you doing about getting back to a
hospital still gotta talk
sure plenty of time later my know now
alone
what do you have to say to this joker if
it wasn't for here
come on he's my buddy
you hang in there
here I'm sticking with you all the way
we all are
what you looking at
you heard the man
yeah
did you see it
see what I know exactly when you hit the
rock
I didn't say anything but it was there
when killed me Kelly
come on I'm telling you I saw was a
thing
oh man it was weird
unreal I never seen anything like a
shell you sure it's ok not lie back and
forget about it
I saw it jump when the blade at the rock
I'm I'm trying to warn you kelly blue
light
it's the blade
I ever tell you introduced him to his
girl in a halloween party back in the
States
yeah but I call her up ahead of time see
and I said honey put on to mass so when
Matt took off the first mask he saw the
second with visit
I said to Mac I said well what did I
tell you
not much of one looks but terrific
personality so what do you think
since his death would you like to play
dump the apples is it certainly he said
with your head i said no way
yeah
don't go in there touch
yeah I want to be with my friends with
Kelly said nation
I don't care what Kelly said what was so
important
nothing
going to get a top
gonna have to bury him for the time
being
is that all you guys
what's a good touch
he's playing in his own way
like a nice cute
yeah
ok
be sure to have a priest for mac they'll
send him back so he spoke can do a
proper server
Dennis gonna grace us with his presence
Kelly's bringing in the niner so we can
work on her tonight I haven't seen
damaged
Dennis doesn't put himself out even for
Dennis where should he care about Mac
him and I and make everybody can maybe a
fellow could care less if he knew how
somebody died
don't read something that isn't there
dead it doesn't help anyone least of all
mac i liked him
chub miss people I like
can we say goodbye now
sorry
you only get one shot at mackay
what do you say his trip was sure to
short rest in peace me
we'd better going to turn in
be working later getting a head start on
tomorrow
yeah
ok
only one way to say goodbye to an
Irishman right
yeah Mac you'd like that
here you
you know invest
did I ever
man that was those crazy beautiful kid
and I worked together on his first job
you know job I sort of showed me the
ropes only did you learn quick
listen let me tell you behind that young
face he was about as green as your
average fire truck
I remember this time we're working down
and Sansa bar you know and it's hot man
is it hot
so we get done and we go at the local
saloon we're going to relax a little bit
have a little coconut juice
so we're sitting in through the door
walk through the local talent
well that gives the eye I look at Matt
macbook is that bang the kids gone like
a shot
I turn around hey
ok what do you think you're doing well
somebody's gotta do it
not much kinda rough on you since when
would you care
sorry mostly science fiction
yeah he ate it up
no sweat
it's got me really stronger
where'd that come from
for having one for mac and returning in
no problem
better make it fast because nobody's
sleeping late tomorrow
I was Luud no one special occasion
nobody's going to report you to the
company for one little shot
the bars closed
yeah
what do you mean reporting to the
company
he's a dried-out drunk making good with
his job his last chance with the company
you're a real sweetheart what's wrong
Kelly you always used to know when to
bear down and when do you that work on
human
well then remember we are - yeah you're
right
how did you get that would be murder
I want you to check her out in the
morning and I mean good
why what's wrong you find out and then
you tell me
air let me do that give me some clue
I don't like the way she is
yeah
I'm telling you was a fluke accident
Bonnie
there was no negligence now listen you
two or Burton nobody's let them down
got my personal guarantee that this job
is coming in right on the money money
one more thing you notified McCarthy's
mother
yeah well I want somebody to go over
there personally I don't want to get in
some lousy telegram right
ok yeah same time tomorrow
hey Kelly Kelly
what you're fine nothin
you sure well I found the compression
lever wire down the drain cox opened the
air intake blocked in the main fuel line
cut
yeah I'll come because I didn't want her
going anywhere you sure made sure when
you saw this
remember that 99 m greater we had nobody
could handle
yep I think we got another it's a
possibility
still if you say she's okay
well they're there was one thing
come here right here listen you hear
that i couldn't locate whatever is
causing it
probably not important
Beltran came by asking for up at
tomorrow pit where he's just gonna have
to make do with the d4
I don't want anybody taking this machine
out until I give the green light ok you
holding back on me
yeah i guess i am for right now well
when the time comes
yeah
maybe I better move your cut into the
8th ed so we can get some work done
around here
no or a government job then get at it
now i'm getting tired of your attitude
and I'm tired of being kept in the dark
what's this with its funny blue light
I'm no piece of candy you're a horrible
yeah the best shovel operator you'll
ever have
not back to the blue light
I'm listening
you breathe one word you didn't take
back seriously it was all of his hand
yeah
makes sense
till last night I wanted I could have
sworn a d9 blade moved to my 12
you better be more careful
yeah
ok
hmm
yeah
makes you wonder
ok how did it happen don't give us none
of that about the d9 are going haywire
we want to know
I don't know what you were there you saw
it
maybe you were seeing pink elephants -
Kelly mcanally dead get off his back I
saw belt and lose control and go plowing
into that radio before the thing ran
away with it must be bailed out
you saw by the tracks how he got it what
more do you need a logical explanation
you know he's got to come up with one
sooner or later it's gonna have to be
later because it's an ir daylight left
and there's work to be done so let's get
at it huh
you believe that guy
yeah
g dennis is real tough you know
I mean beltran and his wife just
starting to plan a family
hey
you know what I'd like to do I'd like to
go swimming
me and Mac used to go swimming weeks
when all the time mostly at night
spliced around like a couple of
seventeen  people
used to think we were crazy
you were crazy you have to be crazy to
be in this business right
live hard laughs hard cuz
hey Dennis come on this one
yeah come on right now we can go job
well we rounded lips send out for some
pizza
yeah
Kelly but Beltran
what exactly did you see
then go straight up
d Niner was operating by itself when it
ran him down
throttling pivoting floating the blade
I don't know how some malfunction and
the controls you seen rogue machine we
operate before
look I heard McCarthy - I'm trying to
warn you it a blue light my god it was
there in the blade
you don't believe that the question is
to you know touch trackpad boys often
get some sleep and out
los around I don't you start Hell that
you can't play ostrich that benign as
harmless now sort of fuel or right up
out there somewhere
so we leave it being that the company
engineers come in and find the box and
it later
and if you're wrong tomorrow is going to
be another top day
you better get some sleep
yeah
review boom
I don't believe that was hilarious I saw
the d Niner operating all by itself
you're paid to work you saw - did you
when it got belted him for good
you know I suppose it's possible for two
guys to have the same hallucination but
for two guys as different as you and me
he never listened post driver got a
completion date no I haven't got time I
fed we're up against something we can't
fight until we can figure it out
I picked up a piece of that rocket you
hit
what about it you know geology better
than me
look close and tell me if you ever saw
anything like it
meteorite maybe all the love of God man
we face it to us are dead
what does it take to make a believer out
of you another one all rights are ball
what do you think I should we gotta
level with the other guys
assuming there is something inside that
dozer we find it and destroy it
how we got plenty of dynamite are you
crazy
that denied her clothes 90
ok come on
you see Dennis bail out of bed this
morning
knob so so in your friend Kelly you're
up to something I mean for them not us
I think the pressures got to both of
them are looking out for number one and
two
I think there's mac thing bought you a
bad dream what bad dream
there are two graves down here on the
beach and there's lots of room for two
more less than Dutch for once and for
all you know there's not a more
experienced construction boss in the
business
so let's climb up this dumb dog and get
this thing back on a job
sure he's most experienced Boston and
business survival of management that's
what they call it
guys like us were expendable you better
take that paper bag off your head and
open up those trusting eyes you and meet
job
we're going to be on the beach pretty
soon stretched out check for little
bodies all in a row
yeah
job fair want to talk to you
and
yeah
Oh
push check it out and gas them all up
with you
yeah
there's food canned stuff to Jerry's of
water
that oughta hold still supply boat day
after tomorrow
hey Dutch will you shut that thing off
he's coming off this spool
remote control that's got to be it huh
that thing is running by remote control
listen
listen you guys we gotta do something
I mean something's wrong machines
machines
just don't run by themselves that means
there's somebody else on this island
you know foreign spies or something
about a mad scientist
no listen Dennis come on I'm serious
we're wasting away
there's gotta be a logical explanation
got him gassed up yeah
sure like to know what that day niners
run on
yeah so what are we going to get out of
here way to that high ground
we're not going after the d9 but until
we figure out how that dynamite didn't
face it
I still say it's remote control we can
move faster will hide and run gain time
until that ship shows up calling the
shots . you better ride with me
yeah
hey Dennis
did I ever tell you I played in the
Cotton Bowl 64 I caught two touchdown
yeah
ok
she won't make it any further up this
grade
I think we better take a look around up
there first
we don't want to get ourselves trapped
hey guys you want to laugh when you hear
the cockamamie story or dennys been
handed me
best we can do best man it's terrific
well the truth is we don't know anything
for a fact except that bulldozer kills
that's good enough for me you stay here
with Dutch sharp let's take a look
there's some logical explanation
hey Dennis
listen
want some music that thing can't hear
look maybe this isn't such a good idea
you know maybe would be smart to split
up
Kelly and chub you and me like teams and
we stand a better chance what do you say
why not every man for himself you
serious
we stick together
yeah
what about this slope you think the
designer can get up
given time it can make a road any word
wants to go
well then we'd better fight back what do
you think about building a signal far
maybe a airplane or a fishing boat might
yeah
chubs got an idea we ambush that dozer
run his truck into it and kapaa Fire
won't stop steal it will take out the
electrical systems in the rubber
hey that's beautiful I I got a feeling
we're going about this wrong
there's a good spot down the road about
a half a mile let's get down there and
set it up
yeah
ok
I'm beginning to get this you know sort
of like being on patrol in Vietnam
yeah sure
yeah
workout
job job
yeah
no matter wife Marjorie two boys in
college and a few good friends
yeah for what that was with i'll finish
yeah
do you believe that thing
what's it waiting for what - Terry
it knew that ambush
I knew what we were gonna do and it did
it first
at least you got out of touch I'm no
coward Kelly
I don't want to die but that's not being
a coward
of course it isn't
yeah
what if it comes
we call for artillery support we got
speed we running keep running until help
gets here might have been four days
we gotta fight to find some way to total
that thing you can't kill a machine
maybe we should appeal to his sense of
decency and fair play
you stink
all right come on be nice at all , but
yeah
wasn't bugging his head on the edge
sorry
k makes me snide we'll take your shirt
off i'll see what i can do mine i can
make it stop her alone
yeah
my script
hey
hear that hear one to serve
man oh man what I wouldn't give for a
moonlight swim you know
hey Dennis I ever tell you about the
time and Kuwait me and Mac we were
what's it doing out there
doing a war dance maybe it won't attack
at night like John Wayne's Indians
you're crazy coach he's crazy he's gonna
get us killed that thing is trying to
murder us a easy take it easy Dutch tell
you what about for medicinal purposes
only
huh hey right why don't you worm
stretch out and relax for a little while
we'll keep an eye on things and private
stock
might as well
Dutch put this back with you
you know you're finished with Warburton
even if we do get out of this thing is
going to be investigations asking for
things we don't have
like a logical explanation
so we tell them the truth like you did
after that and he's power plant she
asked oh I told him the truth then when
they crucified you for what did it cost
you job my reputation
you want a piece of advice never have
anything you care about losing travel
light and travel alone
that's the way you play and nobody
lasered love on me
long as you're happy
yeah
Dutch i'm going to swim and
ok
yeah
now you're gonna want
Wow
one
yeah
Wow
come on
yeah
ok
but she was right you can't kill a
machine but killing machine
hey wait a minute of course you can't
kill a machine
don't you see my mistake the thing
whatever that's what has to be stopped
how I don't know but there's a way it's
got to be a way
think man how do you go about killing on
a killer
it's too heavy to hang it's too big to
put in the gas chamber
electricity Berlin I'm serious
electrocution we should use to that big
dozer we got that generator but it's
damaged
maybe maybe not we need a conductor some
kind of spinning your wheels can or not
it will work
and that's what's going to make it work
come on sorry ball give me a hand
yeah
you got it straight
gonna make that dogs are charged the
greater he gets both treads on that grid
why I'm we pride like bacon assuming it
will come from that direction
I'll jockey the greater assuming it's
dumb enough to be sukkot you're going to
be at the generator ready to throw the
switch right
it doesn't work it has to be under
warranty
you know you may make it yet soluble
yeah
get down it's coming
ok
closer
come on
come on and get me
yeah
ok
listen
nothing
the homes gone the things dead but we're
not exactly home free
no I guess not all we got is our word
that the thing existed
you know we could fake things tell the
authorities the guys got caught in a
landslide
no tell the truth no matter what no
matter what and on about a hundred years
i might get to like you blow your own
philosophy
all i know is i'm sure glad to be alive
so my sorrel
yeah