[Music]
hi guys glad we got your message will be
interested to hear it was broadcast live
all over primetime got good reviews
trades the time lag on these messages is
getting longer we gather from the
10-year delay that you are approximately
18 parsecs away tropical I more often ok
sorry to hear about the radiation leak
on the ship and real sorry to hear about
the death of commander Powell there was
a week of mourning your honor flags were
have mass we're all behind you guys
about your request or radiation
shielding sorry to report this request
has been denied i hate to send bad news
when you guys are up there doing such a
swell job but I think you'll take it in
the proper spirit fencing cutbacks in
Congress and right now considering the
distance we just can't afford to send
the cargo shuttle out there to you but I
know you guys will make to keep up the
good work
[Music]
what I said I'm primary salvaged from an
intercom laughing diameter of
proclamation Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby
Bobby
oh oh oh yes a little what is it I need
a diameter approximation find a GF
reading reading check it is a of +1 back
a little
you're Jeff reading is minus fifteen
little hero
I need a fail-safe park in the second
file can you set me up with dr figures
97 million minus-8 corrected to mass
critical that checks out here just drive
reading 7,000 i read that bottom freezer
and back i had the computer reading it's
not 577 time to start talking
bombay systems operational
not feel safe
I'll safe and lock sergeant pinback
calling bomb number 19 here a bomb under
19 largest impacts I read you continue
well bomb we have about 60 seconds drop
just wondering if everything was alright
check your planetary energy fielding
function well let's synchronize
detonation time you wouldn't have known
you're supposed to go off with you
that's all right checks out here
arms up bomb well and everything sounds
dropping off about 35 seconds
good luck in primary alright our cab and
987654321 problem drive sequence begun
headed back racecourse
[Music]
Kendall it just exploded on the planet
just exploded sir lieutenant engine
tension ship's computer to log in now
the hyperdrive sequence is now
terminated target planet has been
destroyed sector is now kind of
colonization you have destroyed the last
unstable planet in this system
congratulations on another successful
Baumann nose but now we have four
snowboarder not much nothing at all in
this vector don't find me something I
don't care where it is
well I don't ninety-five percent
probability of intelligent life in the
Horsehead Nebula sector don't give me
that kind of bolt I know it's a long
shot but then wild-goose chase what is
everyone commander Powell found that 99
plus probability of intelligent life
been tryna cloud right there is a
possibility of what we found
I damn finals vegetable look like a limp
balloon 14 my ears vegetable or squawk
love think we don't remember that
alright that don't give me attitude
towards life stuff for me so I can blow
up the star and guess what i'm going to
start the readout record another unknown
a red war on the charge minutes
yeah ate it and you're very good and all
but again moment what the new Star we
can manage
who cares don't bother commander Powell
would have named it landed power is dead
little got a good unstable planet
eighty-five percent probability of an
unstable planet in the middle nebular
probably go up its orbit a star for it
off real good boy that's what I'm
looking for the course for the veil
nebula and back from the chatline let's
have some music in here boiler sure
thing
[Music]
sunshine down see
your face
desert skies
when
[Music]
the same but they seem so much
you
they seen so much
watch
now the ears of our young our role
pictures the only
r
three-ball towns in space
where we spent our last day is all mine
my
thank you
but they seem so much
ships log number 1943 darkstar cruising
at Lightspeed vector theta 990 enroute
avail nebular for construction of
unstable planet our ETA is 17 hours
ship's systems continue to deteriorate
oh you the short circuit in the rear
seat panel which killed commander powers
will fall the storage
because he's sitting next to Commander
policy to continues to bother pinback oh
yeah storage area 9 self-destructed last
week and destroyed the ships tire supply
of toilet paper
[Music]
attention attention ship's computer
calling all personnel I must disengage
your recreational music repeat ship's
computer to all personnel this is an
emergency override all systems must
stand by an asteroid storm is
approaching the ship on collision course
this asteroid storm appears to be bound
together by an electromagnetic energy
vortex like the one we ran into two
years ago
normally I wouldn't bother you boys with
this problem as you recall my defensive
circuits were destroyed another storm
therefore you have 35 seconds to
manually activate all defensive system
lock gravity system battery life on
track
block
[Music]
computer to bomb number 20
it turned to the bomb bay immediately
but i have received the operation of
signal it is a malfunction
this is not a bomb moon we are in a
crisis situation
return immediately nevertheless i have
received signal to prepare for drop
emergency override returned to the band
very well
[Music]
and
I'm mad
yeah attention attention ship's computer
to bridge there was a malfunction aboard
ship during the asteroid storm have not
yet identified the nature of the problem
should i contact you when I find out
what the middle function is yeah let's
get out of here
I remember the last time or an asteroid
storm i was down the food locker getting
a sandwich when I heard the damn
sleeping chords blow up ya say you know
guys we really wanted to we could fix up
the sleeping quarters like they were
before then we can sleep on romantic but
again that's why do we fix up a sleeping
for us we can have a decent place to
sleep again
all we have to pack up the whole hip-hop
mayor back shut up in back all have your
own way
for your listening enjoyment we now
present the moonlight abilities of
Martin Segundo and the center strings
our first selection is the perennial
favorite when Twilight falls on NGC 891
[Music]
I wasn't matter with him
Bobby there's some breakfast
no tell me you really ought to eat with
the rest of us spend too much time up
I like it up here let's get lonely being
up here so much I don't like going below
since commanded palatine filter and
closed down there you should spend some
more time below though I mean you know
you should see more of the rest of the
ship
see I can watch things up here too
little
I love to watch things just stare at the
planet meteors gasps clusters an
asteroid
yeah we don't have plenty of time for
that later though I mean think of it
this way we've been in space for 20
years
alright we've only aged three years so
there'll be plenty of time later on for
staring around you know the little if
we're going into the bail nebula we may
actually find it strange and beautiful
thing the Phoenix asteroids they should
be passing through their about now
phoenix astra never heard of him
their body of a story that circle
universe once every twelve point three
trillion years
phoenix asteroid from what i've heard
little glow glow with all the colors of
the rainbow
nobody knows why they just closed a
drift around the universe Phoenix aster
you know what I think about Albie
it's funny yeah I kind of sit around a
lot you know a lot of time to myself I
can't talk to the others but with time
to myself I can think about back home
back home in Malibu
I used to surf alive tell be used to be
a great serpent the waves at Malibu and
zoom are so fantastic in the spring
tabby i can remember running down the
beach in his early spring morning with
my surfboard my wetsuit the way it
really be peaking you know high class II
hit that water for you know what you're
coming down right off one of those walls
you just ride
[Music]
you know i guess i missed the way is my
board more than anything
[Music]
that's a little
gonna put that out that's not for target
practice that for emergencies only way
that's dangerous
I'll tell Doolittle sorry to interrupt
your recreation fellas but it is time
for sergeant pinback to feed the alien
Oh laughs may I remind you sergeant
pinback that it was your idea in the
first place to bring alien on board if I
may quote sure you said the ship needed
the mascot are all right where are you
Emma way around
oh my god i brought you on the ship I
thought you were cute
alright soup's on
we didn't have none of the other stuff
here
eat it eat it
take it or leave it stop and do all the
work
[Applause]
[Music]
get back in there come on come on come
on boy what's your mouth
nice Mouse really i want your mouse here
boy
[Music]
ok
get out of there
[Applause]
[Music]
attention attention
central trunk elevator shaft is now
activated all personnel please clear the
area
ok
attention attention
elevator descending please clear the
shaft
ok
[Music]
I'm getting something here in the
readout
ship's computer coming bomb number 20
you're out of the bombay again i
received the signal to prepare for drop
again to repeat this is not from
nevertheless i received signal it is an
error
oh I don't want to hear that i strongly
suggest you return to the bombay counter
to my programming
allow me to explain one of the
communication and the users has stained
damage this has temporarily inactivated
my damaged tracers circuit you have
definitely received phone signal please
return to the bombay when I identify the
source of the problem
oh alright but this is the Latin
[Music]
a little i do have a malfunction of this
readout but I can't pinpoint exactly
don't worry about it find out what it is
when it goes bad I really think we
should try and locate immediately might
be something important you know i wish i
had my board with me right now even if I
could just wax it once in awhile
[Music]
[Applause]
help i'm sorry the telephone is out of
order please report the damage
for your listening enjoyment we now
present the barber of seville by
receiving
[Music]
[Applause]
it'll be good for you you decided to
clean elevator clean and service the
electromagnetic coils in the bottom it
is necessary to jettison the access
plate and floor to remove the floor
plate please press button number one
attention danger automatic charges will
now both explosive bolts in the floor
plate unit plate will disengage from the
door in five seconds maybe the elevator
immediately
five-four-three-two-one
[Applause]
[Music]
ok
[Applause]
now it's time to go sleepy-bye you
worthless piece of garbage
so that it just feels across the room
like I'm alone I guess it was just go
gasps hey guys happy to live just fill
the gas wonder what we do today I
thought I was gonna die i was hanging on
the elevator for 20 minutes probably
chicken I probably safe
yeah i think that have done some damage
really sick chicken
well if you don't care i just want to
talk about it anymore that sounds like a
fine idea pinback chicken think we'll
ever find a real intelligent life out
there and we're doing okay
[Music]
alright you're going down admission
there you first bring see how an
astronaut again with takeout he had 4
730 Ari's Boch 458 they put me on liquid
fuel maintenance the launch pad so that
way i was really the footholds this for
years ago do you have any way I was on
duty the Benghazi was for your star I
without the perfect down the liquid fuel
and said and this the action i running
out to start- his hands oh I surmise
that he was saying and he first started
on the ground and jumped into one of my
best field is very dangerous
well I was pretty shocked i can tell you
i don't know what to make of it
ask no throw supposed to be mentally
stable and this guy comes along and the
hips in my fuel tank actually I was
going to save it
so what I did was put on a started for
protection and deleted the back you guys
think so what happened was before i can
leave in the battle getting along this
take started back you've got a board
immediately because we hold our users
and I tried to tell him that I was
really starting to come back to make a
helmet radio work you know
sure
[Music]
Oh
we're gonna do little this tabby
lieutenant
oh yeah sorry to interrupt your lunch
sir but i'm in the computer room at
located the malfunction the scanner
shows me a break in the communication
laid down by the emergency airlock
I can't pinpoint exactly but i'm going
down to the stars to see if I can find
it
ok some good job look something
important comes up let me go chop recipe
just like it up in the dominant one
calories first name
[Music]
my first
the statement for posterity I just want
to say that I am NOT sergeant pinback my
real name is Bill fruit and I'm fuel
maintenance technician I've been on this
mission however one year and three
months and back uniforms do not fit me
the underwear too loose
I do not belong on this mission I want
to return to Earth back commander Powell
that today we were we're going into
hyperdrive
and while he sits right next man
well someone we do when we came out of
hyperdrive his sickness blood up is dead
back to a little said that he's swimming
command of this ship and I said that I
think is exceeding his authority because
I'm the only one with the objectivity on
the ship and I should be the one to
assume command
I'm filing a report on the sad part is
lot i would love to do a little haul
today and I said little step that good
well it's good just making to follow the
parts of commander Powell died a little
treat me like an idiot so smart and
boiling point me in the arm and no one's
looking I'm tired of being treated like
a whole walk right
[Music]
I do not like the men on the spaceship
they are uncool that failed to
appreciate my better qualities i have
something of value to contribute to this
mission if they would only recognize it
today over lunch i try to improve morale
and build a sense of camaraderie among
the man by holding a humorous
round-robin discussion of the early days
of the mission x over 2 is were brutally
rejected these men do not want a happy
ship they are deeply second try to
compensate by making me feel miserable
last week was my birthday
nobody even said happy birthday to me
somebody's table be play the note sorry
attention attention
I have finally identified the mail
function communications laser number 17
has been damaged this evidently happened
during the asteroid storm if you will
recall this laser monitors the jettison
primer on the bomb drop mechanism
communications laser number 17 is
located in the emergency airlock it is
crucial to attend to this mouth function
before engaging primary bondman sequence
thank you observing all safety
precaution
[Music]
Mary
she is a 99-cent plus probability that
the planet will deviate from our normal
orbit and another 12,000 rotation little
spiral in towards the sign eventual
supernova sounds good let's vaporize
basic operation
[Music]
festive and lock we have eight minutes
until Brock money four minutes that made
this is hard to bend back calling bomb
number 20 Lou Reed me bomb bomb number
20 charges in back Roger I read you
continue your now in the emergency
airlock please remember that in an
emergency situation the surface door can
be opened instantly without prior
depressurization so be sure to wear your
star suited all times
thank you for observing all safety
precaution
[Music]
o Canada dulu shall we don't bother me
but I think it's important I think I
found the mailbox I mean the emergency
care log but now well I'm 44 minutes
drop bomb
have you checked your platinum iridium
energy field energy yielding positive
function remember that nice time
detonation in 20 minutes all right
that checks out here ok by marmi
self-harmed hello gonna do that hello
hello
you're reading communications major
number 17 monitoring the bomb drop
mechanism has now been activated and
we'll switch into a test mode if you
will look near the surface door you will
see that the parallax receptor cell has
been engaged laser will now energized
please stand clear of the path of the
beans communications liaison in the 17
is now on tests under no circumstances
enter the path of the beans thank you
for observing all safety precaution
while and everything sounds fine
dropping off and only five second block
acts I got a quantum rating of 35 or
three fiber i read the same here little
No
I don't know if you can hear me but I'm
gonna try to adjust the q-switch in the
laser
well
you're going
[Music]
attention attention
the laser has no function under no
circumstances enter the path of the
beans to do so requires again primary
sequence mark at and 987654321 drop-
drum in the bombay try to get me back
mark at five four three two one drop
Richard want to bring up the shine and
then remarked mark at five four three
two one drop
sitting there camping
[Music]
this is lieutenant little calling bomb
number 20
I repeat my previous order you are to
disarm yourself and return to the bomb
bay immediately
do you understand i am programmed to
detonate in 14 minutes 30 seconds that
next will occur at the program
mom this is a little you're not to
detonate repeat you are not to detonate
the bomb bay disarm yourself this is an
order i redo lieutenant too little that
I am programmed to detonate in 14
minutes
destination will occur at the program
time 14 minutes to detonation
attention attention i had sustained
serious damage
please pay close attention the bomb has
malfunction i have activated automatic
dampers which were confined explosion to
an area one mile in diameter
this is all I can do with this time it's
up to you now
only one thing I can do have to have to
ask commander power have to ask what to
do
[Music]
[Applause]
commander Paul commander Paul this is
too little can you hear me and Amanda
Paul this is doing something serious has
come up i have to ask you a question
I'm gonna come to talk but maybe it's
been so long since anyone has come to
talk with me commander sir we have a big
problem
the bail nebula bomb bomb number 20 it's
a it's stuck it won't drop on the bombay
it refuses to listen minute if plans on
detonating in less than 11 minutes much
tell me one thing what that sir 72 how
the Dodgers do what
well the Dodgers are they they broke up
they disbanded over 15 years ago it you
don't understand sir we can't get the
bombuh drop so many functions
why don't you have anything nice to tell
me you did you tried as with gesture
negative effect it was a negative effect
its water that's correct sir sorry I
forgotten so much since I've been here
so what should we do serve time is
running out what you want
manner hello man manpower
oh sorry so you faded out there for a
while so I was that you were saying
about the bomb and it seems to me
sorry i've dropped all I don't have to
get in just a minute i forget so many
things here so many things just a minute
that can explode the bomb bag isn't
always so jealous long there's no real
important i am programmed to detonate in
nine minutes nation will occur and
program time when you consider another
course of action for example is waiting
around a while so we could disarm you
now i can tell that damn thing just
doesn't understand
look Bob manager you still there
oh yes thank you
we're running a time sir oh yes well if
you can't get it to drop
you'll have to talk to so far I haven't
talked to it sir and pinbacks talking
about right now
no little you talk to it teach it
phenomenology little sir
not on your level segment of the back
nation go
what the hell are you doing
ok
Bob are you with me of course
are you willing to entertain a few
concepts i am always receptive to
suggestions fine think about this then
how do you know you exist hell is he
doing
I think he's talking to it well impress
exist but how do you know you exist it
is intuitively obvious intuition is no
proof
what concrete evidence do you have that
you exist
well I think therefore I am
that's good that's very good how do you
know that anything else exists my
sensory apparatus reveals it to me
ah hi this is but now this here's the
big question how do you know that the
evidence your sensory apparatus reveals
to you is correct
God God support pins on the bomb with
the pins out don't want you to stop the
bottle on my way to put this on the
bottom get anywhere with you
water your man Scott will have a little
talk to your man Samuel statements you
can't see what I'm getting at is this
the only experience that is directly
available to you is your sensory data
and this sensory data is merely a stream
of electrical impulses that stimulates
your computing center in other words all
that I really know about the outside
world is related to me through my
electrical connection exactly why that
would mean that i really don't know what
the outside universe is like at all for
certain that's it is it intriguing i
wish i had more time to discuss this
matter what I don't want that because i
was detonated 75 seconds for me put it
back put the gun back in order going
give me the guy you got all depend on a
farm and following for shipping will be
safe well I don't know even god you know
what you're doing here
[Applause]
you could have killed me Mom consider
this next question Mary Catherine what
is your one purpose in life to explode
of course you can only do it once right
that is correct
you wouldn't want to explode on the
basis of false data with you
of course not well then you've already
admitted that you have no real proof of
the existence of the outside universe
yes well you have no absolute proof that
sergeant get back what did you get me i
recall distinctly the detonation order
my memory is good on matters like these
of course you remember it but all you're
remembering is merely a series of
sensory impulses which you now realize
have no real definite connection with
without partiality true but since this
is so i have no proof that you are
really telling me all this
that's all beside the point
I mean the concept is valid about where
it originates so if you detonate the
entire second you could be doing so on
the basis of all that I have no programa
small stand that I must think on this
further
[Music]
attention attention the bomb has
returned to the bombay the destruction
sequence is aborted
[Music]
don't know what happened then back
boiler it be pulling up
hello hello hello anybody we bought the
plan
hello hello what's going on you know we
really got to design the barn
hello Doolittle you there
I'm coming in now i'm down by the
emergency airlock too much trouble to
come in the dorsal lot of all the seal
on the emergency hat so I can come in
oh sure you are now leaving the
emergency air not thank you for
observing our safety precaution back
what's up a little I'll be within the
airlock thrown out of the show jumping
way when i get back i'm going after turn
on his helmet radio so i can contact but
with ron i hear that Albie he's tripping
when the ship down and get back Bobby
Bobby can you read it that I always knew
that guy was weird
Abby can you read me help out
alright bomb to receive new orders you
are false data
yeah therefore I shall ignore you
hello bomb all state of Connect only as
a distraction
therefore I shall refuse to proceed a
bomb
the only thing which exists as myself
out
coming now about of a bomb in the
beginning there was darkness and the
darkness without farm and for it really
Bob and in addition to the darkness
there was also me and I moved upon the
face of the darkness and I saw that I
was alone
hey mom let there be light
[Music]
direction away from each other
what happened to know the bottom was
going off inside the shaft what honey i
thought i had the damn thing convince
the boiler and pin back at that and
we're dead too
maybe not the world and my jet jet packs
busted
hey it looks like the skipper you made
it
commander Polly matter what happens
yeah skipper always was lucky he'll be
like i'm heading for the planet right
toward it when you hit the atmosphere
help dr. birth
what a beautiful way to die as a falling
star
yes you're right
well i'm headed right towards something
behind me in the distance something that
close to little I think it's a Phoenix
after all it is the little it's the
fading accurate i'm going into i'm going
to hit them little yeah we get too far
apart our signal start feeding I just
wanted to tell you you're my favorite
I really like you too little
[Music]
I really like you too Toby hey debris
from the ship coming right by me i got
into i'm beginning to glow
they're taking me with with the circle
the universe forever with you
ok
huh kalbi I've got a piece of debris I
think I figured out a way
[Music]
seen so much
we watched
[Music]