[Music]
but some people clear see ghosts of
soldiers and the battlefields around
absolutely swear to you write a book of
ghosts of the American Revolution when
you are totally totally unbeliever right
i look forward to being free time I plan
to find verifiable estimation all the
coast
here is people downtown ringwood and I
remember i'm dragging
Mary makes me happy coming back so you
think New York City girl like you can
happen
look at that
salon
she's made you the owner know my end
she's one selling we make an appointment
to look at
come on it i'll show it to you
hi im bored asheboro is to meet you
let's marry my daughter Natalie hey you
know to ringwood my wife she slipped
it's nice town
a beautiful cat
that's Margaret lands baby
seriously
[Music]
under this from rage
mrs. asheboro what was that maniac doing
here oh I guess it could head right for
you don't take no for an answer
don't give in to him Brenda will build
those abominable cookie cutter houses in
your lovely field look at a city i got
your present thank you do my favorite
guys know what this is your favorite boy
[Music]
I had to sell his face like never
forgive myself
whatever the animals then don't
oh sure that's simple arrest right now
taxes have gone up supplies more
expensive talking about used to
volunteer your services within you that
charge is almost full rate at the top of
that writers causes Riker want is
bad-mouthing all over town so donations
are down
I honestly think that's why the bank
being so difficult
what break huh
tell me I'm a high-end mortgage and not
happy
that's just what writer needs to hear
it's a tradition new furnace last year
new roof three years before that Lance
lived her whole life such a beautiful
oh I wouldn't prefer you just like
strangers bites and 15 years of age it's
a bad habit she's about to lose
Margaret same is life one sir
really yeah girl took a nap the stove on
dish towel caught fire
margaret walker up the place we're going
to put a tinderbox smart cat aren't you
it's 1-2 sell she's getting on should be
safer living with me or at home watching
the seller sure there's no way you're
going to be bullied into selling i'm
going to help you've already helped no I
mean it I i have a little bit put aside
no I absolutely render it would not be
if you hadn't found market for me
come here Margaret
mar grid home market who are you I'm
Natalie my dad he's looking at your
house was your nephew avoid it's not so
I think they're in the cellar market
doesn't usually respond to strangers
have we met before but I think so face
is very familiar to me
Oh lovely cats Marcus as loyal and
loving an animal issue could ever want
to she she really seems to have taken to
you that's for sure one of the chosen
few
Ruth didn't hear you come in this is
West merit i'm just giving the tour
it's a beautiful house massage well I
hate to disappoint you but i am not
selling
I'm sorry my dear i hope you find a nice
place and when you do perhaps you'll
come to visit us come along market
let's go and have
[Music]
she could be eccentric
not to worry call me if you decide you
want the house look Boyd I wouldn't
seriously if you want mortgage I can
handle my card
thanks but I wouldn't dream of trying
out something just itself called anytime
Laura woman can you imagine i saw the
house you in your whole life
hey aren't you friendly
[Music]
don't understand you have to sell why
because you can move in with me
it's the right thing you wouldn't have
anything to worry about alright i'm
supposed to sell my house hand over the
money to you and go and sit in your
house and not worry about a thing sounds
peachy
why are you so adamant about me selling
always come up all the sudden next thing
i know you'll be carting off to some old
folks home if you can't live on your
best i can and if I can't get someone to
live with me hire someone you don't have
the money to do that
oh yes i do I have something tucked away
for a rainy day but it isn't raining yet
what money you shouldn't have money long
rallies and lying around
it's really none of your business void I
was just trying to help ever don't need
your help
why don't you help someone who does like
Brenda excuse me
she stopped mortgage troubles go back to
that office of yours and use your
influence but maybe I can do something
about that I've right take care of this
whole situation
don't you think that you've caused
enough trouble for one day and I don't
appreciate coming home and finding a for
sale sign on my house I won't have it
fine fine
about many choices with void
[Music]
how can you get so save your house when
you're so many more important things in
life
hey Jan Brenda pretty cold huh radio
said we do for more snow
yeah sure feels like it listen I hate to
bug you but I've got a complaint here
from Walter why I'm dog i was on the
phone half the morning with him
one daughter and I have no idea how I
had a complaint last week as well I
don't happen again
you better not Brenda you've been warned
by
huh
isn't this a happy coincidence i was
hoping i would run into you to apologize
listen to your i hope i didn't appear to
be rude I'm just not ready to sell
no no we totally understand really
where's your father
checking out the archives so why have
you chosen ringwood and you probably
told me it flies out of my mind
well my mom lived here until she was 17
and my dad's writing a book on American
Revolution so I have the strong feeling
that I have met you before I can't get
over it and what was your mother's
maiden name
oh well we're very well but there it is
no wonder you look so darn familiar i
know Marianne warmer
really yes I was the librarian here for
25 years and your mother practically
lived here this this was her favorite
table this fair is very one so cool huh
she loved books and you you're the
spitting image of her how is she your
mother
my mom passed away almost a year ago
My dear I'm so sorry
words don't do much today
Marianne
did you know that your mother was quite
an actress no I'll never forget you must
have been about 10 or 11 i guess
[Applause]
hey you missed the meeting
Oh family business the custom auditors
coming in what this weird stuff going on
with some of the accounts
looks like someone has like fingers
inside job great industries you didn't
get caught in that Fiasco digit is what
I'm a mess when one of the other chris
community and a month i heard this loud
thump like that she threw a book on the
table and think of it turned out the
school was holding auditions for
Midsummer Night's Dream just having
trouble memorizing the lines nerves you
know so i sat down and helped her
wouldn't you know it she got the part
I mr. so much when she moved away with
her family and I never forgot her and
now I've met you I feel like I've seen
her again
wow I'm sure that you're going to find a
house that suits you
I just know it you belong here
thank you when you do you absolutely
must come and visit me
oh yeah I will I promise
y ou weight of a little market for me I
will
[Music]
and how are you today miss Ashwell just
pinching sound check out the family
jewels well let me know when you're
through
[Music]
so I hated the one with the orange
carpets the glass breaks right at that
second one but will the skinny hallway
didn't smell weird was it just the age i
like mrs. Ashcroft house
I mean no wonder she doesn't want to
move
she's such a nice person
so weird that she knew mom I mean
listening to her talk about her when she
was little it was it was amazing
you want to come back next weekend for
sure I guess
congratulations can you just make the
best investment of your life welcome to
have to talk to my friend years ahead of
the game seriously just check out the
specs these properties and double the
value and your smack seriously guys this
woodland development going to put this
town on the map ring was going to become
one of the most affluent little
community times and toasted
human
Boyd asheboro head writer yeah you are
pretty small town begin
yes it is listen em just thought i'd ask
good i have a property up for sale near
Brandis farm big one top of the hill
great read trip
that's the one my aunt interested
no sorry I have a package together just
one property outstanding expect to close
that any day now
sorry I'm asking right no problem
nice to meet you
that we all remember who died you're the
only woman ever confess to them and
memory isn't what it used to be no no
don't get any ideas you've had your
dinner put it where you can I feel like
I accomplished something today market
now Brenda won't have a thing to worry
about
[Music]
you
I'm going to give it to that nice girl
oh my good girl life companions heart
when I
we're not getting any younger
[Music]
dad
the dream I was tracing Margaret mrs.
asheboro scare but I was in a very
strange place and there was a fire and I
lost her in Mom's are two waiting and
then she was gone
miss her so much
we'll find a house to lay down
like mr. school
with my friends visit
email like that yeah
[Music]
so where is that true bigger one it's
one more block says it's partially
renovated can be anything you want to
see you
yeah I guess dad stop you almost hit
Margaret
why folks west right right now I'm sorry
to get your number of call you as your
change your mind about selling we buried
a true this past Wednesday item I'm so
sorry
and Margaret
I wish I just on across the street
good enough cat passed away the very
nice funeral weirdest thing
you sure this is a good time I don't
know no no better time than the present
all this front of my aunt's friend again
see she lives on the farm across the
field
she's the one who gave a true the cat
the first place she says Margaret died
of a broken heart animals 15 years old
for crying out loud ? price
[Music]
dad dad we have to buy this house it's a
sign this was mom's
what problem brother world the dogs up
there
what are you doing here mr. Riker surely
ruin a first-name basis now be dead if
you think you can buy me off with stars
and why you're barking up the wrong tree
I'm not here to buy you off to apologize
Brendan you have to understand you
wanted to buy your land your parcels the
only thing standing in the way the
development and it's a fair price
I don't understand why you being sober
simple i don't want to sell your having
some trouble with the neighbors
it's none of your business I promise you
it's only gonna get worse is that a
threat
cautionary advice surely we can do some
business I want you off my property my
final offer
now right
cnc
[Music]
comfort comfort comfort that's a cool
name so we can be neighbors
yeah I guess I'm not only person so
great-looking dog to comfort you lose a
friend
another one comes along he lost a friend
the cat that used to live here Margaret
they were buddies
oh yeah she's so beautiful so you should
know i'm basically knows the in dollars
seems your dad no brothers or sisters
no it's so it's just us hey Harrison
that's Kurt my brother come on it's
lunchtime
well see ya Mike Cooper
the two thousand dollars this can't be
our only account she just had one
personal savings account i asked me more
of my notice more cashed in retirement
policy $50,000 that's a lot of money
what happened to it mr. asheboro I do
not put tracer dogs on other people's
money
your aunt had a safety deposit box you
could look in there if you have the
correct papers to give you access only
living relative
[Music]
[Applause]
God you scared me
sorry front door was open my dad I he
went to the library but he'll be back
soon if there's something you need
I think I lost a cufflink the other day
I was gathering my hands personal things
would you mind if I just took a look
around and find it
sure sure he just walked right in
totally freaked me out so he was looking
for a cufflink probably this is that
need an excuse to come back game and
crepes told me if I found anything that
was rightfully his
it would be against the law to keep it
was just the wind bag assistant clients
funds anyway here's to those and the new
beginnings new school new book
everything's kind of hold this last year
but we're gonna get back to some state
of there is no normal least we can try
day I found some great stuff a library
today stories about a guy was hung for
treason field not far from here and
charming really charlie apparently he's
seen by about a dozen people an
amazingly they were all drunk at the
time
ok
it's only comfort probably just mrs.
margaret sitting in the window
let's go Stan we can you are a little
nervous though
no yes it is this i always just the
house
Gold Creek yeah I know how much riding
on the deal and I won't let you down
what you get now clearly we're running
out of time but yet what can I do you
cannot make a point here why don't you
give me the go-ahead to make a sweeter
offer i know that's what she's waiting
for that she's way more given tour
okay fine yeah i understand that i'll
talk to you
back so I see
look I apologize for the late hour but I
was driving back from the CD saw the
lights
excuse me but I have a word with people
head office and they allowed me to make
you another offer mr. I think I've made
myself for really clean this is really
very generous but have a look at it if I
were you know I was a difficult one
night
[Music]
dad
hey Natalie what's happened
not so much how'd you like to take him
for a walk maybe we could go across the
field with the animals
what animals at brenda's some she takes
in strays and helps them find homes for
sure went on
covert trap so where'd you move from new
york manhattan hosted so cool
it was ok miss it I don't really know
yet what first month will be afraid to
ask questions told you i was nosy she
passed away get one person that no it's
okay i lost my mom too she served on the
highway disappear
I'm so sorry looking for her
yep
so you have one brother
yeah Kurt and my stepfather a couple
months what happened for guy let me
school is Australia
hey Myron you got out of the building
get some jazzy okay kita what
ok
a card this is not leave so you work
here part-time down to the breaks over
oh yeah you to experience the
indescribable pleasures of room hi
so what gradient 10 i'm a 9-yard the
persecuted ok you and love
let's try just getting getting they must
be fun working on a farm animal shelter
not a fun
hey three helpers just what I need
oh this is Natalie hi I'm Brenda nice to
meet you Natalie merit and I know moved
into my friends house in asheboro she
was just the greatest thing you're gonna
love it there
comfort you come to visit and forth or
miss you too
Brenda found just after mom died comfort
anyone feel like working help me
[Music]
Chand
lunch
[Music]
don't you have that
but cannot jump
[Music]
this is so cool I love animals living in
an apartment it's kind of difficult you
will have a new york was school trip so
you probably want to the mat behind
basket don't
together
[Music]
can you to go play somewhere else
sorry i was going for Pearson betting
yes ever give you one with you want u
sub sad i'm gonna seen you like this
before
did she ever give your money to make
donations
I mean did she ever give you money yes
or no just give me an answer yes she did
so my rightful inheritance was given to
you and yours only I mean she has to
bring buy food she's been doing that for
years and every once in a while she's
very generously donate some money the
clothes but i think that was for
business it's my business when the cast
was supposed to come to me i was under
the impression it was hers to give
I want my $50,000 Brenda 50,000 a horse
out of your mind i'm talking forty or
fifty dollars every once in awhile 15
young and old lady with a ridiculous
amount of compassion for your way but
just admitted your milk sir you're
suggesting that i took advantage of
someone knows my friend mr. you tricked
her
I've never seen in my life well that's
my money and I want it back so i'm gonna
get a court order and have your bank
account check so we have nothing to hide
I think you better leave i'll be back
such a creep the other day i'm all alone
and he walks right in without even
knocking I was totally freaked does
again call me kick his book he
practically call Brent a liar and I mean
you should see all these things she does
with these animals she nursed him back
to health
she finds in homes and she looked really
upset
I heard something come on no I did that
look whether you like it or not there is
something in this house I told you I can
feel it
sometimes but after she died I thought I
thought your mom's presence in the
apartment
little things like like thinking the mug
the offices for morning coffee and then
moved on the shelf for ahead of her
perfume all of a sudden but I was just
so used to those everyday things
imaginable but I didn't imagine the
photo flying off the piano or the piano
keys moving up
I just don't think it's coincidence that
mrs. Ashburn knew her
I'm just saying that your mind is very
open to this kind of thing people
interview one thing in common they lost
and when they want them back at the
stories i'm tracking for my book do not
have perfectly logical explanations but
what about that guy who was time for
treason you said 10 people had seen it
that's just an annual Halloween prank
and feels those people who like to think
that Ichabod Crane still out there
riding to the night without his head
really is
let's both you and I stay up tonight
that way something happens we'll both be
there to see it
ok deal deal
what book
ok family hi hey this is my dad dad
brenda was Mara you must be the animal
lady I mean you look after strays dogs
miss Elson yeah I never tells me you're
a writer you sure must have read some of
your books you read the history our
history buff but it's hard not to be
living around here in fact George
Washington used to visit ring with all
the time
one of his chief mapmakers ordinary
general Erskine i think yeah and I mean
look him up
yeah trapper we're all going on but I've
catch up to the dogs
nice to meet you my pleasure and Natalie
drop by anytime you like okay yeah she's
a good worker
yeah oh right
[Music]
ok
what's wrong
no sensor don't you I told you she's
here with all this water come from
we'll stay up together tonight
what do you want exactly no Ted is what
you want you want bring dances far right
I can make that happen
I md assistant client funds manager
bring with sings along downtown like
things that most people don't like like
Bernie and his client she's in deep
trouble way behind on mortgage payments
i could maneuver foreclosure 14
boy I think we may be able to do some
business after all
well i'm adding this is the case of the
watched pot never boils
I don't cry mom she's always allows full
strange sounds and the creaking moving
all the time with the house that's not
your mom why do you think your mom would
come back because she knows that's what
so i can say goodbye
you said goodbye that I didn't say
everything i needed to there wasn't
enough time I know that
so why didn't you tell me sooner than
you think was wrong maybe it was but I
didn't tell you right away because your
mother asked me not to
we're just trying to protect you we did
what we thought was best if you think
that decision was wrong
I'm sorry God knows at the time it's
hard to think at all you should have
thought me I'm sorry
let's get some sleep
don't know in a minute
[Music]
was it you
what do you want
right
hey would you get a cat walk at yeah
we're from window
[Music]
you're sure it's gone now it looks more
like market I mean it must have jumped
down but you saw it
yeah it's I can do you mean you didn't
get a cat completely crazy
so ever since we moved and let's just
build so we weren't things going to put
pianos playing pictures flying really
freaked me out it i didn't really know
what to think
don't look at me like that I'm not crazy
crazy people don't know what Kurt saw
Morgan I saw a ghost was a real ghost
treated not Kurt I saw Margaret ooh
don't you believe in ghosts know people
die they're gone
period end of story dad might be home
oh yeah yeah you should be back from the
library right away
ok this book I thought you might be
interested in oh I can just take it home
with me I mean you don't have to bother
it was okay was on the way the bank
anyway it's no trouble
yeah I've never seen Brandon clean
changed
she's dressed to impress there's some
cute at that age all our wee little
possessive dad and you should go home
hey my new chaperone sure
this is a great book is just great thank
you god I hope it helps i'm sure well so
are you wondering what just for the
research are you planning to stay a
little while playing it by ear i guess i
gotta change be a good thing for Natalie
for both of us
Natalie it's a tough age as your mother
yeah 15 not the best time for sure and
she was having a very hard time dealing
with it we both are so we decided to get
out of the city
new beginnings and all that it was the
right thing to do
I have to go in mind late
in downtown i am what I will thank you
thanks for two
what this might not be my place to ask
but do you have any plans for dinner to
like you or any other night doesn't know
tonight would be great yes
ok good so I'll see you anything
sure great
I know you don't believe in ghosts but
first of all started happening movies
isn't stopping in front of me please
I thought it was my mother
I really wanted it to be
you just met me you must think i'm only
certifiable some of the coolest people
in the world a little bit so i guess
i'll take that as a compliment than I
just wish everything could go back
nothing seems the same
ok
[Music]
we've been floating you for longer than
we do most clients
I'm really sorry but unless you can pay
the arrears and for the bank has no
choice i just need a little more time
spring is so much better for donations
go way up I don't get it
you've always been very understanding in
the past Brenda it's not up to me
I got a memo you have a week
[Music]
well don boyd you're my man money your
money haha know when Randy and she's off
the property you get your money
only one way to communicate with what
the ghost say on Sam's you two are nuts
tonight
yeah right forget it i'll bring my Ouija
board maybe you could bring your crystal
ball two
it's not gonna happen oh come on it was
so cool right I'll see you tomorrow
tonight sales there has to be a reason
markets comeback ghosts always have a
reason
yeah okay Pearson whatever comfort wrap
hi
that's one today yeah but it doesn't she
really appreciates your help over there
she drop that by day it's a great book
Brenda asked me to have dinner with her
tonight no problem
sure ya go i might do something with
pearson great but I won't be late i'll
be fine
first the neighbors other ones now the
bank know it honestly wouldn't surprise
me things and coots with them
Riker don't get me started he just wants
me gone but then I think I massage bro
and I know she would want me to hang in
there so that's what I'm gonna do good i
can see this means a lot to you
the animal shelter is the only thing I
ever wanted to do since I was a little
girl let me tell you something I'm a lot
better with animals than I am with
people
oh I wouldn't say that Natalie thinks
the world not only is a very special
girl done a good job my wife gets credit
for
I'm just trying to carry on what you're
doing something right
spirit come to us now make your presence
known to us
come from the great other world to join
us need to speak to you now she's being
dog thought I'd join the party spirit
sorry for the interruption come to us
now coming from getting to her will work
Oh spirits make your presence known to
us come from a great other world to join
us
oh come on the great Otherworld you're
not helping this is so lame window whole
know I can do this
spirits of the night great feline spirit
come to us now let us know that you're
there
come on guys ok ok please spirit want to
talk to you
we want you to contact us o Great Spirit
you're not concentrating loss totally
bogus
it's not working it never works leave to
make it work
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't believe it
cat food that's all she wanted cat food
[Music]
so here's the question why would
Margaret Hodge four-banger poon
ghosts can't be hungry there's no way
was just a bag of food
[Music]
oh my god Marty she wanted me to fun
Margaret you are the most wonderful cats
are you guys doing here
I can't stand by and watch such a dear
friend we pulled in all directions
I've always intended to leave you and
your wonderful cause a healthy donation
but what better time than now when you
truly need it left you Brenda
nice ash-blonde Margaret how could she
be so embarrassed when I can buy before
i could pay the mortgage off to find it
Marcus show us our great gonna ask I'll
be home later down bad
don't be late
are these yours
how did they get out Kurt put them in
their pen inside the barn last night
right
yes Jan there's no way they could have
gotten out
well they did take them inside and
getting some food
I got a warning but there's a petition
going around town to policy do you know
who started that I can't help you in the
last month I've had a half dozen
complaints animals going loose scaring
people getting into the garbage you're
at the critical stage
what does that mean it means if there
are any more serious complaints i'm
gonna have to shut you down
I'm sorry
one bad on you lose another I just don't
want you to get messed up again you you
can go to jail
I'm not going anywhere I swear I didn't
want the dogs sweden set that fire to
battle you hurt i'm going to the bank if
you leave before I get that please
please make sure everything's inside
closed up
I'm serious card or history or lock
middle
thanks Terry deposit fifty thousand all
I know
boy that's my money I can do what I
google had it here and left it to me i
will have the bed for the front and i'll
show you the answers you have a letter i
have written proof for what she was up
sell mine she was of sound mind then you
Boyd
I did right there I'm gonna do what I
can't help it you should need your plan
didn't work it didn't deliver the money
now
not until she's off the property if I
didn't sleep it'll become development
deal with millions if if you get around
that's a big if Boyd okay i promise you
i know the right buttons to push and I
can do a lot more damage than letting
the dogs out record believe me much more
okay you do it
[Music]
ok
are you taking me
[Music]
what are you doing here you're gonna get
out trying it out of you going to open a
part of this already won
Roger that you know what's going on in
here
ok so what were you really doing it like
I told Brenda I thought someone might
try and let the animals out again i
decided to check it out the barn was for
things when I got look I don't know what
you heard person I talked about the
other day i'll tell you what i heard
that person thinks you're the one
letting the animals out that you might
have to go to jail
I didn't let the end zone and I don't
have to go to the fire
he said something about you setting a
fire so I went a little crazy after my
mom died I set fire to some guys done it
got out of control i got mandatory
community service
that's one working apprentice so you're
forced to work here
no not forced just the way it started i
used my arms long ago I just stayed
so why didn't you just tell me like I'm
gonna tell you I'm a juvenile delinquent
the moment I meet you
clearly that would impress a girl right
so he wanted to impress me i didn't know
what to do
doesn't want me back she's excited I
didn't swipe
there's no way that happened by accident
I somebody did it deliberately and I
have to find out
and I'll help you
it's obvious someone is out to get me I
I can't believe it's crude but on the
other hand I can't afford to take any
chances
Riker he do anything to get rid of me I
just I can't take this anymore you don't
want to give up now
you don't understand the animals gonna
succeed i'm supposed to protect have not
put them in harm's way
what kind of help I don't need any help
I'm fine on my own night
I'm just on my own
what were you doing over here in the
middle of the night you realize how
dangerous it was Margaret came and got
me hard and it's a good thing she did
if curtain I hadn't been here for Karrde
you don't overwhelm you don't really
know run to either school
sharp brother beautiful day I thought
I'd drop in and see if you have time to
consider my latest offers pretty darn
generous you know what you've been doing
and it's not gonna work
what are you talking about i'm not
selling the farm to you now or anytime
soon if you ever put on my property
again you are going to regret it
look what that's a threat
Susie yes it is mr. maker problem
her
you idiot
whatever you did it didn't work you want
50,000 it's time to get serious
I don't close this deal my back is in
New York never going to give
I'll be crashed we're in this together
boy you understand it's time to take
care of business once and for all
hey how's it going
so big that more hot the honors ring
down the hall
I heard apparently already have a pretty
good idea who's been doing a little best
one on the sign of excitement I would
see
[Music]
ok
nah
now we wait
[Music]
all those months didn't even know she
was sick I want to school from I did my
homework i went with friends and I
wasted before when I could have been
with her I could have spent time with
her and
it wasn't fair no I think they're really
trying to protect you
yeah its deadline to me okay well then
they pretended and all of a sudden it
was too late
it's a lot few weeks past you got to say
goodbye
[Music]
what
you
so get it
[Music]
just stand there
everybody yells out
oh come on
you
[Music]
let's go now
the place
the animals down
what
what are you going
ok
what are you doing
just step all over give me my money I
need to have got others coming in
tomorrow
you still don't get it do you avoid them
to sense to rub together i don't get me
either
this dude was closed slow down
please
we have to get out of here car
diamond
ok
scratches on his face
this guys coming around I was gonna be
okay
chatter weird
[Music]
so boys up to his eyeballs charge
district arson on the works right who's
finally out of my hair red and the
insurance interview about the part
cheers Cheers and here's Margaret the
most amazing cabin world she rest in
peace tomorrow
market to market even though i never saw
I give up
how can you not believe something I saw
with my own eyes use
he's here
[Music]
thank you