[Music]
after supporting falling ladybird ever
supposed to be calling me
[Music]
Michael quality medical by calling
neighborhood
[Music]
[Applause]
no mercy at all Lady birds like
including labor and specifically
ladybirds will be we hang our emergency
every time a lady guards in place
[Music]
after the ocean
we got into anything that is in fact top
of the lightning and Frank
[Music]
to the dog
I wonder bang around the storm like this
never not
[Music]
alpine for emergency a base calling the
ladybird how many planes radio must be
adventurous contact every single Sunday
again but they're all calling on
broadcasting signatures they had a
report they contact us about as corporal
what is the wedding video marine base
radio again
northwich seen anything of a ladybird
someone keeping a good lookout but they
want to know our position get my
position about 750 miles northeast
develop angle nicer whatever capital to
take down from your radio signals 420
polypi no not a chance button and have
any directional radio finder on just the
same if they try to race again don't
answer i'm captain of this ship and I'll
give the order
alright you're captain of this ship
writing forget about qualifying on that
missing plane about
in order to get a good manners will
change right
[Music]
I want to that our Chinese friends all
have his gun just looking at them
upriver
okay fine I've including running around
outweigh what I was gonna say yes and
you'll keep moving around like a chance
to get them out that having those
Marines from qualifying on our next I'm
trying to wait and if that cargo using
abroad by tomorrow and having it shipped
back home and this ship was shot of me
for the purpose of delivering those
jumps to change stay here until I think
differently my dear about it
you really shouldn't argue with our
friends catch and i havenít is now you
can play them from one down to the other
but when you're aboard my ship remember
what I say gold so it goes
that's the way I handled mutiny when I
was captain died on the dunk a low angle
emergency air base calling the ladybirds
commenting demonstrates that your new
khaki cut fuel consumption
we have enough gas supply to the south
I'm not rest of the household world
community will make the dream about all
the money going to make up with money
would make me a champion Jorge make sure
i'll take poverty that your device's
Wi-Fi radio in my car fired
this is a lady good thanks liking
thank them for something else
I'll talk with a tango tango all open up
go ahead
nice
hello my husband you I went more into
this is ok George but confidentially she
needs a little discipline your sister
thinks flying the Pacific is like
leaving a product of two
of course this is the first time we've
had people try barian tried and tried to
shoot down for Homer grounding how are
your cool little Marie this is no time
to be flipped report your position half
hours sleep i'm not one of your old you
have to be overtired that we're coming
down the aisles at the plastic because
stopping you you you letter like you're
taking math kernal party start in your
garden
I think the tenant often sister is the
answer to our prayers idea other why
keep me in suspense happen after you're
going to get your cargo if what I'm
planning works the lieutenant will have
enough worry to make him keep his nose
out of my business
you better check on Solomon Banda taking
a look at it
[Music]
Aaron faster with that calling system
hey right and one thing I can't figure
out what's that
no timeout and the throne officer all
right for the moment so he and his
sister has what do you want a soldier
never taken place like this probably
doesn't mean anything
the olives first one hitchhike on the
Mayflower another one is better than new
way of scouting endings and concur with
the newspaper reports the latest one is
busy enough to thank you fly it around
the world the left and minds and brains
i guess i wish i had seven which money
adult they strike
I cannot ascend away well look like that
doesn't get married
ok but you forgot to play the field
assistant remove your plow outside or
it's not
I was just thinking a little left the
office with top second we're getting
more trouble
the onion meeting
those actions but not those short
exposures neckties and test out with
them again I'll get these orders and get
them straight when the plane lands will
bring this politician and mr. rafter
shark when you make the lieutenant
sister probably gentlemen don't know
where our weekend when you got out just
because your father senator of Virginia
Air shut up their Senators and i'll make
you a gentleman its actions account and
here's another thing that I get you to
forex try any of your run for new tricks
while that ladies at this post
I'll make you wish you never saw the
burning car insurance re-entering not
good but probably the best in birch can
do
get my hands on that guy without a
shepherd son of jeremiah products by and
shot 11s at you feel for this detail by
you blubbering muchas what will be
without me
I side if you got me puckett talking to
help you improve the two Marines better
than six sailors no regular to get your
head special before you talk me into
this transfer come to the South Sea
strikes oh boy for the match the section
make his mates dancing around cars
defeat you sleep on a bed of anomaly the
comments comments for you but I couldn't
dr. whatever that word i had a shortwave
radio but we document from the burning
the polio would have amounted to nothing
of value village at the motivating
conditioning forget our local the life
of yours and remember you are now
just thinking on your feet in and fix
something that's the smart doctor
don't forget to play the part when I was
getting 3dr time Justin in on this week
that's really mean
are you doc can be inaudible get up at
eight in any way that will make a
mistake invincible jail
[Music]
nothing
only by complain fatty figured a guy
that I know I'm here on up and pick up
any of that Island definitely online or
that's my driving registries right mix
of plenty of things you know soldier of
fortune efficient running next against
back wall operating budget qualified
care lucky guy
[Music]
the island
I'll take that long to put
[Music]
burn
right
[Music]
I'm going to welcome development not
afraid to be given here
[Music]
guided reading society worry i'm going
to do my duty soldiers nothing
[Music]
well excuse another neck and my back was
eventually to change the back
welcome to qualify angle with oven now
it's a welcome development is that
already have
well we convey the common dance
compliments and take you ashore that's
all perfectly illustrate what like in
solution when you might wipe your
cancers of the CEO is pretty particular
about finishes
why didn't you tell me I can't have been
tense and gentlemen see me like this
Marianas deserves it he says Ryan Jensen
says streets like my kids mr. but fine
with fiber milord bonds we call it Billy
[Music]
Thank You Donna can't let them back to
meet our checking over yet on the ball
[Music]
away
when you get a double cross with white
guy not be presenting my name
watch the face so what's your
relationship like the ocean
you're right
got to give it a threesome
save some of that idea what one of the
tester oversized the distance between
the journal and the doctor begins to
work with and flesh
first we went to see oh okay all right
around our match the one that when does
the dirty work past all right good
[Music]
I love the olives are looking for a
place to like that will make our own
mermaid
[Music]
my authority
time to get up
I must perform redmax to be singing was
that
always thinks i'm about to fold up and
threatened to call for guests
pitaj if it wasn't for my help
maybe it's like my mom started i can
last a few more days
I hope
I decided we had to drop you can be
doing
maybe cuz i'm still flipping we read
spanish so if i seemed silly
you know
thanks ocean
I'm gonna help me regarding an hour
between how good experiences with your
hands are worried to do any confidence
in a lot of the artists like the
bullseye there knowing your life we can
conclude 04 / dinner I want you to meet
mr. body and doctors Greek this is my
sister Virginia gentleman are those
dollars and patty was great really
having that one of our items iphones
actually company was that lasted
different i don't think you have very
suitable quarters for a lady as a parent
I would like to place my house after
assistant disposal
well thanks but that would be lovely it
would be important important that I be
honest
get their side
[Music]
timing double crop yields on our wait a
minute very we had our wrong she's a
12-person why did you don't get a kiss
in the cavity i think is over you
well wish this is talent angle you have
a picture networking places
what's the matter the big soft centers
boy getting wet
[Music]
so I'm definitely more about your
remarkable experiences you certainly
have the last is a white room quite true
but I could remember 800 incarnations I
can invest 802 the doctor is always for
models you know and even grow a lot lies
what are you alright well you're not
figuring on crashing box by is the
holidays corporate guys got to keep up
appearances are we gonna end up by the
light yeah weather report to me and yeah
i just finished making people well i'll
be picking to the video
okay bye
same address oh that's right the ladder
broke
they don't you have up by any cigarettes
so you know it's a little short little
payday
oh okay help yourself hey wait a minute
one that time for the girl uh-huh you're
about your car right number two and 10
Virginia administrative review easily
weather report there
there's a document has been waiting for
thanks
no they're just friended another weekly
bored college
it seems to me that part of bonds and
from what exactly
may I offer the box confessions of
course before them
thank you and I got the Express what we
watchin you whether you know it just
came out well but i'm about to do you
think i'll take it over the seal for you
now that is a lot of videos right here
and it all made up don't say how about a
cigarette
thanks Jonesy you're going to start
connecting ok actually took the words
right out of the world is alright
that'll pay you feeling alright fine
with you're a great guy Jody a great
guys are you that great guy
you're right thank you doctor mr.
Arafat's may question about the island
but I couldn't
perhaps you can I know exactly been
coming here for hundreds of you
well why do they call it the island of
lost souls when in the old days when we
pirates roll industries this was one of
the hydrogen fuel and discovered in
mechanical wings no nation claimed it my
model we used to become obvious
disabilities are numbers technology in
other words the Genesis unknown or not
get it then there should be buried
treasure
everybody just and beyond that this
island has always been a real 8.4
international gunrunners start writing
in the past when the future so
profitable look at this report again
there's only one low pressure area
whether order it seems to be a lot of
interest in the weather around here did
you say the weather
well this isn't exactly my duty I just
thought that helped up come over here
bonds
[Music]
you can find nobody covered on you
oh yes alright that'll be all better
excuse
oh no they're not Georgie I'm very
flattered so interesting mattress none
of your filial distance I'm sure that
the budget into another glass avanti and
mr. but you could definitely stand
cooling out from the bottom w long and
did not what would it be gentlemen our
iron j
[Music]
here take this and drinking water all of
it
or a barn lot of that RJ is for you and
I mean sir you heard me and detective
few different general of the American
army i never get this the general of the
American army still living dr. no no not
George Washington like why can't the boy
you don't be selfish about I'm sorry sis
but i must observe military etiquette
for the best photos I've got separated
meetups many men it won't separate my
sales are all them down one day they're
gonna put this outline that back to swim
away with it and I think very community
well occasionally I have to shake the
iron fit i don't think any structures
can go yourself if you like but I know
where the fun is
excuse me think about that should become
the princess sakura many other times
they want to officially start LOL don't
you sit down
yes I think I neglected to thank you
boys for bringing in this action is not
about whatever grade
no thanks oh I forgot my purse first
[Music]
introduction to warn you about something
that's about bonds is a very good friend
of mine finish of notices he's the
triangle following you know what I mean
he's an opportunity
he's always after something what do you
mean always told misunderstanding in
your case and probably Washington put in
a good word of the co-ownership
promotion and I could be on my god
differently really your school to pursue
time I knew you would wear this for the
lord I copy i did that because i didn't
watch it no my chinese notes little path
that I don't want you to think that you
can we yeah she said you
try to pull it back huh no telling me
what a good friend you to work or you
know we've been together for three years
but well c ya particularly mundane and
emulating just giving an unscrupulous
very much right here we have to get the
rest of my cannot give you the signal
win course in your case you're rather
than the command
alright you mean he might ask me to get
into the world with the fish just don't
get me wrong and I were passed your
contract thanks thank you guys
you know there's one thing i like about
you to press worth your loyalty to each
other where he's a nice fellow always
great guy
[Music]
why around and breathe out of atmosphere
no I never expected the reception
[Music]
that was very nice of these types of
things together I know you like it you
know it's too bad you're not going to be
around longer
yeah maybe you're right that it's me
you're after one night you're turning it
over your little bit when those motors
vibrated oh come on i might offer a
suggestion development i was following
coastline and medical product article
beyond what we can say an hour that you
better take those standards / don't have
all that many my field trip no but I the
all-female beginning
can i watch you tonight i'll be waiting
for you waiting for you to for you
really you can be publicly that the
challenges of us would you care to make
a friendly region beyond yourself well
supported
five and i'll pick up your check gloves
i'll be waiting at you from the ground
the best with and I think it might
expect nothing about your coffee in the
morning to make a night like that i
don't know why don't we start done but
before the parents 530 tomorrow morning
with almond butter tonight for next i
dunno I'm one thing it will be paying
making with the wings that waiter you're
playing is the fastest her
well we'll try to make the race
interesting for itchy which is long
birth to collect at my feet
calling out to the plane
yes sir thanks man i would guess one of
the women taught us understand that was
a lieutenant alright so much for a
chelating has more to do and visit us
get mr. after that swing
yes I about barton springs layout their
side
yes Sarge will you stop yes sergeant me
get sergeant
oh so the boys want to play today
alright i'll make clothes out of you two
birds just as I can take you
at least sergeant ears you'll have to
hurry the guys only our yard really we
don't ground me for my list with up
havent thinking about that a site when
you really look at a camp for the Panama
or angle place down there to get the
most beautiful that I wanted for me with
that song event even if I feel real it
will be no more of your transfer scheme
for me
strike
[Music]
[Applause]
probably won't make it
I can't think of one embodiment
[Music]
thanks for joining
I just wanted to tell you that stuff
much about the book is really a grand
guy i know it is the first question you
know i'm going to know about it follows
that it was having to leave the Marine
Corps eat goat with and he's not looking
for locomotion these are to Kristen
Street shoes
tell him i said hi and thanks for coming
on the point of thing i want to tell you
about fun and be careful that guy is a
fully thanks so what would you suggest
the race for on your freedom but after
that brush him off as really would
[Music]
we're almost to get so for the writing
smoke by the time i get this is my
friend Miss Virginia yeah it's something
very important I like to study before
your leaders across I think I see what's
been having some of our fundamentals but
take a look what do you want strikes to
know I told you it wasn't his fault it's
like Greg I just say that side
thank you that was something very very
important I want to tell you how excited
the material about that faker but
without the moon
no all right class but after that Russia
North Korea have no truck no problems
[Music]
we work something out
little remember
thank you does this mean garbage detail
[Music]
what about for it could be interesting
day running away from it
why'd you quit drinking well you can't
connect
not often grace don't get too excited
max inside importance they want to
celebrate the marine Joshua's I didn't
know anything
which one
what makes you think they're beautiful
not even blind like a comment on
everything
well I'm my own
yeah well it's likely to be mine
provided the Falcon forget to thank
Virginia it's not going to get out of
except behind that is the spirit open
mic and soldiers sweetheart taken out of
my affairs for the network sorry
Virginia your goals notes
I'm a trained monkey
[Music]
making building standing out of problems
you think the best political 50
one-dollar bills have encountered twice
bad
[Music]
I think I was happy
like
[Music]
thank you
better settle around
medical data because it's coming down
coming down
[Music]
in the
you want
laurent i'm from important from the mind
giving thanks chairs are not so many
questions
what different doing here in the heart
monitor
and here on the cover for a while
thinking maybe front of the heart
jump
get back are you okay well well here we
are somewhere
you're going to know is i'm alright
little a depression be over the wheel dr
glasson lines all right come on let's
see i have many ideology will follow dr.
spring has been doing a little
excavating at the edge of the jungle
swamp adventure to pick up some
specimens but i want to send them from
the ground to catch the next visit new
york i think it would only take a short
time and I can still be 21
why this spent a lot of failing of mine
I i get a great kick out of study and it
uses the doctor it's very exhilarating
it stores the Eagles 7 i'd like to get
with my travels quickly as possible or
is of course right I'm going to get to
check your plane and see what parts are
needed then we can fly back to the base
and pick them up like that
you wait here I wanted on I think that
attractive playing with button
I'll go with you max I tries to the Sun
massages
that's right we're gonna be love I have
records to show
yeah i love the final video alright i
don't have an improvement having junk
streamline I thing
it reminds me of the days when I was
composing now don't tell me you are
getting a stump open our radio like that
where electric important for exchange
enough you should get a message to the
ecology about using the radio on your
place
unfortunately is one of yesterday i'm
going to have to figure out
the radio the house we can use that we
not use the month
stop talking all radios broken wasn't
working on the height of use that i'm
not going to prison especially at a time
like this when I'm talking
let me see your radio maybe I convicted
why worry about breast not going to
outline the basis that the normal but
not available if you want to feel what
I'm gonna wrap but I'm going to spray
the house while you've been right woman
here
what's the matter
[Music]
well if you girls going away tomorrow
that make you happy
[Music]
what are you doing right he's not on the
wing I open the door I want to take a
look at your radio if I can take it
I thought it was me that was fixing one
there's no reason why should my to you
didn't button I didn't say anything
before but I'm telling you now there's
something wrong
I don't understand what I'm beginning to
understand you that kind of up there and
you're far with money
deliberate plan to bring up down here
just why I don't know that it has
something to do with that gun running
message i just read your mind is working
overtime raft imagine it or not I'm
responsible for mythology i'm going to
see if your radio work
[Music]
ok
ultimately there is comparatively little
damage to your plane good
oh my God we're taking up to a partner
in a little while when max told me the
moment that we gotta go down see what's
keeping yes I think it's a good idea i
like to be in front of hungry for
that was relevant how the flames
enrolled yes that's what it might be
better to have it out of the water level
of difficulty making repair so I have
some of the natives put on sure we're
connected gosh it was here working on
the plane when I for the house he must
be around somewhere
I think we should look for you better
stay right here absorbance if you are
overlapping you'll be lost in the jungle
to find him on dark ideal of what
happened to our print I really don't
know doctors unfortunately got in the
way with words but he hears right one
woman corpus delicti vinick's I wonder
what the penalties from negative on the
island you should never forget it but
that isn't going to change our plans
tonight we need to plan your up with
long and there's no word over-the-air
every ship in this part of the Pacific
will start searching just as you planned
yeah but after i'm sorry about wrestled
where he crashed straight off all the
jungles already left
yes I since the before they called a new
jet know that know yet why don't you
guys stop annoying me
you think we also want to be bothered
with you during a race but she keeps
both this
hey what's the idea for you
yeah not allow the old library is wholly
we going next
yeah I got it out with it back to get a
report with no job no I know you're
right
[Music]
run good for business
no I think the bottom line yes
while being a ground like this required
with jungle for your friends didn't get
the button say we'll be back or haven't
had world to move will write about keep
like I had no remember your life we know
like the last tutorial on that
you love him don't you
you my husband not provide valuable
tools waiting list of that didn't come
to stay here to the native try to be
your water for you don't waste the
jungle but make about him that he take
it back to penguin money for people
coming on board room by the migrants
from pride from hopefully find
[Applause]
the model model cool goodnight
30 yards out there come on
[Music]
tonight would have the last of the gun
out of the beach only about 200 cases
not without the river and in can be
watching will again be an Indonesian
business is buying the missing money
truck without even captain Barton an
excuse and trekking around the vicinity
apparently looking for the plane
neither did you ever have a position no
dark about you got money i just had one
a couple of people for my eyes
reincarnation is not mean karnish
incarceration idea Oliver what are you
talking about dark I had a vision of the
level of charlatans finding out that we
were engaged in the anti social
enterprise of gun-running you know what
that word means
how would she find out she's been
robbery / mo my deal honor that the
young lady is even now just around the
corner
each crappy I'm terribly disappointed in
the solvent listening in on a private
conversation the jungle must have
corrupted our good Nana undoubted we
should do something about it
yeah sure you won't need our money back
[Music]
safety of Virginia origins around the
world Lady Bird and all but himself
the two points less terrifying go
yesterday and moved to Guan working
parties are being organized Virginia has
been calling pengal please come into I'm
sorry development but I never allowed us
to use the radio without my permission
where's max acceptable growing influence
look boy
next I'm really for example
they're based in bomb making faces
[Music]
well we're going to command a person
will turn on speaking this is preston
lieutenant sorry we've had no word yet
that'll work on the plane has been taken
up here again some serious intent i
can't understand one of the planes not
coming through will broadcast for an
immediate search and send out all
available
[Music]
[Applause]
what would your friend second ex got to
keep looking you know what I can't
understand is both planes tailor each
one that don't sound off on their site i
want to try to cut across the island was
second actually remember lieutenant
bottle too dangerous
that might be enough to make our triad
turn a little hotel hey that whatever
service world run out of you I'm going
back to the base the base you can't do
that supposed to play around somewhere
much hype i'm doing the best i can
really come out again like you're having
a straight course but probably after all
and harmony with your respiration
partition your flight right right i
don't want to do anything right you guys
whatever doesn't pick up
God again and welcome
[Music]
launch with you check the search like to
change the oil because we'll be showing
up again before sundown and he can't win
right place i'm going to call a co-
field parking lot
[Applause]
why are you playing and just let it ride
is going to pick them up like you have
to the pit box came out with a broken
fuel pump on the other end early autumn
a lot about results
what do you mean if you go right there
too long now I'm not a reckless if you
took off not worried I'm know that's
really fun restaurants
yeah oh come on Jeff
already on the baseline every available
ship in training and research experiment
already has enough when did you last
days the ladies first after we came down
his best performance ever resent the
salt marsh or the trouble remembering
invention government security check for
the young lady in black discretion
review across independent and joining
the budget lumps you think the river
traffic across the area we both get to
the coastline 50 miles outside of
elevation from what you did try to call
the council and the jungle right that
would have been
[Music]
i'm going to say about West Virginia I
don't notice and that's you imagine for
12 hours probably poison you grab it
with plant a story that's another 1i
always strikes given you know Brandon
planned to give the same time and antsy
or right now according to this little
gadget was downright back in the jungle
somewhere
yeah we've got to find out where let's
talk this over the field
ok my new apartment free to give us feel
the same landing gave us a strike
maybe we got Brandon all right now we
haven't checked and get something to
play 5,000 feet in the air it came from
the jungle but Brian summary even though
he is lying the field 10 for any reason
or motive for it or how he's landing in
the jungle could possibly a second
important plane that can i but my head
says it doesn't switch it up just let's
grab the play before it takes always
right remember the CEO said you take a
chance on your own responsibility i'll
take it i get to the record button takes
off a check from a good
[Music]
just the glasses and join in the search
party for me thanks buddy i also wish to
report that right advance to run the
launches without permission
yes even seen going to love the river
calls it is that sawdust and another
thing private auction has disappeared
that available but lieutenant they have
a also him
yes sir or just a minute keep an extra
man on the radio room and having bring
any messages they receive yessir
relation
[Music]
maybe
bookmaker outlander
it always really think when i leave
surroundings that have to come in dear
[Music]
sorry gotta go
normal
[Music]
ok
in this study
[Music]
different techniques and gentlemen
should always be quite have another
window my dress me and I suspect the
button that something to do with its
appearance and I stowed away on the
plane with red killed
[Music]
that's a tough break I don't keep it
general we get out of this
[Music]
why do you think he sold
no I don't think it's michael i sent a
message to the basement to get here and
start until they do them too quick
what about forgiving girls room but that
doesn't read that one time too many
where is the evil dark know if men are
like he was gone
something you should never calimary Nia
[Music]
units over there watching Sensibility
our children ablaze a million brunch
restaurant can come through the guild
Florida replied the stranger
[Music]
Marina supposed to get the 20 minutes we
got down and he works the network
ok
[Music]
before you technically
well you're coming up here you know why
can't we just fiction for a good flight
special
are you
[Music]
that won't do you any good
that's what you think that is pretty
much around it and if you expect any
help from the basement come too much on
it
we haven't forgotten the plane around
here but you don't object too much
not all the moon a pleasure to have a
famous flyer the controls God about that
fellow rookies outside a lot of don't
even remember the last thing about him
alright children I'll talk to a ranger
for the report happened approximately
one of the ground not gonna fire you get
better
where are you
ok to order let's go
ok
right
start up again
[Music]
I understand you've been around these
items for a long time now I think you're
about to leave for good start
what what
we got out of his mind
[Music]
they're like man on skype
women not white girl event
[Music]
and are you doing here so we are fully
data way we only want to help you want
to have your problem is going to keep
working anymore
[Music]
you know I wouldn't leave
coming coming
anybody better one if you kill making
come when I can hear from readers are we
looking
[Music]
private market day we get a bit
thanks right
[Music]
party
reading
[Music]
ok
help me that I left side of and the
jungle wasn't trying to get free time
Thank You Man flying private salt and
burned sure like ever happen street
where where the level is Ernie
you would be minutes or longer ones
getting not really the place back to
Virginia wait a bit of you guys got
through plan heroes this all turns back
there safe for the seal send that listen
socket
take the expression to the launch but
that we got on you guys you know I shot
that guy last night with only a dream
anything going down
I haven't started idea
[Music]
can I just received auxiliary flooding
and I'm looking for the trial of dr.
straight lost mr. button for just one
day after tomorrow you'll take it you
don't have to explain that they don't
get that your binary list and make a son
officer in the service on it's just that
those private one will be able to get
down the children thank you separate
I've decided to take up radiation
missouri by profession I wish you good
luck
I wonder started I have to go to
Honolulu with I can fly with mr. Pallavi
well I'm sorry hon but i think it's
going to take the boat but it will be
like quicker
you've got plenty of time if it's
because you think I can't handle a
control system and us i said no but
you have an accent that's Michael and
he's really become a friendly fly
no you mean I can't fly tamil with all
that's exactly what I made a cute but I
could just like I cannot stress enough
Virginia you want to take up a little
morning
[Music]
I could act as co-pilot so I said no yes
no Dickie dollars in office have to do
you have service
all I wanted to know what you think back
to tenant where I think it has nothing
to do with an airplane leitner very long
hair played
[Applause]
[Music]
chillin with language only like Marina
Bay online burn rate but maybe bad
answering some entangle over here you
forgot something
forgot something yeah you don't remember
yeah I'm so sorry
really for Mahala yeah that's right that
that big love lesson right guy when the
telephone numbers around i'll take them
as usual
not anymore theres a little thought now
ah did you get that big hug
[Music]