future
13 dr. Frank tired like a regular old
like experiment shot
we can find and watch them all
now keep in mind my control
breathe and other back to help show
should be
history
hey everyone welcome to the satellite of
love that big one human back there
what's my mouth like that
well anyway he just got invited to one
of gypsies tea parties and we offer a
spirited game of tennis
favorite game was watching did your lab
and what I thought there was a good as
any woman last night wasn't it
what's that that yeah yeah it was really
funny i think i think the Delta Burke
really is the the glue that that holds
that show together because it was a
thing last night where she came out and
there the stuff started happening
he started the show anymore oh well no
she's not but I think she's on the show
and spirit and you know i mean because
that other woman is on now he should be
creating a disturbance and save his
behind
and after all the candy in the world was
starting to think that you didn't even
watch these I be one of the last night
maybe i didn't think i was i was
definitely watching a show that when
they were the the there was women on it
and all its seemed like they were
designing maybe we'll get you know I'll
be right back
well gypsy this T is really been great
great but we see you next Saturday
well I have a thing that I have to say
my curfew and helena bonham carter
they're finished could we please start
our tennis game will be good but hurt
and I rear calling
good evening ladies and gentlemen good
evening tonight it is my pleasure to
host deep 13th annual celebrity roast
this year our guest of honor is none
other than dr. Clayton Forrester
dr. Clayton Forrester ladies and gents
you know i'd like to say that tonight
we're honoring one of the world's most
brilliant scientists i like to say that
but unfortunately we're stuck with dr.
Forrest
seriously though I'm treated well down
here by paycheck has lots of zeros
nothing but zeros as a matter of fact
what the hell is that
no really I can't the good doctor but I
think deep down underneath it all he's a
real jerk it
there are a lot of reasons you could
give for why dr. Forrester is the way he
is personally I think it's because he's
ugly and stupid
no no seriously
dr. I in all sincerity what I really
came here tonight to say was I hate your
guts and i hope you die a slow painful
death secure the knowledge that nobody
loves you
well let's bring up our guest of honor
for tonight ladies and gentlemen dr.
Clayton Forrester himself dr. Forrest
very happy
Thank You TVs Frank haha you know
there's after a a beautiful tribute like
that
there's only one thing I can say and
that's dope
and in conclusion oh I know I should
have hired red buttons back up to you
move everyone just playing a little
canadian doubles here which the
first-ever satellite of love celebrity
open sea
kristi love Carl it's 30 long I never
all right you ready here we go
holds out
what is your problem what are you blind
what did you grow some hair servo come
on you're out of order here
hi out of order you're out of order
she's not about her the whole damn court
on a hoarder think Jamie's haha oh I do
me a favor Frank take these oranges and
wrap them in this towel all right
sure doc ah mayor Dinkins is a special
treat your movie this week is a little
bit of a change of pace
it's about a bunch of astronauts who go
on a space mission back in the fifties
it's called 12 to the moon but first a
little musical acid trip from our
friends at General Motors called design
for dreaming
what do you do with these clay I just
call me Bob Oh Frank easy
no I am having a hard enough time what
are you something now where we got more
yeah
oh this is my new car
last night the moon was bright and I
hate it when people tell me about their
dreams
and it wasn't mommy when i read that is
the nicest oxygen tent i have ever seen
and Tommy tune arrives toilet paper
spiders become to the place where the
morrow a subpoena for me
thank you it sounds very exciting Mary
come just as I am
no you must come as Geechee guy go to
call him or her dressed in a pair of
pink shaman ali go we're doing okay
haven't got a single thing to one man
she's super freaky me go I'll be the
talk of the town
honey is dinner ready oh my god go after
it
why I followed my beard for takeoff
thousand windows yellow with light down
down it fell and it man in the world or
the story hotel right in the middle of
the steam and hops berg wedding
reception
god she's right there
natural
I mean
white days of those lighters
I clutched the invitation to my bosoms
he was a famous beyond the boy from at
chicago by you is better than me
excited the United job to job think it's
just a dream and involves more money
which one is your eye on the sparrow and
your death experience like this
they're all so beautiful i really don't
know so many girls
excuse me move it buster it's my dream
come on me through
oh no I want a party
I don't give the Kingswood that's why i
entered your head
perils of history is a high-maintenance
days
ok we'll have the usual two-car garage
my lord that due to ignore me that's
different about the final might i'll
take you know
this be you with a beautiful
she's gonna roll it
security to the showroom floor please
I think we are
great i guess i can sell my plasma every
Tuesday
all out and buy a Cadillac cool this is
a rebuttal to Roger and me
anyway the dream Lisa got a good parking
spot
yeah
quick hitter talks of burning
any more girls in there yet
she's no wonder they need to carry us to
carry her everywhere
yeah like a man you forgive my break
yeah you can really belt the Blues
looking like not i mean put a card in
the clock and onto the green picture of
how you need to look at stealing your
ingredients you need to
just because it's futuristic doesn't
mean it's practice for the bride to feel
tragic rested push-button magic to do
you know whether you bake or broil up in
the Frigidaire kitchen does it all for
you to do
the timer and you're on your way where
you can get back and tip back to court a
wild turkey
top pik top 3 on the clock
what it's a solution is to be natural No
hello this would be the up part of
romantic mood swings i'm guessing it is
going to take her for a ride this dream
dome
oh wow
we're know what Freud would make that
Sun Hat well sometimes the Sun head is
just a son hand
your mother's little helpers kicked him
my cake is ready I call no way
Campbell's melon happy birthday 12 jun
jul
what's the hurry so everybody on stage
black time
now a glamorous dancer and a special
number and of tomorrow
chorus line to the wrath of Chaka Khan
to get off of me
everyone says the few more restrained
but i have a feeling you doing all
change two centuries while she's dancing
the Japanese are making great indian
students all of them as you're Duncan in
the narrative month story a one-woman
show show starring Tom Bosley
as possible
well sure
dream part of tomorrow
where jackie gleason Audrey meadows
money include stuff car
eldorado town car by Cadillac ensemble
by christian dior are you
with our tourney and Joyce Randolph
Fonzie's duck are doing the flick
Santeria driving coat by montano of New
York pregnant woman and schnauzer option
entire production supervised by jacket
and Oldsmobiles elegant golden rocket
for about this attack primo of Los
Angeles
close three plants car
executive producer Jack filled in the
shit electric recent our club de Mer
open to the knives club costume by a
media or a free unfettered avarice by
madison avenue in the honeymoon
- I didn't be mortally wounded
clown suit by bargain clown of Hollywood
this is what happens when you go to a
car show with michael profit last of all
designed for the electronic by way of
the future
the fabulous turban power to firebird to
the extension of my manhood car
your deal with the devil is now complete
and I cool
Stockard Channing is Peter Pan
do you have it in red that's a six-week
delivery ma'am step is to get kids camp
and step is a minke had its go ahead to
do
atomic batteries to power why you who i
burned to the control that are we are
about to take off on the highway of
tomorrow
stand by
you sweet-talked
look dead raccoon of tomorrow
my sort of magic
our dreams will come true
that's where President Barbie ventless
Prime Minister Jim J Bullock
the true way you build it
someone invent rock and roll please
yeah
will do
future may not be available as seen
personal face maybe future not available
in Africa India or central South America
and it's probably some giant kids
standing off all that control
well I really should be getting home
conspicuous consumption makes our love
stronger
look out the bridge to the future is out
yeah
hello lady my lay down here like hey
lady
hey i have seen everything yeah
oh wow this is gonna be great it's got a
rocket and everything but look at it
yep
they're bombing Washington bombing
London
bombing friends bombing my underpants
tonight on space court
yeah
donuts no don't oh you're going to the
moon on
whoa kinda like a refrigerator magnet
credits here
hello well 22 wow I think I'm in this
maybe now
yeah
yes whether you're nineteen eighty we
will be living on the moon
remember when we were living on the moon
imagine a do with my personal capital
purple purple for who the more weapony
junior high school festival at horns
these are 12 that are going to the moon
60 nope
yeah
Martha Stewart plan that seating
arrangement
- chicago
by travelpod
ladies and gentlemen the master funny
men of our age Victor barga i love the
world
there's a kind of harsh i am speaking
for the International Space order
hi in the first worldwide radio and
telecast in history
at this moment I may die over 2 billion
people have been so every part of the
world are focusing their attention on
this program and my wrong every nation
of the earth in the magnificent effort
is contributing of its people and
resources in an attempt to reach the
moon and proclaim it dolphin-safe
international territory and House of
Pancakes
the rocket ship moon or equal number one
represents the culminating achievement
of the world's leading scientists the
men and women who would buy her have
been hand-picked from the world's
leading specialist blowing this can be
the start of a beautiful friendship
personally designed and supervised the
construction of this rocket ship or
consider your behind is the oldest
member of the crew
so rod Murdock is the youngest he holds
a doctor's degree in mathematics at the
age of 19 taking place dr. sell him
gamut from turkey is an expert on space
medicine selected to work with him is
dr. secret bra mark from Sweden position
and physicist and member of our ants 80
n martel engineering technician hate his
stupid American pigs
so William Rochester hello did british
geophysicist and my house if you're born
dr. hit a cone murata will be acting as
astrophotographer and father's mother of
five
Russia is represented by dr. feared or
loved you know
map maker from Nigeria of the chief
navigator the great astronomer for
getting this water mechanic from me what
all is born dr. David Ruskin this
aeronautic engineer will serve as the
official recorder of this expedition
you'll be catering the flyer zillion dr.
Lewis Fargus the ship's first pilot will
also be in charge of communications the
leader of this staff can't come to
taking is john anderson of the United
States who has dedicated his life
demands conquest of space where there
was a rockin around here is orbital
flights have made him world-famous yes
I'm counting yourself beep I'll me he
was the unanimous choice of the
International Space order to helm this
project
let's go around here any you your freak
speak English
the rules straight right away with
speaking
within the next few minutes the next
voice you hear to make world-shattering
history that you up our new needle will
take off the ring with your method is
outside the Earth's atmosphere great
elevator to the moon when the moon's
orbit is reached and Jupiter aligns with
Mars the first landing on the moon will
be attempted people all goes as planned
Bob Hope long Nala couldn't get anyone
to take care of the dog
x - you're free during the entire flight
i'll be talking control will try to keep
in communication with the shit that are
we there yet
is aaron why didn't we there yet . range
of mountains on the value and the news
of the landing
that's the Lido deck that can be with
and also with you
they are all i'm looking right at your
hind
pop that's the chair like the first Sun
Country charter to the moon and I could
wrap with them animals
I call the pink lawn chair i call the
one by the window
how did I knew they were ninjas and
world you put the birds here
you're evil evil once again you have our
captain of the flight crew would like to
welcome you all aboard people's express
flight 212 the move
sorry we had to change into a dog cat
but it was necessary
yeah
public broadcasting needs your support
looks like one of those make your own
recording things
yep
it's a quarter to two thousand almost
died by every clock I see
I can't wear gray
oh how all my ears out
I specifically said in my application no
gray and we're great
in France we have better moons and new
people to speak
let's see hi mom
our first day in space couple monkeys on
board problem you may launch
this is dr. David Ruskin reporting his
first entry into the official log of the
lunar ego need not attempt to reports
alien information as it occurs is now
launch time
- something two minutes
great i got the cloth helmet
if are you being served as the kind of
programming
I'm gonna set this the central stood tag
because I'm sledge rip rock shiny tiles
and some do you know stupid Americans
I'd rather be knitting I'm not only in
my Bernard Kalb i hope i like to moon
tank concrete astronaut
no no it goes on your head that Oh one
size fits all up for a year of nova or
Newton's apple you
: ah
why does it hurt my place when I do this
ok
yeah
Rock drywall yes the tension is palpable
of center
that's gonna make a racket go dump huge
large at the controls
27 seconds in class silly group years
yeah
wait Jewish like a pillow and you'll get
the tote bag
when we launch into now no that's the
Mars but noone
go to her is everything ready for our
historic trip to the moon
yeah I am gentlemen . i can assure you
that everything is already helped ready
on your end
yeah i'm swedish so you know everything
i beamed myself on you start tonight
I hope that's okay with you
yeah sure I and new Xena woman of the
future will you dance with me
no come on Mike go talk to really speak
yeah I mean you got to admit you haven't
touched a woman to the Carter
Administration
great I'll go talk to the potentially
evil Specter will you to cower behind
the desk okay you know what do you want
for BOTS try singing like that idiot
from the short right of what through
wall from all's I want to take you and
your roll and rip to my food to risk but
first I want to dance with you
oh well but what would we do in your
futuristic world does it really matter
all right there
uh-huh Oh fucking to them new vena ya
know you know
let me know when a woman of the future
oh yeah yeah
so we go on her watch well i don't know
i thought i'd let her hang out
let's see what happens so no vena but
the nuvi know we've got something to do
but feel free to make yourself outside
which you're gonna kiss her aren't you
know what you call me you write back
from the second theaters everywhere
new Tina
no he never marry 15 miles above our
present speed 16,000 miles below when i
get out stars he's a dead man . 00 are
you know there are four you know three
minutes from mr. power switching to
four-wheel drive
transfer to atomic power accomplished my
hair is holding up just fine on profile
gyro settings people know
according to this we're dead
yeah
Oh
well they're out a windshield wiper
fluid dr. remark me proceed with medical
checkup
all right
looks like Thierry Mugler design these
suits and doctor but I should warn you
you want me to
hey I can see my god and from here the
better
this is about as having quite a rain
storm back first time I see the storm
from the other hand they may be getting
socked with Ray second art I don't like
your boy
we are quite dry but going far into the
unknown
well which women ever it just make with
the squeeze ball i have any time do you
after its course not I never doubted it
one has to develop a bit of fatalism
about all this
I never doubted it for a moment that
will make
well where do papa for the first time of
my life
looks good to be dr. Martell don't you
think we'll make it either but of course
I'm so important is not whether we
should make it
I trust the engines and welfare is there
anywhere
what will happen will happen the Libyans
right
please motel roll up your sleep
oh all these are important details that
i am in the best of health
well we just want to make sure
one forearm later good I'll start a lot
of pilot who's gonna start on the pilot
that new magnet camera
how does work well after taking motion
pictures not going to take
I can with this button shows any frame i
wish to use against it
yeah I should have asked didn't I
No
and this button turns on the bathroom
fan
just taking this picture
seating
oh the photo adds 10 pounds next we have
some free time
give you some point where am I supposed
to plug in my hair dryer physical
condition of the entire group
excellent
except for Hinrich whose age is showing
everyone acting out officially com to
cover up the real excitement about man's
first trip to the moon dr s key
I'll take you first you know this trip
is getting better all the time
busy so soon recording our trip we are
scarce they don't know away
well I'm keeping the most accurate
flight log possible by Jeremy was
remember man's first flight to the moon
your answer recording the next few days
and the milestones
straight
my God look at your blood pressure what
about dr. Heinrich
what what about it what's that supposed
to mean it's only natural I suppose he
is the oldest don't say anything to
anybody else know we live in between
such a brilliant man although only
something I could be like except for
that old part 3 of design and walked
three
god you're drinking again contributes
most to interplanetary travel Jubal h st
corner father is serious girl implanted
open ones with big tools will be paid
nine the two dogs are dogs will survive
these experiments
we have work ahead of my life to start
on the surface of the Moon I'm a
geologist and the best map maker in the
world
I eat met makers yes
Poland is still on your Russian mm of
course it has already been living again
with a finger
already my country is real doctor or
medical check-up please your sugar
aight as your little wire mother
you lucky people nothing seems to worry
you
beds in swear
yes
yeah
sega we're gonna use one magnetic it
tall dark and their stars and stuff
mmm
Oh
well
yes I thought it'd be better I'm sorry
cool so great
well we're gonna die
media questions i had my clothes get on
the Commission cold calls changing over
to her reaction violet Vargas take over
you just don't travel in flocks
cool
captain the navigator on apologies
course and agrees to avoid me or was
that crack in the dead lithium crystals
I'm going to have two hours captain save
the day
yeah
why should the box we need milk captain
I went my little kitty pants I'm so glad
they snatched it from the rain for
smarter so that that's not what
yeah
navigators black stupid me girls picked
up
oh just some straight meteors
that's right knee though they stroll
into action by our change country
no back on original setting let me check
on that
we're very effective after all it was
our invention world its doppelganger
arrived a little help
there's always one death and everybody
things around
colombian problem
turn on Mental Hygiene
much more suiting and practical than
water
JB's of our Moon's door by ultrasound
and massaged by air spreadsheets
no I don't buy it one and I'm gonna have
one installed in my pocket
me too when i get back to Tokyo with the
junk pile on here you can want me now
I'm sorry ladies well you could not well
we're not at the water though
well maybe with although some attic you
climbed into isn't it
I want to don't worry and can test your
work is going to start on the move
they want to see of co-creation take
place up there I look I think we're
moving too fast
maybe when we get back you'll have a
little kittens
yeah
Captain's Log girls get a look at my
space station at the course to harlot
with the creator of many layoffs orbit
or low orbit another hour and 37 minutes
and we should begin rental procedure for
landing
Oh can't get enough of that shot and
mother from my parents she looks rather
small and insignificant doesn't she
started very small job Karen see if
anything else I can help you with
not wonder what they're doing down there
probably watching us
well i'm going to get up the stairs to
get ready for a reversal thanks captain
you can put my motivation and sense of
empowerment
yeah looks like God snag
give me my Romeo
plantation guy that invented I need an
ocean make it right
jeez I didn't think space piece of vast
and stuff
move all slippery stretch little bit
remember turn into the skid brakes
please souvenir for some lucky fan was
my pleasure he take all
reversal accomplished without mishap
landing in one hour and 30 minutes
contents may have shifted during flight
yeah
well up to the room can stick everybody
stupid American computer
what you want your stupid i hate don't
know what elective already
oh my pencil in the formula for our rate
of deceleration for landing on the moon
my morals and study x over G minus 3
considering that the moon's
gravitational pull is 16 birth
that's absolutely right he's always
right amazing robbed they took trainees
to the moon that a good idea
far as the original calculation of all
feel a song coming on for years ago by
burn our have to sketch him
ironic isn't it after all is brilliance
Ron burn our could have been such a Nazi
beast
well we're trying to figure fuel needs
back here
did you know he was directly responsible
for the extermination of more than a
hundred thousand of my people he killed
my mother my father my sisters and my
brothers sisters slow down for down
no come over you will you we have a
problem here
your uniform is way too tight I didn't
want to tell you in front of everyone
risking note behind exxon father was
burned out
it's a surprise ashamed of what his
father did he changed his name to Evelyn
champagne king
you're all man was a Nazi haha
good work so well together too bad they
must die
yes
it's not to wake up a little much again
well we're almost back to earth to wait
a minute
the latest shot of our moon landing area
captain they could you sign it love
Chester captain Anderson the cruise drop
down for landing
oh there
they get a lot of use out of that thing
you're picking up crap ease of 30 feet
solitude 500 feet
cotton farmer Howard police took this
footage of an actual angel
the reason 300 looks 400 again
fluffy lips 100 largest land
time but i have not on my name
sorry but not used to stick
we made it now spread pussy
yeah I must be shot jello shots I'll be
pleased
raise their shape tirana reason why I
want white boy alone are equal number
one to central birth control we will
conclude we run following you throw the
one where r equal number one
captain Anderson speaking reporting
successful landing on the moon time is
calculated plus 37 minutes since the
last surviving our first lunar
disembarkation next schedule contact
with central birth control at all two
hundred and regulations literally the
one you like us you really like the
National Space order drag you out
you may be captain still alive speaking
for all the peoples of the earth
look little all on your crew represent
our heartiest congratulations . nor this
first great step in the exploration of
smoke lens allegiance
Godspeed you know your world but I
Dwight's anymore
rhinestone power boy Luna ego a few
minutes man for the first time will set
foot upon the moon would be excitement
is great for control because of its
momentous importance right
I'm not switching over to my helmet
microphone
I'd love to get the storyboards for this
scene Wow
now i'm turning on my invisible
electromagnetic ray screen
even I don't buy it which forms a
protective shield over our faces on
course and i'll just give you my
commentary to my micro tape recorder no
I'm activating my wings and fly with
extreme care
double check your oxygen supply there's
enough in each tank for to our
standpoint the surface of the Moon zip
me as you remember you must develop an
additional reflex action
make sure your soup radios in working
order at all times the natives will try
to sell your basket while we were going
to fall TV and radio channels open check
also lower the equipment in the winch
check and go light on the sauce is where
equipment check mekonnen a notion of a
corner Radio check check
chunk men must focus on Roscoe more
carry our magnetic media right
deflectors
I remember when we have the surface of
the moment to establish a four-point
perimeter at least a hundred yards from
the ship
check Queen to Queens pawn for check and
mate
where's your invisible playing on yes
checked it's in my post
call you got the pudding pops emergency
equipment
let's see what else I should know mr.
well anyway
handsome is like the airlock party
people let's be excited this is a
historic come on let's feel historic
people felt to have a plan to see if
that and that's the meat locker sir
downtown st. Paul after 50 great planet
tom
- 2010 God why did I believe the
invisible thing
well hey who is that ok you see strip
malls one potato two with some ghost
videos karate schools
well that's the moon we can go back now
little stinks here they must have cats
it's got a bumper sticker sandstone
laughs it's paid for it up
hey it's gum be gummy caca
one small step for a man and one small
soda extra fries
ok look up there you can see the site
like walk slow and stupid were on the
moon the moon is covered with fresh step
doc martens on the moon
that's one small step for a man never
delery all
yeah
captain Ron codpiece on the moon
that's one small so that's taken care of
thank you if there's no steam in a
vacuum
and registering static cling
hi comic book check tote shark eats
chili challenge
Oh looks like we're moving of that
they're singing ladies planet a mic
yep yeah you Trina nutella not see my
new veena
all right one of the future just hope
you know what you're doing
come on gypsy look she's novena one of
the future
sing she dances much is no vena one of
the future damn straight do you really
need all those stocks or perhaps mark
will help to write my munchkin
believe me what me this dental neck haha
she dances a lot like oh yeah sings a
lot to Mike
what did and that's your life from here
on out but just to be on the road back
deck if the experiments . i don't see a
problem but so can do just remember what
happened to Delta need you to cuddle
like what eventually they die here
some sake shot I think that's enough for
you darling
well ok you know what you're doing what
pick up everything and move do not see
us . for I'm really gonna miss this old
satellite
hey can we blow it up when we leave Wow
we'll see honey
yeah
england fans of The Beat Band
laughing of this flag symbolizes the
internationalization of the moon to
prevent individual nations from any
further disputes and pancakes
we will continue with the second part of
our mission already in proc scientific
exploration TV repair man on the moon
you guys have to follow me everywhere
come on let's all get in the shop there
you go a little app and a little and
little bit up there
yeah
there is no steam and vacuum the moon
has serious golfer trouble
well Vince Coleman is here look out
No
oh no the throw pillows are attacking
who
we are constantly being bombarded by
falling rocks and useful stylist Florida
meteors hitting the moon surface
Argus take up this area they stink up
your own area have been remembering you
outside this area to stay within the
protection of the crystal rockz office
where you take charge
everybody here tend to their anybody to
get from street in the unusual mineral
deposits of discovered
please report them to meet one's doctors
Borough Market tamid you will search for
signs of air in life through the
Captain's Log short of a chord
I got to go into my bag
well get going to explore this is the
mode people geez
where are you two going we come along
they're just bigger to hear that you
like judge crater
haha yeah I pretty much made the moon
they wanted somebody who knew the moon i
made it's like a long
fudge
yeah creators my idea because they're
not that way listen
I think we're alone
the series
looks like some kind of portal gym
to get in there and jumpstart that Chevy
he's using the dryer there is no steam
complete know that was a thing there
that thing right there see it
yeah
blow those rental manager here
looks like a normal meeting
yeah
look practice from uncle Barry and
episode
what nothing but we're gonna make it
work
all look at this on this would make such
a statement in our forte
your health you too just browsing
who exploding urinal cake would you stop
handing me stuff like that
you want another one we don't want
another walking various minerals and
stones have been collected some of them
were found volcanic crystals and sharp
coral like formations which appear
translucent people explore take some
samples come on it's cold isn't it
not that cheap crap they said like you
bc
here's use as gold
well really low gravity and rate of its
way to me
a charge on it seems to be something on
user under here
I it's a sample rocks away
careful you force careful don't damage
it she can you dig it out your wrinkled
maxi crunch
what is it dr. off well they did I have
been feeling listless and all the ride
never take any boy he in order to arrive
behold the only thing greater than
yourself beautiful hardened palm kernel
oil right fire like liquid fire
we are the first people to set eyes on
her still like this
it's beautiful however but he'll at not
even sharp like the jewel of Medea
the deer stone very well named city will
named i have named it
it's called me aight
the corner what is
are you listening for something I feel
something you run my foot
did he take the psych test before we
left
but I saw that one first take payment
Bob's rock I saw that when first I get
to name that one
I saw that one bedrock
moon is actually kind of a letdown
strangers on the moon but dooba doo bee
I think they put a diaphragm and all
flat iron
there must be
it's not good air but
something old
they're not gonna I don't think that
there
there's absolutely no way that they call
much
no you can only apply 16 the tongue on
the moon
all-weather let the space procreation
experiment begin
sorry i thought your Frenchy looks like
the logo miss saigon walking into a I
see a sign that says wall drug 200,000
miles pisses me off though
captain captain Anderson I'd like to
search deeper please no
maybe more precious attempts like them a
deer stone here
can we have the explosion yes but with
my story we've only got about an hour
supply of oxygen line one sir
and we brought some cool bottle rockets
to the hole
oh good one parties
my name is not to die me its essence
quite touch it
mariachi touch its take a chance to its
drinking is officially a key
yeah I call it need juice
well fools rush in herb was a kid I know
when I got to well written only oh yeah
let's name it all
Oh stupid on Ricky all right just read
about this yeah yeah whole school like
an old fool you see that he gets back to
the ship please stay with me
way to ruin a moonwalk chuckles captain
Anderson that's me leave the missing
they're not with us
well then we'll have to search but we
must be quick because there's not much
time
follow the sound of their lips
and lo the stone had been rolled away
look they're footprints Messiah tracks
to three days old software the males
we should really get some exploring
yeah
hmm
I forget it
a Screen Gems presentation
another Screen Gems presentation
you know we got to get our Christmas
tree earlier next year these are really
dumb
there's air in this cave dark man from
Sky bring era p life
yeah
a Screen Gems aia
you can see the string
no it's me
come to the end of the cave is a solid
wall of ice
now luckily you're invisible shield will
protect you from
well be good for the vodka tonics pound
on the way back we doing something
really stupid again
you to dump spelunking over there
huh
three
this Omar's head in here let's see that
will make it nine or ten to the moon
oh I sites that is a cry for help but to
take the camera boy what's the six to
the moon
don't get caught here's the Old Course
exceed Andrews its unforgiving
soundtracks from are typically American
boy
the magnet boy right don't let anyone
else get caught
all right oh god the Americans in
trouble in his life of the american ok
ok five words first word sounds like
growth the pope of greenwich village ohh
okk fourth work was progressing ask play
all four games
I ask myself before we even started who
is the most likely person to get caught
in a sinkhole
nari America's I got the magic boy at
two nights
some sort of anti sand device apparently
popping porn
yeah
this makes no sense and yet it's working
like that let go my foot rod
except your frame run so kind of a goofy
with general
yippee the thing I'm the hunky American
leader I would've been done
I would lose back there again another
lie me well then
well I suppose over have been a long day
over
meanwhile friend she's having a dinner
party lost everything
he's not do anything that would anybody
believe it or not i am french side it's
202 degrees below zero your return just
in time
this is only the beginning of the lunar
yes night here like day is equivalent to
15 days and nights upon the earth
it will go up to approximately to look
50 below zero and you can move your arm
now be out there now that the peak of
the lunar day and it's hotter than
boiling water out there having LED and
dr. Rochester's boots contributed to a
sinking into the Promised dust and the
way drag is better on the ship answers
which contributed to the death of dr.
William rochester and microphone is the
devil's the application party returned
to the lunar ego because of diminishing
oxygen supply and the necessity to
normalize our bodily processes
so what do you think up on pillows pizza
sir poor bill such a tragic death for a
man who are dedicated
I know we all feel terrible about it no
I didn't say I can save him
yep is always hold to continue up for a
long search
do you think you'll get back to the ship
if they're still alive
if woman can survive just keep praying
I be well we should talk again rod
dear diary he talked to me again more
later despite the adverse circumstances
we are according to plan
photographing various parts of our
galaxy from which we hope to obtain a
new perspective which I for one think is
long past due
captain Anderson to entire personnel
please assemble on a deck that includes
the steno criminal
well come on up professor mittens
control has been broken off as are told
you we are in complete isolation
let's party yeah whoa boozy but seems to
be working perfectly
they are trying to make contact again
yeah okay fine i'm the captain but i'll
just do a use in our Echo one to Center
birth control our magnetic receiver is
working
do you hear a centralized control do you
hear a central birth control
nobody's nobody's removing his food but
we didn't pay the electric bill
say something men's wearhouse we will
not be undersold I guarantee it looks
right part of drippings
it's not Egyptian not African
looks like oriental picture did the
Chinese oh if only we had a big we do
the members are in the series you
recognize that it was it something you
understand and possibly can't be you
know what it is can you translate it for
us at hole they don't know
child no soup with buffet
i beep for the great coordinator the
moon we advising for you return to Earth
at once you have done enough damage
come on come on it's moving again you
have been but the body is for you is
incessantly leave us in peace
here's hoping Christmas fine - well
you're lying you know every thought you
are discussed speak as you do we
communicate by thought ways strong
letter to follow Morgan Johnson story
moon or how they live
when we live in a great sealed city
below
we were just getting dressed in slate by
your earthly emotions you're our new
breed last passions of conquest
I gonna feel bad about are careful you
stay here for you would only contaminate
our perfect form of harmony secrets and
their fate no suffering succotash
they are here they say they are in love
we are studying this curious emotion you
find it
love turns to evil civilians do run
destroy them
you and your kind it's from pat buchanan
remember we have a power we got to allow
you to catch will
this is impossible it must be a whole is
it evil what do you think
well mr. Boone
these symbols could have been sent by an
earth power already secretly here on the
moon seems that Jerry is already
dicky-bird into the cheese factory sir
howard which is the scares away
Dianetics how do you feel about that
that's needed when I asked me how should
I know
I don't believe there are any more
people are you
I'm convinced it's possible my Fuhrer
made it all up to sexual tension writing
us off we get your
what air ball
God hydrogate one of the cats hold on
i'm resting comfortably now
hey give Hinrich the Heimlich
they're attached these jumper cables to
his nipples
well you guys got it covered i'm going
to get out of here
everybody go below please dr. hundred
suffered from a heart attack
let that be a lesson to the rest of you
yeah
ok
my teacher wow you got a sports ball
going there
can I have a live down your crime you'd
be some paper up now
I hate my thighs burn now I cannot go on
being handshape and I no longer called
me patches
what do you mean I would be very much
and i have Nick Heinrich airing older
Kenny anchoring bad poopy and their
mommy wouldn't talk puppy
you are the son of burn our call me
buttons the door little wiped out my
entire family
oh you know puppies oh my god
slide fist him accounted me on my life
for what I did everything humanly
possible to make good as a scrub
what that sure I forgive you stand very
much
and you're still be my friend sure how
about some general foods international
coffee
you're done over there rest now up the
same symbols we translate a pleaser deco
if you lived in the morning you'll be
home by now before I depart we must have
one thing
yams leave behind the two cats cat
geez we're the only can support and wait
a minute
cats have a lost unusual peel for us
yeah but unfortunately we have not here
on the moon
the interest us almost as much as the
two human bead who joined us that they
were delicious by the way
fascinating yeah turn out
no no no no eyes open those doors again
for the two cats
well I think so I'll go I'll go with you
hey come on guys it's me puffball and
tacky command know what I want to get me
water rationing will be out here comes
his command and I got nowhere else to go
down now in the stands and then
No
yeah
Laura thank you
captain's law we're running away as fast
as we can
lost india and omar -
we left the surface of the Moon at 6700
this decision was based on the warning
which emanated from those mysterious
symbols even though we were in and out
of the survival of settlement secret
we had to make a quick decision in order
not to jeopardize our mission
my dove bars melting gotta go so mission
fraidy cat comes to a close
three hours and 10 minutes of flight
were right on the button we just passed
a neutral line operating towards the
Earth's gravitational pull
you gonna sell me down the river to you
bastards and the smaller than fire
single
scrappy you should have gone before we
left
John it's ready get the dressing I mean
that's their early warning system a
cocker spaniel
beat that
they call throw yourself on the flaming
moon rock
Toro Toro
and don't come back it can burn in there
no oxygen
quick-thinking Louie all right you don't
you have the middle you know how about a
snausage or something that was a close
one
I'd better get up really rushing them
relieve themselves and their name in the
gemstone the officers are introduced
into ride when it came in contact with
the goal
would you shut up let me fix it boy oh
not too bad
thank you I can do that I going to be
hit
time to put us in the Happy Chef captain
lou Nariko one to Center birth control
do you hear a centralized control I'm
making keys over
we hear you're honoring the one we have
your position
why did you leave it alone we had an
urgent departure please give us our
position opposite john command center
with control we've lost you
we've lost you sent to earth control
come in
we're not talking to you until you're
back on the moon
all right last one out nobody will be
there when you get there
Clint start and understand it we've lost
our contact completely remember what the
people on the moon said they had the
power to mobilize that well I don't say
that
but they said it could be true but the
girls I'm ready
all lie down dr. Heinrich there's
nothing you can do now we're on our way
back to earth
I used to take off i missed it off like
you know you please
now we're here to talk to captain . 34.3
track
what
yeah
your mom really in trouble or later
listen
it's just like we saw earlier only
backwards . 10 - sexy
no wait i mean he acts
is this the end of captain Chuck hearts
lab
yeah
joining people don't contact her one
over here rod
ok our special today is roast park
that's served with time and wait wait
captain we are being fertilized
zoom in you try can I try one
okay wait wait no wait now no wait
soon -
no it . 5 know
. seven and five tens no wait that's not
it
hold
you got a plan i'll training
from here we go
who
my mother helped Mike Mike but one rule
my kids are not smart always calling me
oh you can bet oh my god my head I'm
okay i didn't know i can do that i'll
make it off our bankruptcy with your
girlfriend is doing so you guys what's
going on
we want you I'm on it he was able to
make sure i got my am Jenny
no read all weird single lady from the
future
my robot friends are not meant to be in
slave from a machine like anything else
they're meant to be used and put on the
shelf and anti-roll but I had to see
blue
I'll be with you in a moment we'll movie
know even though it breaks my heart
I'm going to have to ask you to the part
what you're welcome i'm loving time
oh wow love the rocks
I don't worry guys I'm sure there'll be
another magical mystical singing lady
coming along any time but yeah that'll
happen
come here you little rude little be
right back
holidays everyone
I don't go exactly at her no one ever
ready to move the grammar of course this
captain the way you like the video game
chair
no thanks thank you thank you are boring
and let me stand on my own two feet
see I told you it's only a passing thing
John
I feel that I must advise you there is
something wrong something unexplainable
I know I know what's going on but
everything is working perfectly on the
ship
I'm cold he is everybody whiny what's
going on
usually that's what I wanted to tell you
John outside temperature reading is 245
degrees below and still falling yeah mom
it's no wonder it's called in here
it's 55 degrees remember all the garden
captain quite captain Rick's truck
already
my god Cuba is huge
yeah
right by this thing is moving
oh no that's my phone and not Paul told
you you're as this being rid of soap
scum thanks to thousands of scrubbing
bubbles
that's it
hey wait up i'm getting researching
captain NBC right
it's a little blurred but i think i can
see the picture oh you've done a
wonderful job
well that's some picture
nothing's moving I cram it to eat
something must be German in the TV from
New York try jiggling the cord
yeah
mayor Dinkins declares New York really
cold books tennis inside there is
something wrong with it
it's turned into an artist rendering the
Machine a perfect daughters
I guess Nancy Reagan's back in town
let's see
yeah
it's kind of weather wouldn't even face
the Midwest
now it looks like Jerusalem
this is squash please bring clarence
birdseye is degree
great you do that some sent it needs a
earlier on the way to phrase all
molecular activity
those wishing noises tips we've seen in
other words one be yucky normal
atmosphere by extracting all from
spending but how could that be possible
sounds very simple it's become it is a
principle of the hydrogen bomb behaviour
we'll see i agree with you through some
superior device they found the means of
achieving a place your phenomenal deals
mr. Flintstone
that must have been that strange noise
sweetie I somehow feel the power
gentlemen let's make no mistake our
situation is extremely serious but movie
we are caught in orbit in order to
survive you have to remain at our
present altitude
how long
and kill me find a solution let's go to
work
go ahead we must be naked John I'm
getting on this is radio clash of clans
something like this has ever happened
before
for the past ten hours the North
American continent remains in an
isolation of silence
no contact can be established by any
means of communication with either
Canada the United States or Mexico
I don't like the station intense car
leaving the world the god of every other
nation bound yeah
who's in command that's how we take a
step by if you informed
we now return to miami on the radio no
wonder all communication is shut off
you know I don't think we could even
come down out of our final orbit
I'm afraid you're right away - why we
gotta go
we are insulated we are safe in here we
yes but for how long no I don't know
we're operating now under automatic
control how about the engines Montell
the engines meal I forgot the engines
over worked on
it's only a matter of time before the
turbines give out to you to come so
close to success and such a month
it may work it's if he has to
listen you want to know a secret our
emergency space taxi works on that Tommy
power
right right right we must fashion a
powerful atom bomb assembling and
uniting it's a number of Bartlett's such
as we used on the move
two men drawn by a lot walk into a bar
to pilot the taxi of our life one can
know I'm thinking of purple capital of a
commander of the moment of the crater
result of the explosion might thought
the big freeze
yes but i'm such a one how all the space
taxi crashed through the frozen
atmosphere
sign on penetration market as it
disperses the micrometeoroid clouds
it should break an opening for the space
taxi to go through
yes it could be piloted through frozen
space but but but we have to inform you
that it might disintegrate in the
explosion
that's why i said the two men should be
drawn by left because the night belongs
to Lover's their chances to return to
the loo my e are quite a report
he'll do it Mickey rock is a genius
you got a job
you it is worth the risk to break up the
big freeze which paralyzes not only the
country but the whole continent
you know as I this is our duty our only
hope wanna see me in a towel and
gentlemen
it's our only chance to accomplish our
mission and bring the ship back to it
that captain genetical parties right
well we'll make the bomb i want to have
long played and cheat on my way
wow you using times X the end you want
hard
I'm one be it you know careful now don't
drop it there looks all right
tell the others it's okay now yes go
ahead
hey module due to do you do
what are you doing
i have millions of interesting you
disconnected your crazy man
but you don't understand it this is our
chance to think
still the North American continent with
remain frozen your greatest rival would
be power less i am one with you don't
you see this way weight control the west
and intimate as well
what do you mean we and his friends for
yet see you are not one of us
I'm not only a scientist I'm also a
human being not an insane matter
you traitor i betray no one particularly
not myself
I want to live to you will have it look
out
- more like four deep little stamp
smells like am embarrassed wrestle
the change
oh that hurts when doing there
get up my mittens
drunk girl is under siege you tried to
sabotage the bomb is it all right now
all I have to do is reset the fuse
yeah on pure beef advance
Redmond's against metal
tips of my plastic can I get a new one
good
I'm one to go somebody ate my fudge
achill and i am the other
ebony numbers we choose his ancestors
where's deeds good or bad whatever just
glad I don't have to go
yes you will we meet again
I need several days to get my affairs
together
refund of your purchase price
call now no 600 universal time I'll be
dead
taxi piloted by dr. Eric handwritten
myself will leave the lunar I eagle to
drop atomic bomb 'let's into the crater
of the volcano popocatepetl be capable
you put me back in an attempt to break
the big freeze
oh and one more thing I don't want to
die this is dr. Ruskin signing off
probably forever
can I do and die
oh and the puppy volunteer to my place
I don't recall asking you to pick me up
I can't go i got a family to take care
of it now smug smile
Betty trade that dog for two or three
more lines
this is my secret place down here I only
let my friends
snuggle in - to denounce the no-frills
control panel
ok and dr. Ruskin the captain Anderson
cabin pressure equal ready for launch
cheese about time
penetration rocket going to say that my
work here is done
now you can all just look at my clearly
defined area
open
right 10 10 take your adventure
elsewhere
ladies and gentlemen the budget just ran
out so from here on out just bear with
us
maybe it would be all of the targeting
one minute and 12 seconds
could be dead in 1 minute 13 seconds
first time you called me David
my name's Larry are you my partner is
David I told that you will carry on my
work
you be you don't think we'll survive
this really are as dumb as you look
I don't know what am I saying no we're
not going to survive it works if you
pull out in time
looks like the arena when video
set the bomb release David dancing drive
away
yeah
bombs ready
we'll be over the target in 12 seconds
or the course
holding steady
ready by release clock yes five
why do they need two people for this
don't swallow down
you guys ever sat on a German before
what I mean right on here
dropped it captain Anderson flopped it i
knew the clear trusted
this backdrop is so lad
lemon sisters to get my dog
it was it work
I've never been so happy in my whole oh
oh it didn't work it didn't work
contact this point that the body is
showing up
they're in trouble I say oh man I
refused to feel bad
wet your pants wet mind David god bless
you did today sneeze or going down
whoa that's gotta hurt
it was clearly a stick and ball
journey to the beginning of time
and now my official report the strong
gay
Tom your lie that's foreign for better
you than me
it was the will of God
here we look at this I guess my stick is
shorter than the Germans I prayed
hey brought dogs markings and everything
real parka
John John we are caught in a big freeze
first
it's so cold hold me switching back to
chemical fuel
it's no use it will work
freeze it's filling the ship villagers
are gonna share not bored
John look you know who dumped dry ice on
the console
captain I left the vent open summer look
I'm not a very good captain
ok pencils down with see your wagers
time at coffees cold
take advantage of the big freeze to warm
myself
let's draw straws to see who we cut open
and crawl inside and frozen
frozen in spare all the weather outside
is frightful all sir
is it too late for me to back out of
this expedition so lunch
cold cuts
yeah
has cold enough for you haha
vehicle
the echo of the same symbol when you
translate them
it says you dye job no artist
please please
didn't like the cats iced earth things
now you have seen our strength
stop but we have seen your human
strength and the way you people have
sacrificed themselves to save the others
still you must burn those you left
behind
we have also learned that all your earth
emotions are not evil and look more like
that you have come to peace when your
people on earth
our bond suspended animation which work
noodle and have not been harmed
you're terrible we turned to her that
once and someday when you come back
welcome to me s will give you your
stinking cat's back they have scratched
up our entire planet
hang on
re on me
captain Anderson stand by the director
of the iso back and still alive
I have no words to express how feelings
that you made it back
it's something most unusual has happened
to us in the last 16 hours is nothing
you're not explain it without you have
escaped it on
prepare for landing I did it I saved us
all I'm chunk iron chest and i won
my guest tonight via satellite the earth
so what do you think we learned here
that three maybe four people would have
worked a whole lot better than 1200 and
always bring cats
yeah that's what we learned from Franco
appease moon people
yeah
ok
there now you now here the guys that was
my one shot at happiness my one grab
that brass ring of love
I one shot at true love in this lonely
world now this is a good chocolate chip
cookie dog
Mike magical singing future ladies are a
dime a dozen
you probably have to work again the
meantime letters
yeah I think that's a good idea yeah
this first letter is from melody born
yours or should I must ask you not ever
do that again
oh yeah probably a good idea okay put
that on still store there cambot
this one says dear mike tom crow gypsy
camp out on the rest of the crew of the
satellite of love
hi my name is melody Munoz and I just
wanted to tell you how much I enjoy your
show
I go over to Kim Mathers house every
weeknight at midnight just watch your
show him and I got our whole biology
class to watch it and finding raj now
it's kind of cute
hi i got one more here is uh I got a
couple more this is from eric able to
put this on still store
Eric rights let me begin by saying that
if I could I would have the show hookup
intravenously to my right arm
permanently when I look for a girl
friend what am I deciding factors is if
she likes your show or not wrong
no I'm wrong it's strange but I hear
you're being at all that's wrong
I back off of that hurt anybody this
next one is signed 13 and 12 , and put
that on still store and there's a lovely
picture so if you think that's 13 or 12
i'm guessing it's 13 but it could be 12
30 years ago
huh anyway we are 13 and 12 we are fans
of your show
it's great and everything but there
could be a few changes no no
there we go should rewire crow light so
that he talks with an Austrian accent I
thought about Tom servo his head with
gum ball so that he's not such an
airhead
I think
hey well hey Mon income poops put that
in your pipe and do the Hokey Pokey yeah
now you see there Frank that's the
trouble with relationships their trouble
yeah but Oh Frank I've said no friends
in the house but it's her it's the lady
I can fulfill your wildest dream right
my man
oh I want a course all their dream
Frank nobody is gonna crash here tonight
so where's Michael son hey
well I'm sure she really liked you Frank
that the killer's this has been a
presentation from Comedy Central
candice bergen those center in that live
next
hey boopie
I don't think so
Baldy right this second
a member of the family is waiting to be
picked up with a Motorola pager
you know now hi boy no well his voice
isn't any higher
nature right this second someone needs
arrived with a Motorola pager
you know now thanks for picking us up my
hug me your went
yeah
those fashionable copper ribbons
thanks for coming
the better coming back to come
coming to you
town
around
we're coming
you coke cola sample packs the only real
holiday refreshment
look for this display just off
we frame
it's always on
started in december 18 for two straight
weeks
comedy central brings you our best from
1995 finish this year with a bang
every weekday from ten a.m. to three pm
will bring you our biggest our best and
our freakiest comedy programs
so while your home this holiday season
we make it simple
wake up roll over and tune in it's the
best of Comedy Central 1995
starting Monday at ten
we at Comedy Central would like to wish
all of you out there the very best of
holidays remind you that christmas is a
time to be with the ones you love and to
give to those who are less fortunate
this often difficult to remember when
Christmas is more often use marketing
gimmick
Santa's you sell liquor salesman and
angels sing fifty percent off everything
in the store
we in comedy central celebrate the
spirit of the season and only want to
wish you and your family happy holidays