down 13
dr. Forrest Frank tired like a regular
old
like to experiment on the target shot
we can find
watch them all my can control the movies
and
and breathe
back to help this show should be
mysteries
here
cops check place cards check
fresh guest stalls in both the men's and
ladies rooms
check okay that I'm got the sparkling
pink guava juice and champagne glass
check hi everyone welcome to the
satellite of love dr. Forrester and TVs
Frank are some sort of a major
announcement so we're supposed to
celebrate and Tom here is head of the
party committees
that's right check my you're not going
to wear that it's mike jumper or broke
it
hey that is good
they but I see a question on the party
limited to collect citizens remember dr.
Forrester
they say play what
well how about i shatter the known laws
of physics symbolically run my sweat
socks is a pimply make you the most
how about any 270 miles
Heather to an orbiting satellite you
like that wouldn't you
Frank prepare to receive the umbilical
hey just what are you . science school
you see you're in a geosynchronous orbit
little brandy often
first and right now even a solution p if
you believe is being deployed from the
satellite of love to us here at her
Wow is by physical link and i'll give me
rocket number nine
what in the heck Ramsay is that that
little rolls is
perfect for old ingenious undefinable
for innovative
as a home owner once said the stuff that
refuse
okay cross block off that job
illusion let me quote a great man once
said excuse me while I go to the Scott
from Frank the umbilicus
oh no problem that Frank these are both
male connectors and you just a minute
folks and history will be made her go
down the hardware Hank and get a 38 c
brass adapter
all right hey hey yeah but while you're
waiting for history to be made
please enjoy girls town and history
I don't want to be linked to the puppies
I know tipsy everyone okay go away
she's okay she's smart
a shadowy figure
tonight on Viper
jaguar dealer is just become class so
what a Jag you are you all right
primitive nuclear power yeah that looks
like john deere is really really cool
the combine
he's dating a kabuki dancer
that's one of my fans it was just a fake
rubber snake come back on the shores of
gitche gumee hiding in the most
dangerous game that kind of put me in
the mood
commun almost Flintstone
haha boy that Kennedy compound
she was easier in From Here to Eternity
what is with him harder
yeah man
look if you want to wear my dress just
tell me
I a weasel rip my dress
r is don't you
solution to the suffocating me why you
looking morale high
carrots right now the guys replaying the
date in his mind where did I go wrong
with happen more tutorials for its
shallow roots the common cliff shrub
gives weight easily too gentle pressure
call me a break dancer huh
that finally got males attention
catch up with the Von Trapps what I was
gonna do - what's going on - vanity chap
ready where are you going to Scarborough
Fair
wait a minute uncle Vicki hey chip
where are you ship but down here I got a
crick in my neck
we're hiding ship we know you're here
missing a great view chip chip say sup
with ya
Wow should we go to do with the body
hey think the dates going pretty well
well played around
check the dairy permitted to return to
me go watch your P's and Q's for you
have the girl
just stick to this day this day is done
in there
- is dead again from girls town boys
club
welcome to the girls town some of them
seem bad i don't know I the shoes then
because when they leave
there they are
but they're all in the same cycling
girls night
where God family and industry come
together from girl know how do you do
mr. ranka she plays all the girls
teaching
and Billy Chapin
you know there has been a cast like this
since judgment at nuremberg filled with
Jim Mitchum you can even skip a day
a dick on to you know boy
but with Fatty Arbuckle jr. Larry Fine
jr. and Sammy Davis junior junior you
know robust key was the big prop comic
of his time
no grabowski in their kids
you need to do listen to me girl yeah
you're gonna have the girl
why does it hurt when i pee and cute oh
this guy's just flaunting his bad
driving now is fine you come out with
piece of five girls and girls
dan rostenkowski goes for a drive
congressman be careful congressman
standing wreath on the front in the to
the poster of lab Wow gap
girls
you always fine you'll come out with
peace of mind from girls girls town
yeah but how's the food truck oh I get
it
fashioned hamburgers what do you know
thank you
i crack a window far oh come on it's mel
torme open up
Mills greater with smaller back then
make barley you want her so she's not
home
where is she I don't know come on we
don't lie to me where it is now always
looked 52 . tell you if I did know how
you feel about our dollar ever see this
before
switchblade lipstick oh nice little bit
no dice
mammals building a frame silver pretty
jazzy do give me that that's my sister's
the year the baby chicken shit
all right come on we're silver she had a
date with chip garden and I didn't she
no not really your talent by to go home
right now call the place how would you
like it if somebody picked you are
apples who is she with so much like now
but with the Dragons bad
- all right really I'll be there in a
sex with what dragon the one we can
enjoy and take your Pawnee him he'll cry
don't you check out you're lying
what the Dragons be doing the lake
malleable they're having a party that in
just duel ever marry they
I've got boiling oil or where - there
with you think I'm too young sexy move
yeah and she's not bad
the colors being displeased
shit all right I'm coming like a
youthful job of the hot you later one
he's dreamy I stayed here just like you
told me what do I get what I guess
nobody wanted to tell you shut up
essentially is one fast funeral of rooms
coming and it's too tight Thomas gang is
I can't tell you how old chap 4 i'd
split a little and divide it feel
Clinton did continos world of possible
to get your dick we brought you a bra
that's looking for trouble we're looking
for silver Morgan you found . we're
going to ship tonight
so what you drove out to the cove with
him guess again
flea brain blog actually why I got tired
of you cats with a fast cars slow heads
you give me a pain in the air
that's telling him chick your lipstick
baby
where did you get chips dead this
lipstick was found lodged in his skull
yeah yeah how did I die you
I always told me told that jag real
crazy
wait a minute out of happen whenever a
cliff but not in his jig silver here mr.
pushed him
your query gonna dress yeah but we saw
you run away over an hour ago
you are nuts chicks been here all the
time it's crazy windy roast began
so why don't you guys just get your
little cars and blow
look out he's going to scan sure
come on baby you're blowing with us haha
ho-ho and a couple of trial Allah
brush and I'm a diabetic it son
don't worry how did the state troopers
won't tell anybody
yeah it's teenage on with Les Brown and
his band of renown to rope you could do
all you make son go away you are
powerful
oh right choreography by Jim even listen
thank you dr. shrunk also
Bridge on the River Wow
and Down Goes blades
I never do with the road Scholar come on
it's the battle of the Laura batteries
there can be only one
whoa girl fight when did this director
look into my dreams low
my saber part of the and it's all lights
out cage baptism
this why there's no alcohol at Euro
Disney
hey Hilary whoo baby
well now she's Stacy Koons
yeah
nobody called us about the party over
nick mancuso his head so girls are you
gonna call you grab the Eucharist I'll
wait here wait
if you hear any shootin just pull around
the corner and get ready to go on it
right right right right right right it's
got my mother superiority complex it get
you
she pulled out her uvula oh all right
look wonderful ronica command come in
it's certainly nice to see you tonight
what you were like a scotch is usually
sit down please
I'm I'm sorry got a little problem black
girls
we can't expect operate girls time
without occasional difficulties they
have problems and faster
even with girls who have parents and
normal home life
mother this is one of my girls to meet
paulo you heard his name
we hear the radio even in girls down how
do you do and thank you what he wants to
intern in the non that's the club where
he sings at a quarter after
- you know music I this hotel - 2:30
he called the night clerk no more than a
couple of minutes after he went up in
the elevator and asked the police be
called I didn't want to make trouble for
anybody mother but I thing like this
could ruin me
I had to do something I understand
can I see Sarafina it's sold out bring
in Sarafina Garcia please
you know mother I'm not completely
square but you're hardly in my room and
seeing this young girl in a lace nightie
I did it my way I beg your pardon no go
on the church is aware of the existence
of nightgowns mr. parla all the priests
wear them
oh please it's the fifties you're
looking for chicks you saw you before
last night
how can you say that over there it's
major barbara i love you
you not me - you wrote it across the
picture what picture
I don't know what she's talking about
honest mother she has this autographed
picture of you hanging
in her room this is a picture of Jesus
to my darling Sarafina with a million
million kisses
forever yours Jimmy I guess I do love
her
this isn't my handwriting mother flipper
der Vings I know to me
Sarafina you're the devil spawn you
don't want to get into trouble
contributing to the delinquency of a
minor is a very serious offense
I don't get it what's your idea I love
you Jimmy
I love you Sarafina let's get you back
to Letterman's house
many of our girls are orphans mr. Parker
would you like one sometimes they need
love so desperately they invented a few
hold patents me mother
they hear your voice on the radio or
listen to the phonograph records you
sing love songs mr. part of your roast
in hell for that sometimes they think
the songs are meant for them
tell the truth Sarafina Jimmy didn't ask
you to come up to his room did he
ok it was Snoop Doggy Dogg you don't
want to go to jail and how do you make
them promise not to sing she's having my
baby and you don't want to go to reform
school yourself at least I get some
actions and her to reform school
she's just a kid she didn't really do
anything wrong
if you won't press charges against mr.
partner I can take her back to girls
time is not a kind of reform school
no it's a home for girls have had
problems with the law with the courtiers
can be rehabilitated if they're placed
under the proper into reform school we
used the girls that have no parents so
we tried to help
they're all white and Catholic by the
way you do want to go back to heroes
town don't you Serafina
it's meatloaf night can i don't know i
don't know this was the Golden Age of
stalking
yeah I don't love you nan n suppose I
could not visit you once in a while
okay mother you know
all we'd be very pleased
maybe I could do a solid to feel the
girls all they're being punished enough
would you really sure why not you just
be a real good kid and do it mother
Veronica tells you to
ok oh yeah yes I will
we're married now right the custody of
girls town then you think of the name
your favorite song when I come out
also it just for you do you know white
light/white Heat Jimmy
all right therapy now another successful
sexual intervention courtesy of the
Roman Catholic Church
okay i can still stop you right well
tell the other girls we haven't been
friends all the time we've been friends
for years
this is really healthy you're ready
Seraphia yeah yeah I'm gonna kill
Eisenhower to prove my love for him
you are not coming to saying what you
said
I mean it would be cruel to build up her
hopes sure mented mother
i'm at the club at nights but how about
a week from Saturday afternoon
you're a fine young man Stephen look at
just a minute mr. God just a minute
nothing
my son's dead I want your promise you
she had a date with chip they found her
lipstick and she's really skinny
evidence room to charge mr. garden she
has a dozen witnesses who swear that she
was at Lake Malibu all evening this is
probably a bad wild animals young
gangsters who swear to anything to
protect one of their own
I water tried for murder excuse me mr.
are here let me go to my none of my teen
idol
this is it out
yeah
guys this movie what was that Mel Torme
and all reminds me that galley I just
really love the scat
hey you wanted to escape with you guys
well you could skate to where sick of it
i suppose yeah okay
it's gonna do bottles got to go without
you . he was secretary but I can do Baba
don't get in and get out of you about
skipping back to my Mac we hurry we can
hold out
oh we don't we got commercial so we
gotta go
come out of there to be in everybody's
gonna do that because his doctor
okay sit down silver if you can
this is chip God his father dropping the
charges my son
I'm sorry for you mr. Gardner but you're
dialing the wrong number
no smoking please I'm not installed yet
you're not helping yourself silver will
never understand what my son song you
know
do these explain anything
silver Morgan senior James Polk high
school father in the State Penitentiary
is third conviction on bad check charge
in typing with his whereabouts unknown
active includes with father sister was
on relief picked up three times twice
where after hours once were solving a
teacher he hit me first today is bell on
probation
all right if she's on probation revoked
put her in jail where I can always find
whoa do you want to find me for pops I'm
not your type
young woman you i'm going to convict you
killing myself I have to hire every
detective in the state of California and
I want to know where you are when they
found the proof
no I always thought ship was a sick kid
now I know why
you gonna throw me that just because you
found my lipstick and chips car can I go
home now we have very little holder on
the Clyde
I want to keep this girl in jail if i
have to go to the governor and JJ Kane
all right mr. God not tell you what I'll
do yes she has no parents
mother Veronica taken I'll commit her
two girls town
you'll do what it's not a prison so it's
just the Catholic Church my crime dad
for not having much more of this jerk
well for a start he wasn't the Social
Register is another reason your crime
was knocking down a high school teacher
probation isn't a right it's a privilege
like stretch you don't want to go to
girls know I could send you to reform
school
but knowing its characters kid
oh man shit you think your greens that
was gonna keep me cooped up your tune in
on the wrong Channel
here let me show you the brochure for
girls down it's very much meanwhile at
Monticello no field hockey
wait a minute hey you feel like a girl
hey Kim stately girls down
hey you want a wheel this hot run and
drive races you get with it does have a
six pack my just this girl's ville girls
town where is the prison walls never
have to be looking right now
my name he will remain we conduct girls
town on the honor system
brother learn we have no brothers here
only sisters too bad
come on let's go you and me mano a mano
hey those kids are hip I mean they
really
send me did it do you think so I with
milk were married nothing wrong shape
you can really knock it off
I will miss you up a bit up your wig i
got your signal
where is the cell block we have no self
can you said you had a nice clean room
with three other
well in that just 10 forms child suffer
bell rings at six o'clock i'll have
prime ribs baked potatoes and fresh
asparagus
you'll take hash now come on try again
and or daily meals hayley mills hayley
mills and haley bills with family meals
in we know
hey you were them apples the junior work
our girls proceed from room to room in
an orderly manner
this pad loosely this is the new girl
mother Veronica
welcome to girls time you'll have to
check those at the death I hope you'll
be very happy here
it's real god I'm customarily addressed
his mother
okay if I call you something else that's
a dirty word to me
many of the girls a bitter when they
first get here we break i'll get over it
in due time do the line get it
but where do I park the light come with
me and I'll show you to your room
Gigantor
but yes it's a tribute to British
bombshell Diana Dors less be Peter
O'Toole home that some guys supposed to
be good for you think Jude the patron
saint of hopeless causes he was with the
Mariners if there's something you want
that seems impossible perhaps you can
intercede for you
I stopped believing in Santa Claus a
long time no lupeter prayer
I don't haha but you do believe we can
hear human voices thousands of miles
away
you mean on TV or on the radio so why
wouldn't God hear your voice if you pray
to st. Jude
what's he got to do with it Oh think of
them as a microphone or radar him send
your voice to the Lord's here dudes
wearing a wire
never tuned into my wavelength yeah keep
trying
sarafina's yes this is your new roommate
silver Morgan would you take her in and
introduce it to the other girls
Yes Mother thank you hi I love you are
we married now it's all that jazz
it's holy water what's Holy One
it's plain ordinary water with the hell
boiled out of it and with only half the
calories right here
she's dressed like many mounts only many
times hotter really isn't so bad
yeah ball court going into today's IAM
great
oh that's your bed on the top those are
the lockers in the second drawer from
the bottom is empty so this is the can
oh heavens we call it the crib yeah
starts around here
any what daddy o's females
thanks only the gardeners and father
father know what do you do for kicks
we go to movies on Saturday night of the
end when Benny Hill comes over and
chases around now and they're you in for
what do you mean what was the rap
shoplifting stealing cars and sorting
with short summer in an orphan my mother
and father died
you don't know what kid with your way
ahead
Oh Romulans Silver's I new room
so this is eden flow flows a big hard
throwing softball iced over
you were got any nails
could be what are you in for
wish I knew I'll take charge of these
back
smoking's against the rules we got a
good school and that's where we're going
to keep it will make the beds and fina
will do the watching you raunchy live
get my life back on a slob you just
described my dream girl
maybe you don't bleed when you have not
a chick eyes gonna have to learn the
hard way
the door flow love you and grapes of
wrath you want your cigarettes to come
and get him
she's gonna christen her mmm i wish i
lived off campus
yeah walking and we're gonna do jump you
girls done
how do you like a killer right there in
my locker
the portable rouse think was just you
all up front
that's going on in here we were just
that
rearranging our lockers nothing we're
going to take our showers before i was
in this little make sure
yeah its end heard such a load of crap
now you have any more trouble with your
locker just come to me
Oh we'll be there anytime you want to
return match
you just say so first I want Joe Frazier
well you should have them over more
often
your father
I love you cigarette thing
why yes it is that never smoked I'm
pregnant with Paul in his childhood not
calls the pole
do you know the girls to break
somebody's neck
her father told her all that you do he's
a bouncer in the saloon
there's a log in judo when you use it to
roll a drunk
mark Eden's greatest trying to you and
goes down for I mean really well
Pollock and I pulled off the Brinks job
together . some clothes you bought some
clothes and I killed a guy lost track of
my charge account or something
honor system seems to be working quite
well don't you think I have as much
right to nice clothes and other girls
sure you do careful great Morris is in
there how'd you like to be my henchman
what's a henchman you know buddy buddy
pal doormat you gotta be wonderful
that wonderful crazy cool fantabulous
married for the moon then tab you
we gotta do
maybe contemplates away over the picket
fence
maybe she could tunnel out stupid
recessed filter
no takes and Doran meets van dam in
death warrant like this
I about some fresh-sliced me with it
I'm really waiting really straight
around here aren't you
fresh out of the box daddy-o what are
you doing in girls will I all the
goodies
that's my chariot you speak sling 6 i'm
tapped out for you beautiful
anything that they were nails thanks
buddy
I'll remember you in my prayers my name
is dick told Ain I'm so you know you're
the first chick around here doesn't give
me the creeps
you're the first I've seen around here .
what you don't like saturday night going
to bed at ten that's lights out of this
pad
oh I mean like oh and getting up again a
quarter after
where do i meet you an easy street where
I am right now probably the best shower
ever
yes the tub is mine all mine
but you kinda looks like robes Pierre
with the robot all you see is your child
may be sabotaged the sister Saviour by
planting multiple afikomen obsessive
compulsive cleaning ritual you know me
terrible
yes excite your husband by hiding your
laundry throughout the house really
snapped the curve over the corner then
oh I had adding a shower like five
minutes
you know so many rules how come you made
to this prison camp some dizzy blonde
right my boyfriend and i forgot the one
about turning the other cheek
I mean she's really collaborator you
don't look so tough to me
you do everything this is just a to do i
give them a fair shake they give me a
shape that you do
Randy brewer so she uses a lot of self
but don't eat too much it will dry your
skin
well be sure to use some nice
moisturizer and have to get back on the
back of my hand I call dibs
I've no doubt you could sister and I
have seen your work but remember muley
Ryan what an act but this one reminds me
of her
I have a feeling we'll get further with
patients lots of patients or maybe so
but when the patience runs out
what then pray earnestly sister
before your poker in the kisser ah
rockets are going on meanwhile at father
or Rourke's house for modeling the
latest and Terry fashions maybe then I
think the rich brother stay at this
house ahead
she's playing at being a perv but yeah
what's the address of the nine-oh-nine
Club
I guess this is back on delivery man
made 40k a year so i have a table for
you are in New York Lee and be subtle
evening gown that screams look at this
new pet
would you care for the full pound stick
with the two-pound petites day and how
many martinis will serve it downing this
evening tom skerritt boy
why does that not surprise lonely
I'm all alone
a Greek not in June
I've got the only talented town telling
you
good God
you just don't see rhythmic gum-chewing
i won yet
someone to George Winston done bearded
someone - oh this is so graphic people
woman like place is just packed with
bakery drivers
somebody clap somebody i'll give you my
love
each night
it's just making this up as he goes all
marine band but somebody stop somebody
somebody please shoot him
you in the butt happy just weighed
anchor burger table 3
figure it's gonna be but that cabins
about it looks like a young share
I my fine my first baseman's glove
yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah what was I thinking
I'm all that out well that's smooth wax
that off
I've got everything
except her career you could but I want
someone to long is longer than
in-a-gadda-da-vida 15 songs
bangladesh so yet another season comes
to an end with the texaco Metropolitan
Opera
mr. tinkles cookie crazy
yeah this is from RT Johnson's point of
view he's just lonely one
and say leontyne price
this is kind of good yeah
the platters of them
my salad up soon
I get my calamari please and sing with
your warmth number of jagermeister ma'am
and
martini service I tell you that
sourdough was my idea
boys to men to women
it girl pretty good
what do the trick you got something
against getting cheeky bird
I'm invoking Landers law how do they
support all these bands with just in
customers
wish it this is a smoother almost not
singing where me
no here comes the big move
come on you know when they appeared on
Sullivan they had to be shot above the
eyebrows among them with the camera
rooms as good as the statler brothers
together is over
great come online heard it
what you talking about Willis
oh yes she kept them hmm
oh yes she put him there more whack have
some of the girls town exactly your pals
over baby
you say you took the mother Veronica
route to keep out of the hotel with
barred window
I'm okay and I'm slang here
I felt so scared world
so I ever read any Balzac with this
dragon everyone
strictly us well solely for that
soo Lee now they're just improvising on
what do you mean true or not
well truth is a subjective phenomenon it
if it were me
yeah
break out the back
hey they made up fast you know you never
did show that jerk off the clip it
could've been anything on you you
driving there in your car
I didn't go there and his car either you
heard with the Dragon said you smell
like ride the Dragons lied for you you
have a clear that parks and a lonely
road and practically attacked you
he had a right to defend yourself yes
but I didn't say what are you a cop
are you trying to trap me into something
nothing like that
the most simple bakery driver ma'am no I
remember ships father said he was going
to convict me if he had a higher every
detective in a state of calif pretty
smart one dumb enough to fall for phony
delivery joy since you're 38 but I good
gardener how are you take it easy
you don't have to get mad at each other
just because I have a job to do no need
to level with me and I can generate a
clear you don't know black
say my girls pound is run by an honor
system
what's that well it's just some kind of
Catholic thing you know it's all about
guilt original sin rot in hell for all
eternity is something along those lines
at that time it is not it's about
accountability it's about taking
responsibility for your own actions
you know as a matter of fact I think the
honor system might just be the thing we
need right here on the good old
satellite of love candy
- she was like you usually keep it
locked up and only let us have one
delicious candy bar a day
yeah well from now on it will be on the
honor system you still get to have one a
day but you have to police yourself
well she might can honor really build
character towards the King crow I mean
ever since demosthenes went walking the
streets thank you doing looking for one
honorable man by lamplight honor has
been one of the most notice traits that
we have history filled with stories of
men and women who are not let our just
stand in the way of their own
d personal sense of honor out George
Washington cutting down the cherry tree
is a parable perhaps but it's still in
doing straight how of Honor contributes
to the dignity and the stature of our
nation's leaders you you ask upon her
can build character
well I say to you my friend without
honor would we even have character to
bill without honor we are nothing more
than wild animals
no good at that oh but wait what was
that you were saying about the other
system . i got kind of distracted all
black
I got a little how we got home
I can't walk
when I can really get the groceries away
no no self-control Scooby grow a garden
like a whole hey sorry about the
football
well Jesus help me lift up in the air oh
oh oh well not kind of fault this is
hell week for nuns
top of six weeks of your life but then
you're not
I'm the outcast here three
gags maybe someone else we operated
girls town
we have a regular court with regular
hail the rest of us
the court has the charges and decides
what to do what's that got to do with me
in the witness chair and find out
I think there's a full of weird but
nobody's gonna drag me
yeah well your cookie full of arsenic
and i'd like to take a bite out of you
there and sing shock the monkey
courts in session
I'm full we've got charges against
silver Morgan what are they
this new chick think she's the smartest
thing I ever walk through the door well
she's so smart how come she's in girls
town
uh-huh we got a pretty good thing going
here
there's no walls around us we're not
caged up like a bunch of monkeys and the
sisters treat is real human so what is
this flea brain do
she sassed sister smoking room last
night goes nightclub
she wiped out a chair a little how long
do you think they'll let us stay here
we'll all be locked up in some stinking
concentration camp with bars on the
doors and grease in the hash just
because it's one
fine guess among us thinks he can get
away with anything well this is
Schindler's List know you deny any of us
tonight
I didn't come to this jailhouse to be
heard around by the keepers came for the
food
chicks have gotten it gets we can take
over this place we got
yes we do that's how about you go single
your bunk will crinkle your Chronicle
single your full go pickle your pond
over
guilty verdict say I I suppose
no just no prisoners found guilty she
has to be hung by her bond girl until
bingle want to suggest a punishment
I have an idea running a death Saturday
night and somebody's gotta scrub up this
whole dance floor you missed the bday
flores crab
all right maybe you missed a spot there
yeah come on lay into it there
let's grab the elbow grease please oh
I'll help you
so you dream book and step with a nice
clean floor
why are you laughing at me Susan
you promised me we'd be henchmen
so what so that means i can help you if
i want to the two of us against the
world
I Love You Man oh ok ok don't make it a
big deal
spoons a greenhorn that flow in here for
beauty parlors
what do you mean beauty parlors she's
always getting permanent ways special
hairdos and fancy cosmetics just to
steal to pay for them
haha i'm gonna be beautiful she's been a
million bucks in a beauty parlor
I know it she has to try top LOL vine
hear the sentence was that you scrub up
this floor alone
hey Gloria this creeps got junior
helping your scrub of my mom that up
it's strictly against the rules come
away from there Sarafina and I want to
help
why don't you great he pushes get lost
before I get what it's going to be post
oh yeah we're rolling down that brought
them often girl girls what's the meaning
of this disturbance
she had a fair trial mother the court
sentenced her to scrub the floor for the
party friday then we came in and found
Sarafina helping her
I want you all to leave immediately you
too Sarafina
oh but silver the Word of God into her
it's ok Paul doesn't want me to work
outside the home anymore
I think what was that I said I must
think
yeah I wanted to help her mother I'm
sure you did therapy now
now run along well we have to meet with
the realtor is anyway
also pirate you know and you risk
dickies looking good sister been working
out
say your prayers blondie
I don't need any help we all need help
robbo those other fun I don't know what
gets into young people
it's more than remember you all times
it's a great world
too bad we don't appreciate it it's not
a perfect world silver but some of us
tried to make it better
so bothered you remind me of a story my
grandmother used to take a rabbi and a
priest wants more animal in Norway
called the lemme has a very peculiar
instinct and older one little lemming is
a perfectly sensible creature in orders
one but you get a bunch of lemmings
together and think they start to run and
they run straight to the edge of the
cliff engle they kill themselves
oh are you driving I'm saying there's no
such thing as a bad girl not really bad
just a bad lemming but sometimes when a
group of you get together you act just
like the lemming reckless and suicidal
for no reason
are you trying to say i push that creep
off the cliff because I didn't I wasn't
there for all I know he jumped off like
a lemme maybe didn't need is going to
jump with maybe in this country they
jump off
you're just a reckless lemming you want
to scrub scrub
but don't you see lemons and then they
open I'll forget it
pitch catch the game last night
I sure did I lost fifty bucks would you
have the points prayer in slips out of
the pocket means a cupcake pigment can
go to blazes
that's the time
yeah
you know if they were Baptist they could
have got the platters one
you know
you're alone
he'll only when you find a theme please
the one and only -
cry
yeah
attack at the lock ready for today
cheese sandwich paper path and fork up
at please congratulate her cross-country
team for getting 5th district that is
all
let's see Sarafina anchor
no no all anchor my like the sound of
that movie you know
never touch you Terry your dirt the
music that rocked America gentle to
sleep
sir could you please present your cabin
cruiser line going to have my shift you
close your tab and signed with the car
door these are something that won't sign
your autograph too bitchy to me remember
oh yeah security security people
yeah
short women only danced with short women
as the way it is a matter of his dad I'm
well I'm taking the children and going
back to your mother's
I heard of us Sadie Hawkins dance
doesn't have a KD Lang dance
Oh Mel insisted on doing his own stunts
the first of many burgers today from El
it's john waters velvet hog wire rope or
fruit
what you like and cheese sandwich and a
root beer
- from what report
do they are having way too much fun
student and the Pope stops by for a snap
inspection
are you kidding Oh dance
this is one of those dances with the
girls went up in one side of the room
and the girls line up on the other hand
and all Tom's please
yeah baby change your mind on the right
in the drag race will be today
no dice lover boy I'm a working women
well in one more time through the menu
Tony Randall need to carry all of its
Matt Joyce
it was early early four o'clock five six
I don't know he didn't finish the cheese
sandwich
man I should have the clown burger - 3pm
and still going strong
how could you dance with another woman
on our honeymoon
better take this prevented if you know
but it don't mean it's going to be a
people bab she tries to steal my Jimmy
we're going steady
we don't say you don't love me anymore I
never told her I loved her mother
I know Jimmy serving you've got to stop
imagining me all I guess BP security
unscripted sister go after Jimmy I'm
sorry our party for you had to end this
way excuse me
all right mother i'm only bleeding part
of what time to chip come after seven
o'clock eight was after dinner
what did she say when you told me she
was gone he said don't push me off a
cliff
I don't remember lying again i don't
recall the last to be straight kidder
you know what's gonna happen
the wind up in jail yourself what the
chip say we give me a dime
what for I'm gonna call them in pairs
summertime it doesn't know where I am
stop giving me that princess look when
did she turn into poly holiday
it was going on here what's the scam
it's Sarafina she's taken a slight thank
you better not be my sleeping pills
wow look how cheap frankfurters were but
Larry Hagman what would you put you will
all you want to milk a cow with me
Sarafina wake up we have to keep your
wake silver until the doctor gets get on
our feet and get sharing here shouldn't
sell class ii narcotics in here
mm-hmm
- the chestnuts roasting that's a number
for Cheston yeah
judy judy judy
I can't believe how many girls towns are
there a lot of girls down girls on
furniture
crazy little goon come on stay on your
feet not gonna hit up being bring know
yet dark calm your dog doesn't think
probably give me what i call multiple
people look at all
girl Dale mall girls build will just
reach out and touch someone be dragging
axle
I don't walk every night well she blew
out a knee out for the season of the
walking on Earl's town about it up my
next not getting any skinnier it
and what about check for 56 to that
clear
he's it's a tugboat with people
crazy crazy got the face of water would
come on here and be careful we know
baptize you
swirly
girl problems please hold our fat guy
says you're taking an awfully long time
you wake up video
wake up and running there's anything
around open your eyes Sarafina watches
uppercut
you got to cut me Mick yeah telephone
mr. gray says it's urgent
take over and I don't know any slander
we must keep walking
turbina Sarafina open your eyes are
currently busy the last call will be
answered first and those who prefers
fabulous let's go
if you're using a girl's got fat please
hold the line all property back it up
with anybody
just follow the trail of scat
dumped on that up ready
hello
I know who you are so what you didn't I
know what you're wearing
hello
oh you have to use the st. Jude step
hello godchild
we're grateful to you for keeping her
away but she's dead
I had this phone call there was nobody
on the other end mr Gray said it was a
girls voice it could have been my sister
liar really not as hard as you pretend
to be are you that's what you see
okay if I use the Alexander dream of
what the telephone I want to call my
sister
certainly would you stop with the slang
it's better than scatting operator
information give me jesus on the line
what's the plan well he's everywhere so
what's it about her I guess
mary lee their sector
well then is Geddy Lee there she even
order and she's
it's the jay leno game with Malcolm for
you
: 3 slide and the burden of the Kota mug
yeah
the banks of the beautiful LA River
senior reading cap ready for the big
drag race you are anytime the checks are
ready to continue looks like getting
grants
yeah
helped our main is jazz Nazi swing into
action Nick 10 to meet us go about the
black 2-minute tour Nazis
you can come with you for this i was
just getting away from that cop but it
takes 24 this chicken race baby
you can make if I don't want to maybe
you prefer that I Drive over to the
chilled to the capsule and why me what
did i do well for one thing you should
know one that scarf today
it's not a pussy when you're more than I
just pushed it over the cliff
no I think Lou salty
he said you saw my sister sorry scarp
found her lipstick but then I saw your
face under that scarf today I knew that
the Dragons weren't lying
silver was at their beer bust and little
sister bartered scarf scarf in your
lipstick and her boyfriend
you said you were sure and you just keep
doing what I say baby face and I to a
Smasher
cool Joe Jackson
hey you ready to go Matt and it's not
free
cantina looks like he's ready for
harness trail rules Joey's when a girl
in each car rolling start to get the
flag
hands off the wheel before you cross the
starting line
this black man first one across one of
the florence avenue bridge wind it can t
know if our friend our chicken get her
if either member of the team touch the
sting will be for the car crosses under
the bridge
that's bad thank our losses
driving with their areas or something
then her and him
all right here
that we give out that we surrender
that's funny
yeah
right
not now honey and thank you well battle
of the Las Vegas crooners
now what I brought you with
well it's a nice day for it will ya it's
just good to be out
ironically they have their seat belts on
and the hell is the driver side airbag
kind of a dirty Larry and crazy Murray
here
kiss my pinky ring Torme
they're not women drivers
and we just stop and ask for directions
only dummy brunch
bath I went there but can t know i can
continue know who you're not dead and
stopped because even when he's dead he
still gets fresh
well you guys forfeit all rights change
slang here
so who's gonna make do this little want
to talk to the cops come on
let's get the Jerry Van Dyke and trained
chimp with football sport so
then i will you be doing
it must do Christina's world and grab us
that jaywalker chimera laughing yeah but
i'm princess
tell it to the judge thank you
now what we're prepared to offer you
single silver sit down or slide down
I'm afraid your sisters in trouble
what kind of trouble girl trouble
yesterday afternoon she was in some wild
automobile race one of the drivers was
injured
you gotta let me out of here there's
nobody to take care of her butt and
screws and she's cracked
would you like me to go to the
authorities and see if I can bring it to
the girls time
Wow representing you listen if you don't
let me go out break out anyhow if you
appear in juvenile hall silver you'll be
arrested
it wouldn't do any of us any good not
mr. Paulo is here bring my leather
having don't know that the mother are
very sort of barge in on you like this
but they told me surfing trying to kill
herself after i left yesterday
congratulations i feel very bad about it
is there anything i can do a quick
showing are very nice if you can speak
with mr. Pardo
she's really not a bad girl it's just
that she needs to be loved I can do that
you tell me what the same I'll do the
best I can
thank you oh that's probably god I have
to take this
hello how is just to see your father
dowling say is David don't
the doctors at the infirmary now Elsie
of Sarafina can have visitors
perhaps your visit will push her over
the edge wait for me here soon
there goes one hell of a nun they don't
come in enter
you know I know a lovely way to say how
much you love me all
did you enjoy the party yesterday yeah
except for that internal song
Kingu becomes a dungeon be able to make
with the song cipolla
that mmm what do you want me to kiss
your foot that's a pretty tough talk
business
but ya know you got a nice face what do
you want to spoil it by hating people
it's from what are you here for to throw
that . chick bread crumbs
what does a cat like you with all that
gold know about a kid without a buck in
the world
no old lady no oh man who are you a big
shot over her a kid that didn't have a
buck in the world
no lady no man what are you hand me an
act
you know I don't have an act you should
see the neighborhood I was raised it
you know when I was fourteen a couple of
us broken or pool hall stole 40 bucks
when we tp'ed the plate you doing in
this place paid back the 40 bucks
yes that's one way of looking at it you
see I've got a lot of the street in you
like to read my kids such as in trouble
the juvenile hall
how'd you like to be down there and get
her a lawyer maybe I'll inertia with
merrily merrily Morgan
she isn't 16 years she's just a baby
I'll see what I can do you mean it
yeah I'll go to this afternoon you doing
whatever keeps the books
sure mark that 40 bucks paid in full the
big comptroller in the sky will forgive
you but doctor
get all dead money and mom the baby is
just fine honey teasing you your mental
Serena
no I'm so glad to finally have fallen
out of my mind and I never happened back
you look up the two of you bought it for
me remember
but I want to talk to you I'm never ever
going to love you there's no way you
could ever attract a man
they're better when I was a little kid I
was always alone
I'm just a lonely ball and one secret
wish baby and that was like to have a
younger sister maker try to commit
suicide ever come true
I like one just like you said not so
spooky with pretty black hair and big
brown eyes and a gut full of pills
keep those file
she's dead oh you know Sarafina
if I was your big brother and you're my
little sister it's nicholas wagon you
become sweethearts
but you know brother and sister make off
the good friends we are knee-deep in a
floridian quagmire here is to me
look sir I'll make a deal with you since
day one hundred yards away from you
behave yourself and do everything
whatever Annika tells you to and i'll
send you a record player for your room
with no further obligation on your part
I'll do better than that I'll have the
record company send you some new lps and
some swinging platters everyone oh great
she's getting all like the home game
schools
Frankie's looks don't get to concentrate
of anyone see understand because in
Coolsville there's no hit parade
understand
yes I mental not stupid
pick up
come on shake ok I'm your fucking now
strike
check
by the way the wedding pictures are in
close-up he's really a pots
next
she bought it come on let's scram
yeah I do a lot of good stuff basically
I'm st. Paul of anchor
but you said you were going to help
first step
bottle rockets please God just one more
hit record please aunt ant ant ant ant
ant
she's good
yeah
you
if you sing I'll become a personal
representative of Satan so help me
what are you doing
that
why are you looking at me at it
what should i do I don't have some
nervous
Oh everybody
you coo Marie but his special lyrics by
semicon
Wow and the 15 in like crazy here I
gotta sit down
I'm not bad at all
oak and is driving all hope from her
soul
now I remember why I left the church is
the believing what time me
it is
yeah
like I'll come women don't look like
maybe Van Doren anymore and they do it's
just that styles have changed so you
don't hear about huh
so women who look the most like the new
style are considered the schools
it's stupid but yeah so say it's 1953
and I happen to look like TWiki
I have to keep my job at the cleaners
and till I became stylish in the 60s
yeah I guess so you know it's all up to
the media they go and change Styles
without consulting us they think it's
funny
so in the future it might be stylish for
women have wings oh hey why wait start
sketching my a great then let's smoke a
butt women in the future
women in the future my basic woman ok
huge ferocious wing but a fire rainn
yeah no I think of the future women will
adorn themselves with Mexican tiles
they're stylish yet easy to maintain
that's too far in the future
okay Nelson add-on huge island yeah
picking up to roll up in and hide out oh
yeah and power take-off and she's got a
power take on an air conditioned cap a
lotion dispenser all complete swing sets
Cadillacs passing to the north star
system
nobody world commercial sign in 15
seconds
man we gotta go what you got there pal
well you guys I have a feeling that in
the future women all pretty much look
like maybe
yeah you make a good point my friend not
throw some wings on yes like boots and
our takeout I can't tell you how much I
believe in that power take i'm in
response to media pressure women will
dress like pencils
we'll be right back
and
one of them Paul Anka mass but usually
things
uses pomade from awards
oh ma
and I'll do the head tilt
second verse same as the first
it will
all right that was ave maria going out
to our lady of perpetual groove in the
meanwhile at the hotel New Hampshire
mmm poison ID for the following a friend
mmm
what happened I went straight to
juvenile hall from here and Clyde told
me a lawyer been in the bail her out
and you know I thought everything was
just fine but my pants are in this
morning to say try to reach his sister
at home
she didn't go look it's nothing to worry
about
he's checking with the Lord Alastair the
bail money came from I've gotta get out
of here I've got to find him
looks over easy but I think you gotta
play it cool
can expect Clyde to tell you anything
especially if you left this place
without permission
Paul Anka . promise to call me as soon
as he finds me when he does i'll let you
know right away
that's a promise yeah and count on me in
fact i'm bringing sarafina's record
player over tonight
i'll give you a report that a very Maria
huh come on Bobby
Stewart killed me
happy on papillon you didn't finish your
beats princess no dice you can't keep me
here
rather go to jail is real high look you
know I didn't mean to her tip it was
trying to you know what he was trying to
do to me not look the guys are out
raising a couple hundred bucks them when
they get it will take it out south get
your job with the headhunter hostess
yourself
go on get up those stairs go on
dad I don't don't die don't die
operator i dialed orchard for 2 12 to 10
times
yeah I can't get anyone to answer what
you want me to go to the house and into
the fried feast at non scared
mmm so where's the Go button oh you know
there's clown burger wrappers everywhere
french fries on the floor well it's not
very good at holding people hostage yeah
you know
hey remember the double clutter or grate
the carrots it's not secret best known
as a little bad carburetors well as
you're going to play Bach crap stupid
dirt
Smith moody blue and gray may help you
here's the file on Thelma Jean my office
Monsignor is waiting mother you may use
my office as long as you like silver and
i'm already here
where you be what's the over it's ok
take tell mama all about it
I didn't want to ride with them and that
drag race but he made me who made you
God made me read one of the jag game but
how could he make you go
I'm a line you know about me and chip
chip Douglas you champ tried to tell you
before but I was scared sit down and
shut up
maybe it's time you level with me
you know how we're both hot
we remember the night just to chip up he
died he was real sore when you didn't
find you and then he died and he asked
me to go in your place
I'm gonna kill the mood I was good thing
I was too young to go anyplace in my way
and they killed him but he got all did
great
I was fun at first I only kissed me he
wasn't dad them any the hype started
you killed by me - fresh and I ran away
really
chip got me and tried to throw me down
on the ground right before you got that
you don't have slipped out from under
his feet and he became killed fail you
died
so that's how they find my lipstick in
his car for his friend come in
he's not good so how it happened i
thought it was you at first
we barely saw me again like you did all
that time you've been letting me sit
here and jails
sorry it's over I tried to tell you the
first time I game right out of the back
yeah it's all over the head just can't
believe you went out with chip
laughing at that something in Dilbert
nevermind other women damn it with a
clear buddy yeah
just forget it
scared friends trying to send it to you
want to trade me for a chicken
21 maybe I could push her belt over a
cliff by the sea freight his dad will
take the car away from him
if you find out about the drag race you
mean that rat which is a
fifteen-year-old kid in Mexico to save
his hot rod men
it's going to give me two hundred
dollars big to you around two are
sisters
let's beat cheeks
mmm
I never have it you want to talk to nip
and since we're just don't you go out
the same way you can you take me to the
door i'll meet you at the highway
ok hey wait are those my dungarees
it's a rod yeah my ride probably still
around here someplace
agent double all happen to do
where do you think you go out no you
know you're staying right here
bury yourself back to the pad tiger
there she did my way
one of these silver the council had a
meeting
who cares about you and your phony
console we care and we decided nobody's
going to bus stop
listen I've got my sister she's in
trouble
your sister my mother my sister my
mother it's my sister
normal people call your local drug with
I see a guy with a dewlap in a triumph
that's all I don't feel a thing
but that what this thing and now it's
saying there was no thing with it that
was that was no thing
not everybody suppose she's telling the
truth
hey thanks for coming down tonight
supporting live liturgy and say what can
I tell you about myself
well I'm st. like a big girl medallion
fucking kidding of course
listen say to move you supposed to help
people who haven't got a chance
that's me I haven't got a chance of
God's world level wants to do ask you to
your house for coffee
no Morgan praying I don't know
one more of her phony baloney Mortimer
Snerd
any chance of all I believe I'll tell my
fellow Mounties
wyd statute doesn't work anymore
you were little you know I you 15 years
old and they're shipping her to tea or
water kidnapped sister
they've been keeping your prisoner the
Jag speech pet with a kid fell off the
cliff
there's Rachel testified gets them santa
claus silver
Jimmy's outside he just drove up his
back from fighting Nazis on the moon
we got transportation maybe we can still
catch them
I haven't seen it praying with my own
eyes let's give her a chance girls
yeah you want full go with silver all we
hit the mother Veronica gets back
little girls suddenly there in a leader
I unit and then going to find Jimmy and
tell them that they haven't stolen his
car just borrowed it
check so anyway I wasn't very popular so
as a freshman I had to work extra hard
to get on the wrestling cheerleading
squad
here we are they're here parks are you
block the road
angels I need you to go undercover as a
high school girl
st. Jude is coming and he's packing heat
maybe we can help you - hi this is
looking to bring the band we cannot
believe she did this house is on the
national register of historic hideouts
Nancy Drew mystery
damn cape cods do good
nobody expects the spanish because of
what hole did you crawl out of
I came from my sister you came to the
wrong tools out the window when you
pushed her in that keyboard your little
skull blow the only way I blow is to
blow the whistle on you
Wow sure baby you just do that little
thing called the cops going to land
right back in the clink
maybe so but I'm not leaving here
without mary lee
not without my daughter she's gone you
suck it
if you send that little kid down mexico
way I'm gonna wait i'm going to say
sauce pressure on a team right
how do you see any t-birds out there now
my sister is a 16 year
you know what they do to you for
contributing to the delinquency of a
minor your and they all know what they
do to you for murder
revoke you do laughs yeah
please write mother Veronica will be on
time to be you must have paid we'll get
you to the köppen time for your gig
here Jimmy
this will strengthen your faith you got
a weird theology mother
that's my minutes oh right right on
woman
oh wow you'd seen me to sneak by here
thanks Sam Peckinpah six degrees of
separation
okay you just won yourself a one-way
ticket itself let me guess mexico veil a
creep early haha yes go on seating find
the world
you just wait till his nuns and croquet
mallets
well just back through the door here and
nothing to see anyway -
you can go and what happened in there
I felt a dark dumb jerk
thank you skulls chips old man's got a
private eye on this case now if i can
find out that really pushed it over the
cliff the detective can too
unless we get her out of the country
look you know I didn't mean to hurt him
he was trying to attack me so I run
after me
nobody else did baby chick you just
remembering check if I say he was
attacking he was attacking if I say you
pushed him you have pushed him
I'm al can we go talk about this by the
cliff we ought to be friends are you
good friends and if I say you could not
marry me i can make more trouble for you
then you can't for us
so gain weight hello well that's the way
you want it
uh-huh oh my well I'm glad you decided
to be friends you know you're not a bad
look a little de minutos to the rock in
Betty Lou's patios and always had eyes
for you right now there are moments like
this at every house hard even just like
your head now say that almost looks fun
all these guys are confusing romance
with football
that's the problem we do my home
all right let's start again you get your
potato and patios and that you're going
to get hurt
show me lover boy
oh that was pure Emma Peel
whoa - OH evening a jake lamotta is now
now there's going to be some real ass
kicking
now i'm going to split your head open oh
now its records Roman Catholic
restaurant that the age-old struggle up
in jazz you want to finish him off
sister
what's with this guy he's the only one
that knows Mary didn't with chip over
the cliff and we can solve the Rubik's
Cube yeah
nobody's gonna believe this babe that
looks like you're gonna be a witness or
you gonna be tried for kidnapping you
know what they could do to you for
kidnapping which way would you rather
have it
which way ok please that's where my
velvet fog emanates browse all run out
of the cabin trip it was chasing her and
she must have been defending yourself
yeah he's not really - he was but he
gets the job done
you heard him whether vodka we are
reading
and if you don't know what to do with
that baseball that I could give you an
idea
sister you're gonna rot in hell but I
love you
I was incredible is this the place i
have an appointment for a facial and
pedicure
where's the water there isn't any
goodbye so goodbye sister Grace all
those in charge
ma veronica was in charge of the
attorney word to me
you learn I've already learned too much
cat
that's why I'm here live does up where
we alone
contd flaws
we've come to say goodbye summer
I'm sorry forgot the leading the
Thanksgiving pageant baby chick
I'm happy now silver really happy i
found somebody you love ya
I'm happy now really I'm glad it will be
a wonderful thing for it
she'll have two years and the novitiate
to make sure
good bye baby whoever you're still my
hinge
I'm happy I'm really happy and you've
become my henchman too soon
ha goodbye
that mother actually the name is Phyllis
good lucks sisters silver wouldn't have
sounded that pregnant
habit listen to me girls
yes watch your P's and Q's uh-huh oh
you're gonna have the grass so long
suckers
have you back - you
brands
he survived from girls down watching
season man i'll never know many girls
need love too many girls we can do if
they're not attend the two
yeah let's go savage a new girl
the whole lot of hands happy you can
always find one of those girls girls
town
yeah
elevator once again i just like to say
how monumental this history-making event
will be the link the linking of the
whole umbilicus after and the departure
that give me that Frank a little crush
and in conclusion I can
the world the first Earth tethered
satellite
haha open 2012
dr. shall i send up the ability pod in
the ability port to be that Frank I am
parked this vessel unto the heavens and
I think I hear something coming inside
supposed to smell like banana cream at
all
Frank I dr. Clayton Forrester figure
welcome
what knows of you from the far reaches
of space from yeah don't push the button
Frank Frank I'll give you three seconds
to stop licking my face counts low
you'll tell everyone to go home right
now my polling place