mystery science theater 3000 show 508
real one in the future
the name show different
you owe me Moloch another face
good job cleaning up the place to shine
yeah
cheesy
the worst we can find
watch this all day
there is my jewels
use those actual
free and other
back
it's just a show
sweet
yeah
all now what is this a whole this is my
2nd grade piano recital and chips you
wake up changes are you actually get a
feeling for what it was like to really
being there
oh yeah this is really our job either
fascinating who took the
I'm called Roy all the other guy with
the mold Brian excited gypsy
so cute everybody welcome to the
satellite of love you can probably tell
by now that you're just transferred all
his old home movies the video tape you
know what I think this is that picnic we
took up to caution on model
Oscar miles can worry about time served
salt so watch what I do not gypsy check
this out
you pull the shorts down dog that's
money you know they are this many kids
there no that's Brett and Brendan there
Brian and bridges kids minis kids are
already and Tony right and free so yeah
this is fascinating and we don't go in
too far
Hey look what I found swing choir choir
whoa haha the world right
explain to me again how this bulky racer
fell out of the closet and onto these
home movie transfers when the closet
isn't anywhere around here
yeah weird isn't it yeah yeah
no matter i've got duplicates in my
footlocker not
yeah yeah I know I found those tall
Marilyn McCoo Billy Davis jr. calling
crawl
Bob Joel I wonder if you would indulge
me today at Frank's been down a bit
lately and well when the poor fellows
not shuffling head down through the lab
he's locked himself in his room watching
old misfits of science episodes so to
pick him up i thought i'd let him do
this week's invention exchange really
put the spark back in
I'm ready for this week's invention but
we're ready for your Frankie right
my invention exchange this week
these fully lined leather sprinkler
pants that i like to call lederhosen
hozan now I can shot - while watering my
plants in my lederhosen in hose in
lalala lalala lalala lalala
hello love haha i just do want to wear
lederhosen ok
it's a stupid man should i had better
I just got to be / variant for one brief
shining but it is that so raha
I'm trying yes it is wrong deeply wrong
but you've been under a lot of stress
lately
tell you what we'll get you and helping
the horn with that make you feel better
yes no why did you move on with your
invention exchange gym
it's joel and if you'll indulge me or
hind earnest I'd like to turn over this
week's invention exchange to our own
crow T robot
thank you all the vulture long
associated with pestilence and death is
in reality a clean and helpful bird who
is quite easy to get along with so to
improve his image i invented Sarah the
bombing buzzards room
yeah based on the water drinking bird
this friendly carrion eater cleans up
roadkill or table scraps that's great
crow that kinda looks like you crawl but
I think you'll agree there are a few
sights in nature as beautiful as a plump
member of the Cathar today family
pulling a sin you a string of fetid meat
off a week dead Thompson's gazelle
there's a theme song want to hear it
oh sure curl five and Buzzard com
go call five advisor ha ha ha ha
bothered me deep what do you think she
hurts me deep of your movie this week
Joel stars the listen to see the cola
well thank you Frank would you just get
back there
your experiment this week Joel scars
Sean Connery's brother Neil and more
than happy to tell you that it's called
Operation double double oh seven and now
i have to strangle frank with you
Robin visor cough cough cough micro yeah
really deep it around assault on a queen
the Danny Bonaduce story
it's me maybe
neon the birds
good thing they have an espresso machine
get over here and turn the music down
how like this
all hands on me
time to do it
it's tuna salad sandwiches
yeah
honey
is there anything this guy doesn't do
power
I sailed to Tahiti within our girl crew
like that was this wet t-shirt
oh you know when there's four people on
a screenplay there's gonna be trouble
me
the one
you know I'm suddenly hungry for cracker
jacks and I don't know what
he sat on his glasses warms she would
like to get permission to come aboard
he likes to wear midterm means he's got
a deviated septum down
he gets his haircut on Tuesday
is he prefers stopping to potatoes
Turner and who are ready for a sec e
close me just I can't possibly live up
to the song they wrote about him
probably just on the comp named Wallace
so you're saying you like this guy
no no please don't hold back how you
really feel
women who sing too much to put the
missing about
ok
port of call Cindy
yeah
now this is one naughty Navy we do more
hair and makeup before breakfast and
most people do all day
it's the old spice guy
it is
must be one of those airplanes I've
heard them talk about you muchly
haha Paul Williams lunch box stay there
my friend
no one else has a lunch anywhere as good
as mine
we now return to ship of fools
ok
excuse me
totally
huh you know William County read where
they could watch a letterbox virtual he
wants to change the channel does he get
another woman
oh yeah she's well being is bad huh
oh the wrong room
should I come back
hmm
yeah
oh thank god has that we're going to see
is naked butt
thank you sir I'll bill your room hello
I'm earth Griffin
how is just going to press pause but
yeah
what's it like being the TV Cindy well
it's better than pho being is back
now showing on my back Morgan Stewart
coming home at two four six and eight
yes may we help you - hi how are you
yeah
this is one great motel 6
I have a life thank you for touching me
sir that will keep me going for the
entire day
alan r is this your robe around the pms
pinafore
someone's gonna programs good
it's been nearly two minutes since
anyone's fondled you sir
so that's for you to tell him I'm not
here
great block really be
yeah
wait a minute how is it that he gets
color on his girl but only black and
white on his TV huh
what's Moneypenny doing there isn't that
a conflict of interest
oh that's nice they have a bar sign up
for the pie
ok
they have a very loose dress code of
this business
thara just the one
Mike Lee
mom this is sister on the back of your
head
yeah
appearance sit and spin
come in under beds
Johnny Astro real radar
Claude Rains popsicle ection tells the
world to eat his desk he who james
brolin in the cock
Michael I want all episodes of Captain
nice band
oh my God he's gone bananas
yeah
this is Bob going to my imminent death
hole
yeah
a Screen Gems presentation
boys Waldo pepper thanks for the all
clear Moneypenny
suddenly she's a coffee table
you know i love my torso
no no no
I think I know why thunderball was a hit
you never saw him kiss anyone in a
little
this is really brave or reporting to you
live from Krakatoa east of Java
they're coming to a close
there might be turning in there
I've got to save them
soon such smells good
Hey look what I found I think it's a guy
but he's catching now
better call Paul Prudhomme
I'm gonna run on the sprinkler will be
thinking now we know there's probably
nothing but Bastion in there
yeah
let's go me is so thick and put out this
fire
our guys I'm gonna go start lunch all
meet back at the ranch sandwiches again
ok
too late instead all right don't be
getting out of here
let's get the money
quick some lip blusher
all this game again
thanks really appreciate your help
well why I should trust like finding
rubble
Mustang Sally you better slow that
Mustang down is speaking
what died in the explosion is that ok
the box with me
ok right now let's get to work on his
girlfriend and the Japanese oh and have
his Secretary's week I bought you a god
how will you make it on your own
it's up to you know who this time I want
the girl alive
I've got a few questions - Oscar
oh and lose the Ringo hat
yeah
here you're not wearing any pants
the banks of circle pines
no city ordinance all buildings be
painted
get Christie war see this is what
happens when you Bob for french fries
gentlemen here we have a practical
example of the theories i have
Illustrated I suggest we execute that
weeks ago the patient you see here mr.
Shue go
sustained first and second-degree burns
at my hands on her face as shown on the
slides
i'm looking for a fang me here from
edinboro last week when i saw this
girl's condition but he decided to
operate immediately before scar tissue
began to form
I'm glad to be back here in time to show
you the results of this operation
personally it's great to be here thanks
for supporting live surgery and testing
you know Michael Jackson's journey is
complete
a miracle in plastic surgery don't you
think America
yes plastic surgery m she's turning
Japanese I really think so
the results are due not only to modern
surgical technique but also to an
ancient tibetan process defined as the
hypnotic process of total recall it
differs from the usual hypnosis in that
it allows us to operate with the
complete surrender of the subconscious
universe obtain their patients
collaboration cpanel dr. marquee to you
my booty Shotter home capture card major
mountain yonder asking on a 10 minutes
yeah
our whole sakai the doctor her phone was
asking me if it would be possible to
make a demonstration of hypnosis of
total recall
no this experiment requires the outlay
of a great deal of energy
why don't you try it why don't you buy
no no not the young lady
her heads too big excuse me doctor I
really thought that I was just
whispering
actually it's my fault I didn't hear you
but I am capable of lip reading i would
say the young lady is not an ideal
subject for this sort of thing
she's hot it appears to have unusual
willpower I'm afraid he would take too
long
I found that out the hard way however we
have mr shikou with whom i have already
conducted experiments of the same type
and it would simplify things it miss
your show go would agree
Thank You mr. Connery's brother right
what if anything
gentlemen please watch Neil rock music
can hear the waves
all right here's the church here's the
steeple open the door and go to sleep
the sixth sense with Gary Collins
the powers of matthew star
you know is rick wakeman on the premises
at attention and
well the cast of jacques brel arrives on
the scene
yeah
Thomas yes you go has lost direct
contact with time he thinks she's in
translator in the water warm right up to
the present day is at our disposal
it can be totally brought back if we so
desire because every experience she has
lived through has been registered on her
subconscious or from the air void of
precision than the most highly developed
electronic brain let Spencer
subconscious only enough for now
what are you doing leave her alone I
ever tell Tuesday
yeah
well Rodney King verdict just came in
Nancy Sinatra's kicking ass
: lots of her fights back
not exactly Jackie Chan isn't it
everybody stop flipping and not a
hundred please
you hurt me you know i can read lips
tight I can't let them read lips right
now
yeah
naughty little girl
Sam Donaldson
sales from the darkside me coffee in
there quick
it's michael caine look out but that was
easy geez I'm already running ahead of
schedule
our wonder who that is everybody
we just came to beat everybody up we're
leaving now thanks
I hate to be interrupted when I give a
lecture or John fries dead
this man is dead no duh yes
unfortunately I found myself distracted
so I use the sublime attend me don't
tell me doctor that there's anything
that would be able to distract you
oh yes for instance when a charming girl
keeps gazing out of the window wall
brawl is going on
good unit it's your fault if my jaw is
broken
I'm sorry but what can i do to make it
up to you meet my house
what do you want your hands through I've
got an idea I think you should let me
marry or season
yeah
Jules really gone off the deep end this
time
all i know is in this up that I feel
like a total femme
you know what I don't have a problem
with it you know well I definitely
yeah
all right time for my daily back rub
who's going to do the honors Joel
none of us have working arms I know
yeah
Hey Joe what is that thing
it's all part of my diabolical plan but
it is a useless prop that you built
it's not even connected to anything I
know
yeah
joel is there a point to this I've got a
lot of work to do what you are telling
us what this is all boat
that's so you're ruining it for me
yeah
it appears to me really fun statue lie
no wait until the judge gives his
verdict
what else can you do don't forget we
have a corpse to deal with here
court this issue goes disappeared to
sorry dr. Todd Lewis College remain in
our disposal until the investigation is
over
how long will that take we're moving as
fast as we can but please don't set foot
outside the limits of montecarlo until
you get the okay from us but i have to
go back to columbia university i have
some operations that are waiting
I can't remain here indefinitely with a
former Miss Moneypenny sir
your highness there's your man come on i
hope you'll be very happy together
oh he's hardly Sean I realize but he
comes cheap the Osterman weekend
mr. shooter was right that's an ugly
beard
you can see the resemblance to john
saxon thinks I'm not so sure that really
I don't think he's quite so good looking
look
oh yeah I don't shave the beard off just
to make sure
just peel it hard is my name attached to
it I wanted to remain right there
and furthermore I'd like to know what's
going on here
I'm coming and I like color espionage
for Western Europe man on the open kids
is Miss Maxwell my assistant
you're the brother of our top agent
michael ovitz so i think we can trust
you
I mean we can eat and eat the flirting
non will get it
mmm Swiss steak for lunch lucky guy
I'd like to make a confession i think
your heart but the an hour day Barry is
not funny
I should use mission turn your head
you're fine drop that night you mind
behind walking with the sea have a fur
ball or something . i said i am the
walrus coo come chill
you think I had her in eighth grade
now time for his catheter
she's a Liberty gibbet of the with cloud
I want this problem called Maria taken
care of
permanently sister Mary may have a
father to me for I have murdered yea
though I walk through the shadow of the
valley of death
make me happy I'd oh she is good
there's a role for women in the church
this isn't doing it for themselves
sin and the art of archery this handy
hostage packs into a compact 9 x 14 case
hard case also available
she's making a human burrito
make it snappy sister we got all the
pickup's come on our marital our journal
boy a shelter that jump cut right about
now
Lord protect my work reflected in our
view the crowd yelled estate where the
dick toes square veiny did it open did
order to boot Wow
is this a documentary on how to do this
whatever this is
she's a start on you know I saw get
interviewed on the SyFy channel
she's consented to an outward bound and
this is the result
now this is when you sit back and watch
it all come together
it hurts but you in the ambulance
Turk 182 will ever back tomorrow
human cleaners will clean your humans
overnight
doesn't your room same right now let's
review the steps on how to run a hostage
down overall
could we stop at a baskin-robbins
holder Repole clergy dr. Connery what
you look at that photo
it was in mr. Shue cos bag she said you
know him
it's ward Jones he was planning to marry
her then I showed up I met him when he
took my course and hypnosis
the one I gave in Japan a very capable
chap thinks he's a chicken star jones
killed this morning
what's been killed by the same people
who tried to kidnap a sugar rush rivalry
she's back in our hands
what had important information he was
the seller's unfortunately was killed
before he got it to us actually ward
asked us to protect your she could
because he'd given her some secret
information and he was afraid she might
be in danger
now she denies this absence of barnaby
jones rapper and I'm inclined to think
she's telling the truth but we can't
find any explanation of these museums
then I'll explain it to you what
happened was just isn't a special yogi
technique quite complicated but very
effective briefly it's very possible to
communicating and eating in job new
state of hypnosis of total recall the
subject himself doesn't know he knows
but he would be able to repeat verbatim
if he was again hypnotized to the same
extent
what do you mean that's how r June's
precisely you're well it's clear ward
use your shoe co as a human electronic
brain a sort of impregnable safe to keep
his secrets in go go go go
save that you know how to open of course
I'm sorry but I can't help you I'll be
too busy for the next few days
my doctor all you have to do is to walk
around mother Carlo the next few days
and so the police decided to let you go
and Richard out and if I help you out
you'll get me out is that what you mean
freedom always has a price tag attached
to it all
oh I guess what early is I hate that
suit
he's had it poor guy
I've never seen a nice like that before
one side the scalar and the other thing
for any kids
yeah
died listing to rush you want well put
it in a projector right away
a man had time to get the photo
a pocket-sized machine that goes ping
this is the GF murder viewmaster sister
Chuck Yeager that flower actually tastes
pretty good pictures and it's
planet us by nettles one of the most
powerful gangs in the world they beat me
up when I was a kid so they're mixed up
in this then
what kind of a hospital a running here
this is beginning to appreciate
everybody bring Sean in
a spy movie is starting to sag and
asthma is there
looks like the bigfoot video same stride
the Alps are beautiful but dumb
from the street this place looks really
small but from the back is huge
Wow good god i'm likely scared my own
children out of the nursery today
I decided we're ordering from
schlotzsky's standing in front of a drop
of the world
we're ordering lunch what do you want
excuse me I'm three minutes late
that's okay we're a pretty loose group
I said
is three minutes late
gentlemen start your engines operations
like Mellie is drawing to a close it's
been a lot of fun for all of us to carry
it through a successful it suddenly they
control the world's gold reserves
requires on 43 different that up sponge
for me sir
here represent the gold reserves of the
six wealthiest nations of the world and
your respective duties are where it's
alright to lower the six powers my crap
you're real I gentlemen I'm binding that
this is the greatest financial
undertaking in history who we trace the
japanese girl she's in malaga missed
being if you mean you want me to go with
you to Spain I can't accept the
invitation but it's a quick trip and
pleasant
sorry but I won't play any spy games if
you let them snatch your sugar from
under your nose that's your fourth
take off the tam-o-shanter wait a minute
you come back out now I have a cable
from the Minister of Health Minister for
anyone but my orders for a month
seeing I like you you like me luck
Minister of Health and operation double
girl scout
I can't read that's an order dumped
well guess my whites cutters are so we
have time to change
7 i'll be waiting the valve user how do
you have a plane to catch
waiting in the Baja the broad
I'm going to get to I well
just hanging out in the organ hmm
have you lost anything yeah it's a third
of my dress
the button came off very thought to bow
she has handles thank you it's very kind
of your dorm and a reward
oh yeah can I get your brother's
autograph come on got to you were
playing to catch one second there's a
reward I must collect you just remember
your name is Neil Connery not getting
the plane to leave your child open
Max's wedding people the airport
that's our below double entendre
I hope I see you again I think she's
neat you say good blood and now and it
sounds like the british invasion is
waiting for a flight out
and when you deplane and model you will
be greeted by manfred mann
he should be leader
I have enough time to beat up the band
they call it the mercy be in five
minutes you'll be screaming for mercy
thank you
the plane a penguin song
it's money but he pulled for 20 people
at ok
Alex will you marry me the telegram just
came and I left my dear little pride
Consuelo and all of the other guests in
front of the church
you see max I'm getting married today
car Moneypenny where's your shoe co
watch me dance oh not another Bowl is in
love at first sight I to a few boards in
where you lost them in my necklace is so
sweet to see you again doctor
hey it's Bernie from 22 to conquer
you're so very kind as usual
my pleasure having very kind by nature
all remember the air by jims why don't
you remember
hey who's your favorite clown although
ok that's me
dr. sorry my husband bang
this friday on streets
this must be the traditional called the
gambling money
what get some air fatso
well it's a little drafty in the winter
but you can really stretch out
he shook this isn't how we left it with
you
he who withdraws the blade is Right was
born King of England has been here
some guy with a knife but worker she
didn't have anything to do with this
but this is not yet you go there was no
your so called she's a double I tell you
a good double but that's all solid
double down the line
are you sure positive I know her pretty
well I've operated on her face
that means that they used her as bait to
keep us off the track
are you gonna marry me or why I want to
find the reader schuco and still alive
I have a feeling you'd better begin
moving fast don't don't
but what if you lost this time lost my
lighter and my dignity
do you ever walk upright like other
people pantsuits from The Mary Tyler
Moore collection are a lighter where
would I go
ok it is huh excuse me huh
yeah it is up you have a nip the
cigarettes man in front of Sir Walter
Raleigh
yeah
plant plant
my reward that's it
you've got gorgeous eyes you know do you
really like them very much and i have
one
all kneel this isn't right I don't think
that she's got a key
secret agent John Ivan Palmer and now
you will do whatever i want and you will
tell me everything I want to know
let's talk hockey and you must obey me
who sent you here
Bennett awesome yes lip-sync it was
their chief every day Wow
nobody knows the trouble of Syrian money
I don't know do you know where they've
hidden your sugar
yes in lot his villa near malaga just
past the crossroad of marbella by a Tom
found and is it heavily guarded
it's surrounded by a high-tension fence
and there's a machine gun to whether
that's heavily guarded i suppose it
depends on your definition of heavily
guarded
can I get you for this autograph you
know you've got beautiful eyes to know
you've got beautiful eyes
No you've got beautiful eyes and then of
course it
oh yeah go ahead well it looks like
nobody in your family is a rank amateur
but let me get rearranged I think this
was supposed to be my wedding night
I'm sorry to break up your little
tete-a-tete
but we received information that your
shoe co is being held prisoner outside
granada that's funny
the opposite direction who told you that
she told me she told me not let her go
or we might ruin everything
wow what a cigarette sweet max mechanic
the president's analyst
you know some people just can't wake up
no matter how many alarms they said
looks like you got an extra game there
sacre bleu
sacre bleu huh but oh yeah sacre bleu
well let's go look good it's all right
you can rest
calm down on the ground with her hair
down they've made you suffer having
faith
how can they make such a pretty girl
suffer like that I'm asking myself the
same thing you must be afraid of me
here I have to say no Miller clear we
women understand each other
don't hear water
it's what's for dinner do you think
it'll do you good
your bread will be out shortly i'll let
you look at the menu
what you want from me don't you i don't
know anything
I really don't know anything why are you
so obstinate
I get it from my father we know that
warrant confide in something to you
it's not true no it's not true it's not
how many times do I have to tell you I
don't know anything
for how can I convince you if you talk i
should reward you in a way you can't
even imagine
I'll leave you live with me do you smoke
a princess but I don't know anything I
sweat it
how come to newquay hell
I love in turn that down there is better
I mean it they all of you to use I feel
like God gand friggin - 80 here and I'm
really hot are you hot cheese
Charlie you're my knight in shining
armor up
hey Greg heard it through the grapevine
that guy thing going to work
operation double-double oh he hauled my
calculations are correct the short
circuit should cause a return of current
capable of blowing up the torrid with
the ammunition
anyway I got Lulu backing me up
who do you who do you keep this is your
local utility company reminding you to
call before you are
yeah
tran little wet lolz everybody
to a segment we like to call the Shona
neal schultz parallel lives in which we
look at and contrast the careers of Sean
Connery and his brother Neil Connery
started a movie
yeah yeah this line represents Sean's
live this one represents Neil's life
give you example
Sean's acting talent is discovered in an
early age and leads to a long and
lucrative film career while Neil's
talent for selling light bulbs over the
phone is discovered leading to a long
life of menial jobs and aimless drifted
well up here is when Sean gets his first
million-dollar royalty check for the
james bond series while Neil gets his
first $65 unemployment check after being
laid off from the cheese factory
yeah here sean has declared sexiest man
alive by People magazine while Neil is
declared the sticky Catman and room for
be by the other tenants in its si roll
hotel here
sean calls the most powerful and
influential people in Hollywood and just
put your immediately while Neil calls
pizza hot and is told that they would
deliver to him because of bounced checks
here sean is quoted as saying during the
making of the man who would be king i
had creative differences with director
john huston while Neil is quoted as
saying my manager at the happy chef will
let me off for weekends with the big man
here Sean goes to Spago's and is seated
immediately while Neil's hot plate
malfunction and burns down a shabby
furnished room Jojo what about that
point on the graph for Sean's line
actually goes lower than meals are all
well that was the point where Sean
agreed to do highlander to the
quickening and ironically that's when
neal had to comfort shown boy
you know we should remind the nice folks
out there that this is merely artistic
speculation on our part of Neil
countries life for all we know he's
leading a prosperous happy existence on
a farm in Scotland with his beautiful
wife and adoring children
that's right time and no matter what's
gone wrong with his life
Neil can always look in the mirror and
say to himself well these they didn't do
is our ties you
and sonia wherever you are we would all
just like to say
I went well don't you go along in that
one
ok move by the girls if you love your
hostage let her go
drop that knife
drop it in your samples and Linda hunt
in a deadly game of cat and mouse my job
she's so , roommate just got shot she is
something that's why Julie pig ab
and the calla lilies are raining hot led
to pick up
yeah
I'm lon coming through cam lon Jeffrey
effort is the shaky is gone in the world
baba me Norman
the Rockets here
it's the only way he can talk to women
I am warning you are June ward
I told you something about that a tous
remember what I told you about the
animals
yes danica thrall war new comic looking
good
what else did I tell you God 22
r6 to work at work
two words bite me
Judy carne
wait a minute she looks like shields and
Yarnell now she's a Tony girl
yeah
go on what happens in that one watch
bomb take your time we're in the back
oh I don't like that take up and touch
the second out the blind dragon wanna
come on Lady you are due back in the
space 1999 set
joan jett just walks in and she took so
sorry
it's nothing I'd hoped to get here
before she talked couldn't get a cab
perhaps I could have saved you how was I
supposed to do that no more picking and
I'm a killing me
nice going you just killed Sacagawea
what did you get out of your shoe co
nothing much mostly in a sort of quote
just be deciding as if i'm not busy
enough
she spoke also of th1 something strange
the blind to die in take one
what else did she city and she wanted my
brother's autograph
it seems that planet ours isn't joking
they're planning to steal an atomic
nucleus atomic nucleus
oh that's what i use online or not
possible
north dakota before the apocalypse the
that the wow . uh data consider northern
illinois university
atomic nucleus and only a g4s could
become a bride's does a road show
why man you went to her to miss Keating
looking at 63 spurts tailhook takes it
on the row a few good men made a few
naughty women you my love
it's a man's life in the new modern army
a partridge family van broke down to who
she looks like an oil fire
yeah
torn down
it's the pussy dark band no oh well
they're just going to tag and check for
parasites
Dada camera
I'll see gays in the military right now
hi girls when does the SEC start slowly
no good
that's become running now just one of
these women trying to liberate all right
go get out of those clothes mhm
where angels go trouble follows she
could be a candidate for Big Bird
definitely very my dress at wounded knee
now let's get to work on the truck we
gotta hit the pews place
so the composer's whistling enemy
am i tripping Joel
and Las Vegas was born
sorry
they keep busy don't know
you want to help out here Susan tonight
the dirty doesn't meet Glen skis
beauties like the seductions polecat
other things anymore
they're setting up coonie call all right
terrorists were more fun back then this
is even better the mission impossible
when they take a street in LA and make
it look like Belgium
it's Big Al Hirt he found Martinez all
out of this like you remove the hell was
luck gentlemen
I prefer blondes with his usual
brilliance and imagination
carrot top it has secured the atomic
nucleus week
yes i did the Democrats is in a position
to continue with our plans
they don't explain to you the
experiments our technicians are being
County out dressed as showgirls the past
few weeks
thanks for the marvelous introduction
curve I'll take it from here
gentlemen I shall start by saying these
are all just small-scale experiments
these are all just small-scale
experiments
Cory's but now with this powerful
material with our disposal we are at
last able to generate ultra-high
frequencies
he and to direct for magnetic wave to at
least a third of the globe all metals
will be instantly affected animals will
be breeding slot angry will few solidly
chilitos will be half all animals
animals ships planes guns tanks on
events everything mechanical must be
selling a useless lump of metal or
important
from high atop the topkapi palace in
downtown is to bowl
it's fred waring and his orchestra
yeah
battle may drop later
remaining monkey brains have been
reduced to a dollar ninety-nine arm
nice digs Austin's and where's the guy
with the pickled eggs
take it to the red room
one more time
you look like Electra woman and Dyna
girl
another guess coming from Europe
artur rubinstein semicon walking arm in
arm
dr. nice to see you a thank you
one second you're dressed as a space
angel why
how lucky am i asked you to come I was
going to get in touch for you to arrange
a meeting
could you feel this bumper like a horse
they return game
I had no idea you were so interested in
archery no I'm not
it's your services as a plastic surgeon
I'm interested in why would you like to
have your features change me
I don't know I'm quite satisfied with my
face all and with my notes also although
i do weather vane in high winds
it's for a friend he wants to become the
exact double of another man
Bob Cubans but for the time being
there's no need for you to understand
and of course you don't
you can state your price Welch's for me
it's not a matter of money
it's primarily a matter of principle
although I'm a little low today will
come down agreement
you'll see
we'll have time to talk about it I lost
my pockets
Bobbie Gentry so good to see you again
I don't know who invited him will you
excuse me for a minute
I won't be long I've been advised that
look we can show so many beautiful girls
around
it won't get bored no no you're right
that gives women artists all over me I
mean I got the problem you know
yeah
rocky mountain oysters
like it
well thank you do you have any snackage
type foods here summer sausage to expect
maybe a little mints
Roth is it well what have you done
not very much it's difficult there are
afraid of alpha idiots
maybe the right after all our Vice
powerful you've got a good bench
come in
there's a message from the yacht it's
very urgent
night shoots just take off that
ridiculous getup and it's signed yacht
it
yeah it's from our friend is having a
good time
he said today he wants me to join him
immediately
we're to be married dining it'll be the
last time he gives me an order
I'll destroy him and I'll be the head of
fanaticism is very very risky
it's not for me what about the girls
that may be dangerous witnesses as soon
as the operation is over the yacht will
blow up
remember folks you can read lips is
really what's right now the girls about
yes yes by a tool
it's inevitable german yellow monkey
what Bozo the piano chive used to be
good at this
there must be no witnesses only you will
share my secret
you know that you can trust me all right
now let's go inside and see if we can
convince and remember to have fun
Marla maples
doctor my eyes have seen thank you for
your meditation coincidence i was just
thinking of you
I've flatten that looks like your tomato
aspic got away from her
Maya there's a big RBI guys in danger in
serious danger
are you threatening me no certainly not
but i have just overheard a conversation
between mr. favorite
yes I've seen a few dollars as beautiful
as this one it's quite splendid natural
that's my people
Oh Donald in your windows are Jesse
Norman wants her kaftan back
you're not going are you I was hoping to
play your hand from an affair with you
mm I don't gamble mr. there I don't bail
on winning horses
that's why you should stay another layer
is getting cheesed I have an important
announcement to make on broom MacLeod
any of their I thought you had the
voting majority as far as I'm concerned
this meeting never happened
let's drop it leave things as they are I
shouldn't advise that
sorry Colin I want to know whether you
are with me or without or with child
I want you to be careful how you answer
the beatles you can put yourselves in a
dangerous spot under my cat has a lot
more dangerous to listen to you
who in a few days alpha will be dead
criswell predicts and don't go boom
but no one will know except us within
hours i have an exact double for alpha
neat huh everything will go on as if
nothing happened
nothing has that mmm but with this
difference
your hair can have more body and shine
the new welfare will be my man my man i
love insoles going to blow up soon
maybe even tomorrow with you one . your
kind of hard to dance with you read too
many novels by planning
Jerry climbing means brother I assure
you it's true
your life is great danger I'm not bad
events of a little serious test
ah keep everything under control somehow
with my control top pantyhose
but seriously if my information is right
you'll be indebted to me it sounds like
a turkey
anyway why does mr. Thayer hire only
blind people in his rug factory
wait I know this one I
hi Largo
I don't know I've never been in there
only blind people are allowed to go
inside and I'm blonde
but seriously I can excuse me I have to
go talk to an interesting person
she seems nice enough
yeah
should have had to bring me back some
three-bean salad
Oscar bloat
mhm I should get me one of those
it's red october eyes on that could have
gotten a ride on that I didn't want to
we've installed the screen door sir God
you get this thing out of reverse this
land could win five thousand dollars
it would benefit you
your brother to see your land
I hope you can read real lips
you're new here
got it all done done
and food and they say you read shall
guide them
casting call for name of the rose
it's the boys in the woods I see
no I bet often temp as a hard time
filling these positions
Bruno Bruno all right you win they're
all blind dick enberg here
hold on to each other by the shoulder
and come with me well it felt like
shoulder any of you sure plays a mean
pinball 20 minutes the blind leading the
blind leading the blind leading the
blind leading the blind leading blind
I am blind yet blind it is an illogical
and you shall hear hear you will weave
rugs
don't worry it's a simple easy job
you'll get your food and your family
will get your pay
there's a Coke machine in the living
room of you will be placed at the loop
and we'll begin with an easy liquors
with whether you will learn quickly
now get the way we will start with a
heart card holder first
wait a minute he's infiltrated a
quilting bee goodwill industries now it
can be told somebody heard him looking
I'm sorry
you know ironically Connery wears a rug
over it
who is the sign for it must be where
they make the nuclear-powered rose
shut the door i do believe i am
developing pictures of the rugs in you
ha tell Baltimore hot out Baltimore out
of the Baltimore
would you please stop tapping right that
you know I'll buffet would never work in
this place are you Hank smell like oh la
la
this is like so quality only in a rug
fact that the silkworm
now that we've got some marmalade on
your hand
you're working with radioactive material
kidding what is it that you mean by that
sometimes I think you want me to fail
you are working with radioactive
materials do you understand
yeah well I get paid to dollars more an
hour you gotta try two murders that is
why we have the songs we must go on
meals a skilled rabble-rouser
guys that's not the door that's the
whore
I'm staying I need the money when
players are you
I can take you to the police fire
department the National Guard to get me
out of here
hey this is kinda fun
this must be five o'clock on a Friday
you wanted to win a wrestling me can't
you tell I am fragile
that everybody be sure to sign Nicky's
birthday card before Alicia will be here
on monday looks like casual day backfire
responding
this morning
all right let him go home
he was just on the road to Damascus and
when I look at me wearing a brown jacket
and kind of been a kind of tenants
pretty good hole in her neck and I'm
isn't bad patch your arabic is quite
good
all of it dates from the time of the
Crusades dr congo all I could never for
you give me a hard
nice to know that goes in mind
ladies and gentlemen Maynard Ferguson in
the centennial senior high school gym
happy child back here you're an
extraordinary man doctor
I know let me show you my time lively
imaginative and resource for my sons of
humor - it's too bad you prepared to
play on the opposing team too bad
from your point of view who yes that is
my point of view but come
I know you are but what am I if you done
me the small favor I asked me to be in
marketing by now
it would have been more tip tip no such
complications as these
now you have to operate any way under
less favorable circumstances
you understand well what else can I do
again oh it's a new car will meet
where's the bar
here is your patient doctor doctor
patient patient dr. everything's ready
for you
I want to be generous so here's a
quarter in return for your services and
get to rub my tummy your life to come a
long way baby
to get where you got to today can I do
you need food for the party leader in
Africa
I've got two one
I have just learned that we're going to
have to fight for our lives there has
decided to blow up the yard with all of
the support
come on that's a bad thing right
if it stops so will your look I just
came in for a haircut really just a
little off the sides
oh ok how are we today
good drug harm looking cool how's that
little prostate problem
all right you can do can we have the
night canopy please
you know I think that operating room
clashes with the college
just relax
you're tired you wanted resident
hmm
that's right relax you have nothing to
fear we're going to enter your nostril
good
Steve Austin
special
sources couple of talks he could be Roy
Thinnes where was your chest on the
night of the 23rd how he kept that
speaker from a drive-in know as soon as
country is completed the operation
you'll get new spread on his eliminate
ill Toni Basil all must book
what women really broken through the
glass ceiling in this movie yeah but
there's a guy looking up through it all
women can't live weather talent without
I want
it's closing time and owners they
deserve that
still it was worth a world olay now you
will follow my instructions it
state you won't have a moment of peace
till it's all finished and you even buy
my eyes to match my doll any old time
you know let's see here that you haven't
been flossing know how do you like your
martinis shaken or stirred
I'm taking the president's knows
now go this little war whoo
I love your damage
police squad in color
make this john and with all full
boo Danny let's settle this in court
we watch out for the model ship and
actual Donnybrook & Easy Spirit pumps
it's the wac is ship and the baby went
up with people goes bad
that was a real cap in yo kick
monday fight
enter the chiropractor
yeah
report
stop this thing right now I violate some
rules
and the couple went there I hate that
with it
watch out for the model
Oh
right into a bob fosse routine mrs.
Partridge look out
no this is a one seater home
the blue were
where the action is a good nanny
happening 16 yeah
if Sam pack and Paul directed the boat
Knicks
look he's wearing a line is sure it's no
reason that hit him
there's no wonder the little blue guys
well that's a cute top Cindy where'd you
get it
with that is one figure-hugging
turtleneck
all p
yeah
licorice all are great now the boats
sinking
finally got used to this
wait a minute is becoming part of his
own entertainment center
excuse me pardon me comin 20 students
dropping out of high but folks use me
pardon me
oh I'm sorry or I got too cold to be
funny
and as well call shows his true colors
of yellow and please the clips though
and as we left the clam flowers that day
stop
let's see hypnotizing premier mr. cool
thing that we can't worry about that
right now we've got to find that his
headquarters of the radioactive runs
were made at the factory where were they
said I really never knew that but once I
heard something about a place near
Munich
yeah
no no no mind just let me try to
hypnotize you crow like sort back to
what you can't make me you can't make me
you can't make me
what come pop Joel so sorry to interrupt
your little skit
but Frank would like to do a number i
was a little hard on him during the
invention exchange
so here's our own TVs Frank accompanying
himself on the accordion with the
hunting beer barrel polka
what'd you bring - and the one two three
four other guys really poker forum are
very familiar your guard the mister
tibbs that you ordered there
I think you just put them on that you
what the any leader Pibb
I specifically ordered a diet squirt I'm
so sorry gentlemen I'm make it right
no no no Frank have to mr. pip you can
have a mr. Pibb this time no my doctor
says I can't have mr. Pitt Frank I'm
your doctor and I say have the mister
pip a master good wanted you to have
these coupons for
for our veggie feast he wanted you to
have them but i'm getting them to do
that
thank you thank you very much i have to
thank you thank you
yes have a nice day I was thank you
goodbye
Oh may I use your bathroom
they're on the laptop
all right let's land directional
relevant indicates that survived
Oh high on a hill little lonely goatherd
so you might want to take an alternate
route this afternoon
this place is crawling with Chad
maybe you should land before you get out
all what do you got your keys your keys
she's new oh that's right
oh this feels great leather is really
something
I'm beginning the god damn countdown
knock it off forever and 20 seconds
warning signal . it's comfy
he's found the secret entrance such a
curious lamb it out satisfy his
curiosity
amen double double on Silva's on turn it
off
sir someone's doing a drug test outside
wow I'm gonna shut you down till about
20 okay Trevor trav are
yeah
economy is now in the tunnel
Alex the outer limits I'm not going in
the tunnel
oh I am in the tunnel
reach down here I put that thing away
stop right there well she's not the only
smooth one
that's for stealin my naugahyde couch
oh my you better Colin over the
vibrators vibrators and certain yeah you
can't say that
so welcome everybody's got count basie
following me
writings grown up
I'm old
yeah
the back stab stab wounds
thank you Ron Popeil
yeah
I mean what would my brother do
well that must be the finite building
so I guess nobody's going to notice the
guy in the tan suede ranch jacket other
yeah
your eyes been
I leave me alone
airwolf meets dr. Zhivago
what should we be moving or something
gold gold / - everybody when that lady
gets off the helicopter check on her
pants
thank you Lord Jesus
yeah
we can get help for crying out where's
the valet
forget it was more than a long as it's
pat's that mean
shoot i would be an espresso please
terribly urgent London in England how do
you expect to do that character on
please help me it's a matter of life or
death
you can try i don't know if you get
through well there's wall though
low 31 30 seconds
magnetic intensity at concentration
level with you Charles Aznavour me when
he barked at the grave ready to function
system elaborate close to three
hello London extension 142
I want to speak with commander
Cunningham immediately it's terribly
urgent
never mind Who I am Harry five bottles
beer and off all bottles of beer on the
wall
free to a castle hill and lonely
goatherd behalf of munich one singular
sensation the head produce had 20 miles
papa
hello I don't know why you say goodbye i
said hello
we can cut up well I'm not calling her
back
I'm wondering what do the simple folk do
whatever where they stood to my
underwear bra especially that doesn't
know where did I park the smooth
admit it well you know those slacks hurt
me and you say but people
the cloud
so mr. bonds brother
I'm happy to have you as my guest again
i'll show you how the operation works on
our anti magnetic you could think more
you give me one neat go to figuring and
that's the last favor I can do you
I only allowed you to live because I
wanted you to witness my success
I've got what I wanted without your help
yeah take him away i think i'm supposed
to have some snappy comeback
no further keep going don't look at me
like that
suddenly it's the brothers freaking
terawatts off the magnetic wave is
blocked it out you a champion at you two
are sorry about that have a pretty good
fighter when I guess that can be useful
to 10 it
their cars broke there
horses will poop on the parking lot to
put the
but they outlawed night guys look really
stupid plastic pants plastic pants
your group is going there
oh boy another staredown with Neil
girl mental wreck what's wrong with you
there's my philips screwdriver
due to do
we know or we go
would stop pretending this is exciting
looks just like an EQ video under a
black grad school
the old country you should be able to
get him
oh my pants my hands
oh what a time for a fire trailer
yeah
you know that alligator skin and helps
you know
come on girls they heard buddy
my man chosen
he doesn't know we're not together I got
it now
where you going to try to blow up the
tower
texas my grandma gave it to me it's an
anti magnetic thing and i set the dial
cheek good will come to you
ok we'll meet you there
it's a llamar fuckig a
all right on it again
come on
do not start for triple-a hi Michael by
the room
trade ya Oh
you Archer must be honest because
everybody gets a turn here
encore mommy
mr. Belvedere it apart the hard drive
here let's go
this is your last chance for a witty
remark at your own game
dr. it's a perfect setup for witty
remark ma I mean come on doctor
it's no good if you don't report can be
anything to me about my nose or my
stupid elegance with anything
hey that's not fair
is your soggy in this sand off to use
the stunt batch
you know guys I think this is about more
than just magnetizing this goes much
deeper stuff Margo what guys
yeah
hey somebody punched the fully guy
okay okay take back everything you ever
said about me
oh man am I moist totie Fields was never
this moist found
prepare to meet Ali's brother near
no fight at the ok corral
I'm gonna do it
good today
thank you
yeah
you know he's gonna need a vinyl patch
kit yep
how are these guys still at a range
they're beating up the ball later he did
he turn out for some reason i like to
fight on the boat better
haver
I do
hey everybody there's a party going down
at that we've got you know for the tower
blows on well
oh oh and i forgot to tell you earlier
that there's a tower that's going to
blow up in this too
oh i just got it that's the tower that's
gonna blow up ya know it's about quick
we're gonna die we're really not that
far away
he bring it on compound exploded today
you wanna make escaped unharmed
unfortunately bonnie jean has died
kind of like watching bonanza Andrew
birch
that must be the Thunder ball I heard
them talking about
hey hey relax we want your hot head to
put okay , okay
you were fantastic you even made my best
agents look like beginners
oh I shouldn't think so commander I was
lucky that no you're too modest you
should have seen your brother space
doctor when he had it settle back with a
smooth-running you happen to have a few
days free i'm just thinking I'd be happy
to have you back in the reserves with
the red good major if I wasn't so Placid
right now who here would
as church Stevens get sleeper
which one Major Nelson
what was I say that you have to return
to London immediately
isn't that right commander boom it works
on my brain tumor
yeah
yes cars
i miss return the needed
i would say this loud singer i am mrs.
Norman made
yeah this is the part my brother told me
about it
no I guess I should take my own life
Red Angel of just the powered rifle
a little brush fire we're having fun at
his expense it's fun
ready girls let's go he probably hid the
Kaiser no liking it
yeah i just think that life will lose a
lot of its if you had ultimately power
over everyone
- Sean Connery's brother won't be back
again in anything about it
yeah
I guess what's that suppose this happen
we started the war on crime any leak at
wow are you guys stuck to the wall yeah
we were immobilized where style oh I bet
I know whose idea this was service was
this your idea on what Joel I you got me
haha nolo contendere I saw the movie
remembered i had my old magnetizer huh
these things are great
gotta admit it's pretty funny i'm stuck
in a wall
it's no use Joel any kind of work
I'm stock hello oh no quick given rocket
number nine
oh that is very funny service but i am
going to know that you're probably
interrupting at your godly man don't
tell the communication yeah who wouldn't
want to do that
don't worry will demagnetize you guys
later
ha ha ha ha ha
ok do my hair walenz ein li
I want to recall an hour and a half
until next time Joel off
yeah