I'm fond of close up photos
because they reveal something more of
what we are unable to see in larger perspective.
When you take portrait photos,
what do you focus on?
I think I focus on the eyes.
You'll have to excuse me, the little one's crying.
Gosh! He's gorgeous
but too bad he has a baby already.
Hey, why are you crying? Are you hungry?
Are you a furious little baby?
You feel better now?
Everyone has special someone in their hearts.
The heart tinkles every time we think about them,
but they will always remain in our hearts.
Even though, I don't know...
how he's doing or where he is now.
At least, he has taught me about
my first love.
"A CRAZY LITTLE THING CALLED LOVE"
No wonder why you wanna come here everyday.
What? He's got really weird scooter.
Hey look...
she's a very pretty thing!
He's gorgeous, no doubt you're so into him.
I'm not into him at all.
"James Bean."
Good afternoon.
Oh, hello.
Follow me.
Okay.
This way please.
Hello...
I wondering if you have a room for tonight.
Yes, how long are you gonna stay here?
I think 3 nights.
American breakfast.
Fried rice and breakfast for this table, mom.
After you're done with that table,
can you go to the market for me?
Sure, mom.
Good girl.
How's school dear?
It's going well. I'm hanging out
with my old gang, Cheer, Kie and Nim.
You've been with them since first grade.
Aren't you sick of each other already?
Well, you wouldn't have
anyone else to hang out with,
even if you wanted to.
You guys are ugly ducklings.
There...
Let me tell you something,
who we hang out with
is not all about looks you know.
But how you look is the first impression.
Good that I took after you,
if I looked like dad,
I'll never have a boyfriend.
There!
Enough you two,
you're too old to fight.
Don't talk like that about your father,
if he hears you he'll be upset.
Now go, be on your way.
He's in the states. He can't hear me.
You want some mangoes?
Mangoes?
The new seniors are so cute.
Yes, I was in all girls school since kindergarten,
so sick of that.
Have you got it?
Yes, mine adds up to 28.
25-35,
you're compatible with men who're leaders,
warm and kind.
Must be Tong, the Chairman of Buddhist Club.
Cheer got 15.
15-25
you're compatible with athletes, just and fair.
Must be Ken, the basketball player over there.
Couldn't be him.
Mine must be a bad boy.
That's quite right.
It must be...
Meaw,
tough guy.
Kie.
30, Nam got 30
30, you're compatible with artists,
unique and artistic.
Who must he be?
You seem a little down for English class.
Could you be a little more active like during lunch?
Don't smile just yet.
You seem to be doing well only in English.
Other subjects are so bad.
You little ugly duckling!
Today, we'll be studying grammar from song lyrics,
please pass on the paper.
His name is Shone, he's a junior.
He has quite a reputation.
Maybe it's just a rumor.
Students, if we change A to E
in the word 'inspiration',
it becomes a verb 'inspire'.
Two girls left the school because of him.
So better stay away from him.
You know?
Yes...
My friend's sister went to the same school as Shone.
Really?
Yes.
Do you think the story is true?
What are you guys talking about?
But I'm teaching...
Cheer.
Stand up.
What does 'You are the inspiration' means?
What does it mean?
Just moment.
You inspire me.
Yes...
You're the inspiration.
Everyone is inspired by someone.
Even I'm inspired
by someone...
Sit down.
Thank you teacher.
All right.
Let's read all together now.
You are the inspiration...
Again.
Akarin, would you solve this equation, please?
Who did this?
Prof. Orn.
It's in.
You're good. When are you going
to try out for school team.
Playing just for fun is much better.
You're still scared? Come on let's play.
Shone...
Hey, I'll be right back.
Who is that girl?
Who?
Why is Shone talking to her?
Or maybe she's his ex?
That's not true!
Sorry.
Uncle Chang!
Mom, Nam, Uncle Chang's here.
Hello, we miss you so much.
Uncle Chang...
Hello, Chang.
Hey, Pang, long time no see,
you head still smells funky.
Oh, Nam? You're all grown up now,
I hardly recognize you.
Hey Pim, oh...
Hey, uncle.
Are you that sleepy?
I think it's jet lag.
I haven't adjusted to Thailand's time yet.
Here we go again.
Hey, hold it!
Is my dad as fat as you are?
Your dad is working as a sous chef.
He's doing all the heavy jobs,
he's very buff right now.
I have a photo from him to show you.
Hey, let me see.
Hey... wait.
Pim,
your man said he'll transfer more money this month.
He told me to tell you that...
I promise,
I'll pay off the mortgage of this house,
you and kids hang in there.
He should visit us sometimes.
He said that if one of you
can be top of the class,
he'll send to a ticket to visit him in the states.
The airfare is quite expensive.
Do you think he'll keep his promise, mom?
He knows that being top of class
is quite difficult, dear.
You'll see.
I will be the top of my class,
so he knows I can do it.
You're going to the top from the rank 30?
2 strawberry soda and 2 orange soda please.
Hey, 2 Pepsi, I'm so thirsty.
How can you do this?
I'm just really thirsty,
do you have a problem with that?
Haven't you heard that men, children,
and basketball players get the privileges
at this school.
And I'm a basketball player.
Can I have 4 sodas for the soccer players please?
Will Pepsi do?
Yes...
Darn it!
Hey, don't kick at me.
Sorry... don't you get it?
Hey!
Hey... I can handle this.
Nam, Shone and Ding
are having a fight behind the school.
Stop...
Where are you going?
Let's take the scooter, it's faster, come on.
Hurry!
I think you can handle him.
So you want to be hero like your dad?
He was a loser and cost us National Championship.
Did you guys know
that he missed the penalty kick?
It took ages to make it to National Championship.
Darn it...
We just missed seeing Ding getting beat up.
Let's go.
Do you still want this soda he gave us?
If you're not going to drink it,
can I throw it away?
Do not drink.
Why is it in the freezer if you can't drink it?
All right students,
I have 2 announcements today.
Our school has become filthy due to littering,
and the students are ignorant.
So from now on,
anyone who litters will be fined 1 baht per piece.
I have a promotion if you think this is too expensive,
this is a great deal.
Pay 50 baht per day
and you can litter anytime and anywhere,
I'll just clean up after you.
Students with the following names
please proceed to Disciplinary Office,
Jakawan Class 4/5
and Achawin Class 4/7.
Everybody understand?
Understand?
Yes...
Thank you. I love you.
Cross your arms.
If you get into fights again,
I'll inform your parents, do you hear me?
Shone, you have great talent,
in photography.
Why don't you enter
the provincial photography contest?
I think you should apply for it.
Maybe you can do something for our school,
instead of wasting your time fighting.
Do you understand me?
Yes, sir.
You may go now.
Thank you.
Next.
I'm sorry about what happened yesterday.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
Band aids for you.
Get well soon.
Nam.
Thank you.
Yes, he knows my name.
He actually knows my name.
He knows my name.
What?
They actually have books like this?
Oh... 20 ways to get your guy.
There goes the 'White Ribbon' girls.
I'll be right back.
Look at her,
since when is she friends with them?
Is she for real?
I miss my dad,
I haven't seen him for 5 years now.
Earn,
Kai's now in love with me,
because of this book.
Really? This book really works?
Yeah, Pooh also bought this book
before she got together with Toh.
9 love tips really works.
You're not going with them anymore?
No, they're saying I outshine them.
Tip No. 1.
Greek belief on how to win someone's heart,
look at the stars in the sky,
connect the stars with your fingers
to make the name of someone you love in Latin.
Hey, wait up!
Hey, I can't do it.
Nam, why don't you join us?
No, I think it's nonsense.
Gotta get this right.
I'm going to do it at home.
We're going, Nam. Later!
You're practicing real hard.
Do you have a soccer match somewhere?
Just around here.
Hey, I can't!
Catch!
I told you I can't, watch where you kick.
I though you were Chinese?
My ancestral accent comes out every time I'm upset!
Come on.
Look at this, Shone.
How about it?
A poster of the 3rd Photography Contest
that you asked about.
I see.
Look at him. He can play soccer day
and night on the streets
but refuses to join his school team.
He's just having fun,
I don't think he's taking soccer seriously.
Even if he is, he wouldn't join the team.
I should've scored that penalty kick.
Here you go again, don't blame yourself.
Maybe he's not really feeling ashamed
about what you did.
Or even if he is, he has to get over it by himself.
Look at you now, how far you've come.
You look a bit strange.
Look, I have new braces for my teeth,
do you like them?
They don't look anything special to me.
Hey, here, look here.
I still don't like them.
Hey, you picked Ken?
Yes,
eat now,
eat now.
Yes, he ate.
Are you crazy? He's in the middle of his lunch.
This is not hypnotizing.
What are you guys doing?
Tip no. 2,
from Mayan, the indigenous people,
concentrate
and look at the one you love,
try to hypnotize him
to do what you want.
If he acts as you ordered,
it means that he is your soulmate.
Hey, he turned around.
Who...
Oh, no one.
Are you hypnotizing Shone?
No...
I didn't do anything.
I though you said this book is nonsense.
Well, taking beliefs from different culture
and various islands is kinda weird.
Then why are you following the book?
I... hey!
You can tell us the truth.
I don't wanna be teased.
Don't you worry about that.
Because we will definitely tease you.
Tip No. 3.
Scottish way of saying you love someone.
Give a gift to someone anonymously,
just for the person to know
that someone has a crush on him.
This jelly is mine.
How can you drop it?
Thank you so much, Prof. Pol.
Salted eggs.
Oh, I must be on your mind
when you were travelling.
I'll finish it all,
thank you so much.
Thank you.
Prof. Pol's eggs.
Prof. Pol's eggs and some salts.
Prof. Pol's salted eggs, it's correct.
Prof. Pol brought me eggs.
Prof. Pol's salted eggs...
Oh, don't tell me...
Yes, there's from Prof. Pol.
How many boxes have you got?
4 boxes.
4 boxes?
Salted eggs.
Hope you can finish them all.
See you.
Oh, no!
My scooter's ruined!
I forgot we live in a tropical country.
Mangoes?
People give flowers and handkerchiefs,
what's so romantic about mangoes?
Hey, look over there.
Cool dude! Go...
Mango cake, I made it myself.
Thank you, looks delicious.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Okay, we're dead.
She only has to do that.
She's adorable and she bakes.
How can you beat that?
Better find another boy.
Actually I already have a date,
but if you invite me over for dinner
at your place,
and this is would be our first date...
If you're not free, that's okay.
Next semester then.
Oh, wait,
actually I'm free, I accept your invitation.
See you later this evening.
This dinner is not just for the two of us?
It's not actually a dinner,
it's a party for the end of semester,
a lot of our colleagues are coming,
it'll be fun.
Oh, okay.
Prof. Orn.
Prof.
I never give up.
This time it's war.
That's my answer sheet.
Higher...
Prof.
Lift me higher, Nam.
I got it.
We have to make Shone give Nam a lift home.
Yes...
It's your once in a lifetime wish isn't it?
Yeah.
He gives you mangoes after he drives you,
how romantic is that.
You have to pretend your scooter's broken.
How?
He'll know once he tries to fix it.
That's true.
You must lose your keys.
How?
It's here.
Hey...
It's gone.
Hey, there he is.
Mango cake girl, what's wrong?
I tripped and must have sprained my ankle.
Come, I'll give you a lift.
That's all right!
Come on, let me take you home.
I'm a little clumsy.
What a show!
She went to acting school or what?
"Bye Bye Grade 7. See you all Grade 8."
Mom, come see this.
Pang, you little brat.
Mom, Nam has a boyfriend.
Nam, I think this can wait until you grow up.
You're going away to see your dad,
concentrate on your school, dear.
Hey, Cheer.
Your little sister said
you've been depressed for weeks now.
Listening to sad tunes all week.
I thought you must have gotten over Shone by now.
Keep your voice down, mom might hear us.
She's off to the market already.
Don't push me.
When's your mom going to expand these stairs?
Hey, Nam, hear one more tip okay?
Tip no. 7
is from the Gypsies, let love inspire you.
The power of love shall make you smarter,
prettier and better in every way,
then that person will finally notice you.
Hey what?
Shone is gorgeous so Nam should be beautiful...
Okay, do that later, my skin's coming off now.
What is this?
Turmeric.
Let's go.
Hey, hello girls.
Let me know how I can help you okay?
Have a look around.
"Pornchai missed PK."
"Failed to hand Provincial cup."
I don't see him anywhere.
Maybe he's not home.
He's probably out. I don't see his scooter.
Have you found what you're looking for?
Yes, this one.
What are you buying?
You guys play table tennis?
Why are you so yellow?
Do you have jaundice?
Shone.
Mango cake girl.
Are you here to buy something?
I need a dozen of table tennis balls.
Come, I'll get them for you.
Come on kids, join my Drama Club.
Drama Club, anyone?
We have a lot of plays for you.
You can be a princess or a prince.
You can star in our plays.
The lords of comedy were in my club.
Anyone interested?
Join us?
Father of talk show was also in our club.
Really?
If you wanna make it in the business,
this is your chance.
Join us, dear? Don't pass over me.
Take off your glasses.
Your glasses.
Hey, but I feel awkward without them.
I think we totally don't fit with that
pretty-polis-posh concept
of that Dancing Arts Club.
Prof. Orn always selects the smartest and prettiest
for her club and when they perform,
the whole school goes to see them.
Unlike those weirdos in Drama Club,
no one ever watches their plays.
Well, it's worth giving it a try.
We maybe a little dark,
a little dorky but pretty in our own ways.
Shone,
which club are you joining?
Photography.
Whenever you need a model, just let me know.
I like photographing landscapes, not people.
Are you kidding me?
If you say so.
Come on, get in the frame.
You're not yellow anymore,
your skin seems lighter?
Maybe...
a little.
I'll be watching your performance okay?
You see, Nam,
he said you look prettier,
keep up head high okay?
If we get to do dance performance,
would be fantastic!
We'll be so pretty and fabulous.
If you're not sure that you're pretty enough,
you're always welcome in other clubs, you know?
Hey, that's not a very nice thing to say.
I wasn't talk to you, I was talking to Funn, right?
Liar,
you said it to us.
Stop it, girls.
I don't want any troublemakers in my club.
Wait...
Faye and Funn, stay behind.
Nam...
I'm sorry about earlier.
I have to apologize too.
Yeah.
I bought extra drink, you can have it.
Wait,
let her drink it first.
Why won't you drink it.
Go.
If you don't want a drink spiked
with fish sauce, throw it away.
How can she do that?
There you are, I was looking all over for you.
Look at me
and smile...
Frown...
Laugh,
oh perfect!
See you tomorrow at the auditorium okay?
Professor.
Keep your voice down,
I'm only accepting a few students.
Understand?
Can I have some?
Prof. In,
oh, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Prof. In.
How can I help you, sir?
Nothing, how are you?
I'm fine.
See you tomorrow.
Water, need water.
No...
It's a perfect match and I mean it.
Prof. In.
Maybe I shouldn't let you do the play,
if you're this late.
Okay...
Oh, wait!
I was just joking!
We meant to tell you that...
No worries,
I'll give you the best parts.
We meant to tell you...
Come on, help me out...
We want to dance...
dance...
in you play,
because we're so happy to be in your play.
This year, I proudly present the play called
"Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
Nam, your English is better than the rest.
You play Snow white okay?
Me?
Yes... ready! Oh, a rabbit,
what are you doing here?
I'm here to paint.
Then what are you doing inside the box?
I bought interior paint.
Go paint elsewhere.
Wait a second,
get me all phone numbers of those
in Art Production.
My students are so gifted in acting,
I'm sure it's gonna be a great play.
Are you all right? Are you sick?
No.
I feel fine.
Oh, maybe you're not used to my natural beauty.
Lipsticks are waste of money.
And most importantly,
I just wanna give someone a head start.
Perhaps you went a little too far?
Let's compete with our work.
Because judging from our looks,
we're neck and neck.
I've trained the students to put make up on
like my natural style.
And this is how you get the natural look.
Are you sure you've trained them?
It this a play or a circus?
Could be a circus, Prof. Orn.
This is the kids' creativity.
You're going home?
Yes.
Shone.
Home safe.
She was walking fine
when she got here wasn't she?
Professor.
Yes.
Would you like some water?
Thank you.
My football's going to be out of air.
Sorry about that.
This is Pin, a junior,
she'll be taking care of
costumes and make-up for our play.
May I have a round of applause for Pin.
Please take care of this for me, Pin.
I think we should get started.
Okay, let's get started with me.
I forgot I'm not in the play.
Let's start with Snow white then.
Start with me?
Yes, you first.
What do you think?
She looks the same to me.
Snow white with braces.
I don't want braces anymore.
I wanna take them out.
Nam, are you there?
Okay, ready. Stand by.
Where's the Prince?
He has diarrhea.
On a final rehearsal? Is he crazy?
You... the painter.
Can you fill in for the Prince please?
Me?
Yes, be a Prince, it'll be quick.
Closer, get closer.
When I say action, lean towards her to kiss okay?
Action.
You so beautiful, I have to kiss you.
Hey, Nam...
You're going to break you neck there.
Hey, too long already, go back to painting.
Nam standby. Koi, ready.
What?
Ready, action.
Hello, this is Pornchai Sports Shop.
May I please speak to Shone?
Shone speaking.
Hello...
He hung up.
Mirror mirror on the wall,
who is the most beautiful one of all?
Where are you going? Toilet?
The witch is here,
this is the climax of the play.
There's the witch.
Yes, eat.
Apple?
Eat.
Look...
She's not dead.
She's gonna solve her problem, you'll see.
Death snow white... death.
No one informed me about our student
who won the provincial photography contest.
They just called to inform us now, sir.
Try to keep up with the performance
of our students okay?
Hurry up.
Yes... I'm trying.
The iron's not working so well, sir.
Prof. Rabue, this is why.
Could you plug it for me?
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
And so snow while and the prince
lives happily ever after.
Well done, students, great job!
You can still see the footprints.
I ironed, I didn't wash his shirt, sir.
Do you want me to wash it?
We don't have time.
Don't forget your bag.
Get going now. Go.
Well done!
Dinner's on me tonight.
"For Snow White, I tasted it for you,"
"it's not poisoned."
Hold on.
One more time, eat your heart out tonight,
my treat!
Let's pack up now.
For Snow white.
Who is it from? A bitten apple.
Must be from Shone.
You really think so?
You ugly thing!
Nam, maybe it's from that guy...
Prince Frog.
Princess Frog and Prince Frog.
What a jerk, why didn't you come see the play?
I bet you were watching those dancers.
What a jerk!
Mac doesn't feel a thing.
Hey, how's my little boy?
Hey, what brings you here?
Hello.
Guys, this is Top, my friend since kindergarten.
Hello...
Hello.
He's cute.
Hey!
Let's go.
How long are you going to stay this time?
Probably until my dad retires.
But if I can get into university,
I'll move to Bangkok with my mom.
Cute!
Let's go see the cafeteria.
Hey, pretty girl,
what's your name?
Yes, you. What's your name?
Don't be shy. Going already?
You wanna a little fight with me, girl?
I think Prof. In put it on.
It's probably been showing all day.
Let's go.
Hey, that's Snow white on TV.
She's cute. Does she have a boyfriend?
I don't think so but I don't think
you should ask her out.
Why not?
Isn't she too young?
Hey, I've asked for numbers of 5th graders before.
"Bye Sophomore. Hello Junior!"
"2 more subjects to make up for"
"Will follow you to Junior year!"
Shone, this is yours.
I thought so. Every time we play soccer,
you'll always have give me a penalty kick.
You do it.
Hey, you're still not over it?
Your dad must have forgotten about it by now.
It's not that. That was too easy.
Yeah right, Mr. Cristiano Ronaldo.
Top, can I take a photo with you?
Yeah, sure.
Can I have one too?
Then who's going to the photo for me?
Will you take one for me first?
I can take it for you.
Thank you...
A bit closer.
Okay...
1... 2... 3...
Hey, why are you stealing my scene?
I asked him first, you know?
Stop...
All of you stop it!
Stop it right now!
Isn't this too much?
I have no idea.
Stop now. Stop!
I was the referee, sir.
How many days to district sports day?
About 2 weeks, sir.
The athletes and cheer squad are practicing hard.
Who's going to be drum major now?
I think...
I have to ask Prof. Orn for some help,
see if she can find someone.
Don't worry about that, sir.
I got it.
It's nothing.
Nam,
in my entire being,
I've never met anyone so perfect
and excellent like you.
You look incredible and fabulous.
Please get straight to the point.
What can I do for you, Prof. In?
I was wondering if you could be the school's
drum major for the District Sports Day?
What?
I'm not looking for anyone else.
You're perfect for it.
But that's in 2 weeks.
I don't think I can do it.
I can not find anyone else.
I promise I'll make it up to you in a religious way.
In a religious way?
I can pray for you for 6 months...
or forever. I can definitely do that.
Hold the baton upright then throw it up,
keep your eyes on the baton then catch it
then continue marching.
See?
As easy as that.
Can you show me?
I have my own baton.
You can do it. That's yours, this is mine.
Focus on how high you want to throw it,
then throw it up when you're ready,
123, up!
This is difficult.
Why didn't she pick someone else?
Don't give up just yet, it's only been a few days.
The most important tip
in 9 Love Tips
says that you should give it your best shot in love,
wholeheartedly give it all you've got,
then the person you love will find you.
Hey, you've come this far,
you have to keep fighting.
This is not only for school,
you're representing our town.
You can do it.
Top, pass the ball.
Hey, you're distracted by girls again.
I promise you that our marching band
will be the best in town this year, sir.
What about the drum major?
You need not worry.
She's pretty, tall and fabulous.
She's just perfect.
Watch out!
Sorry.
Don't tell me that's our drum major.
Oh, yes. But she's been doing well, sir.
It's the first time she messed up.
She's throwing her baton like a boomerang.
What happens if she mess up on the sports day?
No incident like that will happen, sir.
Get a new drum major
or I'll be after you.
Oh, sir. But,
we only have 1 week to practice, sir.
This is not looking too good.
The director confiscated the baton?
Who's going to be our drum major now?
I don't know. Serves Prof. In right.
She should've picked one of us, pretty girls.
I don't know how she could pick such ugly student.
Her students are always losers.
I'm glad she didn't pick us,
would be bad for our reputation.
How can you say that?
It's true.
Bug face.
I'm going to prove them wrong.
Students of Prof. In are not always a loser.
You're going use a broomstick?
Where did you get that?
I borrowed from the janitor.
It's a bit light, but it'll do.
I will not let anyone look down on us and Prof. In.
Everyone, I'm asking for 100% from you today.
There...
Hey, that's a foul. Hey!
You're going to take the penalty kick?
Hey, my son's going take the penalty kick.
Let's leave.
Wait, hold on.
Unbelievable, Shone's going kick a penalty goal.
I can't believe my eyes,
come on, he's going to kick now.
Do you guys know why
we lost the National Championship?
It's because of his dad.
Wait...
That was just a warm up kick.
Have another go.
Is there such thing as a warm up penalty kick?
In my book, there is.
In my book too.
Mine too.
And I haven't blown my whistle.
Yes, sir.
One more time.
Why?
He's going have another go at it.
Come here.
He's gonna do it.
If you kick like that,
you're ready to join our school team.
Yes.
Yes, Shone did it...
He's all smile now.
I get it now.
Very good, perfect, dear.
My goodness, excuse me Prof. Orn,
I was wondering whether your students
can throw their headdress that high and catch it?
So high, very good!
So, your sister is as pretty as I am now?
She much prettier.
Fabulous, Nam.
I don't wanna move anywhere.
You say that every time.
You're way to hot, Nam.
Last Valentine's day, she was still very dark.
I'm gonna take Kai's gift for her.
Have you asked Nam?
I don't know.
Can I have this pink chocolate Nam?
What's wrong with her? She looks a bit down.
She's been waiting for him all day
and he hasn't shown up.
Hey, Nam, come here... hurry.
Go ahead.
Here,
it's from a friend of mine.
See you tomorrow at 4,
on 3rd floor staircase.
I have something to tell you.
Do you wanna leave together, Shone?
You haven't left yet?
You can go ahead.
Nam.
I knew you'd come.
This letter was from you, Top?
Yes, it's from me.
Did you want anything?
Would you like to be my girlfriend?
What were you going to tell me, Shone?
I was just going to ask why you're here.
But now I know.
So what do you say?
Silence means yes to me.
What?
Top? Where did he come from?
And that's what all Shone said?
What was your answer?
I didn't say anything.
What should I do?
You have to think twice
since he's Shone's best friend.
If you make a wrong move,
Shone's going to kill you.
Mistake.
Are you free today? Wanna go see a soccer game?
No, I'm not free.
It'll only take a while.
Shone's playing for the team first time today.
Do you wanna go?
Okay, I'll go.
Nam.
Get on.
Some water.
Thank you.
Do you have some water?
No.
Let's go to plan B.
Faster...
Dear button, I really wanna ride with Shone.
"Summer Holiday!"
"See you in Junior Year."
What kind of cake would you like
for your birthday this year? Go pick one.
Vanilla cake,
Nam loves it.
Hello, where are you?
We're picking a cake for Cheer's birthday right now.
I'm at the Dam with Shone and his friends,
I won't make it back in time.
I called Cheer this morning but she didn't pick up,
please tell her Happy Birthday for me.
Sorry guys.
Okay... we'll tell her.
We'll take this one.
Grilled squids.
I'll be right back.
What are you doing here all alone?
It's a great view here.
Would you like some grilled squid?
Have you heard a story about squids?
No.
I'll tell you.
Once upon the time,
two squids met
and fell in love with each other,
they decided to be together
and eventually got married.
On their wedding day,
the reverend squire told them to hold hands
so they held hands,
held hands...
You're so silly.
But that's sweet.
The story teller or the story?
The story teller.
Oh, the story.
I'm all confused now.
No more appetite for squids?
I never ate squids again after I heard that story.
Have you ever held
someone's hand like the squids?
Once I held hand of a clumsy girl
who was about to fall off the stage,
so I grabbed her hand.
Nam...
Why don't you eat the squids?
They're really delicious.
Don't...
Why? They're yummy.
Seriously,
do you like Nam?
You're going out with her,
why are you asking me this?
Oh, it's nothing.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, just hurts a bit.
Can you try to walk?
Come on, get on my back.
Dear button, Shone carried my bag today.
Happy Birthday...
Is that you Nam?
Cheer's not here.
She went with Kie and Nim.
You didn't go with them?
No.
Give them a call okay?
I miss the old times,
when we would do reports together, don't you?
Angels should be in heaven,
not in hell like us.
Take it easy, Cheer.
There's always next year.
I only have 3 friends.
I wouldn't do that if I were her.
Do you wanna come over later to do the report?
Why don't you write report with your new gang?
Top's not here yet?
He told me to tutor a sophomore.
He's not here yet, he said
he was going to borrow a book for the sophomore.
That day, I was in the hospital.
Which day?
The day my dad missed the penalty kick,
I was born on that day.
My dad never played soccer again
after I was born.
I'm such a bad luck.
Our team never made it to the finals again.
Are you okay?
I'm used to all the teasing.
My last name is
Shone, the son of the guy who missed the goal.
But it's okay,
I'm in the team now.
Are you thinking of playing professional soccer?
I don't know.
Right now, I just wanna have someone.
Nam, I still can't find the book.
Can you come help look for it?
We won't take long, Shone!
What's the surprise for Ake's birthday?
You'll see.
Time for our special show for tonight.
The story happened when we were in 5th grade.
We happened to like the same girl.
Her name is Bo, she's in 4th grade.
So we both practiced dancing
hoping to be her partner in the event.
And when the day comes,
Shone...
got chicken pox,
so I got to be her dance partner.
But Top backed out on that day,
so we both didn't get her anyway.
He threatened to not be friends with me
so we promised each other
since that day...
That we will never like the same girl.
Right?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday...
Same time tomorrow?
Let's go see Shone's soccer match.
You don't have to pick me up anymore.
Why not? Are you busy?
No,
I mean...
you don't have to pick me up ever again.
Are you upset because I kissed you?
But you're my girlfriend, aren't you?
I never said I was your girlfriend.
After all these?
I'm sorry,
but I have someone I like.
Who is it?
Who...
This is the worse ever
in the history of my love life.
Can I ask you a favor?
Could you not ask her out
no matter what happens?
Do you think she broke up with you because of me?
No,
I just can't take
if my best friend
is seeing the girl I love.
There's not much I can do, can I?
Are you okay with that?
Yeah.
Thanks mom.
I've spoken to the manager
of Bangkok Glass team, son.
What did he say?
He said,
maybe he'll accept you for training camp
of Bangkok Glass League.
Hope he's not kidding about this?
Nobody jokes about things like that.
Just be ready,
maybe you'll have to move
to Bangkok after high school.
Dad.
Thank you.
You should've told me,
I would've applied for the grant to go with you.
Sorry,
I was really preoccupied.
I think the director
has found a new P.E. Replacement.
You're just irreplaceable,
I can confirm that.
May I ask for something from you before you leave?
What can I do for you?
This...
Maybe too much to ask from you?
I asked for you heart but got a whistle.
There's...
the new P.E. Teacher.
I think you should hurry and be on your way,
you might miss your flight.
I feel occupied all of a sudden. Bye now.
You don't waste your time at all.
Hello...
Aren't you the new P.E. Teacher?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Boat.
I'd love a boat ride.
"Bye bye Junior. Hello Senior!"
"It's summer break again."
Why won't you stay for high school?
I just love the pink uniform
of the technical school I applied for.
Very very pretty.
So the whole school's in pink?
Monday, I wait.
Tuesday I still wait for you.
Wednesday, you never show up.
Thursday, all are empty.
Friday, Saturday or Sunday,
not a day goes by without missing you.
We can never turn back time.
To the day we met, the day we got closer,
the day we held hands,
the day I love you, the day I told you,
the day you dream.
No matter how long,
how many months or years,
my memories of you shall remain.
Cheer,
I'm sorry.
Your song is so cheesy.
Why did you sing along?
We're laughing at your song.
Friday, Saturday or Sunday
not a day goes by without missing you.
We can never turn back time...
Nam.
We heard from Prof.
In while we were buying ice cream
at the market that your...
your exam result...
What about my exam result?
That you are the top of the class.
I thought so...
Right.
I'm the top of the class.
Mom, I'm top of the class this semester.
You'll get to see your dad now.
I'll get to see dad, get to see dad.
Dad...
I'll get to see dad.
Can I kiss you for him?
I ranked 8 in my class, can I come too?
Sure.
I'll bring you some toys and sweets.
I'm going to the states.
Bring us back some snow please.
You got it?
Is 50 Baht, okay?
It's a 100 Bath, take it or leave it.
I had to sneak in, almost got bitten by stray dogs.
70 Baht?
Leave it then.
No, give it to me.
He's cute.
Is he your boyfriend?
It's Bam's girlfriend.
No, I just took the photo for her.
Please don't tell mom.
Mom, Pang's...
Nam.
Yes?
Pang's hungry, is the food ready?
Almost done, dear.
Just be a good girl, okay?
What about you?
What about my money?
Come on have some snacks, kids.
Thank you...
Snack on these first, okay?
Does Shone knows how you feel about him?
You've like him since first year.
I don't think you should tell him,
so it can be a world record that a silly girl
has been in love with him for 3 years
without him knowing.
Maybe you'll never
see him again for the rest of your life.
Aren't you going to anything about it?
I've done everything the book says, haven't I?
We're here to support you, what are you afraid of?
You pretty, smart,
nice and cheesy.
How can he not fall for you?
Is that a compliment?
Tip No. 10 from Thailand is probably
the best and straight to the point.
This is for you, sign here.
Thank you.
Sign here...
Take my photo...
Love...
Write on top right there.
Thank you.
"On top"
Go, girl.
The pool's out of order, sorry.
Hey, you haven't signed my shirt.
Shone...
I have something to tell you.
I really like you. I've liked you for 3 years.
I've done everything I could for you to notice me.
I...
I've tried out for a dancer,
been in a play, a drum major
and even studied harder.
But I realized that I shouldn't have been
straightforward with you
about my feelings a long time ago.
I just want to tell you that I like you.
"Pin loves Shone"
Pin and you...
Since when?
Just last week.
You two are together.
What a perfect match.
You guys make a great couple.
I wish you both good luck.
Nam!
Nam.
I'm okay...
You guys are perfect.
Nam, are you all right?
Nam.
Let her go.
What wrong?
Pin.
Hi dad.
Welcome to Glass Rabbit Junior Team.
Thank you dad.
This is Uncle Neng, Bangkok Glass Team Manager.
Hello...
This is Uncle Nguan, the coach.
Thank you all.
Yeah!
He's happy!
Congratulations, son.
Pack your things, you're leaving tonight with them.
The training camp starts tomorrow.
Tonight?
What are you waiting for, son?
"This scrap book is funny, it shows how hard you try."
Home safe.
"Just want to let you know that,
you had my heart since we met."
She looks the same,
a Snow white in braces.
"I told Pin that you look the same."
"You look cute as usual."
"I held your hand for the first time,"
"but had to let go, so no one would suspect."
"I tasted an apple I gave you."
"You're doing much better now. Keep it up."
Throw it up!
"Love conquers all, especially fears."
"Planting a rose is a tough job."
It's from a friend of mine.
"I gave you a rose today,
but told you it was from a friend."
"I couldn't tell you the truth."
"Do you know it hurts me
to see Top said he loved you?"
"How come we never have our moments?"
"I wish you could ride on my back."
Nam.
Would you be my girlfriend?
Can I ask you a favor?
Could you not ask her out?
"9 years later"
There's a window on that side.
Kai, could you take the customer?
I'll be right back.
Hello, handsome.
You're sleepy aren't you?
Sorry to bother you every time.
No problem, your kid is like mine.
Come on, don't be a cry baby.
Don't mess up my hair.
Gotta go now.
Bye kiddo.
I wish his real dad would love him like this.
Come on now.
Call me.
Shone.
Are you going to that TV show?
I don't know yet.
Bye Shone, say bye!
Please hurry up!
Continue to Break 2, are you ready?
-A min
OK
Clothing staffs ready?
- Yes
No worry, it will be perfect!
I'm ready now!
Please relax.
Our show isn't formal.
Yes
- You're so beautiful
-Thank you
It's good that Nam is fashionable.
If Nam was beautiful as mom like me....
Teacher Boat!
Hello
Since that time,
I've rode the boat all this time.
So envious!
He likes to do sweet things
I'm jealous
He always surprises me
Surprise again
Uh.. That.. That is a rose
I have to eat, if not he will sulk
5..4..3..2..
Now, we're here with Nam
The designer of the beautiful clothes that we've just watched
Hello
Our fans may know her well
cause she is the designer in only a few of Thais that are famous in New York
and this is the evidence
This is only a part of her work
Nam, do you know that...
In Thailand, you're also well-known
I still have to develop my skill
So, what work will you do as you came back to Thailand?
There's a brand that would like to organize a fashion show
I think it's interesting, so I agree to do
and because I want to come back
I miss my mom
Nam used to tell reporters that....
When you were young
Umm... I'm sorry
You were so ugly and had bad sense of fashion
That's totally different from now
What make you've changed yourself this much?
Because, I fell in love some one
falling in love?
Could you tell the story?
Yes, he was my senior
M.4 senior
He was a football player
and very cute
At that time, I.........
Had bug face studying M.1
Developed myself a lot
If It could make me to be beautiful, to be better
I tried to do it
and tried to study better so he might interest in me
Did he know it, in the end?
He knew but it didn't have a happy ending
I went to study in the US
to stay with my dad
It's bad
but when I think about it.
He is like....
my inspiration
He made me use the love in good way
He is like....
The power that support me to be better and better
Till I am today's Nam
Khun Nam, you remember this notebook?
You may recall it?
Yes, I remember
If so, let's welcome the owner of this book
Shone, the former footballer of Bangkok glass
Now, he's changed his career to be a pro-photographer
I want to give it to Nam
Nam???
It's Nam's
Please sit
Shone, after you've never met Nam for 9 years.....
Do you have something to tell Nam?
I want to tell you that......
This button
is not mine
It may be Ding's
How about you Nam?
Do you have something to tell him?
I want to ask Shone that......
Have you been married?
Umm.........
Um...I
I have been waiting for someone to come back from the US