Wake up.
Wake up,
wake up, wake up.
Up ya wake, up ya wake,
up ya wake.
This is Mister Señor Love Daddy.
Your voice of choice.
The world's only 12-hour
strong man on the air,
Here on We-Love radio, 108 FM.
The last on your dial,
but first in your hearts,
and that's the truth, Ruth.
Here I am.
Am I here?
Ya know it. It ya know.
This is Mister Señor Love Daddy
doing the nasty to ya ears,
ya ears to the nasty.
I's only play
da platters dat matter
the matters dey platter,
and that's the truth, Ruth.
From the heart of Bed-Stuy,
you're listening to We-Love radio.
Doing the ying and the yang,
the hip and the hop,
the stupid fresh thing,
the flippity-flop.
Awoo!
I have today's forecast for you.
Hot! Sss!
The color for today is black.
That's right, black.
So absorb these rays
and save that heat for winter.
So wear that black
and be involved.
Also today's temperature
is rising over 100 degrees.
So that's a Jheri-curl alert.
That's right, Jheri-curl alert.
If you have one, stay inside,
or you'll have
a permanent plastic helmet.
All right, we're going to
say hello to Mister and Missus,
that's Mister and Missus.
Happy birthday to Big Red
and Miss Annie Mae, 100 today.
Stay out of this heat,
and you might live that long.
There's a water shortage,
so keep those showers
to one minute.
Two, if you're with a friend.
Get on out there.
Damn! Whoo!
It is hot!
Get that pink slip.
So get up, get out!
That's what I'm talking about.
We don't want to see
anybody lose their job
'cause nobody
got no money as it is.
All right. Now we're
going to talk about it.
We're going
to rock 'n'roll...
Good m-m-morning.
M- M-My name is Smiley.
This is M-M-M-M-Malcolm...
X.
And this is
M- M-M-M-Martin K-K-King.
Now,
th-they are d-d-dead...
but w-we still
h- h-have to f-f-f-fight
a- against ap-apartheid.
10, 15, 20, 30, 40, 50,
60, 70, 80, 100.
20, 40, 60, shit!
80... 300.
20, 40, 60, 80...
Wait, that's 300.
300, 350, 450...
cash dollar bills.
Mookie. Why are you always
bothering me when I'm sleeping...
Wake up, wake up.
Stop breathing
down my neck.
Why should I wake up?
It's going to be hot, Jade.
Saturday's the only day
I get to sleep late.
Damn.
Stop, Mookie.
That's not funny.
Leave me alone
when I'm sleeping.
You don't love
Brother Mookie anymore?
I loves you, Jade.
I'll get a lock
and keep your ass out of here.
Why don't you go to work, man,
and leave me alone?
Later, got to get paid.
Yeah, brush your teeth.
I brushed my teeth.
Your breath stinks.
It's your upper lip.
What's up, Sal?
How you doin' there, boy?
Man, I got to get me
a Cadillac like that.
I'm getting a car
just like that.
Oh, it's hot.
Sonny, how's the vegetables, huh?
Good morning, Sal. Vito. Pino.
Pop, you talk to that
air-condition guy?
I been calling him all week.
He won't come around
unless he has a police escort.
Pino, get a broom
and sweep up front.
Vito, get a broom
Huh?
Sweep up the front.
What?
Get a broom
and sweep out front!
See? Every time
you tell Pino what to do,
he tells me what to do.
He's brain-dead, Pop, for years.
Both of you, shut up.
Tell Pino!
Am I talking to myself?
I didn't want to come anyway.
I hate this friggin' place.
I detest it like a sickness.
You, you detest this place
like a sickness?
That's like really hate, you know?
That's hate.
I didn't say that.
Oh, you didn't say that?
I just heard it.
Am I going crazy?
Did I just hear that, Vito?
I mean, do you think
you can do better?
No, I didn't think so.
This is a respectable business,
and there's nothing wrong with that.
I mean, if there's
something wrong with that, tell me.
Is there something
wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong. OK?
Do me a favor.
Get a broom and sweep up.
Tell Vito.
What are you... deaf?
Pop asked you.
I'm going to kill somebody today.
I can't believe it.
What?
That you like her.
I don't like her.
Yeah?
Hell no.
Hey.
Hi, Mookie.
Mookie.
Hey, Mook.
Mornin', Mookie.
Morning, Miss Mother Sister.
Mookie, don't work
too hard today.
It's going to be hot as the devil.
I don't want you falling out,
you hear me?
I hear you, Mother Sister.
Good.
All right.
I'll be watching you, son.
Mother Sister always watches.
Mookie...
You're late again.
You live up the block, what?
Your Cadillac broke?
Hello, Sal, Vito.
Yo, Mook. What up?
Just coolin'.
You're still late.
Relax, Pino.
Take it easy.
You'll live longer.
Take the broom.
The front needs sweeping.
Wait. You sweep.
I bet Sal asked you first anyway.
That's right.
Vito, sti cazzi.
Fuck that.
I get paid for delivering pizzas.
You're paid
to do what we say.
What we say?
Did you hear Sal?
Sal didn't say nothing.
Who's working for who?
Shh.
Come on in, Mayor.
Morning, gentlemen.
Pino, Mookie, Vito, Sal.
How are you?
Ooh-whee. It's going to be
a scorcher today.
That's for sure.
Need any work done here?
Daddy, perchè tu dai
questo azupep soldi per niente affatto.
Why don't you
leave him alone?
He's a good man.
Leave him alone.
Choose your weapon, Mayor.
You dropped something, Mayor.
You are going to have
the cleanest sidewalk in Brooklyn.
Clean as the Board
of Health. Ha-ha!
All right, Mayor.
Pop, I don't believe
this shit.
You running welfare
or something?
Every day you give
this azupep a dollar.
What's azupep?
Are you Italian?
The Mayor ain't no azupep.
You give this azupep a dollar
for sweeping our sidewalk.
What's Mookie for, huh?
He don't even work.
I work harder,
and I'm your son.
Let's see you carry
six large pies up six flights,
no elevator either and shit.
Shut up, you two.
Yeah, Pop.
Why don't you shut up, too, Vito?
We're going to talk.
Says who?
Says me.
What did I just say?
Don't start that
"Mookie don't work" shit.
Yo, Ahmad!
I coulda done that.
Man, shut up.
Yo, Ahmad!
Shit. Look, stop.
Punchy, you want to do
any more screaming,
be my guest.
Yo, who's yelling my name?
Well, Punchy told me to.
Punchy told me to.
Don't listen to this knothead.
It'll get you in trouble.
Heard that, Punchy.
Yo, Ella? Ella?
What?
You got a brain.
Use it.
Peace, y'all.
Peace, Radio Raheem.
Peace, man.
You the man.
I'm just visiting.
It's your world, G.
For real,
in a big motherfuckin' way.
That boy's livin' very large.
Even walks in stereo.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yo, P.E.'s in full effect...
Boyee!
Radio Raheem
like a motherfucker.
Radio Raheem.
Blastin' that big box.
Cold rockin' the scene.
Where's the Miller High Life?
Where is the Miller High Life?
No more High Life.
You look what we have.
No more High Life?
What kind of a joint is this?
How come no more High Life?
Look, doctor,
this ain't Korea or China
or wherever you're from.
You get some Miller High Life
in this fuckin' joint.
You buy another beer.
Da Mayor...
don't drink this Lite shit.
Tastes like cold pot liquor.
All right, all right.
But you're askin' a lot
to make a man change
his beer. A lot, doctor.
Hey! You old drunk!
What did I tell you
about drinkin'
in front of my stoop?
Move on.
You're blockin' my view.
You are ugly enough.
Don't stare at me.
The evil eye doesn't work on me.
Mother Sister, you been
talkin' about me for 18 years.
What I ever done to you?
You a drunk fool.
Besides that?
The Mayor don't bother nobody,
and nobody don't bother
the Mayor but you.
The Mayor just tend
to his own business.
I love everybody.
I even love you.
Hold your tongue.
You don't have that much love.
One day you gonna be nice to me.
We may both be dead and buried,
but you gonna be nice.
At least civil.
I told you, I'm not going
to baby-sit for you,
and that's it!
What are you
talking about?
Yesterday you said you would.
Now today
you're changing your mind?
No, I'm not changing...
¿Ay, Mommy,
que mucho jota?
Get off of me, please!
I do everything for you.
You can't do shit for me!
Yo tengo
el derecho de salirte.
Right, right.
You know it's not like that, Mommy.
I can do everything for you,
but you won't do shit for me.
Stop it!
That lady makes me sick!
Your father makes me sick, too.
Everybody makes me sick.
Shit.
Your father ain't no real father.
He's a bum.
Chump change, to-the-curb,
pulling no major pub, bum!
Mike.
Fuck Mike Tyson!
I remember when he mugged
that woman on Lexington.
I remember that shit.
You're going to tell him?
I'll tell him.
Fuck Mike Tyson!
To his face?
You goddamn right!
He'll knock
your goddamn ass off.
You talk shit now.
I'll drop him like a bad habit.
If Tyson dream about whippin' my ass,
he better wake up and apologize.
Well, gentlemen, the way I see it,
if this hot weather continues,
it's going to melt the polar caps
and the whole wide world.
And all those parts
that ain't water already
will surely be flooded.
You dumb ass, simple motherfucker!
Where you read that shit, eh?
The polar caps.
Don't worry about it.
When it happens,
and I'm in my boat
and you black asses are drowning,
don't call for me
to throw you no rope,
no lifesaver, or no nothing.
You 30 cent away from a quarter.
How the fuck
you gonna get a boat?
Here, boy.
Don't worry about it.
Goddamn right.
Look at you.
You're raggedy as a roach,
eat the holes out of doughnuts.
Raggedy motherfucker!
Don't worry about it.
I'm in good shape.
I will be.
I'll be back on my feet
soon enough.
Look, raggedy-ass shoes!
So run over, you gotta
lay down to put 'em on.
So, ML, ML, ML, tell me.
When is all this goddamn ice
supposed to melt?
Hello. Sal's Pizza.
Yep.
Meatball hero,
eggplant parmesan.
You got it.
Yeah, we deliver.
Of course, we deliver.
All right. Where is that?
You going to pay now
or on layaway?
How much?
You been coming here
three times a day.
What are you, a retard?
It's $1.50.
Put some cheese
on that motherfucker.
Extra cheese is $2.00.
$2.00?
Yeah, $2.00.
Hey, forget that shit.
Damn, Sal, you're cheap, man.
Yo, Mook!
Mookie! How come
ain't no brothers
up on the wall?
Man, ask Sal, all right?
Hey, Sal, how come
ain't no brothers there?
You want brothers on the wall?
Get your own place.
You can put your brothers and uncles,
nieces and nephews,
your stepfather, stepmother,
whoever you want.
But this is my pizzeria.
American-Italians
on the wall only.
Take it easy, Pop.
And you, hey, don't start
with me today.
What?
Yeah, that might be fine, Sal,
but you own this.
Rarely do I see
any American-Italians eating in here.
All I see is black folks.
Since we spend much money here,
we do have some say.
You lookin' for trouble?
Are you a troublemaker,
is that what you are?
Yeah, I'm a troublemaker.
I'm making trouble.
You're a ball-breaker.
You're always coming in here
looking for trouble, aren't you?
Suppose I busted your head.
How would you...
Mookie, you want to get
your friend out of here?
What, you gonna
kick me out now?
I'm not.
You're kicking yourself out.
We want some brothers
up on the wall...
You know, Malcolm X,
Nelson Mandela,
Michael Jordan!
Tomorrow!
Mookie, get him out.
I'm trying! Take your slice.
I know you paid for it.
All right, you're kicking me out.
Beat me on the head
and kick me out.
I paid for my...
Look, boycott Sal's!
Boycott Sal's.
I got your boycott swinging.
Yo, what you laughin' at?
Mookie, I paid for my slice.
I spend much money in there!
What are you trying to do?
I want brothers on the wall.
You're fucking my shit up.
It's between me and Sal.
You're fucking me up.
I ain't trying to fuck you up.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
In a week, it'll be squashed.
A week?
A week.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right?
Bet.
Mook...
Stay black!
This guy's your friend, right?
If I'm wrong, tell me.
He's my friend.
If he don't behave,
I don't want him here anymore.
I can't do nothing.
Talk brother talk to him.
Brother talk?
People are free to do
whatever the hell they want.
Free? What the hell
are you talking about?
Free? There's no free here.
I'm the boss.
No freedom.
You want freedom?
There, that's free.
Take that order out.
He's got an order.
Let's go. Come on!
Get to work!
You're standing here doing nothing.
You're afraid of the goddamn oven.
Hit the oven!
Is this the address?
Is that the address?
Is that what he just asked me?
Mookie.
Come here, doctor.
Mayor, I got to go.
I'm working.
Come here, doctor.
This is the Mayor talking.
All right.
Doctor?
What?
Always do the right thing.
That's it?
That's it.
I got it.
I'm gone.
M- M-Mookie...
How you doin', Smiley?
P- P-Pay...
2... 2 d-d-dollars.
The other one.
The other one, Smiley.
1... 1 d-dollar.
That one.
Tonight, when I get paid.
When...
When you get p-p...
Bye, M-Mookie.
M- M-M-M-Malcolm.
M- M-M-M-Martin.
Shit.
Seen your brother this morning.
Yeah, on his way to work, I hope.
This might take
a little bit of time, Mother Sister.
I got nowhere to go.
We haven't had a good sit-down
for a long while.
Tender-headed runs in my family.
Are you tender-headed?
Yeah. Me, too.
I don't fool with it.
That's why only you can touch it.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
The comb got caught.
Be gentle, child.
Mother Sister's old.
Yes, Mother Sister.
Ooh-whee!
I didn't know you had
such beautiful hair.
There's a lot you don't know.
I'm not stopping.
I'm on my way.
Mother Sister,
why are you so cruel to the Mayor?
It isn't right.
I ain't studying no Mayor.
He reminds me
of my least favorite peoples...
my tenant and my ex-husband.
Goddamn!
Bless his soul.
Whew!
¡Salud!
What are you doing?
Ahmad, put me down!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's Radio.
Radio, man.
Hey, what's up, Radio?
Radio!
Don't! Stop!
Hey, yo! Don't be
fucking with the water now.
Oh, man, go ahead.
You got it!
There's going to be
a lot of fucking trouble
if this car gets wet.
Ain't nobody
fucking around, man.
Why don't you just go ahead?
This is an antique here, hotshot.
Man, go ahead!
It's what?
Hey, man, I'm...
I'm serious, man!
All right.
OK, you won't get wet.
Make sure I don't.
Go ahead! Go ahead!
Drive the car!
All right,
I'm driving it.
Get out!
Get out, motherfucker!
Fuck you back!
Turn the fucking water.
Go!
Those son of a bitches!
They got me fucking soaked!
Officer!
Wait a minute.
Hold it!
I want an arrest made now!
Right now!
What's the matter?
Calm down.
Sir, tell us what happened.
Two black kids soaked me
with the fire hydrant.
They ruined my car!
It's an antique!
They got me soaked!
So where are they?
Brilliant fucking question!
They ran away!
What do you think?
Do you wish
to file a complaint, sir?
Yeah. I want 'em locked
under the fucking jail.
I'm going to turn off the water.
Where you going?
Where's he going?
Did you catch their names?
Officer, what the fuck
are you doing?
Just calm down.
Did you catch their names?
Fuck you, their names!
Moe and Joe!
Moe and Joe what, sir?
Moe and Joe what?
Moe and Joe Black.
How's that?
They're brothers, sir?
Brothers. Yeah,
they're fucking brothers.
This hydrant
better not come back on again,
or there's going to be hell to pay!
Come answer to me, goddamn it!
Ask him. He knows.
He witnessed
the whole fucking thing!
Tell him what happened.
Let us do the questioning, sir.
Fucking bullshit.
Know anything about this?
Who were the punks?
Doctors, those that'll tell
don't know,
and those that know won't tell.
What the fuck is that, voodoo shit?
Hey, the Mayor don't
know nothin', all right?
Hey! He's leaving?
Keep this hydrant off.
Go swim at Coney Island.
I'm talking to you!
He's leaving?
What about me?
I suggest you get to your car
before these people
strip it clean.
Have a nice day, sir.
He left there
about a half hour ago?
No, no problem.
Thank you.
Mookie left...
Where the hell you been?
I got a business to run.
Run it then, OK?
That's for the station.
Love Daddy?
Yeah. Love Daddy.
Hey, Pop, I'm going
to go with Mookie, OK?
Yeah. You make sure
Mookie don't jerk around.
Wait up, Mook!
You ain't going anywhere.
How you doing?
Vito, I know Pino's
your brother and shit,
but you should kick his ass
the next time he touches you.
The next time he hits you,
fuck him up!
Whoa! Whoa!
Yo, hey, Mook.
I appreciate this concern,
but I don't think
it's any of your business, Mook.
Yeah, but you need
to kick his ass.
Smiley, not now.
If I had a brother like him,
we'd fight all the time.
Smiley!
Mook, you don't got
a brother like him.
Smiley, get out of here!
If you did, you wouldn't know
what to do with him.
He's my brother.
I'm not going to hit him.
I got a sister.
You never clocked your sister.
Does she bug you?
You don't hit girls
like you hit guys.
Just fuck your brother up once,
it'll be over with.
We'll be out
of this fucking conversation.
It might do some good?
Yes, all right.
A lot of good.
Let's give...
Love Daddy!
Peoples, my stomach's
been grumbling,
but help has arrived.
My main man Mookie
has saved the day!
Straight from Sal's
Famous Pizzeria up the block.
Step up to the mike, Mookie.
Come on. Come on!
Don't be shy.
Mmm, this smells good.
Go ahead.
This is your Love Daddy talking,
Starvin' like Marvin.
Say something.
All right, Love Daddy.
I'd like to dedicate this record
with all my heart and soul...
to Tina.
All right!
Let me put this song on
while I go to work
on this chicken
parmigiana hero
with extra cheese
and extra s-sauce.
Salsa. Musica latina.
El sonido de mi pais,
el pais mas bello,
Puerto Rico.
Chill, man.
Shut up.
I'm trying to read.
Have some fucking respect, huh?
Not so loud!
I want to listen
to my salsa music!
Chill! Chill! Chill!
You think you got it
like that, bro? ¿Chocolate?
Let's go, motherfucker!
Turn it up, Stevie!
Blow it away!
Blow it!
Yeah, blow it away!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Turn up the bongos!
Oh, yeah!
Yo, Steve!
Put it up loud.
Yeah, man!
You got it, bro.
¡Hey, pendejo!
¿Qué pasa, la neta?
Come on, Steve, man.
Rafael, suba el volumen.
You're dead, choco-man.
He's a punk anyway, man.
Yo! Hey. ¡Pendejo!
Hey, ¡pendejo! What's up?
¡Pendejo!
He's a sucker, man.
A punk.
See last night's game?
Uh-huh. I saw it.
Best pitcher in the game...
Dwight Gooden.
I knew you'd bring that up.
Who's better?
Roger Clemens.
Clemens sucks.
He can't carry Dwight's jock.
Dwight's best in the game.
What's up, Buggin' Out?
You the man.
No, you the man.
I'm a struggling black
trying to keep my dick hard
in a cruel world.
What's with the white boy?
Don't start no shit.
Vito's down.
Vito's down, all right?
Yeah, right.
Vito's down.
Yeah.
Phew.
Yo!
Damn.
Yeah?
You almost knocked me down.
The word is "excuse me."
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
You stepped on
my brand-new white Air Jordans.
That's all you can say?
You're serious?
Yeah! I'll fuck
your prick two times!
Two times!
Who told you to be
in my neighborhood?
I own this brownstone.
Who told you to buy a brownstone
in my neighborhood?
What do you want to live
in a black neighborhood for,
anyway?
I understand this is
a free country.
A man can live
wherever he wants.
Free country?
I should fuck you up for saying that.
Yo, man.
Your Jordans are fucked up!
Might as well throw them shits out.
They're broke.
They looked good
before he messed them up.
He was even talking
about your mama...
Shit, you used
to be so fine!
How much they cost?
$100!
$108 with tax.
You're lucky
I got a loving heart.
Next time, cross the street quick.
I'm out of here.
Break his feet!
You should buy me another pair!
Black Panther'd whip his ass!
You're lucky I'm
a righteous black man!
Otherwise you'd be
in serious trouble! Serious!
Let's fuck him up.
Move back to Massachusetts!
I was born in Brooklyn.
- No! -
Oh! - Man!
Get outta here!
I should send Vito
with you all the time.
Yeah. No more
90-minute deliveries
Around the corner.
I work hard like
everybody else here, OK?
You know that's true, Pino.
Vito, come here.
Come here.
What's going on
between you two?
You boyfriend and girlfriend?
What did we just talk about?
What?
What you talking about?
Smack him.
Any smacking
around here, I'll do.
You going to listen to him
tell you to smack me,
your older brother?
Remember who you are.
Your name is Vito Frangone,
not Vito Muhammad.
OK?
I'd love for you
to stay out of my business.
Stop putting these thoughts
into my brother's head, OK?
Look, I don't play
that Muhammad shit, all right?
What Muhammad shit?
Look... don't fuck me, all right?
Oh, man.
Fuck, man.
I hate this place.
What a waste.
As I was saying
before we were
so rudely interrupted
by New York City's finest...
What was you saying?
The motherfucker
wasn't saying shit.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Look at what?
It's a goddamn shame.
What's a goddamn shame?
Sweet Dick Willie.
That's my name.
Do I have to spell it out?
Make it plain.
OK, but listen up.
I'm going to break it down.
Let it be broke.
Can you dig it?
It's dug.
Look at those Korean motherfuckers
across the street.
Bet they haven't been
off the boat a year
before they opened
their own place.
Right. It's been about a year.
A motherfuckin' year
off the motherfuckin' boat,
and they got a business
in our neighborhood.
A good business,
occupying a building
that had been boarded up
for longer than
I care to remember,
and I've been here a long time.
Yeah, a long time.
Hear, boy.
Now, for the life of me...
you know, I can't
figure this out.
Either them Korean motherfuckers
are geniuses...
or you black asses
are just plain dumb.
Fuck you.
It's got to be
because we're black.
Ain't no other explanation.
You know it's true.
They're always keeping
the black man to about shit!
Oh, oh! You motherfuckers
hold that shit down.
I'm tired of that
old excuse, that shit.
I swear, man,
I will be one happy fool
when we open
our own business
right here in our neighborhood.
I swear to God,
I'll be first to spend
what little money I got.
You motherfuckers
are always talking
that old Keith Sweat shit...
"I'm gonna do this,
I'm gonna do that."
You ain't gonna do nothing.
You're gonna sit on this corner.
When you going
to get your business?
Just like I thought.
You ain't going to do
a goddamn thing.
But I'm going
to go give them Koreans
more of my money.
Out of my way.
It's Miller time, motherfuckers.
Old Moosehead fuckers
telling me what to do.
Coconut, you got nerve.
You got off the boat, too.
Leave me alone.
Kung Fu, give me
one of them damn beers.
No more free beer.
Don't push me, baby.
Don't start no shit.
Mr. Sweet Dick Willie.
Right. That's my name.
It's a motherfuckin' shame.
Man, ain't that a bitch?
Here, Doctor.
What's your name?
Eddie.
How old are you?
10.
What makes Sammy run?
My name is Eddie.
My name is Eddie Lovell.
Relax. I want you
to go to the store for me.
What'll it cost?
How would I know?
What am I buying?
Eddie, you're too smart
for your own britches.
How much do you want
to go to the store
for the man?
50 cents.
You got a deal.
I want you to get me
a quart of beer.
Miller High Life.
Say it's for your bedridden,
old granddad.
Now, go. Go.
What is wrong with him?
He ain't got no money for nobody.
Look at this here, man.
Cut this shit out.
What makes you the Mayor
of this block?
Shit, he's self-appointed.
Leave the man alone.
Shut up!
Look, you all leave me
the hell alone.
I ain't going out
like that, man.
You walk around this block
like you own it.
For real.
You're so old,
you're like a fossil.
You're a bum.
You're an old drunk zero.
Now what do you got to say?
What you know about me?
Can't even pee straight,
nary a one of you.
What you know about anything?
Unless you...
Unless you done stood
in the door...
and listened to your
five hungry children
crying for bread,
and you can't do
anything about it.
Your woman standing there...
You can't even look
her in the eye.
Unless you done that,
you don't know my pain,
my hurt, my feelings.
You don't know shit!
Don't call me bum.
Don't call me a drunk.
You don't got the sense
God give a billy goat!
Don't call me nothing!
It's disrespectful.
Your mamas and papas
raised you better.
I hope you finished
your little soliloquy
'cause I been peeing straight
for years.
Understand what I'm saying?
And you're right.
I wouldn't stand around
listening to my children
go hungry.
I'd be getting a job,
anything to feed them.
You're right.
I don't want to know your pain.
I don't care.
You did this to yourself.
Every day I see you walk
up and down this block, inebriated.
Never sober, but that's
what D-A stands for...
Da Mayor... drunk ass.
Come on!
This man's getting me mad!
He don't get no respect!
You'll never get
respect here, boy!
I respect those
who respect themselves!
Ahmad!
Come on, man!
Tina, I know it's been four days.
I'm a working man.
I work, too,
and I seem to make time.
What do you want me
to do, huh?
Spend some time
with me and Hector!
I want you to try and make
this relationship work.
If not, I'd rather not
be bothered with your ass.
Mookie, you're too, too tired.
OK, all right, damn.
I'll be over sometime today.
You always say later!
Later when I get off work.
Bring some ice cream.
I'm burning up.
Mookie, do you love me?
Do I love you?
Mookie, get off the phone!
Be off in a second,
all right, Sal?
Do I love you?
I dedicated a record
on Love Daddy's show to you.
So what?
How's anybody going
to call in, Mookie?
All right!
One time.
You probably wasted...
If that ain't love, you're crazy.
Are you deaf or what?
Pino, I'm talking on the phone.
I think I see that.
Tina, I got to go.
Yeah, Pino's an asshole.
See you later today.
Later!
Everybody happy?
Sal's Famous.
Yeah. Yeah, hold it.
OK, two large anchovy
and pepperoni.
OK. Just hold on one second.
See, Daddy? Mookie's
fucking talking on the phone,
people are trying
to call in orders.
He's making us lose business.
Mookie!
20 minutes.
How come niggers
are so stupid?
If you see a nigger,
kick his ass.
Fuck you.
Stay off the phone.
Hey, Mookie.
Forget about it.
Can I talk to you for a second?
What?
Who's your favorite
basketball player?
Magic Johnson.
Who's your favorite movie star?
Eddie Murphy.
Who's your favorite rock star?
Prince.
You're a Prince freak.
Boss. Bruce.
Prince.
All you talk about is
nigger this and nigger that.
Your favorite people are niggers.
It's different.
Magic, Eddie, Prince...
are not niggers.
I mean, they're not black,
I mean...
Let me explain myself.
They're...
They're not really black.
I mean, they're black,
but not really.
They're more than black.
It's different.
It's different?
Yeah. To me,
it's different.
Deep down you wish
you were black.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go ahead, laugh.
Your hair's kinkier than mine.
What does that mean?
And you know what they say
about dark Italians.
You know, I been listening...
and reading...
You been reading now?
I read.
I've been reading
about your leaders.
Reverend Al
"Mister 'Do" Sharpton.
Jesse "Keep hope alive"...
That's fucked up.
"Keep hope alive."
That's fucked.
Don't talk about Jesse.
And even the other guy,
what's his name?
Faraman, Fairakan...
Minister Farakhan.
Right. Sorry.
Anyway, Minister Farakhan
always talks about the so-called day...
when the black man will rise.
What does he say?
"We will one day rule the earth
as we did in our glorious past"?
That's right.
What past?
What did I miss?
We started civilization.
Man, keep dreaming, man.
Then you woke up!
Pino, fuck you.
Fuck your fucking pizza,
and fuck Frank Sinatra.
Yeah? Well, fuck you, too,
and fuck Michael Jackson.
You dago, wop, guinea,
garlic-breath,
pizza-slinging,
spaghetti-bending,
Vic Damone, Perry Como,
Luciano Pavarotti,
solo mio,
nonsinging motherfucker.
You gold-teeth,
gold-chain-wearing,
fried-chicken
and biscuit-eating monkey,
ape, baboon, big thigh,
fast-running,
high-jumping,
spear-chucking,
360-degree basketball-dunking,
tit, soon, spade, moulan, yan.
Take your fucking pizza piece
and go the fuck back to Africa.
You little slanty-eyed,
me-no-speaky-American,
own every fruit and vegetable stand
in New York,
bullshit,
Reverend Sun Yung Moon,
Summer Olympic '88,
Korean kick-boxing,
son-of-a-bitch.
You Goya bean-eating,
15-in-a-car,
30-in-an-apartment,
pointy shoes, red-wearing,
menudo, mira-mira,
Puerto Rican cocksucker.
Yeah, you!
It's cheap.
I got good price for you,
Mayor Kochie,
"How I'm doing?"
Chocolate-egg-cream drinking,
bagel-and-lox,
B'nai B'rith, Jew asshole.
Yo! Hold up!
Time out!
Y'all, take a chill!
Ya need to cool
that shit out!
And that's the double truth, Ruth!
Sal, can you do me a favor?
That depends, Mookie.
Can you pay me now?
I can't do that.
Sal, just this once.
Can't you do me a solid, man?
Not till tonight when we close.
Sal, I want to get paid now.
You know you get paid
tonight when we close.
We're still open, OK?
If I pay you now,
you won't show tonight.
That's a bet.
Yeah, that's a bet.
I'm going to remember that.
You got to do
what you got to do.
I'll remember that.
I want you to.
Please do me a favor, hey, Mook?
Remember that.
Come on, Sal.
I can't.
Radio Raheem!
Mook.
What's happening?
It's your world.
Where you headed to?
I'm going to get a slice.
You going to Sal's?
I'll check you back there.
On the rebound.
You bet.
All right.
Oh, shit!
Let me check it out.
That's the hype!
Newest latest.
Let me tell you the story
of right hand/left hand.
It's a tale of good and evil.
Hate.
It was with this hand
that Cain iced his brother.
Love.
These five fingers,
they go straight
to the soul of man.
The right hand...
the hand of love.
The story of life is this...
Static.
One hand is always
fighting the other hand,
and the left hand
is kicking much ass.
I mean, it looks like the right hand...
love... is finished.
But hold on.
Stop the presses.
The right hand's coming back.
He got the left hand
on the ropes now.
That's right.
Yeah. Ooh!
It's a devastating right,
and hate is hurt.
Down! Ooh! Ooh!
Left hand, hate,
K.O.'d by love.
If I love you, I love you.
But if I hate you...
There it is...
love and hate.
I love you, brother.
Bet.
Radio Raheem,
check you later.
Peace.
Two slices.
No service till you
turn that shit off!
Two slices.
Turn it off!
Mr. Radio Raheem...
I can't even hear myself think!
You are disturbing me!
You are disturbing my customers!
Two slices.
You come into Sal's...
There's no music.
No rap, no music,
no music, no music.
Capisci?
Understand?
Yo, put some extra mozzarella
on that motherfuckin' shit.
Extra cheese is $2.00.
Pizza delivery!
All right. Later.
Mousie, what's up?
Watch out. Move!
People are in the same shit!
What's up, buddy?
How you livin', man?
Here come Mookie.
Mookie!
Give me some of that!
Get a job.
Don't need no job.
Get a job, man.
Shut up!
Buggin'.
Where are the females?
You don't do nothin'
with them anyway.
Hey, I've got it like that.
M- M-M-Mookie.
All right.
Here you go.
Stop bothering me.
Th-Th-Thank you,
b- b-b-black man.
All right.
Leave me alone.
Jade!
What?
Mookie, how come
you're not at Sal's?
I'm working.
What's this... Another of your
patented two-hour lunch breaks?
I wanted to come home
and take a quick shower.
Sal's going to be mad.
Sometimes I think you're more
concerned about him than me,
and I'm your brother.
That's real smart.
Sal pays you.
That's why you should work.
I work.
Slavery's over.
My name ain't Kunta Kinte.
I just don't want you
to lose the one job
you've kept over a month.
I'm carrying you as it is.
I'll always get paid.
Yeah. You always get paid.
What about
your responsibilities?
Why don't you
take better care of those?
What responsibilities?
What are you, deaf?
You know what
I'm talking about.
Take care of your responsibilities,
all right?
Who you yelling at, anyway?
I'm yelling at you.
I'm going to take care
of this shower.
I'm your big brother.
Don't be yelling at me.
You're a bum.
Don't call me no bum.
Whew!
If I want to shower
in the middle of the day,
it's OK.
Fuck Sal.
We love roll call, y'all.
Boogie Down Productions,
Rob Base, Dana Dane...
Marley Marl, Olatunji,
Chuck D., Ray Charles,
EPMD, EU, Alberta Hunter,
Run DMC, Stetsasonic,
Sugar Bear, John Coltrane,
Big Daddy Kane,
Salt 'n' Pepa,
Luther Vandross,
McCoy Tyner,
Biz Markie,
New Edition, Otis Redding,
Anita Baker,
Thelonious Monk,
Marcus Miller,
Branford Marsalis,
James Brown, Wayne Shorter,
Tracy Chapman,
Miles Davis,
Force MD's,
Oliver Nelson,
Fred Wesley, Maceo,
Janet Jackson,
Louis Armstrong,
Duke Ellington,
Jimmy Jam,
Terry Lewis,
George Clinton,
Count Basie, Mtume,
Stevie Wonder,
Bobby McFerrin,
Dexter Gordon,
Sam Cooke,
Parliament Funkadelic,
Al Jarreau,
Teddy Pendergrass,
Joe Williams,
Wynton Marsalis,
Phyllis Hyman, Sade,
Sarah Vaughn,
Roland Kirk,
Keith Sweat,
Kool Moe D,
Prince,
Ella Fitzgerald,
Diana Reeves,
Aretha Franklin,
Bob Marley,
Bessie Smith,
Whitney Houston,
Dionne Warwick,
Steel Pulse,
Little Richard,
Mahalia Jackson,
Jackie Wilson,
Cannonball and Nat Adderly,
Quincy Jones,
Marvin Gaye,
Charles Mingus,
and Mary Lou Williams.
We want to thank you all
for making our lives
just a little brighter
here on We-Love radio.
It's hot as a motherfucker.
Fan me with your ears.
Stop playin'!
Leave it alone.
Why don't he leave me alone?
Shut up.
It's too hot for that.
That's why I asked you.
We don't have money for anything.
I'm beat.
Daddy, you know,
I've been thinking.
Maybe we should sell this place.
Get out while we're still ahead...
and alive.
You really think you know
what's best for us, Pino?
I mean, couldn't we sell this
and open up a new one
in our own neighborhood?
There's too many pizzerias
already there.
Maybe we could try
something different.
What am I going to do?
That's all I know.
I been here 25 years.
Where am I going?
I'm sick of niggers.
It's like I come to work...
it's "Planet of the Apes."
I don't like being around them.
They're animals.
Why you got so much anger in you?
Why? I'll tell you why.
My friends...
They laugh at me.
They laugh right in my face.
They tell me,
"Go to Bed-Stuy.
Go feed the moulies."
Do your friends put money
in your pocket, Pino?
Food on your table?
They pay your rent,
a roof over your head?
Huh?
They're not your friends.
If they were your friends,
they wouldn't laugh at you.
Pop, what can I say?
I don't want to be here.
They don't want us here.
We should stay
in our own neighborhood,
in Bensonhurst,
and niggers in theirs.
I never had no trouble
with these people.
I sat in this window...
all I see is
little kids get old.
And I seen
the old people get older.
Yeah, sure,
some of them don't like us,
but most of them do.
I mean, for chrissake, Pino,
they grew up on my food.
On my food.
I'm very proud of that.
You may think it's funny,
but I'm very proud of that.
Look, what I'm trying
to say, son, is, uh...
Sal's Famous Pizzeria
is here to stay.
I'm sorry.
I'm your father,
and I love you.
I'm sorry, but...
but that's the way it is.
Hey, S-S-Sal.
How you doing?
These are $2.00.
Get out.
Get the fuck out of here, man!
Get the fuck out of here!
$2.00.
S- S-Sal.
Come on.
Get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here!
Every day it's the same shit.
Hey, leave that boy alone!
Get a fucking job.
Why don't you get a fucking job?
Go to fucking work!
S- S-Sal.
Get out. Get out!
See what I'm saying?
Leave that boy alone.
You know he ain't right!
Get a fucking job, man!
I'm sick of this shit.
You get a job!
I got a job.
Bring your ass here, punk!
I ain't going over there.
I ain't got no reason
to go over there.
F- F-F-Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Get the fuck out of here!
F- F-F-Fuck you!
Go inside.
Smiley, here. Here.
Smiley, here.
Here's a couple of dollars.
Come on. Come on. Here.
Fuckin' asshole!
Hey, Willie,
take it easy.
He didn't mean nothin'.
OK?
Motherfucker!
This is what I'm talking about.
Whoo!
Let's go, Jade!
Da Mayor,
we need your leadership.
Doctor, what are you talking about?
I'm organizing a boycott
of Sal's Famous.
Shit.
Keep walking, Doctor.
I don't want to hear
none of your damn black foolishness.
Damn. No juice.
No, man, no.
No!
Hell, no, goddamn it.
Sal ain't never
done nothin' to you before.
What you ought to boycott
is that barber
that fucked up your head.
Yeah!
Shit.
Come out here fuckin'
with Sweet Dick Willie.
Get the fuck away.
Would you sign a petition
to boycott Sal's Famous Pizzeria?
I ain't boycottin' jack,
string-cheese
head motherfucker.
I'm going for a slice now.
I was raised on Sal's pizza.
What you talkin' about?
You crazy, man?
Good as them
motherfuckin' pizzas is?
Black Panther eat pizza,
we eat pizza.
I'll do it without your help.
That's 75 cents.
Thanks.
Thanks, honey.
Sal, we're going to boycott
your fat pasta ass.
You're going...
You're going to boycott me?
You haven't got the balls
to boycott me.
He's going to boycott me.
Are you kidding?
Here...
Here's your boycott.
Up your ass.
You're going to boycott.
Where you going?
I'm talking to you, Pino!
I'm right here.
Go inside.
I can take care of myself.
Take it easy, OK?
No. Go inside.
Here's your boycott!
Messed up my Jordans with muck.
Damn!
Get this thing
straightened out, man.
White guy/black man.
I can't believe this crap.
Ah, your Jordans are dogged.
Oh, man, you, too. Stop.
Yeah, me, too.
Hangin' out with baby sis.
We're not hangin' out.
She's escortin' me back to Sal's.
I'm just goin' to get a slice.
You can't. Not today.
I'm organizing a boycott
of Sal's Famous.
What did he do?
You know them pictures
he got on the wall of fame?
So?
Notice somethin' about them?
No, Buggin' Out,
I haven't.
You're wasting my time.
Leave that shit alone.
You really should.
I'm gone.
I'll see you there.
Buggin' Out, how you been?
Every single one of them pictures
is somebody Italian.
And...
We want black people.
Did you ask Sal?
Yeah, I asked him.
We want nobody in there,
nobody spending
good money in Sal's,
until we get black pictures
on the wall.
What good will that do?
If you tried hard,
you could direct
your energies more usefully.
You got to be down.
You ain't?
I'm down, but I'm down for something
positive in the community.
Are you down for that?
Jade...
Jade, I still
love you anyway.
Yeah, I still love you,
too, Buggin' Out.
Later.
Man.
You're pushing it, Mookie.
You're really pushing it.
I don't pay good money
to have you jerk me around.
Keep it up,
you'll be in the street
with your other homeboys.
About time, Pop.
Jade.
How you doin', Jade?
Where you been?
Just working hard.
Keeping busy.
How's business?
Business is great.
We were wondering
when you'd stop by.
How's Mookie doing?
He's, uh... Mookie is...
He's great.
A good kid.
Hey, Pop.
Stop lying.
He's kidding.
I know.
What'll it be?
Regular slice.
No, I'm going to make you
something special,
if you don't mind.
No, that'll be great.
OK. What do you
want to drink?
Cream soda.
Used to be root beer.
Tell me if I'm wrong.
I want a change of pace.
Vito, clean the table for Jade.
All right, Pop.
Come here, Jade.
Sit here.
20 "D" Energizers.
20 "C" Energizers?
"D." Not "C." "D."
"C" Energizers?
"D," motherfucker. "D!"
Learn to speak English first,
all right? "D."
How many you say?
20, motherfucker. 20.
Motherfuck you!
Motherfuck...
Motherfucker, you,
you all right, man.
Just give me
the motherfuckin' batteries.
20 "D" fuckin' batteries.
Hey, yo. Yo, wait.
What's the date on them?
The date!
The fuckin' date!
What?
Can you fuckin' speak English?
The date!
The date?
Marcha!
Marcha?
What you talkin' about... Marcha?
1991.
Oh, March.
That's March, motherfucker,
March.
Yo, man,
you sure that's 20?
20.
No. No. Take them out.
Count them again.
Count the shits again, man.
Motherfucker.
May I help you?
I want some flowers.
The whole thing?
The whole thing.
It's very expensive.
I know. I'll pay.
I thought you might like these.
I guess not.
There is nothing
like the smell of fresh flowers.
Don't you agree,
Mother Sister?
Summertime...
All you can smell is the garbage.
Smell overpowers everything,
especially the soft,
sweet smell of flowers.
You don't mind,
I'll sit right here,
catch a breeze or two,
then be on my way.
Thank the Lord,
the sun is going down.
It is hot as blazes.
Yes, Jesus.
Well, guess I'll be on my way.
Oh!
Oh, goddamn, man!
Cut that shit down!
A person go deaf
or something.
Fucker!
Man, I don't know
how he does it.
Oh, man!
Goddamn.
That is shit.
ML, come here.
What?
Come hold this fucker, baby.
Hold what, sucker?
You know what I'm talkin' about.
That's OK.
At least my moms
didn't name me...
Sweet Dick Willie.
Uh-huh.
I told you about that mama shit.
Nobody talkin' about your moms.
I ain't say nobody.
I said you!
Just squash that shit.
I didn't mean it like that.
You did, too.
I just wanted to know
who named you
Sweet Dick Willie.
Man, it's just a name.
Goddamn. Shit.
How'd you get the name ML?
ML stands for ML.
Now that's some stupid shit.
Hear me?
That's some stupid shit.
'Cause everybody know
why they call me
Sweet Dick Willie.
You Negroes kill me.
Always holding on to...
always talking
about your dicks.
It's too hot to fuck.
Man, you out
your fuckin' mind?
It ain't never too hot
or never too cold for fuckin'.
I had my best piece of woman
on a humid day.
Over in the projects.
Close to your woman.
Get out!
Oh, Lord, have mercy.
I better not see her
naked on payday.
Piraguero!
Everybody out!
The icee, icee man is here.
Hey hey!
Looking good.
Here we are.
Look at these beautiful people.
The icee man is here.
I want coconut.
Give me lemon.
Tell me what you need.
There you go, my love.
That's your color.
That's your flavor.
I want more syrup on mine.
He's always drinking, man.
Hey, hey!
Where's everybody going?
Ice cream!
Doctor!
Doctor, don't you
know no better
than to run out
in front of a car?
You trying to kill yourself?
Come on.
Let's get up.
You gonna be all right.
You gonna be all right, my boy.
You gonna be just fine.
Eddie, what's wrong?
Mayor knocked me down.
You ought to be
shamed of yourself.
Ha ha. That boy's
just scared to death.
What happened...
I was walking,
minding my business.
I seen your son
about to get hit by the car,
so I dashed out.
I knocked him down
to keep us both
from getting hit.
I saved two lives today...
his and mine.
Eddie, is that the truth?
Eddie, you hear me
talking to you.
I'm talking to you, boy.
He gonna be fine, miss.
Mommy, Mommy!
I'm sorry!
Get upstairs now!
Your father gonna
wear out your behind.
Miss, you didn't have
to hit your boy like that.
He's already scared to death.
I appreciate you
helping my Eddie,
but I'll have nobody question
how I raise him.
You're right, miss.
You're right.
I don't want to sound like a jerk,
but can I say something, Jade?
Yeah, Sal.
You got the biggest eyes
I've ever seen.
They jump out of your head.
I feel embarrassed
even saying that.
Thanks, Sal.
Don't even mention it.
It was delicious.
I got to talk to you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Jade, don't forget
to come back soon, OK?
Hey, Mookie.
Take it easy.
You're going to bust her arm.
I don't want you
in Sal's no more.
Mookie, what?
Stop tripping.
Read my lips.
Don't see Sal.
What are you worked up about?
The way Sal looks at you.
- He's being nice.
- Nice?
- He's completely innocent.
- Innocent?
You heard me.
Sal just wants
to hide the salami.
You're really crude, Mookie.
Do not come in Sal's anymore.
You are not welcome.
You got a lot of nerve.
I'll tell you one last time.
Stop playing
big brother to me.
I'm a grown woman!
You can't pay your rent,
and you're lecturing me?
That makes no sense.
Oh, it doesn't, huh?
You got $250 a week.
I'm getting paid.
Peanuts.
In a while,
I'll be making a move.
Yeah, when?
Don't worry.
When, Mookie?
Don't worry about it.
Don't come here no more.
We're not talking about that.
I'm tired of supporting
a grown woman, OK?
a grown man, OK?
When are you going
to pack up and go?
Don't come in Sal's no more.
And no more pizza, either.
I don't care if you fire me
this exact fucking moment.
If you're saying
what I'm thinking
you're saying,
you better not say it.
You hear this?
Do me a favor.
Leave Jade alone.
You know, Mookie,
not for nothin',
but if you were
just a little taller,
I'd kick your ass
for what you're thinking.
As a matter of fact,
I should kick your ass
on principle alone.
Here.
You got a delivery.
This the right address?
What is this...
Yeah. It's the right address.
That's the right address.
I wrote it myself.
Sometimes you make mistakes,
and I deliver fucking pizzas
to the wrong fucking address.
I don't make mistakes.
You don't make mistakes?
Hurry back, OK?
Don't get lost.
We're still open.
Make a pizza, huh?
Mr. Mayor.
I saw what you did.
That was foolish but brave.
That child owes you his life.
Wasn't trying to be a hero.
I just seen what was happening,
and I reacted... didn't even think.
Probably wouldn't have done it
if I had thought.
Da Mayor's getting old.
Ain't run like that in years.
Went from first to home
on a bunt single.
Scored the winning run.
Two outs.
Bottom of the ninth.
August 1, 1939.
Snow Hill, Alabama.
Mud Cat Bones
was the pitcher.
He hated my guts.
He come down off that mound,
and I took off
like white lightning
up a black snake's ass.
Maybe I, uh...
Maybe I ought to be
a hero more often.
Maybe you shouldn't.
Don't get happy.
This changes nothing
between you and me.
You did a good thing.
Mother Sister just thanks you.
I want to thank you.
You're welcome.
Delivery from
Sal's Famous Pizzeria.
Is it hot?
I've never delivered a cold pizza.
Come here.
You think you're slick, Tina.
How else could
I get you up here?
I haven't seen you all week.
I'm working.
Making money.
You forgot the ice cream again.
I forgot.
Your memory's getting ridiculous.
I got things on my mind.
I really wanted some ice cream.
I'll run out and get some.
No, no. That's out.
You won't come back.
I can't be staying long.
How long?
Long enough to do the nasty.
Come on, Mookie.
That's out.
First of all, it's too hot.
If you think
I'll let you get some,
put your clothes on and leave,
and I won't see you again,
you're bugging.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, right.
So no nasty, huh?
No.
Something else.
What?
Trust me.
Last time I trusted you,
we got a son.
Remember him?
His name's Hector.
You saying I'm a bad father?
On the strength.
Let me talk to you.
What? What?
Over here.
Tina, take your clothes off.
I already told you
it's too fucking hot
to make love.
It's too fucking hot.
Why are you always cursing?
I don't fucking curse that much.
What the hell you mean?
All you do is curse.
Anyway, no rawness
is jumping off tonight.
All right?
That's it.
No rawness?
No. No rawness.
Why's it always like that
when you come over?
It's not always like that.
It's always...
What are you doing?
I'm not cursing.
Mookie. Come on.
I mean it.
I'm not playing.
Don't be so anxious.
That's right.
Take it off.
You're sweating.
Of course I'm sweating.
It's only 100 degrees in here.
Look, freeze.
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
What do you mean
you'll be right back?
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Why you got me
standing on the bed?
Where you going?
How's my son, Hector?
Honey, do you hear that?
He wants to know
how you are doing?
And he has the straight face
of asking about it.
Sinvergüenza.
Good for nothing.
Callejero.
Que se la pasa por la calle... -
English! English!
I want my son speaking English.
Get out of my kitchen.
Bad enough his name's Hector.
I don't want to hear anything.
Out, I said.
Yes, children.
This is the cool-out corner.
We're slowing it down
for all the lovers in the house.
I'll be giving you
all the help you need.
Musically, that is.
This shit is cold.
Supposed to be cold.
It's an ice cube.
Later for your shit.
Mira.
What?
You don't got a forehead.
You got a eight-head.
Mookie, you're full of shit.
You got one of them
Sade foreheads.
Fuck you.
Goddamn.
Big-ass forehead.
I need an iceberg...
rather than this ice cube.
Thank God for lips.
Thank God for the neck.
Thank God for kneecaps.
Thank God for elbows.
Thank God for thighs.
Thank God
for the right nipple.
for the left nipple.
Feels good.
Ah. You likes.
You likes.
Amen.
I got to be going.
You better come back.
I'll be back tonight.
You better,
'cause I'll kick your ass.
Oops. I got to be back then.
All right.
Get out of here.
I got to go.
Bye.
I'm not leaving yet.
Get out of here.
All right. Later.
Later.
Just out of curiosity,
how long you
sticking around here?
You mean tonight?
I mean the neighborhood.
I figure about 50 years.
'Cause I'm going into real estate.
I'll put up a high-rise
in the neighborhood.
Yeah. Lot of people
want to move here.
Why not?
You want a condominium?
A couple of straws, Mr. Trump.
Trump's Pizza.
I heard of that.
That's Trump's Plaza.
Get out of here.
Take care, Salvatore.
Pino, take the soft drinks
from the back
and load up here.
OK, Pop.
You want me to deliver faster,
I need a rocket... something.
I can't be running.
The cheese lands on one side.
Mookie, I didn't say nothing.
You must have a guilty conscience.
I'm not guilty of anything.
You're guilty of something.
Otherwise you wouldn't be saying that.
Come on, Sal.
Where we going?
Oh, shit.
Vito, give me a hand.
Come on.
What the fuck's the matter?
Vito, I want you to listen to me.
I'm your brother.
I smack you around
once in a while,
but I'm still... your brother.
So what, Pino?
So fucking what?
I love you, man.
I'm listening.
I want you to listen.
Jesus Christ, Pino.
I said I'm listening.
Vito, black... white. No.
No, no, no. No.
What the hell
you talking about?
Are you listening to me?
Stop busting my balls.
I said I'm listening.
Mookie's not to be trusted.
I trust him, Pino.
They can't be trusted.
First time you turn your back...
Boom. Aah!
The spear in the back.
How do you know this?
How do you know, man?
I know. I read.
I never seen you read nothing
in your fucking life.
Read your history.
It's historical.
He, them...
They're not to be trusted.
What do you want me to do?
Be on fucking guard.
Mookie has Pop conned,
so we got to look out for him.
You don't know
what you're saying.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Vito! Pino! Let's go!
We'll be right there, Pop.
One minute.
You better listen to what I say.
I'll rip you.
I'll fuck you up.
You know something, Pino?
You don't know everything
you think you know.
You think you know,
but you don't know.
Mookie, he listens to me.
You don't, man.
You fucking don't.
You'll fucking stab me
in the back, man.
Radio!
Buggin', what's up?
How you been, man?
Living large, bro.
Yo, that the only tape you gots?
You don't like
Public Enemy, man?
The shit's dope.
I'm down, but you don't be
playing nothing else.
I don't like nothing else.
Yo, check this.
You know Sal?
Yeah, I know
that motherfucker.
I've been trying
to organize a boycott
of Sal's Famous.
I almost had to bust him
in the head today.
Gonna tell me...
Tell me, Radio Raheem...
to turn down my box
and shit, man,
and didn't even say "please."
Who the fuck he think
he is, Don Corleone?
He make much money
off us black people,
and all he got on the wall
is Italians...
Sylvester Stallone,
okey-doke-lookin' motherfuckers.
On the strength.
We shouldn't buy one slice,
spend one penny in there
till he put folks of color
on that wall.
That's what I'm saying!
You got my back?
Your back is got.
My bro.
Yo, Smiley.
Come here, man.
What you listening to?
M- M-M-Malcolm.
M- M-M-Malcolm, huh?
Cut off that rap music!
I'm in here trying to get me
some motherfucking...
I'll fuck you up quick!
Two times!
Th-Th-Th-Three t-times!
Th...
Sal, start counting
my money tonight
'cause I gots to get paid.
Come on, Vito.
Come on.
This is terrific.
I mean we had
a great, great day.
You know something?
There's nothing like a family
in business working together.
I'm going to rename the place.
I'm going to call it
Sal and Sons'
Famous Pizzeria.
Why not?
You guys are going to
take it over someday, right?
And, Mookie...
Mookie, I want to tell you
that there's always
going to be a place for you
right here
at Sal's Famous Pizzeria
because you've always
been like a son to me.
Sal! Can we get some pizza?
We're closed!
Shut up!
You shut up!
Shut the fuck up, man!
All right, let them in.
They love my pizza.
Four slices, and I'm gone.
Sal, we're trying to go home!
Shut up!
You're a delivery boy, bitch!
Man, you don't know shit!
Shut the fuck up!
Sit your black ass down!
Shut up! Fuck you!
Yo, Sal.
Four slices, man, regular.
To go, all right?
Why you gotta curse?
Looking good.
Looking real good, man.
Come on.
Move it, man!
I told you about that noise!
What about them pictures?
What the fuck, are you deaf?
No! Are you?
Fuck you!
We want some black people
on that motherfucking
wall of fame now!
We're trying
to go fucking home!
We've been here all day!
Turn that jungle music off!
This ain't Africa!
Why it got to be
about jungle music?
Why it got to be about Africa?
It's about them fucking pictures!
It's about turning that shit off
and getting out of my place!
Radio Raheem!
Fuck you!
And fuck you, too!
Kick ass, Sal!
Get in there, Pino!
This is music!
My music!
Fuck your music!
Well, turn it off, then!
Get the fuck out of here!
We're closed!
Fuck you!
We're closing you
guinea bastards for good!
For good, motherfucker!
Until you get some black people
on that motherfucking
wall of fame!
You're gonna fucking close me?
You're goddamn right!
You black cocksucker!
I'll fucking tear
your fucking nigger ass!
Oh, we're niggers now?
We niggers now.
Fuck them up!
You fucking white trash!
I'll fuck you up!
Sal, put the fucking bat down!
Come on,
you fucking guinea trash!
Open the motherfucking counter!
You black cocksucker!
You nigger motherfucker!
I just killed your fucking radio.
My music!
You motherfucking...
Aah!
Get off him!
Get the fuck off him!
Get off!
You fucked up my eye!
Ahmad, stop!
Please, stop it!
Stop it!
You fucked with my box, man!
Get the fuck up!
I'll kick your ass some more!
Come on!
Somebody got it at Sal's, brother!
Fight!
Mookie!
Hey!
Break it up!
Hey! Hey!
You're gonna kill him!
- Stop it!
- Break it up!
Stop it!
Stop! Break it up!
You're gonna kill him!
Let me at 'em.
Let me at 'em!
Get...
Get the fuck out
of the way, man!
Move it!
Get off!
Let me through!
Get the big guy!
Get off me!
I'll kill you, you motherfucker!
Just take him off me!
Get away!
What are you doing? Sal!
Get the fuck off me!
Get off of me!
You're taking me to jail, huh?
You're not taking Vito
or Pino or Sal out!
Get the fuck off me!
Aah!
Get his other arm!
Take him down!
Just take him down, man!
Let him go, goddamn it!
You're killing him!
Give it up, asshole!
Aah! Aah!
Just take him down!
Come on!
Aah!
Let him go!
Stop it, goddamn it!
Stop it!
Aah!
Get his arm!
Gary, that's enough!
Shut up.
Gary, that's enough, man!
Gary, that's enough!
Shut the fuck up!
Radio Raheem!
No!
Radio!
Radio Raheem!
Get up!
You ain't dead!
Get up, asshole!
Quit faking it!
Get the fuck up!
Let's get him out of here.
Goddamn it!
I'm a black man!
You can't kill us all!
You can't fucking
kill us all, goddamn it!
Motherfucker!
Let's get him out of here!
Come on!
Get him to the car.
Let's go.
Back off, assholes!
You pig-fucking murderers!
You can't kill us all, man!
You can't fucking kill us all!
Back off!
Back off! Back off!
Everybody, back off!
Get back!
Fucking bastards!
Shut up, man.
Fuck off, you fucking...
Damn it!
I told you to shut up!
Back off!
Radio!
Mookie, they killed him.
They killed Radio Raheem!
It's murder.
They did it again,
just like Michael Stewart.
Murder!
Eleanor Bumpers! Murder!
Damn, man!
It ain't safe
in our own fucking neighborhood!
Never was.
Never will be.
We ain't gonna stand
for this shit no more, Sal.
Ain't gonna stand for
no fucking police, punk!
It's as plain as day.
They didn't have
to kill the boy.
You do what you gotta do.
Fuck that, man!
Listen, listen, listen.
Good people, please.
Let's all go home.
Somebody's gonna get hurt.
Yeah. You, boy!
If we don't stop this now,
we gonna do something
we're gonna regret
for the rest of our lives.
Sal had nothing to do
with what the cops did.
One of the police was black!
Leave him alone.
We'll get you
and them three stooges, Sal.
Go on, Mr. Sal.
You see how they had him
in a choke hold?
I knew that choke hold
would kill him!
You might have saved him!
A fucking radio!
He died because of a fucking radio!
He wanted pictures
on the wall, and he died!
What you got to say, Sal?
Your son called the cops!
Get the fuck out of here, man!
Somebody's getting hurt!
Fuck that, man!
Hate!
Ohh!
Whoo!
What are they doing?
Sal, come on.
Come on, quick.
Get them out of there!
Get...
That's my place!
That's my fucking place!
Sal!
Fucking niggers.
Radio! Radio!
Burn it down!
Come on.
Let's clean house.
Shit. Come on.
I no white.
I no white!
It's your turn, sucker!
I'm black!
What?
I black!
Me black!
Where you black at?
I'm black!
You, me... same!
We same.
Same?
Me black!
Open your eyes, motherfucker!
ML, leave the Korean alone, man.
He's all right.
Yeah? He's all right.
He's black.
Shit.
Oh, fuck you, man!
Howard Beach!
People, please disperse!
Please disperse!
Howard Beach!
We're giving you
one more warning
to please go home!
This is our home!
OK, you've had your warning!
Hose that black sucker down!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Get off of me!
Yo!
Well, come on! Come on!
Come on, asshole.
Come on!
Come on. Move it.
Motherfucker, come on!
What you think this is, Birmingham?
Fucking Alabama.
Yo, where's Bull Connor?
Son of a bitch!
Oh, no!
No!
My people, my people...
What can I say?
Say what I can?
I saw it, but I didn't believe it.
I didn't believe it, what I saw.
Are we going to live together?
Together are we going to live?
This is your
Mister Señor Love Daddy
talking to you
from We-Love radio,
108 FM on your dial,
and that's the triple truth, Ruth.
Today's weather?
Hot!
Wake up!
Fuck!
My money. Shit!
Where are you going?
To get my money.
Don't try that shit, OK?
You're going to run out,
and I won't see your ass
for another week.
It's not like that.
You don't give
a fucking shit about me,
and you don't
give a shit about your son.
I care about you and my son.
Why don't you be a man?
I am a man.
Then act like a man.
Why don't you be
a fucking man, Mookie?
I'm so tired of your shit.
Why do we have to
go over this again?
Because you don't
fucking listen, Mookie!
If you listen to me,
I wouldn't have to repeat myself
like a fucking radio!
What kind of mother you are
using fucking language like that?
What kind of mother am I?
Your ass isn't even here!
Get another vocabulary, right?
Get a fucking life.
Yeah. Look...
Look what?
I'll be back.
Don't leave, Mookie.
Don't leave.
I'm tired of this shit.
You walk out that door, that's it.
All right?
I have to get my money from Sal.
I'll be back.
Your shit's to the curb,
and I'm tired of it.
You need to step off
with your stupid-ass self.
You need to get
a fucking life, Mookie,
because the one you got
is not working!
I ain't going to deal
with this shit no more!
Shit.
Fucking ass, stupid ass,
fucking pendejo.
Shit. Fuck.
Fucking shit.
Good morning.
Is it a good morning?
Yes, indeed.
You almost got yourself
killed last night.
I've done that before.
Where did you sleep?
I didn't.
I hope the block is still standing.
We're still standing.
What do you want?
I want my money.
I want to get paid.
You don't work here no more.
I want my money.
Your money couldn't begin to pay
for the window you broke.
Motherfuck a window.
Radio Raheem is dead.
I know he's dead.
I was here, remember?
He's dead because of his buddy.
That cocksucker started this shit.
He's responsible
for that kid's death.
He wanted to close me,
and you stood there like a fuck
and watched them
burn me down!
I also watched the cops
murder Radio Raheem.
You'll get it all
from the insurance anyway, Sal.
What the fuck's
wrong with you?
This ain't about money.
I could give a fuck
about money.
You see this place?
I built this fucking place!
With my bare fucking hands!
Every light socket,
every piece of tile.
Me! With these fucking hands!
You know what that means?
It means pay me
my motherfucking money.
That's what it means, Sal.
OK, Mookie.
How much do I owe you?
My salary is 250.
250 a week.
1...
that's 2...
that's 3...
that's 4...
and that's 5.
You got $500.
You're a rich fucking man.
Are you happy?
You happy?
He's got 500 fucking dollars!
He's a big man!
He's a rich fucking man!
He's never going to have
any more trouble!
Not Mookie!
He's fucking rich!
Who the fuck you yelling at?
You're wealthy, Mookie.
You're a real fucking Rockefeller.
You got your fucking pay.
Now leave me alone.
Sal, my salary's 250 a week,
all right?
I owe you 50 bucks.
Keep it.
You keep it.
No, you keep it.
I don't believe this shit.
Believe it.
Are you sick?
I'm hot as a motherfucker.
I'm all right, though.
Well, they say it's even going
to get hotter today.
What are you going
to do with yourself?
Make that money.
Get paid.
Sal, I got to go see my son
if it's all right with you.
Hey, Mook.
It's the Mook man.
I see you walking.
Go home to your kid.
Now the news and weather.
Our mayor has commissioned
a blue-ribbon panel...
"to get to the bottom
of last night's disturbance.
The City of New York
will not let property
be destroyed by anyone."
His Honor plans to visit
our block today.
He should hook up
with our own Da Mayor,
buy him a beer.
Your Love Daddy
says register to vote.
The election is coming up.
There's no end in sight
from this heat wave,
so today,
the cash money word is chill.
That's right. C-h-i-l-I.
When you hear "chill,"
call in at 555-LOVE,
and you'll win
cash money, honey.
This is Mister Señor Love Daddy
coming at you from
what's last on your dial
but first in your hearts,
and that's
the quintessential truth, Ruth.
The next record goes out
to Radio Raheem.
We love you, brother.