1
00:05:17,942 --> 00:05:20,485
Your move:
bishop to knight four.

2
00:05:20,695 --> 00:05:23,322
My move:
knight to rook three.

3
00:05:24,407 --> 00:05:27,326
Poor baby,
you're starting to lose it, aren't ya?

4
00:05:33,249 --> 00:05:35,792
Your move:
king to rook one.

5
00:05:36,294 --> 00:05:38,754
My move:
rook to knight six.

6
00:05:39,339 --> 00:05:41,631
Checkmate. Checkmate.

7
00:05:46,971 --> 00:05:48,764
You cheating bitch.

8
00:06:52,662 --> 00:06:56,331
- Childs, what's he doing?
- Circling the camp.

9
00:06:57,708 --> 00:06:59,251
Who is he?

10
00:06:59,335 --> 00:07:02,838
- Said "Norge" or something on the side.
- It's Norwegian.

11
00:09:07,713 --> 00:09:09,339
- George, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.

12
00:09:09,423 --> 00:09:10,423
- Are you?
- Yeah.

13
00:09:10,508 --> 00:09:12,008
What's going on there?

14
00:09:34,282 --> 00:09:35,574
Watch it.

15
00:10:00,516 --> 00:10:01,600
Easy.

16
00:10:01,684 --> 00:10:05,186
Easy, easy, easy. Yes.

17
00:10:17,742 --> 00:10:19,951
First goddamn week of winter.

18
00:10:29,879 --> 00:10:34,215
Oh, come on. Four stitches.
Barely grazed you.

19
00:10:35,551 --> 00:10:40,096
What were they doing flying that low,
shooting at a dog, at us?

20
00:10:40,890 --> 00:10:44,309
Stir-crazy. Cabin fever. Who knows?

21
00:10:45,102 --> 00:10:49,481
U.S. Number 31, calling McMurdo.
Come in. Over.

22
00:10:51,901 --> 00:10:56,237
U.S. Number 31, calling McMurdo.
Urgent. Come in. Over.

23
00:10:58,324 --> 00:10:59,532
Great.

24
00:10:59,909 --> 00:11:02,410
- Come on, come on.
- Nobody!

25
00:11:02,495 --> 00:11:04,329
Nobody. Get a hold of somebody.

26
00:11:04,413 --> 00:11:06,831
Get a hold of anybody.
We gotta report this mess.

27
00:11:06,916 --> 00:11:09,959
Look, I haven't been able to reach shit
in two weeks.

28
00:11:10,044 --> 00:11:13,296
I doubt if anybody's talked to anybody
on this entire continent,

29
00:11:13,381 --> 00:11:15,215
and you want me to reach somebody!

30
00:11:27,019 --> 00:11:28,937
Maybe we're at war with Norway.

31
00:11:33,609 --> 00:11:38,488
I was wondering when the El Capitan
was gonna get a chance to use his popgun.

32
00:11:42,535 --> 00:11:45,995
- How long have they been stationed there?
- It says here only eight weeks.

33
00:11:46,080 --> 00:11:47,997
Well, that's not long enough
for guys to go bonkers.

34
00:11:48,082 --> 00:11:49,207
Bullshit, bwana.

35
00:11:49,291 --> 00:11:51,710
Five minutes is enough
to put a man over down here.

36
00:11:51,794 --> 00:11:52,836
Damn straight.

37
00:11:52,920 --> 00:11:56,589
I mean, look at Palmer.
He been the way he is since the first day.

38
00:11:57,007 --> 00:11:58,591
How many in their party?

39
00:11:59,009 --> 00:12:01,302
They started with 10.
There'd be eight others left.

40
00:12:01,637 --> 00:12:05,223
How do we know? Guys as crazy as that
could have done a lot of damage

41
00:12:05,307 --> 00:12:06,725
to their own before they got to us.

42
00:12:06,809 --> 00:12:09,602
- Nothing we can do about that.
- Yes, there is. I wanna go up.

43
00:12:09,687 --> 00:12:11,396
- In this weather?
- Bennings?

44
00:12:11,480 --> 00:12:13,648
Winds are gonna let up a tad
next couple of hours.

45
00:12:13,733 --> 00:12:15,191
A tad?

46
00:12:15,443 --> 00:12:19,154
Can't condone it much myself,
but it is a short haul.

47
00:12:19,780 --> 00:12:21,948
An hour there, an hour back.

48
00:12:23,325 --> 00:12:26,244
Shit, Doc, I'll give you the lift. No problem.

49
00:12:26,328 --> 00:12:30,206
- Forget it, Palmer.
- Hey, thanks for thinking about it though.

50
00:12:34,086 --> 00:12:36,755
Loaded with kerosene. I count 15 cans.

51
00:12:37,673 --> 00:12:39,966
MacReady! Mac, get your gear on!

52
00:12:50,895 --> 00:12:53,104
- Mac, it may not clear up for a week.
- Yeah.

53
00:12:53,189 --> 00:12:55,565
- We're the closest ones to them.
- It's all right by me, Doc.

54
00:12:55,649 --> 00:12:58,526
I'm just letting you know
we're taking a chance.

55
00:12:58,611 --> 00:12:59,986
Quit the griping, MacReady.

56
00:13:00,070 --> 00:13:02,447
Those clouds keep moving over the sun,
we're gonna get a whiteout.

57
00:13:02,531 --> 00:13:04,866
We get caught in that,
you can scratch one doctor and one pilot.

58
00:13:04,950 --> 00:13:07,702
This is real thin.
It'll clear as soon as you get up.

59
00:13:10,623 --> 00:13:14,042
It's up to you, Mac.
If you don't wanna fly, we don't fly.

60
00:13:15,544 --> 00:13:17,253
You really wanna save
those crazy Swedes, huh?

61
00:13:17,338 --> 00:13:18,379
Norwegians.

62
00:13:18,464 --> 00:13:20,465
- Which way, Doc?
- Southwest.

63
00:13:20,549 --> 00:13:22,967
You're gonna have to read the map.
'Cause I'm gonna be busy.

64
00:13:30,100 --> 00:13:31,935
Mac's really taking it up, huh?

65
00:13:34,230 --> 00:13:35,897
He knows what he's doing.

66
00:14:38,294 --> 00:14:40,211
Nauls, will you turn that crap down?

67
00:14:40,296 --> 00:14:43,131
I'm trying to get some sleep.
I was shot today.

68
00:14:44,466 --> 00:14:46,217
Read, bwana. Will do.

69
00:14:48,304 --> 00:14:50,930
Writing's on the wall

70
00:14:53,267 --> 00:14:55,852
Very superstitious

71
00:17:11,989 --> 00:17:13,489
Anybody there?

72
00:17:15,200 --> 00:17:16,284
Hey, Sweden!

73
00:17:16,368 --> 00:17:19,287
They're not Swedish, Mac.
They're Norwegian.

74
00:18:43,122 --> 00:18:44,205
Mac!

75
00:19:20,075 --> 00:19:22,827
My God. What the hell happened here?

76
00:19:25,038 --> 00:19:26,539
Come on, Doc.

77
00:20:05,495 --> 00:20:09,957
- Portable video unit. Anything?
- It's all in Norwegian.

78
00:20:16,131 --> 00:20:18,007
What are you doing, Doc?

79
00:20:18,091 --> 00:20:19,800
Could be important work.
I wanna take it back.

80
00:20:19,885 --> 00:20:22,386
Well, it's getting late. Let's hurry it up.

81
00:20:22,471 --> 00:20:24,555
I'll check out the last few rooms.

82
00:20:43,450 --> 00:20:45,368
Hey, Copper, come here!

83
00:21:28,704 --> 00:21:30,454
Maybe they found a fossil,

84
00:21:30,539 --> 00:21:33,374
the remains of some animal buried
in the ice, and they chopped it out.

85
00:21:33,458 --> 00:21:35,710
- But where is it?
- Look at this.

86
00:21:50,225 --> 00:21:51,726
What is that?

87
00:21:53,270 --> 00:21:55,771
Is that a man in there or something?

88
00:21:57,733 --> 00:22:00,735
Whatever it is, they burned it up in a hurry.

89
00:22:02,779 --> 00:22:04,905
Help me find a shovel, Doc.

90
00:23:00,962 --> 00:23:02,505
We found this.

91
00:23:03,423 --> 00:23:04,882
Jesus Christ.

92
00:23:30,325 --> 00:23:33,619
Blair, I'd like you to start an autopsy
right away.

93
00:24:34,848 --> 00:24:36,557
Did you reach anybody yet?

94
00:24:36,641 --> 00:24:39,977
Reach anybody?
We're a thousand miles from nowhere, man,

95
00:24:40,061 --> 00:24:42,730
and it's gonna get worse
before it gets better.

96
00:24:42,814 --> 00:24:45,566
Well, stick to it, Windows. Stick to it.

97
00:24:50,530 --> 00:24:53,866
Nothing wrong with this Norwegian,
physiologically anyway.

98
00:24:53,950 --> 00:24:56,243
No drugs, no alcohol. Nothing.

99
00:25:20,685 --> 00:25:23,562
Well, what we got here
is what appears to be, anyway,

100
00:25:23,647 --> 00:25:25,981
a normal set of internal organs.

101
00:25:28,068 --> 00:25:29,276
Heart,

102
00:25:30,362 --> 00:25:32,738
lungs, kidneys, liver.

103
00:25:33,990 --> 00:25:35,407
Intestines.

104
00:25:39,454 --> 00:25:41,163
Seem to be normal.

105
00:25:58,807 --> 00:26:01,767
One, door number two
and door number three.

106
00:26:01,851 --> 00:26:05,729
And I think that Dawn Screen here
has got the one to trade in the most.

107
00:26:05,814 --> 00:26:07,606
I went to you first.
You brought your friend Anna.

108
00:26:07,691 --> 00:26:10,025
You've been consulting Anna all through
the show anyhow.

109
00:26:10,110 --> 00:26:11,735
You may as well consult her one more time.

110
00:26:11,820 --> 00:26:13,821
I know how this one ends.

111
00:26:50,108 --> 00:26:53,402
Clark, will you put this mutt with the others
where he belongs?

112
00:26:56,197 --> 00:26:57,615
Yeah, okay.

113
00:27:18,595 --> 00:27:19,887
Go ahead.

114
00:27:23,350 --> 00:27:25,851
Go ahead. What are you waiting for?

115
00:30:17,398 --> 00:30:20,818
I don't know what the hell's in there,
but it's weird and pissed off, whatever it is.

116
00:30:20,902 --> 00:30:22,319
Bennings, go get Childs.

117
00:30:22,403 --> 00:30:24,613
What is this? What's going on?

118
00:30:24,906 --> 00:30:27,324
- Hey, Palmer, what is this?
- I don't know.

119
00:30:27,408 --> 00:30:30,661
- Childs, Mac wants the flamethrower!
- Mac wants the what?

120
00:30:30,745 --> 00:30:33,372
- That's what he said. Now, move!
- Damn it.

121
00:30:46,594 --> 00:30:48,637
- Stay back.
- Hey, Mac, what is it?

122
00:31:36,352 --> 00:31:39,563
- Don't! No!
- Get away!

123
00:31:39,689 --> 00:31:41,398
Get back! Get back!

124
00:32:06,591 --> 00:32:08,508
Get your ass over here!

125
00:32:10,136 --> 00:32:11,345
Burn it.

126
00:32:15,391 --> 00:32:17,476
Damn it, Childs. Torch it!

127
00:33:39,142 --> 00:33:40,559
Oh, my God.

128
00:33:47,692 --> 00:33:50,986
Oh!

129
00:33:56,617 --> 00:33:59,578
Look. Son of a bitch. Oh.

130
00:34:16,012 --> 00:34:18,221
You see, what we're talking about here
is an organism

131
00:34:18,306 --> 00:34:22,100
that imitates other life-forms,
and it imitates them perfectly.

132
00:34:22,185 --> 00:34:25,645
When this Thing attacked our dogs,
it tried to digest them,

133
00:34:25,772 --> 00:34:27,189
absorb them,

134
00:34:28,316 --> 00:34:31,860
and in the process,
shape its own cells to imitate them.

135
00:34:34,155 --> 00:34:37,949
This, for instance... that's not dog.

136
00:34:40,912 --> 00:34:44,164
It's imitation.
We got to it before it had time to finish.

137
00:34:46,375 --> 00:34:47,834
Finish what?

138
00:34:48,878 --> 00:34:51,046
Finish imitating these dogs.

139
00:34:58,179 --> 00:35:01,848
Easy, easy. Good.

140
00:35:04,727 --> 00:35:06,394
Easy, easy.

141
00:35:12,443 --> 00:35:13,902
- Clark.
- Yeah?

142
00:35:13,986 --> 00:35:17,572
Did you notice anything strange
about the dog, anything at all?

143
00:35:17,740 --> 00:35:19,199
Strange? No.

144
00:35:21,744 --> 00:35:23,954
What was the dog doing in the rec room?

145
00:35:24,539 --> 00:35:25,789
I don't know.

146
00:35:25,873 --> 00:35:28,250
He was just wandering around camp all day.

147
00:35:30,795 --> 00:35:34,881
Are you saying to me the dog wasn't put
in the kennel until last night?

148
00:35:35,049 --> 00:35:36,216
Right.

149
00:35:38,427 --> 00:35:40,387
How long were you alone with that dog?

150
00:35:40,888 --> 00:35:44,808
I don't know. An hour.
Hour and a half, maybe.

151
00:35:46,936 --> 00:35:49,938
What the hell you looking at me
like that for?

152
00:35:52,400 --> 00:35:54,151
- I don't know.
- What?

153
00:35:55,361 --> 00:35:57,404
I don't know. It's probably nothing.

154
00:36:00,658 --> 00:36:02,450
It's nothing at all.

155
00:36:13,254 --> 00:36:15,172
How much more of this crap is there?

156
00:36:15,256 --> 00:36:17,465
Oh, about nine hours, I'd say.

157
00:36:18,885 --> 00:36:22,053
- We can't learn anything from this.
- Guess not.

158
00:36:33,524 --> 00:36:35,442
Where'd they take these shots?

159
00:36:36,527 --> 00:36:38,320
Seems like they were spending
a lot of their time

160
00:36:38,404 --> 00:36:41,114
in a little place northeast of their camp
about five or six miles.

161
00:36:41,199 --> 00:36:42,616
What's that?

162
00:36:44,285 --> 00:36:46,661
It looks like something
buried under the ice.

163
00:36:53,336 --> 00:36:56,129
And look at that.
They're planting thermite charges.

164
00:36:57,131 --> 00:37:00,425
Whatever it was, it was bigger
than that block of ice you found.

165
00:37:10,228 --> 00:37:14,064
Here. This is it. The place where
they were spending most of their time.

166
00:37:14,148 --> 00:37:17,692
- Pretty nasty out, Mac. 35 knots.
- Screw it. I'm gonna go up anyway.

167
00:37:41,676 --> 00:37:43,301
Half a mile due east.

168
00:39:21,609 --> 00:39:24,486
Jesus, how long do you figure
this has been in the ice?

169
00:39:25,821 --> 00:39:29,282
Well, the backscatter effect's been
bringing things up

170
00:39:29,784 --> 00:39:32,410
from way down around here for a long time.

171
00:39:32,495 --> 00:39:37,123
I'd say... I'd say the ice it's buried in is
100,000 years old, at least.

172
00:39:40,378 --> 00:39:42,712
- And those Norwegians blew it up?
- Yeah.

173
00:40:12,493 --> 00:40:13,743
I don't know.

174
00:40:13,828 --> 00:40:17,205
Thousands of years ago, it crashes,
and this Thing...

175
00:40:18,332 --> 00:40:22,252
Gets thrown out or crawls out,
and it ends up freezing in the ice.

176
00:40:22,336 --> 00:40:25,046
I just cannot believe
any of this voodoo bullshit.

177
00:40:26,173 --> 00:40:28,842
Childs, it happens all the time, man.

178
00:40:29,468 --> 00:40:32,137
They're falling out of the skies like flies.

179
00:40:32,346 --> 00:40:34,597
Government knows all about it.
Right, Mac?

180
00:40:34,682 --> 00:40:37,100
Do you believe
any of this voodoo bullshit, Blair?

181
00:40:37,184 --> 00:40:41,521
Childs. Childs. Chariots Of The Gods, man.

182
00:40:42,481 --> 00:40:44,649
They practically own South America.

183
00:40:44,900 --> 00:40:47,485
I mean, they taught the Incas
everything they know.

184
00:40:54,869 --> 00:40:56,161
Come on, now, MacReady.

185
00:40:56,245 --> 00:40:59,664
The Norwegians get a hold of this,
and they dig it up out of the ice.

186
00:40:59,748 --> 00:41:02,208
Yes, Garry, they dig it up. They cart it back.

187
00:41:02,293 --> 00:41:05,628
It gets thawed out, wakes up,
not in the best of moods.

188
00:41:05,713 --> 00:41:08,298
- I don't know. I wasn't there.
- Which one of you disrespectful men

189
00:41:08,382 --> 00:41:11,885
been tossing his dirty drawers
in the kitchen trash can, huh?

190
00:41:12,303 --> 00:41:15,555
From now on
I want my kitchen clean, germfree.

191
00:41:15,848 --> 00:41:18,933
Now how's this motherfucker wake up
after thousands of years in the ice?

192
00:41:19,018 --> 00:41:21,644
- And how could it look like a dog?
- I don't know how.

193
00:41:22,396 --> 00:41:25,356
'Cause it's different than us, see?
'Cause it's from outer space.

194
00:41:25,441 --> 00:41:27,484
What do you want from me? Ask him.

195
00:41:32,531 --> 00:41:34,657
You buy any of this, Blair?

196
00:43:35,487 --> 00:43:39,240
Mac, removing those things
out of the lab into the storeroom.

197
00:43:39,491 --> 00:43:41,659
Can you come get your stuff?

198
00:43:42,369 --> 00:43:44,329
Be there in a minute, Doc.

199
00:44:01,597 --> 00:44:03,056
Through the door.

200
00:44:06,685 --> 00:44:08,603
Right over here. Right over...

201
00:44:11,982 --> 00:44:14,776
Sorry, Mac. You have to move your stuff...

202
00:44:15,235 --> 00:44:18,488
Doc says we gotta lock him up.
Stash him in here and lock him up.

203
00:44:19,156 --> 00:44:21,324
- I have to talk to you.
- I'm tired of talking, Fuchs.

204
00:44:21,408 --> 00:44:23,201
I just wanna get up to my shack
and get drunk.

205
00:44:23,285 --> 00:44:25,745
- Mac, it's important.
- What is it?

206
00:44:27,498 --> 00:44:29,666
- Outside.
- It's 40 below outside.

207
00:44:29,750 --> 00:44:31,918
In the Thiokol. Please, Mac.

208
00:44:47,476 --> 00:44:51,938
- We ought to just burn these things.
- Can't burn the find of the century.

209
00:44:52,731 --> 00:44:54,982
That's gonna win somebody the Nobel Prize.

210
00:45:08,330 --> 00:45:09,997
You got the keys?

211
00:45:10,082 --> 00:45:13,501
Get them from Garry.
I wanna get some stuff out of here.

212
00:45:47,703 --> 00:45:49,412
There's something wrong with Blair.

213
00:45:49,496 --> 00:45:52,749
He's locked himself in his room,
and he won't answer the door.

214
00:45:52,833 --> 00:45:54,834
So I took one of his notebooks from the lab.

215
00:45:54,918 --> 00:45:56,669
- Yeah?
- Listen.

216
00:45:58,547 --> 00:46:01,632
"It could have imitated
a million life-forms on a million planets.

217
00:46:01,717 --> 00:46:04,010
"Could change into any one of them
at any time.

218
00:46:04,094 --> 00:46:05,386
"Now it wants life-forms on Earth."

219
00:46:05,471 --> 00:46:07,472
It's getting cold in here,
and I haven't slept in days.

220
00:46:07,556 --> 00:46:08,806
Wait.

221
00:46:08,891 --> 00:46:12,852
"It needs to be alone and in close proximity
with a life-form to be absorbed.

222
00:46:12,936 --> 00:46:14,437
"The chameleon strikes in the dark."

223
00:46:14,521 --> 00:46:16,647
- So is Blair cracking up, or what?
- Damn it, MacReady.

224
00:46:16,732 --> 00:46:19,358
"There is still cellular activity
in these burned remains.

225
00:46:19,568 --> 00:46:21,527
"They're not dead yet."

226
00:46:32,623 --> 00:46:34,957
Let's go, Bennings. I gotta get some sleep.

227
00:46:54,603 --> 00:46:56,896
Holy shit.

228
00:47:01,819 --> 00:47:03,402
Go get the doc.

229
00:47:04,738 --> 00:47:07,198
I'll get Garry. We'll meet in Blair's room.

230
00:47:13,664 --> 00:47:15,206
It's Bennings!

231
00:47:25,384 --> 00:47:28,678
Bennings was right there.
Mac, I swear to God. It had a hold of him.

232
00:47:41,525 --> 00:47:44,151
Windows! Windows! Keep away from him!

233
00:47:47,781 --> 00:47:49,574
Get back! Stay back!

234
00:47:53,453 --> 00:47:55,162
It isn't Bennings.

235
00:48:28,572 --> 00:48:30,239
My God, what was happening to him?

236
00:48:30,324 --> 00:48:33,784
If it had more time it would have looked,
sounded and acted like Bennings.

237
00:48:33,869 --> 00:48:35,745
I don't know what you're saying.

238
00:48:35,829 --> 00:48:39,290
That was one of those Things out there
trying to imitate him, Garry.

239
00:48:43,670 --> 00:48:45,588
- Come on.
- MacReady, I know Bennings.

240
00:48:45,672 --> 00:48:48,633
I've known him for 10 years. He's my friend.

241
00:48:50,427 --> 00:48:52,637
We've gotta burn the rest of them.

242
00:49:26,755 --> 00:49:28,589
All right, step back.

243
00:49:53,615 --> 00:49:55,366
You sure that's all of them?

244
00:49:55,450 --> 00:49:59,328
We cleaned out the storehouse, the lab.
There is nothing left.

245
00:50:00,747 --> 00:50:02,289
Where's Blair?

246
00:50:43,999 --> 00:50:45,750
I can't find Blair.

247
00:50:46,918 --> 00:50:48,377
Where's everybody else?

248
00:50:48,462 --> 00:50:50,379
Windows is in the radio room
still trying to get through.

249
00:50:50,464 --> 00:50:52,214
Everyone else is in the rec room.

250
00:50:53,216 --> 00:50:55,301
Well, you go on. I'll be in in a minute.

251
00:51:18,950 --> 00:51:23,287
Blair?

252
00:52:22,389 --> 00:52:25,891
Don't! You son of a bitch.
You understand me?

253
00:52:25,976 --> 00:52:28,978
- He's got a gun. Get back.
- Anybody interferes, I'll kill them.

254
00:52:29,062 --> 00:52:31,188
- Jesus.
- Just leave it here. We're gonna talk.

255
00:52:31,273 --> 00:52:32,690
He smashed up some of the chopper
pretty good.

256
00:52:32,774 --> 00:52:34,483
Nobody talk to nobody!

257
00:52:34,568 --> 00:52:36,944
Childs, go see if he got to the tractor.

258
00:52:37,904 --> 00:52:41,073
Nobody gets in and out of here. Nobody.

259
00:52:46,621 --> 00:52:51,041
You guys think I'm crazy. Well, that's fine.

260
00:52:52,627 --> 00:52:55,171
Most of you don't know what's going on
around here.

261
00:52:55,255 --> 00:52:59,425
Well, I'm damn well sure some of you do.

262
00:53:00,552 --> 00:53:01,760
Christ.

263
00:53:05,015 --> 00:53:08,809
He got most of the chopper and the tractor,
and he's killed the rest of the dogs.

264
00:53:12,397 --> 00:53:14,607
Garry, wait a minute, wait a minute.

265
00:53:15,400 --> 00:53:19,486
Now, Childs, go around to
the map room door. Talk to him.

266
00:53:20,322 --> 00:53:21,447
Okay.

267
00:53:22,032 --> 00:53:24,450
Norris, get a table from the lab.

268
00:53:27,329 --> 00:53:30,456
Do you think that Thing
wanted to be an animal?

269
00:53:30,665 --> 00:53:33,876
No dogs make it a thousand miles
through the cold.

270
00:53:37,047 --> 00:53:39,173
Nah, you don't understand!

271
00:53:40,008 --> 00:53:42,593
That Thing wanted to be us.

272
00:53:43,678 --> 00:53:44,970
If the cell gets out

273
00:53:45,055 --> 00:53:47,932
it could imitate everything
on the face of the earth

274
00:53:48,016 --> 00:53:50,517
- and it's not gonna stop!
- Okay, Blair.

275
00:53:51,686 --> 00:53:54,188
Come on, man,
you don't wanna hurt anybody.

276
00:53:54,773 --> 00:53:56,065
I'll kill you.

277
00:54:22,467 --> 00:54:24,093
Good shot, MacReady.

278
00:54:24,177 --> 00:54:25,594
- Excuse me.
- Okay.

279
00:54:25,679 --> 00:54:27,805
- All right, bring him up.
- Yeah.

280
00:54:48,034 --> 00:54:49,535
Come on, Blair.

281
00:54:55,542 --> 00:54:57,126
What about your shack?

282
00:54:57,210 --> 00:55:00,546
I don't want him in my shack.
We'll lock him in the toolshed.

283
00:55:04,759 --> 00:55:08,345
- Why am I in here?
- For your own protection, Blair.

284
00:55:23,445 --> 00:55:25,070
How you doing, old boy?

285
00:55:29,117 --> 00:55:31,160
I don't know who to trust.

286
00:55:32,912 --> 00:55:35,080
I know what you mean, Blair.

287
00:55:36,666 --> 00:55:39,585
Trust's a tough thing to come by these days.

288
00:55:41,171 --> 00:55:44,089
Tell you what.
Why don't you just trust in the Lord?

289
00:55:46,968 --> 00:55:49,928
- Watch Clark.
- What?

290
00:55:51,431 --> 00:55:54,266
I said, watch Clark.

291
00:55:55,101 --> 00:55:57,603
And watch him close. Do you hear me?

292
00:56:16,039 --> 00:56:18,040
And now the radio's gone.

293
00:56:18,291 --> 00:56:21,210
- And so are the choppers.
- We're completely cut off.

294
00:56:21,294 --> 00:56:24,880
All we can do now is hole up
'til spring, wait for the rescue team.

295
00:56:24,964 --> 00:56:26,632
No, we don't wait.

296
00:56:27,217 --> 00:56:29,635
Somebody in this camp
ain't what he appears to be.

297
00:56:29,719 --> 00:56:33,180
Right now that may be one or two of us.
By spring, it could be all of us.

298
00:56:33,264 --> 00:56:35,474
So how do we know who's human?

299
00:56:36,518 --> 00:56:39,478
If I was an imitation, a perfect imitation,

300
00:56:39,979 --> 00:56:42,648
how would you know if it was really me?

301
00:56:48,613 --> 00:56:50,406
Is there some kind of test, Doc?

302
00:56:50,490 --> 00:56:54,660
Well, yeah, possibly.
I've been thinking about a blood serum test.

303
00:56:54,828 --> 00:56:56,245
What's that?

304
00:56:56,454 --> 00:57:01,333
We could take a sample of each person's
blood, mix it with uncontaminated blood.

305
00:57:01,709 --> 00:57:04,711
I suppose if there's a reaction,
we'd know who isn't human.

306
00:57:04,796 --> 00:57:08,424
- We've got whole blood in storage.
- Start working on it.

307
00:57:09,008 --> 00:57:10,801
Keep an eye on Clark.

308
00:57:11,261 --> 00:57:13,262
He was close to that dog.

309
00:57:14,013 --> 00:57:15,639
- Yeah.
- Yeah.

310
00:57:20,603 --> 00:57:25,023
Mac, we need Blair's help.
He's the only one who knows this organism.

311
00:57:25,108 --> 00:57:26,442
He's too far gone.

312
00:57:26,526 --> 00:57:29,778
But get the rest of his notebooks.
Start going through them.

313
00:57:42,125 --> 00:57:44,668
Garry! Hey, you guys, come here!

314
00:57:46,963 --> 00:57:49,965
- What?
- Somebody got to the blood.

315
00:57:50,049 --> 00:57:51,175
What?

316
00:57:51,759 --> 00:57:53,886
- Where's Clark?
- Right here.

317
00:57:54,387 --> 00:57:58,056
- Wait a minute. Was this broken into?
- The lock is undamaged.

318
00:57:58,391 --> 00:58:00,726
Somebody opened it, closed it,
then locked it.

319
00:58:00,810 --> 00:58:01,852
Great.

320
00:58:01,936 --> 00:58:03,854
Who's got access to it?

321
00:58:08,568 --> 00:58:10,569
I guess I'm the only one.

322
00:58:10,904 --> 00:58:12,779
And I got the only key.

323
00:58:16,618 --> 00:58:20,162
- Would that test have worked, Doc?
- I think so, yes.

324
00:58:20,246 --> 00:58:22,164
Somebody else
sure as hell thought so.

325
00:58:22,248 --> 00:58:25,250
Well, who else could've used that key?

326
00:58:25,710 --> 00:58:29,129
Nobody! I just give it to Copper
whenever he needs it.

327
00:58:29,589 --> 00:58:31,965
Could anybody have gotten it from you,
Doc?

328
00:58:32,050 --> 00:58:36,053
I don't see how. As soon as I'm finished,
I return it right away.

329
00:58:37,597 --> 00:58:38,764
Great.

330
00:58:40,308 --> 00:58:44,144
- When was the last time you used it?
- Day or so ago.

331
00:58:45,897 --> 00:58:48,524
I suppose somebody could have
lifted it off me...

332
00:58:48,608 --> 00:58:49,775
Oh, come on!

333
00:58:49,859 --> 00:58:52,194
That key ring of yours
is always hooked to your belt.

334
00:58:53,613 --> 00:58:55,447
Accusing everybody...

335
00:58:56,282 --> 00:58:57,783
Stop it! It ain't worth it!

336
00:58:57,867 --> 00:58:59,535
Copper's the only one
who's got any business with it.

337
00:58:59,619 --> 00:59:02,204
Wait a minute!
You've been in here on several occasions.

338
00:59:02,288 --> 00:59:03,705
Doc thought of the test.

339
00:59:03,790 --> 00:59:06,166
So what?
Is that supposed to clear him?

340
00:59:07,710 --> 00:59:09,461
Windows! Windows!

341
00:59:22,600 --> 00:59:24,101
Put that down!

342
00:59:24,811 --> 00:59:27,646
- No.
- I'll put this right through your head.

343
00:59:29,357 --> 00:59:31,191
You guys gonna listen to Garry?

344
00:59:31,276 --> 00:59:34,486
You gonna let him give the orders?
He could be one of those Things.

345
00:59:34,571 --> 00:59:35,821
Windows.

346
00:59:37,073 --> 00:59:39,950
Wait a minute. Just take it easy.
Put the gun down.

347
00:59:40,326 --> 00:59:42,703
Put it down.
You don't want to hurt anybody.

348
00:59:42,787 --> 00:59:43,787
Right.

349
00:59:44,080 --> 00:59:45,539
On the floor.

350
01:00:00,305 --> 01:00:01,972
It's on the floor.

351
01:00:08,730 --> 01:00:10,772
I don't know about Copper,

352
01:00:11,983 --> 01:00:15,360
but I give you my word,
I did not go near that blood.

353
01:00:22,952 --> 01:00:25,954
But I guess you'll all feel a little easier

354
01:00:27,999 --> 01:00:30,292
if somebody else was in charge.

355
01:00:31,711 --> 01:00:34,671
Norris, I can't see anybody objecting to you.

356
01:00:38,009 --> 01:00:40,719
I'm sorry, fellas, but I'm not up to it.

357
01:00:41,304 --> 01:00:43,722
- I'll take it.
- Like hell you will.

358
01:00:44,724 --> 01:00:48,352
It should be somebody
a little more even-tempered, Childs.

359
01:00:58,404 --> 01:00:59,738
All right.

360
01:01:22,929 --> 01:01:24,554
I know I'm human.

361
01:01:28,142 --> 01:01:31,645
And if you were all these Things,
then you'd just attack me right now.

362
01:01:31,729 --> 01:01:34,022
So some of you are still human.

363
01:01:34,982 --> 01:01:39,653
This Thing doesn't want to show itself.
It wants to hide inside an imitation.

364
01:01:40,988 --> 01:01:42,989
It'll fight if it has to.

365
01:01:43,074 --> 01:01:45,617
But it's vulnerable out in the open.

366
01:01:46,828 --> 01:01:48,620
If it takes us over,

367
01:01:50,289 --> 01:01:52,416
then it has no more enemies,

368
01:01:53,459 --> 01:01:55,335
nobody left to kill it.

369
01:01:56,462 --> 01:01:58,130
And then it's won.

370
01:02:01,718 --> 01:02:04,469
There's a storm hitting us in six hours.

371
01:02:04,846 --> 01:02:07,139
We're gonna find out who's who.

372
01:02:07,807 --> 01:02:12,060
All right, Doc, Garry and Clark,
move over there away from the others.

373
01:02:23,823 --> 01:02:26,408
Norris, you and Childs
shoot them up with morphine.

374
01:02:26,492 --> 01:02:28,201
Tie them down in the rec room
and watch them.

375
01:02:28,286 --> 01:02:29,870
Fuchs, you start working
on a new technique.

376
01:02:29,954 --> 01:02:32,497
- I need Doc's help.
- You don't wanna drug me.

377
01:02:32,999 --> 01:02:34,958
Mac, I'm not a prisoner!

378
01:02:56,689 --> 01:02:58,940
Let me do it.
You're gonna break the needle in my arm.

379
01:02:59,025 --> 01:03:01,568
No, Doc, he's doing a real fine job.

380
01:03:10,912 --> 01:03:13,747
I'm gonna hide this tape when I'm finished.

381
01:03:14,040 --> 01:03:18,001
If none of us make it,
at least there'll be some kind of record.

382
01:03:18,377 --> 01:03:21,379
Storm's been hitting us hard now
for 48 hours.

383
01:03:22,632 --> 01:03:24,633
We still have nothing to go on.

384
01:03:36,854 --> 01:03:40,690
One other thing,
I think it rips through your clothes

385
01:03:40,775 --> 01:03:42,692
when it takes you over.

386
01:03:43,444 --> 01:03:47,697
Windows found some shredded long johns,
but the name tag was missing.

387
01:03:48,741 --> 01:03:50,700
They could be anybody's.

388
01:03:52,119 --> 01:03:53,370
Nobody...

389
01:03:56,082 --> 01:03:58,124
Nobody trusts anybody now.

390
01:04:00,002 --> 01:04:02,003
And we're all very tired.

391
01:04:09,262 --> 01:04:11,304
Nobody trusts anybody now.

392
01:04:15,601 --> 01:04:17,853
There's nothing else I can do.

393
01:04:18,521 --> 01:04:19,855
Just wait.

394
01:04:23,609 --> 01:04:26,903
R.J. MacReady, helicopter pilot,
U.S. Outpost, number 31.

395
01:04:42,003 --> 01:04:44,254
You come up with anything yet?

396
01:04:44,630 --> 01:04:46,298
One or two ideas.

397
01:04:50,303 --> 01:04:52,512
But, MacReady, I've been thinking.

398
01:04:52,597 --> 01:04:56,558
If a small particle of this Thing
is enough to take over an entire organism,

399
01:04:56,642 --> 01:04:58,727
then everyone should prepare
their own meals.

400
01:04:58,811 --> 01:05:01,396
And I suggest we only eat out of cans.

401
01:05:02,648 --> 01:05:04,149
All right.

402
01:05:37,892 --> 01:05:39,267
Who's that?

403
01:06:16,722 --> 01:06:18,390
Anybody see Fuchs?

404
01:06:21,352 --> 01:06:23,395
Somebody blew out a fuse in the lab.

405
01:06:23,479 --> 01:06:26,898
Lights were out for an hour.
Anyone of us could've gotten to him.

406
01:06:26,983 --> 01:06:28,858
All right, we gotta find him.

407
01:06:28,943 --> 01:06:32,028
Nauls, why don't you come with me
and we'll look outside.

408
01:06:32,113 --> 01:06:34,656
Palmer, you and Windows check the inside.

409
01:06:34,740 --> 01:06:36,866
I ain't going with Windows.

410
01:06:37,910 --> 01:06:40,912
I ain't going with him. I'll go with Childs.

411
01:06:40,997 --> 01:06:43,498
- Hey, fuck you, Palmer!
- I ain't going with you!

412
01:06:43,582 --> 01:06:46,918
- Who says I want you going with me?
- Cut the bullshit!

413
01:06:49,755 --> 01:06:52,465
Windows, you come with us.
Norris, you stay here.

414
01:06:52,550 --> 01:06:55,844
Any of them move, you fry them.
You hear anything, cut loose on the sirens.

415
01:06:55,928 --> 01:06:59,014
We all meet back here
in 20 minutes regardless.

416
01:06:59,849 --> 01:07:03,601
And everybody watch whoever
you're with... real close.

417
01:07:26,375 --> 01:07:27,751
Hey, Blair.

418
01:07:30,129 --> 01:07:32,255
Blair, have you seen Fuchs?

419
01:07:35,801 --> 01:07:39,637
I don't wanna stay out here anymore.
I wanna come back inside.

420
01:07:43,184 --> 01:07:45,393
I hear funny things out here.

421
01:07:45,728 --> 01:07:48,563
- Have you come across Fuchs?
- It ain't Fuchs.

422
01:07:52,026 --> 01:07:53,568
It ain't Fuchs.

423
01:07:55,196 --> 01:07:58,073
I'm not gonna harm anybody.
There's nothing wrong with me.

424
01:07:58,157 --> 01:08:01,409
And if there was, I'm all better now.
I'd like to come back inside.

425
01:08:01,494 --> 01:08:03,495
Now you've got my promise.

426
01:08:06,499 --> 01:08:07,832
We'll see.

427
01:08:09,085 --> 01:08:11,669
Wait a minute, man.

428
01:08:12,671 --> 01:08:15,757
I wanna come back inside,
don't you understand?

429
01:08:16,217 --> 01:08:20,595
I'm all right.
I'm much better... and I won't harm anybody.

430
01:08:20,679 --> 01:08:23,348
You gotta let me come back inside.

431
01:08:29,939 --> 01:08:31,189
Hold it!

432
01:08:46,539 --> 01:08:47,956
Is it Fuchs?

433
01:08:55,464 --> 01:08:56,548
Yeah.

434
01:08:57,842 --> 01:08:59,717
Why would it burn him?

435
01:09:00,386 --> 01:09:03,096
Flare. Maybe he tried to burn it.

436
01:09:07,226 --> 01:09:10,603
Maybe he burned himself
before it could get to him.

437
01:09:17,236 --> 01:09:20,446
Great! Now what are we gonna do?

438
01:09:22,032 --> 01:09:24,742
You go inside.
Tell the others we found Fuchs.

439
01:09:24,827 --> 01:09:26,995
We'll be in as soon as we can.

440
01:09:27,079 --> 01:09:29,455
- Where are we going?
- Up to my shack.

441
01:09:29,540 --> 01:09:30,832
What the hell for?

442
01:09:30,916 --> 01:09:34,377
'Cause when I left yesterday,
I turned the lights off.

443
01:09:57,610 --> 01:09:59,485
How long have they been out there?

444
01:09:59,570 --> 01:10:01,404
Forty, 45 minutes.

445
01:10:02,281 --> 01:10:05,283
We better start closing off
the outside doors.

446
01:10:37,358 --> 01:10:39,943
Hey! All of you, come here!

447
01:10:55,834 --> 01:10:59,712
Open up! Open up this door! Open up!
Open up!

448
01:11:02,383 --> 01:11:04,008
Close that door.

449
01:11:06,679 --> 01:11:08,304
Where's MacReady?

450
01:11:09,014 --> 01:11:11,266
I cut him loose of the line up by his shack.

451
01:11:11,350 --> 01:11:13,059
- Cut him loose?
- Yeah.

452
01:11:13,143 --> 01:11:16,521
We were up checking around his place,
I found this.

453
01:11:18,190 --> 01:11:22,193
Look. It was stashed in his oil furnace.

454
01:11:22,444 --> 01:11:25,905
Wind must've dislodged it,
but I don't think he saw me find it.

455
01:11:25,990 --> 01:11:29,784
I made sure I got ahead of him
on the towline on the way back.

456
01:11:29,868 --> 01:11:31,411
I cut him loose.

457
01:11:31,537 --> 01:11:33,955
- MacReady?
- He's one of them.

458
01:11:34,039 --> 01:11:36,332
- When do you think it got to him?
- I don't know.

459
01:11:36,417 --> 01:11:38,876
It could've been anytime, anywhere.

460
01:11:38,961 --> 01:11:40,753
If it did get to him.

461
01:11:41,171 --> 01:11:42,755
Look, Childs, come on.

462
01:11:42,840 --> 01:11:44,757
- When the lights went out.
- That would've been perfect.

463
01:11:44,842 --> 01:11:47,969
Right. You said guys were missing.
Windows, where were you?

464
01:11:48,053 --> 01:11:49,929
I told you to shut your mouth!

465
01:11:51,223 --> 01:11:54,642
This is just what it wants!
To pit us against each other.

466
01:12:01,400 --> 01:12:03,276
- Let's open it.
- Hell no!

467
01:12:03,360 --> 01:12:05,028
You think he's changed
into one of those Things?

468
01:12:05,112 --> 01:12:06,154
He's had time.

469
01:12:06,238 --> 01:12:09,157
Nothing human could've made it back
here in this weather without a guide line.

470
01:12:09,241 --> 01:12:11,367
- Let's open it now.
- Why are you so anxious to let him in here?

471
01:12:11,452 --> 01:12:12,493
Because it's so close.

472
01:12:12,578 --> 01:12:15,913
- May be our best chance to blow it away.
- Let him freeze.

473
01:12:15,998 --> 01:12:18,916
Childs, what if we're wrong about him?

474
01:12:19,001 --> 01:12:20,501
Well, then, we're wrong!

475
01:12:22,087 --> 01:12:23,755
The supply window!

476
01:12:24,214 --> 01:12:28,092
All right, all right, we got no choice now!

477
01:12:30,971 --> 01:12:33,389
Damn it! He's got the keys!

478
01:12:33,474 --> 01:12:35,725
What's going on?
The towline snapped.

479
01:12:35,809 --> 01:12:39,270
Bullshit, Childs.
He's got to know damn well I cut it!

480
01:12:42,024 --> 01:12:43,858
You're a dead man, MacReady!

481
01:12:45,903 --> 01:12:48,112
Or a dead whatever the hell you are!

482
01:12:57,915 --> 01:13:00,917
Anyone messes with me
and the whole camp goes.

483
01:13:02,086 --> 01:13:04,087
Come on, Childs, burn me.

484
01:13:05,631 --> 01:13:08,549
Put those torches on the floor and back off.

485
01:13:16,600 --> 01:13:19,394
Back off. Way off.

486
01:13:29,196 --> 01:13:31,906
- You asshole.
- You'd have done the same thing.

487
01:13:31,990 --> 01:13:33,783
Don't argue with him.

488
01:13:35,327 --> 01:13:36,661
Where's the rest?

489
01:13:41,583 --> 01:13:43,084
Come on, man, I mean it!

490
01:13:43,168 --> 01:13:45,211
It's cool, MacReady, come on.

491
01:13:45,295 --> 01:13:47,422
Yeah. Yeah, man, just relax.

492
01:13:48,590 --> 01:13:51,384
Anybody touches me... and we go.

493
01:14:04,398 --> 01:14:07,483
- He's not breathing!
- Go untie the doc.

494
01:14:09,778 --> 01:14:12,405
Get him in here. And bring the others.

495
01:14:15,951 --> 01:14:18,369
From now on, nobody gets out of my sight.

496
01:14:27,963 --> 01:14:29,213
Let me at him.

497
01:14:35,262 --> 01:14:38,973
So, you sweethearts were about to have
a little lynching party, huh?

498
01:14:40,350 --> 01:14:44,228
I might just have to put an end to you
on general principles, Nauls.

499
01:14:44,313 --> 01:14:47,315
Did it ever occur to the jury that anybody
could've gotten some of my clothes

500
01:14:47,399 --> 01:14:50,318
- and stuck them up the furnace?
- We ain't buying that.

501
01:14:50,402 --> 01:14:54,489
Quit that bickering over there!
Windows, wheel that defibrillator over here.

502
01:14:55,282 --> 01:14:56,866
Give me those paddles!

503
01:14:57,409 --> 01:14:59,827
You're gonna have to
sleep sometime, MacReady.

504
01:14:59,912 --> 01:15:02,580
I'm a real light sleeper, Childs.

505
01:15:04,750 --> 01:15:07,251
If anyone tries to wake me...

506
01:15:11,256 --> 01:15:12,423
Clear!

507
01:15:20,265 --> 01:15:21,933
- Clear!
- Clear.

508
01:16:20,659 --> 01:16:24,495
- We're on fire, MacReady! We're on fire!
- Get back! Just wait!

509
01:16:32,713 --> 01:16:34,213
All right, go!

510
01:16:55,319 --> 01:16:57,528
Windows! Windows, get in here!

511
01:17:23,555 --> 01:17:26,223
You gotta be fucking kidding.

512
01:17:46,036 --> 01:17:48,537
- What do you got in mind, MacReady?
- A little test.

513
01:17:48,622 --> 01:17:52,792
And, Windows, you and Palmer,
tie everybody down real tight.

514
01:17:52,876 --> 01:17:54,502
- What for?
- For your health.

515
01:17:54,586 --> 01:17:57,254
Let's rush him!
He's not gonna blow us all up!

516
01:18:01,093 --> 01:18:03,719
No, no, wait a minute. Wait a minute.

517
01:18:04,137 --> 01:18:06,472
Let's do what Mac says.

518
01:18:07,766 --> 01:18:11,018
I mean,
he wasted Norris pretty quick, didn't he?

519
01:18:11,103 --> 01:18:12,687
That's close enough, Clark.

520
01:18:12,771 --> 01:18:14,271
He ain't tying me up.

521
01:18:14,898 --> 01:18:17,108
Then I'll have to kill you, Childs.

522
01:18:17,567 --> 01:18:19,026
Then kill me.

523
01:18:28,328 --> 01:18:29,662
I mean it.

524
01:18:36,878 --> 01:18:38,421
I guess you do.

525
01:18:50,684 --> 01:18:52,560
Geez. This is bullshit, Mac!

526
01:18:52,644 --> 01:18:55,271
- Finish it, Palmer.
- They're dead, Mac!

527
01:19:00,694 --> 01:19:02,236
- Windows?
- Yo?

528
01:19:03,989 --> 01:19:06,115
You tie up Palmer over here.

529
01:19:10,412 --> 01:19:13,539
We're gonna draw
a little bit of everybody's blood

530
01:19:16,126 --> 01:19:18,711
'cause we're gonna find out
who's the Thing.

531
01:19:20,046 --> 01:19:23,215
Watching Norris in there
gave me the idea that

532
01:19:24,217 --> 01:19:26,761
maybe every part of him was a whole.

533
01:19:28,346 --> 01:19:31,348
Every little piece was an individual animal

534
01:19:31,892 --> 01:19:34,977
with a built-in desire to protect its own life.

535
01:19:37,397 --> 01:19:39,523
You see, when a man bleeds,

536
01:19:41,693 --> 01:19:43,319
it's just tissue.

537
01:19:45,405 --> 01:19:49,325
The blood from one of you Things
won't obey when it's attacked.

538
01:19:49,826 --> 01:19:51,702
It'll try and survive.

539
01:19:53,580 --> 01:19:56,207
Crawl away from a hot needle the same.

540
01:20:18,230 --> 01:20:19,438
Now you.

541
01:20:43,255 --> 01:20:44,672
That's good.

542
01:20:45,298 --> 01:20:47,716
All right, move back, over there.

543
01:21:35,390 --> 01:21:37,057
I guess you're okay.

544
01:21:39,311 --> 01:21:42,271
All right. Put that on and watch them.

545
01:21:52,115 --> 01:21:54,742
Now I'll show you what I already know.

546
01:21:59,748 --> 01:22:01,540
It's a crock of shit.

547
01:22:02,375 --> 01:22:04,501
Let's try the doc and Clark.

548
01:22:22,604 --> 01:22:23,938
Now Clark.

549
01:22:33,365 --> 01:22:35,407
Then Clark was human, huh?

550
01:22:36,493 --> 01:22:39,078
Which makes you a murderer, don't it?

551
01:22:39,371 --> 01:22:40,746
Palmer now.

552
01:22:47,462 --> 01:22:50,547
This is pure nonsense.
It doesn't prove a thing.

553
01:22:51,007 --> 01:22:53,133
I thought you'd feel that way, Garry.

554
01:22:53,218 --> 01:22:55,636
You were the only one that could've
got to that blood.

555
01:22:55,720 --> 01:22:57,388
We'll do you last.

556
01:23:00,725 --> 01:23:03,769
Get him away from me! MacReady, burn it!

557
01:23:06,398 --> 01:23:07,773
What is it?

558
01:23:16,992 --> 01:23:18,242
Come on!

559
01:23:24,916 --> 01:23:26,792
Get me out of here!

560
01:23:32,924 --> 01:23:34,591
Windows, blast him!

561
01:23:37,512 --> 01:23:40,347
Get me out of here!
Get me out of here!

562
01:24:09,169 --> 01:24:10,419
Windows!

563
01:24:31,775 --> 01:24:33,484
Get me out of here!

564
01:24:54,380 --> 01:24:57,591
MacReady, get in here! Come on, hurry up!

565
01:24:57,675 --> 01:25:01,095
He's coming back! Burn it!
Burn it, for God's sake!

566
01:25:01,179 --> 01:25:03,639
Hurry up, MacReady! Burn it!

567
01:25:37,382 --> 01:25:38,799
Let's do it.

568
01:25:52,397 --> 01:25:55,399
Get me out of here! Cut me loose!

569
01:25:55,859 --> 01:25:59,778
Cut me the hell... Come on, get me
out of here! Come on, get me out of here!

570
01:25:59,863 --> 01:26:01,738
Cut me loose, damn it!

571
01:26:19,757 --> 01:26:22,718
I know you gentlemen
have been through a lot,

572
01:26:23,761 --> 01:26:25,888
but when you find the time,

573
01:26:26,764 --> 01:26:31,435
I'd rather not spend the rest
of this winter tied to this fucking couch!

574
01:26:53,833 --> 01:26:55,042
Childs.

575
01:26:55,501 --> 01:26:58,545
We're going out to give Blair the test.
If he tries to make it back here

576
01:26:58,630 --> 01:27:01,131
and we're not with him... burn him.

577
01:27:21,527 --> 01:27:23,570
Mac, the door's open!

578
01:27:38,336 --> 01:27:41,838
How'd he get out?
The door was bolted from the outside.

579
01:28:26,718 --> 01:28:27,884
Blair?

580
01:28:31,431 --> 01:28:35,767
Hey, Blair, you down there?
We got something for ya!

581
01:28:46,821 --> 01:28:49,614
Blair's been busy out here
all by himself.

582
01:28:59,667 --> 01:29:00,917
What is it?

583
01:29:01,586 --> 01:29:03,211
Something he's been making.

584
01:29:03,296 --> 01:29:05,297
It's a ship of some kind.

585
01:29:06,883 --> 01:29:08,759
He stole the parts from the helicopter.

586
01:29:08,843 --> 01:29:11,762
The smart S.O.B. put it together
piece by piece.

587
01:29:13,514 --> 01:29:15,557
Where was he trying to go?

588
01:29:16,726 --> 01:29:18,393
Anyplace but here.

589
01:29:58,309 --> 01:30:00,644
Hey, you guys, come here. Come here.

590
01:30:07,360 --> 01:30:11,196
I think I saw Childs outside
the main entrance of the camp.

591
01:30:11,322 --> 01:30:13,990
- What's he doing outside?
- I don't know.

592
01:30:25,169 --> 01:30:26,545
Got a flare?

593
01:30:29,382 --> 01:30:32,175
He got back inside and blew the generator.

594
01:30:34,345 --> 01:30:37,222
In six hours,
it'll be a hundred below in here.

595
01:30:37,306 --> 01:30:39,099
Well, that's suicide!

596
01:30:40,017 --> 01:30:43,728
Not for that Thing. It wants to freeze now.

597
01:30:44,939 --> 01:30:46,022
It's got no way out of here.

598
01:30:46,107 --> 01:30:49,568
It just wants to go to sleep in the cold
until the rescue team finds it.

599
01:30:51,279 --> 01:30:53,697
What can we do? What can we do?

600
01:30:55,324 --> 01:30:58,869
Whether we make it or not,
we can't let that Thing freeze again.

601
01:31:00,204 --> 01:31:03,540
Maybe we'll just warm things up
a little around here.

602
01:31:08,588 --> 01:31:11,089
We're not getting out of here alive.

603
01:31:13,134 --> 01:31:14,885
But neither is that Thing.

604
01:33:04,495 --> 01:33:06,162
Generator room.

605
01:34:13,939 --> 01:34:15,815
The generator's gone.

606
01:34:15,900 --> 01:34:17,734
Any way we can fix it?

607
01:34:20,029 --> 01:34:22,072
It's gone, MacReady.

608
01:34:30,498 --> 01:34:31,831
All right.

609
01:34:32,625 --> 01:34:36,169
We gotta bring this whole place
right down into the ice.

610
01:34:36,504 --> 01:34:39,339
Garry, plant yours in the old storage room.

611
01:34:39,924 --> 01:34:42,133
Nauls, down by the generator.

612
01:35:34,019 --> 01:35:35,270
God!

613
01:36:45,132 --> 01:36:47,133
How's it coming in there?

614
01:36:48,803 --> 01:36:50,470
I said, how's it...

615
01:38:35,868 --> 01:38:37,869
Yeah, fuck you, too!

616
01:40:03,247 --> 01:40:05,331
You the only one who made it?

617
01:40:06,166 --> 01:40:07,792
Not the only one.

618
01:40:10,337 --> 01:40:11,921
Did you kill it?

619
01:40:13,090 --> 01:40:14,966
Where were you, Childs?

620
01:40:16,468 --> 01:40:18,261
Thought I saw Blair.

621
01:40:19,596 --> 01:40:23,725
I went out after him
and got lost in the storm.

622
01:40:34,194 --> 01:40:37,280
Fire's got the temperature up
all over the camp.

623
01:40:39,533 --> 01:40:41,534
Won't last long, though.

624
01:40:42,327 --> 01:40:43,953
Neither will we.

625
01:40:46,123 --> 01:40:47,874
How will we make it?

626
01:40:50,085 --> 01:40:51,794
Maybe we shouldn't.

627
01:40:56,967 --> 01:40:58,551
If you're worried about me...

628
01:40:58,635 --> 01:41:01,471
If we've got any surprises for each other,

629
01:41:03,223 --> 01:41:06,851
I don't think we're in much shape
to do anything about it.

630
01:41:10,689 --> 01:41:14,776
Well... what do we do?

631
01:41:15,986 --> 01:41:17,779
Why don't we just

632
01:41:19,490 --> 01:41:21,657
wait here for a little while?

633
01:41:24,328 --> 01:41:25,953
See what happens.

