THE MANSION OF THE GHOST CAT
A Mitsugu Okura Production
Starring
Present Day
Toshio Hosokawa
Yuriko Ejima
Period Drama
Keinosuke Wada
Ryuzaburo Nakamura
Directed by
Nobuo Nakagawa
Hospital
Wing 3
It's an evil night... those footsteps...
No one but me has reason
to come to this lab...
...but footsteps draw near
from the direction I've come.
Who is it walking down
that dim hallway?
Who else knows it well enough
to walk it on a dark night?
Of course I don't believe
in ghosts.
But at times we can be seized
by a weird feeling...
...like the one I have now.
Six years ago, something strange
like that happened.
My wife had tuberculosis,
and needed a change of climate.
We moved to the small town
in Kyushu where she's from.
We left Tokyo behind
for a while.
Her elder brother had arranged
things for when we arrived.
Does it hurt, Yoriko?
I'm fine, Kenichi.
Shouldn't she have an operation?
This isn't the time.
An operation could spread
the bacilli further.
We'll wait and see for now.
I hate to see a man of your talent
dragged way down here, though.
I'm happy to work somewhere
with clean air and a slower pace.
What a scare!
That was close.
I'm sorry. A black cat
ran right out in front of me.
Did you hit it?
No. It's fine.
Good!
It's in pretty bad shape.
It's well over a century old.
The shutters haven't been opened
for years.
Around here they call it
'the haunted mansion'.
A haunted house
in this day and age!
Yoriko...
...shouldn't you wait in the car?
I'd like to see the place,
if I'm going to live here.
What a mess!
It gives me the shivers. They say
crows gather where there's death.
That's not true.
They can smell it.
I hate the noise they make.
It's not very cheerful.
A cat...
It scared me half to death!
I hate cats!
Let's look inside.
Tetsuichiro!
What?
There's someone there!
No,
there isn't.
I'm sure there was!
You're seeing things.
Look!
Footprints!
A tramp, maybe.
That's strange..
. they disappear.
You're right.
You're so high-strung...
This place is so eerie!
The living-room...
These old places
were sure built to last.
You couldn't build
like this now.
That's right.
Tetsuichiro!
That looks like
blood on the wall!
It's not blood.
We'll paint it over.
Kuzumi Clinic
Sort yesterday's files,
would you?
How are you,
Yoriko?
This rain depresses me.
A big house is so dark
when it rains...
It'll stop.
When it does, this place will be
much better for you than Tokyo.
It's like my brother said... this
really could be a haunted house.
Since I came I've been having
strange dreams.
Last night I dreamed of
a weird old lady...
Well,
it's a new place...
What's wrong with Taro?
He doesn't usually bark like that.
It's all nerves!
No.
He sounds strange.
Taro! Taro!
Quiet!
Taro, stop it!
Taro!
You scared me!
Don't sneak in like that!
Can I help you?
Don't you hear very well?
You're soaking wet!
I'll get the doctor.
You wait here.
Doctor...
A patient.
A really strange old lady.
There's no one here.
That's strange... I'll go look
out front.
She's not here.
Who are you?!
Yoriko!
That weird old lady was in here!
There's no one here.
She was here!
You imagined it.
But the nurse said
the same thing!
You're seeing things.
Don't get too excited.
It's bad for you.
Tetsuichiro!
What's wrong?
Can you hear footsteps?
No.
I can... it's that
horrible old lady again!
You're imagining things.
And I'm here.
Go back to sleep.
I'm scared,
Tetsuichiro!
Who's there?
A child's sick.
The Sudos need the doctor
over in Higashi Matsumura.
The Sudos?
Just a minute.
Mr. Sudo!
Dr Kuzumi's here!
Coming!
Oh, hello,
Doctor...
We didn't call you,
though...
So nobody called the doctor?
Maybe another house...
No,
she said here.
I'm afraid not.
It's me, Yoriko.
Open the door.
Yes?
Hurry up! I'll catch
my death of cold out here!
Tetsuichiro?
Yeah, it's me.
That didn't take long.
Wait while I open the gate.
Taro! Taro!
Taro?
Taro!
Yoriko!
What's wrong?
Wake up!
Yoriko!
Yoriko...
Kenichi?
Is that you?
I was so scared!
I keep having nightmares...
All these cats come
and start biting me...
Don't try to talk.
You'll tire yourself out.
Lay back and sleep.
But what if I start
dreaming again?
The doctor's here.
Relax and go to sleep.
How is she?
She's fine now.
But another shock like that
could kill her.
Really?
I've been thinking...
Yes?
I'm told there are reasons
they say this house is haunted.
The priest at Ryofukuji Temple
once told me...
...the best thing to do with
this place was tear it down.
I can't help but think
there's a connection.
The nurse saw an old lady,
too.
And then there's your dog...
I'm wondering if you might
come talk to the priest with me.
It's just what I thought it was.
It's a cat-spirit
seeking revenge.
A ghost cat?
Yes.
It's a tale of karma
from long, long ago.
On one side of the house
was a bed of spiraea flowers.
It was called 'Spiraea Mansion'.
In it lived Ishido Sakon no Shogen,
castle-warden of the Omura Clan.
He was a man famous
for his very short temper.
Saheiji!
Where are you?!
Coming!
Yes, Milord?
Pick up those stones!
Is Kokingo really coming?
He's late!
Where is he?!
He won't be here yet,
Sire.
Why not?
His lady mother is blind,
you will recall.
He must tend to her.
Yes,
I know that!
Why do you cry so?
I'll be home soon.
Here, Mother.
Take Tama.
Kokingo... don't you feel
she wants to tell you something?
I have a bad feeling myself.
Have no fear. I'm simply going
to teach him the game of Go.
But Lord Shogen is such
a difficult person...
Bear my words in mind...
...and hurry back.
I will.
I'll be going now.
Be very careful.
I will.
Don't cry, Tama.
I'll be back soon.
What's keeping him?!
What manner of samurai
cannot be on time?!
Have patience,
Milord.
Does he think his reputation
as a Go master...
...allows him to scorn me?!
Of course not, Milord.
You see too much in this.
Are you telling me...
...I don't know when
I've been insulted?!
Not at all! I mean only
that you should calm yourself.
Make sport of me
and I'll have your head!
Milord!
Forgive me!
Halt!
Father, wait!
Stand aside!
I will not.
Saheiji is a valued retainer.
For my sake, spare him!
No!
Stand aside!
Whatever he has done,
it cannot be worth his life!
Your temper is a matter
of regret to me.
Saheiji... at Shinnojo's request,
your life is spared.
Be careful!
Milord!
Now I can leave in confidence
for the castle.
You stand night watch?
I do.
Look to your duty.
I will.
Kokingo!
Welcome.
My father awaits.
Angry that I'm late?
You know him well.
Be easy on him when you play.
I am warned.
Later we can talk a while...
perhaps of your marriage.
Tonight I stand night watch.
That's too bad.
Another time, then.
Forgive me.
Grandmother...
Ah, Shinnojo...
Yes.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Kokingo will play Go
with Father today.
I'm concerned Father's temper
might make him impolite.
I thought that
a word to you before...
It's not polite to your opponent
to choose stones without asking!
But I was asked
to instruct you...
Instruct me?!
That is what Shinnojo said.
He doesn't know how good I am.
Today we play a game!
Might I take back that stone?
Not in a real game...
No?
All right!
Tama...
...why do you wail so?
Are you so lonely
without Kokingo?
Your medicine,
ma'am.
Thank you.
Kokingo is late.
Yes. And he said
he would return early.
His opponent is a difficult man.
I told him to let Lord Shogen win
and to hurry home.
But he's as stubborn as
his father was.
I pray nothing happens.
I didn't see that move!
Let me take back my stone!
This is a game.
Yes, I know,
but...
'But'?
Let me take back my move!
I will not!
Let me take that back!
Milord!
I will take my leave.
Before the game is done?
What is the meaning of this?!
I will not play against a cheat!
You dare use that word
to one of my position?!
I say it again.
A cheat is a cheat!
Silence!
You disgrace your position!
You insolent pup!
What did you say?!
You old fool!
Halt!
Pup!
Villain!
Milord!
What's happened?!
Saheiji!
You cannot see this and live!
Prepare yourself!
Or will you help me?
What will it be?
Think well on it!
I will.
I'll help you!
You are Kokingo's attendant?
Yes, Milord.
I am Hachirota.
Go quickly and tell
the Lady Miyaji...
...that Kokingo, mortified by
his defeat at Go...
...has left immediately to study
further in Kyoto and Osaka.
He is a rash young man.
Convey my regrets to his mother.
Yes, Milord.
Are you sure there
is no mistake?
Yes.
Those are His Lordship's words.
There is no mistake.
Kokingo!
Why do you appear as a corpse?!
Who killed you?
Who was it?
Speak his name!
Lord Shogen?
Kokingo!
Satsuki!
Where are you?!
Coming!
Yes, ma'am?
Tell me what
this piece of cloth is.
Blood!
It bears the
three-diamond crest!
Shogen's crest?
Then it's true!
Lady Miyaji, you're as beautiful
as ever.
Seeing you now
it seems like only yesterday...
...you were always
in my thoughts.
I'm sure Kokingo's leaving
is a great disappointment to you.
Lord Shogen...
...is it really true that Kokingo
has left on a journey of study?
Do you doubt my word?
A samurai does not lie.
And what is this,
Lady Miyaji?
Are you saying you do not know?
I do not.
What is it?
Then I'll tell you.
Kokingo's ghost has come
to tell me you have killed him!
A ghost?!
I'm sure it was a dream.
Great worry sometimes
brings us strange dreams.
Put your heart at ease.
Will you drink with me?
What do you say?
Where's the harm in it?
There's no one else here.
Die!
Have you gone mad?
Revenge!
Lady Miyaji...
You filth!
Hear me, Tama!
Listen well!
Kokingo, who was
so good to you...
...has met cruel death...
...at the hands of Lord Shogen.
And more, Shogen has violated
my honor!
I cannot bear to live!
Hear me, for you are wise,
beast though you are.
Kokingo and I make
this request of you.
Avenge us on Sakon no Shogen
and on his children, and theirs...
...until his line is extinct!
This is the last thing
I will ever ask you.
Tama! Lap my blood,
and imbibe my hate!
Saheiji!
Yes, Milord?
It's blood!
Quickly!
Wipe it away!
Who's there?
Sato?
I won't need you tonight.
You may retire.
You may not have use of me...
...but I have use of you.
What?!
Lady Miyaji!
What brings you here
at this hour of the night?
Your Ladyship...
...Lord Shogen,
without cause...
...has most cruelly cut down...
...my only son,
Kokingo.
And as well...
...though I am blind,
he has abused my person.
May the hatred I bear...
...curse the house of Ishido
and all who bear its name...
...unto the last of its line!
I know nothing of this!
I know nothing of it!
Lady Miyaji! I know
nothing of this!
Forgive me,
Lady Miyaji!
Yae...
...I have to pick the right time
to ask Father to let us marry.
You know that.
Yes.
I'm very happy,
Shinnojo...
...but your father won't let you
marry a woman of my station.
Don't you understand
how much I love you?
Yes, but...
...I am not well-born.
To be here with you like this
is all the happiness...
...I need.
Yae!
Shinnojo!
Yes?
His Lordship wants you.
I'll go to him now!
This is a game.
I do not play against cheats.
Kokingo!
Go back to hell!
Who's there?
Yae, Milord.
I'm glad you've come.
Enter.
Yes, Milord.
Will you massage my back?
You're a very beautiful girl,
Yae.
You jest,
Milord!
Not at all!
Come here...
I mustn't,
Milord!
Please!
Don't be so formal!
There's no one else here.
Keep your voice down!
No! Please!
Please!
Marry Yae?
You are heir to this house!
A 3,000-koku samurai!
Think of your position,
you fool!
Forgive my impertinence
in disagreeing.
We have pledged our love.
I would not be the first
to marry below my station.
Grandmother gives her blessing.
I ask you for yours.
Shinnojo, you're old enough now
not to go mad...
...over a woman!
Father!
Enough!
Shinnojo...
Grandmother...
What did he say?
I asked to marry Yae...
...and he got angry.
Why would a great man
like Shogen...
...do such a thing?
Just because of her birth!
Perhaps there's something else.
Something else?
Yes.
It's rumored among
the servants...
...Shogen summoned Yae
to his chamber late at night.
Yae?!
No, Milord!
Yae!
Let go!
Milord!
Blood!
Father!
After what you said to me!
What?!
Kokingo!
Father!
Stand aside!
Miyaji!
Let go!
Yae!
Father!
Speak to me!
Yae!
Fiend!
Blood!
Who is it out there?
Sato.
If there's something you want,
come in.
You saw,
didn't you.
No, Milady! I thought
you might be in distress!
Liar!
You've seen. I cannot
leave you alive.
Come to me!
Forgive me!
Yae!
Mother took a carp from the pond
and went under the house?!
Yes, Milord.
Those strange things last night,
and now my mother...
Saheiji! Tonight we'll go
and look into this!
It's Sato and Her Ladyship!
Oh, Shogen...
What brings you here
at this hour?
Silence, fiend!
You killed my mother!
Now you'll die!
Fiend!
Father!
Why is your sword drawn?
Have you seen anything strange?
Speak!
Kokingo!
Go back to hell!
Father!
Are you mad?!
What are you doing?!
Father!
Milord!
This is the story that has long
been told of Spiraea Mansion.
A frightening tale.
But why is my sister involved?
Yes.
Why Yoriko?
According to this
Register of Deaths...
...Saheiji, the servant there,
was your ancestor.
Really?
I've never told anybody that.
Is that so?
Cats have always been held
to have magical powers.
That's why I once said
you should tear the place down.
But vengeful spirits abhor
the name of the Lord Buddha.
I'll give you this charm.
Hang it in your house.
Thank you!
Tetsuichiro,
don't leave me.
I won't.
The nurse will watch
the patients.
And the priest gave me
that charm.
There's nothing to fear.
When I was a girl,
when I got sick...
...my mother would get
a charm like that.
It's strange, but I'd always
get better.
You're so superstitious!
But if you get better,
that's fine.
Tetsuichiro!
Yoriko!
Calm down!
I'm scared!
Close the shutters!
All right.
Yoriko!
Who is it?
Who's there?
Oh, it's you...
I brought you some dinner.
Thanks. Did it scare you
when the power went out?
Yes.
I kept my eyes shut.
But you got here...
Tonight even I started thinking
about that house down in Kyushu...
That time?
Yes.
I thought you were dead.
That certainly was strange.
We buried the mummy
and the old lady vanished.
Hatred is a terrible thing.
A cat!
It's so cute!
What,
you like cats now?
Can we keep it?
Sure. Why not?
The End