"Funds transferred."
"Mamuro was being followed."
"Maneuver Area 6"
"Special agent" "The LTC is innocent"
"The LTC is innocent"
(mem mem mem mem mem)
(memories memories memories)
(memories memories memories memories)
(my memories my memories my memories)
Fragmented memories
Here flowers (here birds); this is the sky
Clouds, grass, the house I grew up in
I search (and search) through the photos
But I'm nowhere to be found
Why am I not there? Why am I not there?
Why am I not there?
Fragmented beautiful memories
Look right (look left); where is this (place)?
Buildings, streets, hustle and bustle
I walk (and walk) through it all
But I'm nowhere to be found
The world, the world, the world, the world
The world, the world
The world, the world, the world...
(Just) keeps on going
Sweeping (skies)
Vibrant (greenery)
Mountains and (seas and)
The wind (from the past)
To the future (blows)
Leaving me (behind)
Deserted here (all alone)
Whoosh
(me me me me)
(me me why me why me)
Why am I not there?
Why am I not there? Why am I not there?